Chapter 1

Hellhound (1)

◆

The years of bloodshed had finally ended

The war between the humans and the demons that lasted for decades left a terrifying record in the history books as the 'Age of Destruction'.

And the day when the victory of the humans has been written down in the books.

A neck was hung at the front gate of the Baskervilles, famous for their iron-blooded swordsmen.

Vikir. 'Vikir Van Baskerville'.

The illegitimate son of Hugo Le Baskerville, the head of the Baskerville family.

The shadow that has been covered with countless blood on the back of the family.

It was the hound of the Baskervilles.

Vikir struggled

He had always struggled.

A bastard. Son of a Concubine.

So 'Van' middle name.

He was not born with a surname such as 'Le' or 'Re', which his half-siblings in the main family received, and because of that, he had to work hundreds of times more than others.

But in the end it was all for nothing.

Spying, assassination, kidnapping, blackmail, smuggling...... For the sake of his family, he crossed over 500 dangerous missions but in the end, they forsook him.

The moment when he is accused of being a spy for the demons and executed along with an unfair false charge.

He gritted his teeth.

He wanted to live

Aye- Aye- Aye-

A baby's cry echoed throughout the large room.

The iron-blooded swordsman, the Baskerville family, had dozens of layers of slopes.

The head of the house, the Marquis Hugo Le Baskerville, raised a nonchalant eye and scanned the children born this year.

“There aren't any guys that look useful.”

It was quite harsh for a father's first evaluation of children born this year.

......At that time.

Hugo, passing through the cribs in the nursery, stopped at one point.

Vikir. Vikir van Baskerville.

Originally, an illegitimate child who did not even deserve to be here.

Unlike the other siblings who are almost 6 to 8 months old, a being who has just entered this room after having just completed 100 days.

The baby wasn't crying.

He just lay still with his eyes closed, as if he were dead.

“.......”

Hugo looked at Vikir and relaxed his complexion a little.

It's not that he was happy that Vikir's qualities seem superior to those of his other offspring.

However, it was from the thought that if it was a place where only garbage was lined up anyway, it would be better to have garbage that was a little less noisy.

Eventually, Hugo spoke to dozens of nannies in the city behind him.

“Move the children to the 'Cradle of the swords'.”

The children of the Baskervilles are put to the test from the moment they are born.

From cradle to the grave.

The first of these tests began right away.

......What is the cradle of swords?

It is a unique rite of passage for the Baskervilles.

Countless knives are planted like a maze on a round hill and a baby is dropped in the middle.

The baby is trapped in the maze created by the blade and wandered through it.

Even if it moves, he get cut by the blades all over his body.

In this environment, babies have to crawl on the floor and through a labyrinth of needles.

It is only when you immerse yourself in the river 'Styx' outside of the labyrinth that you become a Baskerville in its true sense.

'The Styx water is only effective for children under one year of age. If you soak your body in this river, your whole body becomes as hard as steel.'

Of course, the power of this river is not infinite.

If one baby sucks up most of her power, the other sucks in relatively less since the power remaining is lesser.

It's like her mother's lifeline.

The children of the Baskervilles were now thrown into the cradle of the sword.

Who is the first to get out of this labyrinth and jump into the river first? That will determine the future of these children.

Thirty-two children born this year, including all of the family's rightful sons, bastards, and cousins, compete with each other in the middle of the cradle of swords.

The blades, densely packed with tracks for the children to the go through and become the sharpest of thorns.

Aye- Aye- Aye-

A baby who cried looking for a babysitter, while another was already crawling, he was bleeding from being cut by the blades, and another one who sat down and sucking his finger as he had no intention of escaping yet...... Babies are usually like that.

In fact, since these babies are less than a year old, it is a natural result.

However.

“Useless.”

Hugo Le Baskerville's assessment was terribly cold.

A small, fragile creature. A creature that cannot survive without the help of others.

There was contempt in Hugo's gaze at the human body.

Even if it is your own child, there is no exception.

Being one of the seven best swordsmen on the continent, he was famous for being an iron man from birth.

“Only like this can we fight the demons. The strong will survive and leave the weak behind”

Hugo stood high and looked at the waters of the Styx, which flowed around the cradle of the sword, and lamented.

The secret river, which flows only in the Holy Land of the Baskerville family, has the effect of increasing mana, purifying one's aura, and making one's body as tough and hard as steel just by soaking one's body.

If it hadn't been for something that only worked for children under the age of 1, Hugo would have soaked himself right away.

When Hugo is looking at the river with a sad expression.

“......Hey, over there!”

“Ah, how can it be!”

“Nonsense!”

Arguments erupted from everywhere.

What was there to be astonished at by the family's guardian knights, who were not shaken by anything?

Hugo raised his head with a puzzled expression.

And that moment.

“......!”

His eyes, which had been filled with bitter boredom, contempt, impatience, and disappointment, lit up.

The cradle of the sword.

For through this thick forest of blades a child was heading straight for the River Styx.

Jjoeok- Jjeook- Fit-

The child's body is already covered in blood.

Surprisingly, the child was going straight through the cradle of needles, which were spiraled like a snail's shell.

Instead of going round and round on a relatively safe road, he directly squeezes into the small gap between the blades.

There was a knife mark on his white, soft cheek.

His soft waist and forearms were cut and torn all over.

His knees were all bruised and the soft palms were already bloody.

A child crawling forward, making a bloody path by squeezing between the countless needles.

Everyone in the family was overwhelmed by the spirit of this child who was less than 100 days old.

It was the same with Hugo Le Baskerville, the head of Baskerville, the iron-blooded swordsman.

Before long, the child was completely out of the maze.

His siblings were still trapped in the center of the cradle of the sword and could not get out.

...With a plop!

Soon the child came out of the cradle, he threw himself into the River Styx.

The river water started turning red.

Hugo moved forward in an unusual way, clutching the railing with both hands.

Seeing the cracks in the marble railing, the attendants widened their eyes.

It was because it was the first time I had seen him, who usually showed an emotionless attitude in everything, be so agitated.

“What happened to him?”

Hugo raised his voice.

The child who fell into the River Styx still did not come up.

Before long, several of the family's guardian knights approached the River Styx and peered into it.

And. The knights were frightened at once.

“Sir, he is drinking the river water!”

It was an answer that would make Hugo's mouth turn into a grin.

Chapter 2

Hellhound (2)

◆

'Where is this place?'

Vikir checked his body.

There was no mana and it was extremely weak

There is not even a handful of auras that he had built up across his countless battles

'Did I fall into hell?'

But it is not.

This place...... It's too barren to even call it hell.

A place where even hell would look more hospitable. Because that is the Baskerville family.

' There is no way that I do not know the atmosphere of the place where I have lived as a hunting dog for the past 30 years. '

The smell of blood, of pus, of all that was filthy and dead.

Vikir van Baskerville had a hunch. That he had returned to the time when he had just been born.

'What should I do now?'

A body that has just lived for about 100 days. There's not much you can do.

Just turning over and signaling the shared nursery nanny to breastfeed?

Right then.

“There aren't any guys that look useful.”

A familiar voice was heard.

Hugo Le Baskerville, patriarch of the Baskervilles, was seen standing in the center of the nursery.

The moment he heard his voice, Vikir almost got up and bowed, as was his habit in life.

Fortunately, it was impossible because of the body of a newborn baby.

Pudeuk-

Seeing the main culprit who had executed him , he gritted his teeth.

However, because the body had not yet grown teeth, there was no sound.

'Let's calm down.'

In the past, in order to become a member of the Baskerville family, to be recognized by his father, and to get rid of the pretense of being an illegitimate child, the days of shame and shame he struggled with.

Inferior blood, the tag did not leave him no matter what he did.

I would live differently in this life. If the rabbit disappears, it will not live a life like a hound being boiled.

Right then.

There was an opportunity that made Vikir's determination even stronger.

“Move the children to the 'cradle of the sword'.”

I heard Hugo's words.

As she left in the hands of her nanny, Vikir's mind was racing.

'Is it the first rite of passage?'

The Cradle of Swords is a journey to the River Styx, which took place around a small hill.

The moment they moved through the maze made of swords and dive into the River Styx, the children of the Baskerville family are reborn as warriors.

Of course, the blessing of the River Styx did not give strength equally.

The weak die and the strong survive.

The strong get more than the weak.

The children of the Baskervilles must get out of the cradle of swords as quickly as possible and dive into the River Styx.

You need to soak in the river as quickly as possible and for as long as possible to gain an advantage over your brothers.

So Vikir moved as soon as he was thrown into the center of the cradle of swords.

...Bck!

He moved the blade with two soft hands.

It is said that children from some prestigious families take things that help them in the future, but children from the Baskerville family have to grab the blades that threaten their future from the first birthday.

Spit- Pot- Jjik- Jjik-

The blade cut through his skin.

Every time he squeezed between the blades with force, a burning pain rushed through his whole body.

But it didn't matter.

This level of pain is something he had become accustomed to after living as a hunting dog for the past few decades.

'Moreover, the deeper the wound, the better, so that the water of the Styx can permeate the body better.'

Vikir knew all the secrets, legends, myths, and ghost stories of the Baskervilles.

That's why he knows how to make the most of the River Styx.

Eonggeum... Eonggeum... Eonggeum...

The child's soft body is led to hell by the hound's hardened soul.

The blood flowing from his body and going down the ramp indicated the straight route and the shortest distance to go forward.

Vikir continued to crawl in the direction as he continued to bleed.

And soon, he reached the holy ground of the Baskervilles.

River Styx flowing through the swamp.

When you soak in this place, your body becomes as hard as steel and your soul becomes extremely strong.

Vikir threw himself into the river in his fetal position.

...With a plop!

Heavy. It was as painful as if I had been submerged in boiling molten iron.

Water hot enough to steam up. Having fallen here with countless stabs all over her body, there was no doubt that it would not be painful.

But Vikir endured the pain of being boiled. And he waited

The waters of the Styx permeated through the cuts, torn, and bursting wounds.

Yet.

Tsutsutsutsutsu......

The body began to change.

The water of Styx, which permeated through the wounds and penetrated into the bones and intestines, was transforming Vikir's body from one to ten.

'It's definitely different.'

Vikir was amazed that his good start could make such a dramatic difference.

The body of the previous life was tough and seasoned, but it was still small and thin compared to the others.

Since the bones themselves were weak, there were limits to attaching muscles, and since the mana paths were narrow, there were clear restrictions on raising the aura.

But his brothers were different. Tall, thick bones, and a wide mana veins.

It is different in talent, quality, and starting line.

In his previous life, Vikir almost came out of the Tower of Swords in last place.

So he couldn't properly enjoy the effect of the River Styx.

Because all of his brothers had already absorbed that power.

Since then, due to his background as an illegitimate child and poor talent, he has been given only the last rank every time.

When others ate healthy food, wore the best stuff, slept in comfortable beds.

He ate dirty scarps, wore shitty clothes, slept in dirty places.

The achievements obtained by him were taken by his brothers.

It was the same in the war with the demons.

No matter how many demons and demons he killed, the achievements always belonged to his father or half brothers.

There was little to no reward.

It was not only the demons that had to be killed, but also his father's political enemies and humans.

He had to spy, assassinate, espionage, ambush, and intimidate the entire seven families, and in doing so, he raised Baskerville to the top of the seven families.

......But what was the result?

Execution

When the rabbit disappears and the hunt is over, there is no need for a hunting dog.

Accused of conspiring with the demons, Vikir was executed while bearing all the dirty sins of Hugo.

His sin was only one.

'Knowing too much'.

Sigh-

Vikir gnashed his teeth.

The teeth that started to grow in the mouth collided fiercely before he knew it.

The water of the Styx rushed in following the fury that reached the marrow within the bones, and soon changed the bones thicker, the flesh tougher, and the mana barrel wider.

Of course, the burning pain continued to creep in, but it didn't matter.

Vikir even started drinking water.

He was thinking of strengthening the internal organs as well.

He was thinking of an old legend passed down in the Baskervilles.

'A long time ago, there was an invincible warrior in Baskerville, right?'

The strongest swordsman who did not even get a single scratch on his skin, let alone a bone, even when hit by an axe.

But his end was truly absurd.

A poisoned arrow shot by a rival from another clan struck him in the heel, and he died from the aftereffects.

It was because, when he was a baby, his nurse grabbed him by the ankles and dipped him upside down into the Styx, leaving a relatively weak spot where the water didn't reach because of the nurse's palms.

'It shouldn't have that kind of part.'

Vikir did his best to stir himself in the river.

He twisted his body as best he can, leaving no part untouched by the water.

In the meantime, the wound opened and opened, but it was even better.

Because the water can permeate well into the body.

Bubbling bubbling......

The blood drained out and his body started turning numb..

He was out of breath and wanted to get to the surface as quickly as possible.

But it can't be.

The River Styx never accepts a child once it has left its arms.

If only the head was exposed to breathe, only the head would no longer be protected.

So Vikir desperately held on to the stone in the river.

He continued to stir his arm so that the river water could touch the palm holding the stone.

At that time.

I hear faint voices in my ears.

“Young master! You must come out!”

“If you stay submerged any longer, you will die!”

“Oh my god! He might die like this!”

“Get it! We have to pick him up!”

It looks like there was an uproar from above. Well, that's bound to be the case.

Excessive greed becomes poison. It's good to strengthen the body, but shouldn't it be suffocating and dying?

Even.

“Son. Come up now.”

The voice of Hugo Le Baskerville is also heard.

But that voice only fuels Vikir's rage.

Soowook-

Vikir stood up.

But he just didn't get up.

Gulp- gulp- gulp- gulp-

Drink the water of the River Styx in your mouth. To the very end.

And.

“Puha-”

As soon as you come up, breathe in the air to your heart's content.

Vikir opened his mouth wide to breathe.

Seeing him, Hugo Le Baskerville smiles brightly, which is rare.

“Hahaha, look at this guy? Didn't your teeth grow back then!”

Hounds boiled in boiling water exposed fangs.

Chapter 4

The Baskerville Dog (1)

◆

Eight years have passed.

Vikir van Baskerville had turned eight years old and, as is the case with children in the Baskervilles, was taking his classes.

“Okay, last question. How did you say to classify the level of a swordsman?”

Vikir replied with a calm expression.

“Regardless of swordsmanship proficiency,

A swordsman who does not know how to load mana into a sword is a 'sword beginner',

A state that knows how to load mana into the tip of a sword, but the aura raised by doing so is weak like a gas is a 'sword expert',

The state where the aura rising from the sword becomes sticky and dense like a liquid is called 'Sword Graduator',

and the state where the aura becomes hard like a solid and the shape can be changed according to the caster's will is called 'Sword Master'. ”

Of course, all of these are separated for convenience.

Basically, combat is affected by numerous factors such as health, terrain, climate, humidity, gravity, experience, and the density of mana in the air.

You can calculate it, but when you calculate it, the result will already be different.

But the calculations for 8-year-olds aren't that complicated yet.

When Vikir answered without hesitation, the other children around him raised their hands and shouted along, as if competing.

“If a beginner and an expert fight, the expert wins!”

“If you fight an expert and a graduate, the graduate will win!”

“Master is stronger than graduate!”

“And the head of household is the master!”

Vikir was silently listening to the children around him.

The words of one of the guys stab him in the chest.

'The head of the household is a master!'

Hugo Le Baskerville, head of the Baskervilles.

For a wizard, he possesses as much as 7 circles of mana.

However, as a master of swordsmanship, he transformed mana into aura and used it on a sword, and it is said that the level reached the sword master respected by the world.

The tutor nodded as he looked at them,

“Lord Hugo, is a sword master. This is a stage that only 7 people have reached in this country, 'Rock', and each head of the 7 families corresponds to this.”

Of course, Vikir already knew this fact.

He even knew that there were several more sword masters in and out of the empire.

This is information no one knew about right now.

Vikir is thinking hard about something alone.

The tutor's eyes were on Vikir from earlier.

'He's amazing.'

A truly overwhelming talent.

It is a small legend in the family that a child who was only 100 days old dived for more than 7 minutes in the River Styx.

But who respect muscle brained idiots?

Even though it was overshadowed by the extraordinary of the body, he had the brains that were unmatched.

It is worthy of being dared to call it 'a talent that learn a hundred things after being taught one'.

'The lord must be happy today.'

He was going to report all this to Hugo.

Originally, Hugo is not very interested in the rest of the children unless they are the eldest or the second.

Hugo, who had been acting as if he was just a livestock wholesaler, stopping by occasionally to record the growth and value of livestock, has suddenly increased his interest in Fang castle over the past few years.

Of course it's because of Vikir.

It was extremely unusual for Hugo to come to Fang castle, a place where only children under the age of 10 gather and raise children together, so the tutors who were in charge of this place had a hard time on their shoulders these days.

'Thank you, Young Master. I will do my best to assist you.'

Thanks to Vikir, the budget has increased a lot and his position has grown compared to other knights in the family, so everyone was looking at Vikir with favorable eyes.

Of course, Vikir himself was not interested.

After class, around the time when the children were going back to their rooms throughout the castle.

Vikir was looking back at herself now.

'Hugo is a master,'

Unfortunately, that is true.

Its density and rigidity were on a different level from the 'solid aura' that only masters could express, and his own 'sticky liquid' aura that was a senior graduate.

Aww-

Vikir gritted his teeth

In this life, he would never live or die a meaningless death.

'At least before the coming-of-age ceremony, all his previous strength should be restored.'

Currently 8 years old.

Vikir's level had reached the advanced level of Sword Expert without anyone noticing.

In his previous life, it was a state that he had barely achieved until he was over 20 years old.

Before his return, he was at the age of ten, and he had risen to the rank of Sword Expert.

In fact, even this much was great enough to be passed as a genius by the standards of the world, but within the Baskervilles, it was mediocre, or slightly less than that.

Usually, the children of the Baskervilles knock on the door of advanced sword experts around the age of 20 and graduates around the age of 30.

If you can put 'liquid aura' on the tip of your sword in that way, you will rise to the position of an executive from here.

Even the elite of the Baskervilles, who are said to be the geniuses among geniuses, reached the age of 20 as the threshold for advanced sword experts.

But Vikir was stepping on it now, at the age of eight.

In his previous life, he was at an age where he had never felt mana.

This is a state that even the super-elite within the family would not dare to surpass.

When Vikir is feeling a new emotion.

“Hey.”

A voice called from behind.

Wanting something, I turned my head and saw three children in my 9-year-old class.

Highbro Le Baskerville, Middlebro Le Baskerville, Lowbro Le Baskerville.

The surname of 'Le' given to boys of direct lineage, and the surname 'Ra' to girls.

The three here are said to be direct descendants of the Baskervilles.

The pedigree is very clear.

How cliché, Highbro, the eldest in the front, started to argue with Vikir.

“'Half' trash, where are you going?”

“Where are you going?”

“Where are you going?”

If the guy in front sings the lead, the two guys behind sing the afterword.

It was a fight like a nine-year-old.

Well, anyway, the Baskervilles are thorough on talent supremacy, so this won't happen when they get a little older.

However, the reason Vikir kept a close eye on the triplets in front of him was for another reason.

'......The trident of Hugo Le Baskerville.'

In 10 more years, those guys will grow into quite troublesome enemies.

In fact, before returning, these are the three hounds who tenaciously pursued and stabbed Vikir, who escaped through the siege.

'Come to think of it, these guys have been harassing me a lot since I was young.'

Vikir's growth was very slow when he was young because they took away so much food.

During various evaluations, he sneakily stepped on his feet and backstabbed him.

Because of that, there were many times when he almost died on various missions in the wind that caused him to lame a little.

...Flash!

Vikir's eyes turned red.

Unkowingly, the triplets, who had just turned 9, giggled and surrounded Vikir.

“Hey trash, you said you submerged in the Styx for 7 minutes? And what, strangled two vipers in the cradle? Bluff a little bit. Where can a guy who is only 8 years old lie!”

“Lie!”

“Lie!”

Hive, the most vicious of the three, took a step forward.

“Can you do this?”

At the same time, a small sphere glows faintly above the palm of his hand.

The young children of the Baskerville family are different from the majourity in mana sensitivity and mana management.

It was already possible to condense mana and gather it in a circle.

It seemed that he hadn't been able to put it on his sword yet, but even so, it was enough to be praised as a genius in the world.

Of course, even within the Baskerville family, he can be praised for being quite talented.

“This is a talent. Do it soon too! See how much mana you can take out.”

“Look!”

“Look!”

The triplets continued to push Vikir.

“.......”

Vikir looked at the lump of mana that Lowbro had created.

A mana sphere the size of a child's fist. Yeah, at that age, they should be good enough to do that.

But Vikir had already done that much at the age of eight months.

When he strangled two poisonous snakes in the cradle.

Since the mana proficiency of 8 years after the return was added to the 30 years before the return, where does that level reach?

Vikir looked around him once.

There are not many things to worry about in the 'Fang Castle' where only children live.

The few guardian knights and tutors are now all out to the outer castle.

...Pod!

The power of Vikir was expressed.

Vikir who raises his palms high and started collecting mana.

Seeing this, the faces of the triplets turned into astonishment.

“......!”

“......!”

“......!”

Nothing was created on Vikir's palm.

The triplets put on a dazed expression for a moment, then started laughing loudly.

“Ahahahaha, you little shit! Could it be that you couldn't even respond to mana until you were that old?”

“Couldn't you?”

“Couldn't you?”

The guys are so intent on ridiculing that they even shed tears.

......But.

At the same time, a watchtower not too far from Fang Castle.

One of the guards on duty was perplexed by the unexpected change seen through the windows.

“What? Why are there two suns above Fang Castle?”

Chapter 5

The Baskerville Dog (2)

◆

“I don't like you. Follow me.”

“Follow me.”

“Follow me.”

The 9-year-old triplets of the Baskervilles, Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro started dragging him.

“.......”

Eight-year-old Vikir thought with his mouth shut.

In my childhood before returning, meeting these guys was as terrifying as meeting a god of death.

Decades later, these guys were also involved in his own execution.

Above all, these are warriors who will be so outstanding that they will be called 'The Baskerville's Trident' or 'Hugo Le Baskerville's Trident' in a decade or so.

Aren't they youngsters who will make great achievements for the Baskervilles?

So it was necessary to nip the buds in advance.

In order to devour the Baskervilles in the future.

“......Hee. I'm afraid of you guys.”

Is this the right way to do it?

Vikir looked up and cried like a child who was scared.

As he said to the triplets scoffed arrogantly.

“Shouldn't we rather go to a place where no one is around?”

Then the triplets giggled.

“So you know what honor is,”

“Ah yes.”

“Ah yes.”

Beating in a place where there are many eyes is a nuisance even for triplets.

They would break Vikir's arms, cover his mouth, and drag him to a secluded place.

'Fang Castle' is a castle that has been built for a long time, and there are many secluded and nooks and crannies, like a building that follows the old architectural style.

Crossing the submerged cellar entrance, past an abandoned food warehouse and an unrepaired crack, up the spiral staircase.

The triplets were dragged into a secluded room in the hallway where they didn't wear their bikinis.

The captain, Highbro, said with a smile.

“If you scream, one place might get cut off. Well, if you go to the infirmary in time, you should be able to attach it.”

“You can attach it.”

“You can attach it.”

I can't believe that I'm 9 years old when I take out a dagger from my waist and see her smiling darkly.

Are young children more cruel?

Children laugh while taking off the head or wings of insects and stepping on them to kill them.

Even ordinary children do this, but the children of the Baskervilles needless to say were far ahead in this.

These three little demons surrounded Vikir.

“I heard you dived for seven minutes in the River Styx? I laughed for a while after hearing that brag from the nanny.”

“Laughed.”

“Laughed.”

Highbro nodded to the youngest, Lowbro, who was next to him.

Then Lowbro smiled and nodded his head, then went back to Vikir's back and covered Vikir's nose and mouth with both hands.

Highbro looked at Vikir's face and laughed meanly.

“What about 7 minutes? If you can last for three minutes, I will cut off my finger.”

“I will support you!”

“I will support you!”

Low Bro puts even more pressure on Vikir's hand, which covered his nose and mouth.

I could feel innocent malice from his tightly clasped hands, as if he wouldn't allow me to take a sigh of breath.

Highbro and Middlebro are smiling brightly, holding both arms tightly in the hope of subduing Vikir.

......But.

“......?”

“......?”

“......?”

The triplets turn his head with a puzzled expression.

For Vikir stood still, not moving at all, watching the triplets.

“Hehehe, do you want to hold on? There is quite a bit of spirit. Let's see how far it goes.”

“See you.”

“See you.”

The triplets give more strength to their hands.

One minute passed like that.

Since he didn't even raise his mana, he would be short of breath as a kid.

“.......”

But Vikir just stands there with calm eyes, just like the first time.

“......You're holding up pretty well, kid.”

“Kid.”

“Kid.”

The triplets were busy tightening his hands, not realizing that the smiles on their lips were slowly fading away.

And he was over 2 minutes.

The triplets had stopped talking a little.

The time surrounding the still standing Vikir began to feel too long.

“......What is this child Is he not breathing?”

“No?”

“No!”

Lowbro shook his head. Clearly, Vikir was holding his breath.

And 3 minutes.

4 minutes.

5 minutes.

6 minutes.

7 minutes.

8 minutes.

9 minutes.

10 minutes.

Vikir stands still.

In the meantime, there was only a chilling silence in the room.

At this point, the backs of the triplets, who are rather bullying, are drenched in cold sweat.

If you actually feel them counting from 1 to 60, you could see their nervousness.

All the while, Vikir was staring at the triplets, blinking his eyes calmly

......With grave silence.

Yet.

Highbro forced a smile and gestured to Lowbro.

“......Jae, that's not funny. Set this bastard free.”

“Free him.”

“Free him.”

The moment Lowbro was about to removed his hand from Vikir's mouth.

“Keah!?”

A sudden noise bursts out.

It wasn't the sound of Vikir gasping for breath or struggling.

Blood was gushing out of Lowbro's index finger.

“......Twi.”

Vikir spit out what came into his mouth after chewing it a few times.

Then he smiled at the triplets in front of him.

“You said that I would get my fingers cut?”

Vikir laughed with blood still in his mouth.

Seeing this, the complexions of the triplets turned pale for an instant.

Before long, Highbro shouted as if chewing and spitting out.

“......Joy! If so, ha, I'm not afraid at all!”

“......I'm not afraid!”

“......Scared!”

The last comment was off-putting.

When Highbro and Middlebro turned their heads, Lowbro raised his hand and whimpered.

“My finger was cut off!”

The triplets' conversation started to go awry.

Seeing blood is familiar to the children of the Baskervilles.

However, the story is a little different when it goes beyond blood, torn off flesh and broken bone fragments, even if all of that is your own.

Like a trident, the guys who always moved together and in the same direction began to play separately.

The eldest Highbro soothes the youngest Lowbro.

“Calm down Bro. Let's go to the infirmary and ask the priest to put a finger on us.”

“Let's do it.”

“Ooh ooh...... okay. Quickly!”

Middlebro carried Lowbro.

As Highbro quickly reached out and opened the door.

“Who said you could go?”

Vikir stood in front of him.

Highbro's expression twisted sternly.

“You are.......”

Of course, the distorted expression did not straighten out again.

Wagjak-

Vikir's fist flew in and shattered his nose and teeth.

Highbro lying on the floor clutching his face.

...Pudeuk!

Middlebro, who was standing there with a dazed expression on his face, got his jaw turned by Vikir's kick that immediately followed.

“What!?”

“Keuk-”

“Sobbing.......”

The triplets, all screaming, moaning, and crying with different sounds.

Vikir sat quietly in front of the door and said.

“You will be maimed for the rest of your life if we don't get proper treatment within the next hour.”

“.......”

“But looking at my older brothers, I don't think I will be able to leave this room today.”

“.......”

“When it rains and your teeth, chin, and fingers ache, always remember today.”

The triplets then glared at Vikir as if to kill him.

The cruel temper nurtured in the Baskervilles for the past nine years does not go anywhere.

'......But at least they are children.'

Vikir smiled.

There is no existence that does not listen to the passer.

If there is a person who doesn't listen to you even if you lose, you should think about whether you're not a fan less.

This was Hugo Le Baskerville's view of childcare, and it is also the code of conduct for the entire Baskerville family.

“Aww!”

At least the eldest brother, Highbro, gathered his courage and attacked again.

But.

Puck!

Highbro's dagger did not draw a single drop of blood, even though it was stabbed right into Vikir's body.

“......Uh?”

Highbro makes a blank expression.

When the dagger touched Vikir's chest, it seemed to be dyed black, but he soon returned to his flesh color.

The protection of the River Styx.

Vikir's body reached the state of complete sword invulnerability at the age of only 8 years.

Puck!

Sound similar to when a dagger was inserted earlier.

But the result is completely different.

Highbro sat down as he felt all his remaining teeth were completely broken off.

It happened in just two punches.

Walgrak... walgrak... Garr-

The clattering sound of tears, mucus, saliva, blood, air bubbles and teeth mixing in the mouth.

A dark shadow of Vikir is cast in front of the triplets who tremble as they held their injuries.

...Klang!

A dagger thrown into the middle of the triplets.

But no one had any idea to figure it out.

Instinctively, everyone knows.

'......If you catch that one, you will be beaten even more severely.'

The triplets are on their knees on the floor, unable to even raise their heads, dripping blood, tears, saliva and cold sweat.

All three of them had wet crotches, so it looked like they had lost their urine.

At that time.

Vikir said.

“There is only one older brother who can leave this room alive.”

The expressions of the triplets who found a rope change rapidly.

“Who?”

“Who?”

“Who?”

Vikir's answer to that was simple.

“It's up to the brothers to decide.”

At the same time, the triplet's gaze suddenly focused on the dagger in the center.

...Great!

Baskerville's trident began to split from within.

Chapter 8

Hounds of Hell (1)

◆

Children in the Baskervilles are tested twice a year, midterm and final assessments, until they are 15 years old.

In order to get rid of the stigma of being a family of berserkers, I tend to make the usual liberal arts classes hard...... In the first place, the reason why they are called the berserker family is because of the practical test that is so difficult that it is murderous.

It was not something young children who had just turned 8 or 9 should go through.

The children of the Baskervilles receive a rigorous education.

From the point of being able to walk on two feet, in order to cultivate basic physical strength, it is made to run continuously on a wide gym and steep hills.

You cannot even lie down outside the designated time.

The Guardian Knights become instructors and polish them like crazy.

During breaks, they plays with a rubber knife, and when they sleep, it is often beside the corpses of large monsters or small monters.

To get them accustomed to the hideous appearance of their prey and their savage ferocity.

And from the age of 8, real training begins.

Meals changed.

In the broth made from boiling chicken bones, various types of fish, which are full of meat, are beaten and boiled until they turn into mush.

Then put it in a tough intestine and boiled again to remove the last bit of fat.

Haggis, which is a regular meal, is eaten right at this stage.

Here, it is salted for storage, and after a long time, it is dried hard and hardened jerky is completed, which is the preserved food that the children of the Baskerville family always carry with them.

Today, children aged 8 or 9 from the Baskervilles were sent to the mountains outside the manor with sacks of these beef jerky.

'Le Rouge' mountain.

This is an alpine area with a harsh environment where only a few vicious monsters can live.

The young hounds of the Baskervilles are thrown here and have to survive for about a month.

Of course, they live only within the restricted area, and at the boundary of the restricted area, guardian knights within the family, called 'hounds', are there to keep the dangers controlled.

The tasks of children abandoned in an unfamiliar environment are as follows.

'Survival', 'If possible, hunt big and strong monsters'.

The original task was simply to 'survive', but the current owner, Hugo Le Baskerville, said that this task was too easy and added another task.

Sometimes, among the children of the Baskerville family, there were those who would lock themselves in safe caves or tunnels and survive by eating only beef jerky.

'A child who bravely fought against monsters and survived shouldn't get the same evaluation as a child who stayed in a hole like a coward and only ate food.'

This was Hugo's idea.

-If you managed to save your life, 10 points.

– If you managed to save your life without being crippled, 30 points.

-50 points if you drop other children and survive.

-70 points if you catch the monster and survive.

-90 points if you managed to save your life without being crippled despite dropping other children or surviving by catching monsters.

There is no 100 points.

A swordsman dies the moment he becomes conceited.

That were Hugo's instructions.

...Of course, if you die in any situation, you get 0 points.

Of all deaths, dying like a dog is a shame in itself.

Eight-year-old Vikir arrived here today in Le Rogue Mountain.

When you get off the wagon, you can see piles of reddish dirt.

Black ants swarmed on the parched mound.

A dry wind blows through the burnt old trees.

All I see is dark red hue.

The Guardian Knights spoke up.

“You have been handed out badges. As soon as you leave this place, you can steal each other's badges. If you steal the other person's badge, you get extra points.”

“Even if you hunt monsters, bonus points are given. However, points are deducted if you are fatally injured. In case of death, all points are lost. Well, at the time of death, the score is already not a problem.”

“We do not recommend going outside the restricted area. You must only move within the space we have patroled over the past few days. This is because there are still many unknown areas in Le Rogue Mountain.”

The Guardian Knights explained other intricate rules.

But to Vikir, it's just annoying nagging.

'It's been a while since I've seen you.'

He, too, has often been to Le Rogue Mountain.

As a student in his childhood and as an instructor in his old age, it was a place he frequently visited were Le Rogue mountains.

It was a strange and scary place when he was a student, but when he came as an instructor.......

'It's became even more scary and unfamiliar place.'

Because he had to search outside of his comfort zone.

The area where the children of the Baskerville family survive is actually more like a cozy cradle.

The real danger is the area outside the boundary guarded by the Guardian Knight instructors.

[Forbidden zone].

Outside the ridge called 'Cradle', and beyond a few mountain ranges, powerful monsters and barbarians swarm.

Since the Baskervilles declared this place as their territory, they have steadily pioneered the enemy and beyond the Mountains.

It was also because there was an order from the emperor.

The expansion of the territory of the Baskerville family was the expansion of the territory of the empire, and for this, various tax benefits and autonomy of military facilities were guaranteed.

Before his regression. Vikir also spent a very long time here in the Le Rogue mountains, passing through his days as an examinee, his days as an instructor, and his days as a hunting dog.

So the environment here was very familiar.

Not to mention it was not in the 'Undiscovered Zone' beyond the ridge, nor in the 'Cradle'.

...But. Most children seem to feel unfamiliarity and fear in the environment they are seeing for the first time.

The dry, crumbling dirt cliffs, the pungent wind blowing from the burned forest, the dry ashes, the unpleasant eyes and cries that can be felt from somewhere.

“...Ugh, this is the first time I've ever been in such a bad weather.”

“It has become more barren than when I came last year.”

“You want me to stay here for a month!?”

8-year-olds cried.

The 9-year-olds were pretending to be indifferent, but their expressions are not good, perhaps because of bad memories from last year.

In fact, this test is a battle between 8-year-olds who want to keep the badge and 9-year-olds who want to steal it.

For today's 8-year-olds, who will turn 9 next year, this experience will be very important.

And in this situation, 8-year-old Vikir stoods still, waiting for the bell to signal the start of his exam.

Nearby, 9-year-old children aiming for Vikir's badge were laughing sinisterly.

“Is that him? He took a seven-minute dive in the River Styx.”

“Does that make sense? Well, rumor has it that he strangled two poisonous snakes while he was in the cradle.”

“You say that the guy with the perfect writing score? Let's see if he can do well.”

A buzzing sound all around.

But there is one strange thing.

“.......”

“.......”

“.......”

The three strongest and fiercest 9-year-olds in the class, Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro, are somehow silent.

The other 9-year-olds just tilted their heads as they were always eager to show Vikir a lesson.

Soon, some of the children who were noticing came forward and began to quarrel with Vikir.

“You cheeky bastard. As soon as the practical evaluation begins, I will beat you to death.”

“A guy who isn't so great gets smug.”

“You're going to feel like hell here for the next month.”

Then Vikir finally responded.

“I don't think I'm great.”

Unexpected humility makes 9-year-old children look puzzled.

However, Vikir's words soon made the guys' faces frown.

“......You guys are just too weak.”

Immediately after that, fresh curse words flew in and stuck.

“You, you, I'm the real best here!”

“Come to the place where the old tree is later in the evening, you son of a bitch!”

“Get out of the way! I'll beat that bastard! Even if he dies, I won't stop!”

The children of the Baskervilles are easily drawn into even low-level provocations.

One-day puppies that hadn't even seen death were baring their fangs that weren't ripe yet.

As an old dog who has gone through all of the deadly battles, he didn't even smile.

Right then.

Ding-

Pavlov van Baskerville, a guardian knight and instructor in charge of the “Head Hound” rang the bell.

The practical test has begun.

Chapter 9

Hounds of Hell (2)

◆

In the Baskervilles, practical tests are frequent, several times a day.

Most of the brothers fight each other to determine superiority in strength, but most of the start of the fight is announced with this species.

Ding-

The young hounds of the Baskervilles, who were nervous in the unfamiliar environment, immediately came to their senses at the sound of a familiar bell.

And as it has been learned in the meantime, it was an instinct.

A young Baskerville from the nine-year-old class quickly ran across the wasteland.

He was the guy who benefited quite a bit last year by occupying the advantageous terrain first.

But he was intelligent enough to remember last year's points, but he was not intelligent enough to keep his eyes on him.

The quick-witted 8-year-olds chased after him.

They didn't know what it was?, but they planed to stop him from doing what he wanted.

Smarter kids pretended that they knew something.

And lure others into dangerous pits or swamps and get rid of annoying flying flies all at once.

The triplets, Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro, were such cunning guys.

“Go there.”

“Don't tell me what to do.”

“I teling you because you can't do shit on your own.”

9-year-olds who are already showing their prominence. By the way, these guys used a similar methods last year to eliminate a lot of upperclassmen.

Within hours of the bell ringing, dropouts began to appear one after another.

From shock and fainting, from rolling down a steep slope, or from falling into a swamp, from being stabbed or cut.

The reasons were varied, but the root cause was one.

It was at the hands of other brothers.

...Kang!

You can also hear the sound of metal pieces colliding with each other throughout the forest.

As soon as the competition began, the children of the Baskervilles were fighting each other with Blunt swords were given to them.

A dull knife so that it cannot be used to kill.

Killing opponents is not encouraged in this tournament.

It is not prohibited, but it stops at a level that is not recommended.

If you kill someone, points are deducted...... This score range was quite large, so the children did their best not to kill the other person 'by hand' if possible.

Of course, it doesn't matter if your skills are good enough to take a deduction and you have accumulated enough points, or if you can kill your opponent secretly enough to be unnoticed by the leader dogs.

Well, even though the guardian knights who act as guide dogs keep their eyes open 24 hours a day, mysterious deaths and accidental deaths occur frequently during the practical evaluation, so this opportunity may be used to eliminate a rival or a guy you hated.

...But.

There was no Vikir in this fierce competition.

Vikir acted like he had no interest in scoring from the start.

All he did was, as soon as the bell struck, to move swiftly out of the reservation and settle down in the wasteland outside the boundary bordering the bodering Zone.

'...Was it here?'

Vikir was reminiscing about his days as a student before returning and his days as an instructor.

If you go straight this way, there is a wasteland that is narrowly inside the border area.

There, an old dead tree stood tall, but the roots that extend deep into the ground were soft and rotten, so the whole ground is soft.

Before long, Vikir found the land he was aiming for.

Unlike other places, the soil there is exceptionally reddish.

Vikir broke a branch and began digging and poking the ground.

While the other brothers fought in the distance, winning and losing points, Vikir silently dug the ground.

The guide dog guardians kept observing Vikir while hiding in a secret place.

However, even after several days, Vikir continued to be seen digging a pit.

'Looks like he's just hiding there to kill time.'

'It's a little disappointing?'

'There's no need to keep watching.'

Since he was a Vikir who had been prominent since his childhood, the Guardian Knights had high hopes for him, but this was quite disappointing.

Digging and hiding in pits was typical behavior of cowards, low-ranking and insignificant children.

In the end, the Guardian Knights who couldn't keep an eye on him began to take their eyes off Vikir one by one.

...But.

One still didn't pay attention to the fights between the children.

Just how deep the 8-year-old Vikir digs the pit and what he does in it.

◆

“This place is still like a cradle.”

Vikir.

He was sitting at the bottom of the pit and having a good time.

Le Rogue Mountain, was such a comfortable and cozy place for him.

Outside, the Guardian Knights stood guard instead, and competitors did not come to check on him.

When he was thirsty, he would collect dew that formed overnight on a large leaf hanging in the pit, and if he was hungry, he would catch a passing snake or mole and roast it.

Rather, they were much better than the food that comes out as a school lunch.

Even the bed that he made myself was better.

The beds for kids were made of monster skins or thorns, so they were very hard and rough.

But here in the pit, well-dried straw, sawdust, and burnt ashes are softly laid out, so it's very warm and comfortable.

Vikir closed his eyes for a moment while roasting a rat he had caught the night before.

<The rat 'Norvegicus'>

Hazard Class: F

Size: 50cm

Found in: all continents

– A mouse that has been stricken with demonic energy.

A adult Norvegicus has the intelligence and size of a small dog, so it is an object of disgust for women and girls.

After cleaning, it is surprisingly edible if you cook it well over a fire or boil it well in water.

When it comes to information about monsters, no matter how low they are, Vikir clearly memorized them all.

It was thanks to the monster encyclopedia that he had before returning.

Of course, Vikir wasn't the only one who memorized all the monster books in the world before returning.

In the Age of Destruction, everyone was a hunter.

'......But now I'm the only hunter alive.'

Maybe it's a situation closer to the hounds than the hunters.

But that would only make the hunter more miserable.

“What could be more ironic than a hunter who dies from being bitten on the neck by his dog?”

Suddenly, I recall the conversation I had with Hugo before returning.

This happened shortly before being executed.

'When you train a dog, you have to risk dying. Usually two out of three die. Do you think it's heartless?'

'No.'

'Of course not. Because the owner also trains with the preparedness to die from being bitten by a dog. Owners should always be trained. You never know when you'll die from being bitten by blind teeth.'

It was a fact that Hugo himself was aware of.

Maybe that's why Hugo didn't trust anyone in this world. Even himself.

“.......”

Vikir shook his head to clear his thoughts.

Then he took one of his peas from a sack hanging from his waist.

Blood Bean. Dark red bean with a huge coca concentration.

Vikir tossed a pea into the fire.

The stinky and other odors are removed from the plump fat rat meat, and replaced with the faint scent of coca.

'Cacao beans, especially bloody beans, are the best for removing odor!'

It was a recipe he learned from a late sergeant in the same platoon when he was drafted into the war against the demons.

“......Camping makes me think a lot about the past.”

Vikir looked around him.

All the eyes that had been watching him were now gone.

Perhaps the guide dogs, who found his behavior uninteresting, moved elsewhere.

...If so, now is the time.

Vikir reached out to the pile of firewood.

Then he took out a dagger from his waistband and started cutting down trees.

Wooden spear.

Vikir began planting these pointed wooden spears upside down all over the pit floor.

The tips trying to pierce the sky.

Dozens or hundreds of them are embedded in the bottom of the pit.

Like the lower jaw of a beast.

Even Vikir himself hadn't thought about what these teeth would bite into.

Outside the boundary between the Le Rogue Mountains, in the Forbidden Zone, there are monsters that are so big and powerful that people in this world couldn't even imagine.

...Well, most of them were familiar to Vikir who had passed through the age of destruction.

Vikir had cut all the wood that he needed.

But it wasn't enough to sharpen a wooden spear or toss it into a bonfire.

Vikir moved his body out of the pit to fetch the wood.

The gaze of the Guardian Knights had also disappeared, so now you can cross over to the forbidden land and cut down trees.

Before long, Vikir crossed the border with a stealthy spirit and entered the forbidden zone.

◆

The sea of blackened trees is incredibly dense.

The stems and roots that grew into a huge labyrinth.

If you looked around the dark caves poking through the roots of trees that had been burned by the forest fire, you might doubt that they are passages leading to hell.

Any normal young hound of the Baskervilles would avoid this gloomy place, but Vikir rather walked in on his own feet.

'Let's see. I guess this was the rough habitat?'

Vikir wandered through the forest for a long time.

When he was an instructor or skirmisher, he roamed around this place as if he were eating, so his eyes were clear as if he was going in and out of his house.

Yet.

Vikir found something.

Sizzle sizzle......

It's the sound of a ember burning in the ashes.

After following the smell of something burning, he finally found what he was looking for.

It was a pile of shit.

A fire that has not yet been extinguished burns in the blackened pile of dung.

As far as Vikir knews, there is only one monster that was like this.

He lifted his head and walked a little further through the trees, and before long he saw the owner of the dung.

A large body, sharp teeth and claws, and two eyes that glowed yellow.

<Hell Hound>

Grade: B+

Size: 3m

Discovery Location: Le Rogue Mountains Part 2 Ridge

-Aka 'the dog from hell'.

It is a being that unconditionally brings a terrible disaster to those it encounters, and if it is bitten once, it can never survive.

The brimstone fire spewing out from the eyes and mouth comes from the embers of the depths of the hell, and does not go out until the life used as fuel is completely burned away.

Even in the encyclopedia, there was not much information about this dangerous monster.

However, Vikir has faced quite a few monsters of this type through the age of destruction.

“Finally found you.”

The reason he came to Le Rogue Mountain is to meet these guys.

Vikir turned quickly.

As soon as the Hellhound saw Vikir, it rushed at him.

Kong! Kong! Kong!

The roar of a hound pursuing closely behind.

As soon as he got out of the way, he threw himself to the side of the hellhound ran past.

Chow ah-

Hellhound took several steps, unable to stop.

“As expected, you're an idiot who only knows how to go straight.”

Most beings who have climbed up from hell can do nothing but go straight.

Even elite monsters like Hellhound show weakness.

Grrrrr......

The hellhound turned around and started pursuing him.

Vikir prepared the following pattern.

Chow ah-

Drinking water made by collecting two days of dew was sprayed and drew a long line on the floor.

...Flinch!

Hellhound came to a sudden stop with the same momentum as it was running.

This hellhound species unusually did not cross water.

No matter how thin and shallow the water is.

Since it is a monster that is not good at anything other than running in a straight line, it is a hellhound had to run around water spots scattered on the ground.

It is a fact known to all hunters who have passed through the era of distruction, but it is a habit that is not well known in this world yet due to lack of research.

'Well, it will inevitably come to light later when the Pandemonium Gate opens and Hellhounds swarm all over the continent.'

Vikir faced the hellhound.

Although the speed of the Hellhound running had decreased, it is still terrifying.

Hey, the hellhound is a monster that even knights of expert intermediate level or higher have a hard time with 1:1.

Vikir before returning is also a monster so powerful that he was able to catch it alone only when he was 18 years old.

But.

Vikir did not come all this way without taking any measures.

“Canine monsters always open their mouths when running.”

Like a seasoned hunter who has lived through the era of destruction, he brought out a secret weapon prepared for this situation.

The most effective weapon for catching canine monsters.

...Fing!

The sound of beans hitting each other in his hands.

Bloody Beans.

It was chocolate.

Chapter 11

Hounds of Hell (4)

◆

An unpleasant growl that might be heard when metal pieces rub against each other.

<Cerberus>

Risk level: A+

Size: 7m

Discovery Location: Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain 7th ridge

-Aka “Hell's Guard Dog”

It is not interested in the ghosts who want to enter hell, but the ghosts who wanted to get out of hell are immediately torn to pieces and made into rags.

It lives in the depths of hell, where all the ghosts finally head, and leads to the ultimate of monsters of the Canine species.

This monster that spewed gas, oil, and flames from deep inside its three throats is Cerberus, the guardian dog of hell.

Even for a seasoned hunter Vikir was a super-elite monster that he had only seen once from a distance before returning.

One day, the gate to the demon world suddenly opened, and demons would explode from all over the place.

On the day that announced the beginning of a long disaster, warriors selected from the family died by more than three digits to this Cerberus who was rampaging at the forefront.

Because it was the beginning of the war when everyone was clumsy, the damage was even more severe.

The damage would have been out of control had it not been for the youngest female head of the House of Morgue at the time, Empress Dowager Camus Morgue.

And now, that same Cerberus appeared before Vikir's eyes.

“.......”

Even in the face of this mighty monster, which would be useless even if a hundred hellhounds attacked at once, Vikir remained calm.

“Right. Has Cerberus already crossed over? Why did a guy who only lived around the 7th ridge come all the way here?”

As the saying goes, the area where Cerberus was first discovered was the highlands of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

But now, Cerberus is down to the lowlands of the first part of the ridge here.

I don't know what brought him here.......

[Kreureung!]

It was a pretty embarrassing situation for Vikir.

“I can't help it.”

Vikir decided to flip all of his hidden paddles.

There is no room to hide his pre-return skills.

Fortunately, I had crossed the border quite a bit, so I didn't feel any stares around me.

He doesn't even have Young Do Dog Guardian Knights, so he doesn't even have to fight while hiding his skills.

...Flash!

Vikir took out his shortsword and blew mana into it.

At the tip of his sword, a gaseous aura that can only be created by those who have reached the advanced level of Sword Expert overflows.

Low Expert = Wizard Circle 1

Expert Intermediate = Wizard 2nd Circle

Advanced Expert = Mage 3rd Circle

Lower Grader = Wizard 4th Circle

Graduate Intermediate = Wizard 5th Circle

Advanced Graduate = Wizard Circle 6

Sword Master = Wizard 7th Circle

This is the general martial law formula.

What burns at the tip of 8-year-old Vikir's sword is a dense gaseous aura that seems to turn into liquid at any moment.

It symbolizes an expert advanced level, and it is a skill that corresponds to a whopping 3rd class in terms of magicians.

Before he returned, he was about 20 years old.

Vikir raised his mana and quickly moved his hand.

The shortsword moves while drawing strange scars in the air.

A trajectory shaped like a sharp tooth, it looked as if three teeth had been summoned in the air.

Baskerville Type 3. A swordsmanship in which three teeth are drawn with a sword and driven into the opponent's neck.

Vikir in his previous life had mastered this Baskerville formula up to the 4th formula, and was originally able to create four teeth.

On top of that, he had even the mana and aura of a high-level Duator, so if you compare then and now, the level is shabby.

But Vikir has another weapon.

His small body and quick mobility, as well as his body hardened by the blessing of the River Styx, are just that.

The pros are clear and the cons are clear.

Vikir swung his sword and created three teeth.

The child's hands and arms were small and short, so he couldn't create the 'fourth tooth', which was an organ in his previous life, but nevertheless, the gaseous aura and three teeth clearly extending from the tip of his sword were able to block Cerberus' claws well.

“......?”

Vikir felt something strange.

It is Cerberus that was too daunting even with the strength before the return, but is it possible to be an opponent with the body of an infant who is far behind the inaction at that time?

This means that something is wrong on the Cerberus side as well.

Indeed.

“......!”

Vikir's keen eye caught something.

If you look closely at the inside of Cerberus' side, you can see a dent.

His movements were a little unnatural, so it was clear that he had several broken ribs.

Even in the area where the fur was torn off, clear arrowhead marks were engraved.

“Who caught it?”

Vikir laughed incredulously.

Come to think of it, barbarians live on the other side of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

In the meantime, the barbaric tribes that the iron-blooded swordsman Baskerville and the prestigious mage have been harassing Morgue.

If he was driven to this place by the backslidings of barbarians, it seems that Cerberus' situation is not very good.

Earth! Daang! Kang!

Vikir gathered the aura that was scattered like a gas and continued to block Cerberus' claws and teeth.

Every time the sword and teeth clashed, there was a sound of iron and bronze clashing, and sparks flew.

[Kreureung! Kong! Damn!]

Cerberus tries to bite Vikir by moving his three heads, but fails every time.

“I'm kind of used to fighting triplets.”

Not that it isn't It is true that the three twins Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro's swordsmanship and trident tactics were inspired by Cerberus' fighting style.

I'm used to it because I was terribly bullied by the triplets during numerous performance evaluations in my previous life.

Most of the numerous anomalous patterns were familiar.

The triplets in the previous life were skilled and smart, so they learned Cerberus' attack patterns as if they were born with them, and Vikir is reminiscing about those days and dealing with Cerberus.

Booung!

Baskerville Type 1, sharp teeth bounce off Cerberus' teeth.

Kang!

Baskerville Type 2, second tooth half lodged in Cerberus' neck.

...Fu-wook!

Baskerville Type 3, the third tooth strikes the second, driving it even deeper into Cerberus' neck.

Vikir's Baskerville ceremony was clearly similar to the normal Baskerville ceremony, but was subtly different.

The swordsmen who have passed through the age of destruction have something that the swordsmen of the previous era cannot copy.

Existing swordsmanship theories of the peaceful era were completely reinterpreted through the era of destruction, and unnecessary flab, fat, and grease were drained to the limit.

A sword that only moves to kill its opponent.

Here, extreme practical experience was added.

To put it in an analogy, the swordsmanship of the general world is like beef with good marbling, the swordsmanship of the Baskerville family is tough chicken breast, and the current swordsmanship of Vikir is like dried beef jerky.

The essence of the extreme, that is the intention to kill the other person.

Vikir's sword has a clear sense of purpose.

...Fuck!

The shortsword hit Cerberus' side.

The gas-like aura exploded and Cerberus let out a scream.

However, Cerberus, the guard dog of hell, does not faint at this level.

The guy stabbed his claw into the empty part just below the trajectory the shortsword had drawn.

Knock!

Since I took the bones of my opponent, it is natural for me to sacrifice my own flesh.

Vikir's back snapped.

But. Surprisingly, his body, which was almost pickled in the River Styx, withstood Cerberus' claws.

“......But twice would be impossible.”

Vikir frowned.

No gut burst, but several of his ribs were definitely broken.

Besides, to make matters worse.

Pacan!

The short sword that couldn't withstand Vikir's aura eventually broke.

“This.”

Difficulty. But a seasoned hunter always finds the best route even under these circumstances. That.

“It's a series of 36 lines.”

Thirty-six strategies devised by the head of the Leviathan family, who is the most knowledgeable in the art of war among the 7 families.

Among them, the 36th is the circumstance sangchaek (走爲上策).

Hodak-

Vikir quickly turned around and kicked the ground as hard as he could.

Then Cerberus, who seized the victory, goes after such a Vikir.

[...] Kreureung!]

Cerberus, who attacked in an instant, would have been caught right away if it hadn't been for the huge wounds carved on his side.

Vikir escaped the floodwaters, deeply grateful to the nameless savage tribe beyond the mountains.

Yet. You can see the boundary that Vikir has crossed.

Unfortunately or fortunately, there were no guide dogs around.

Vikir jumped over the barbed wire marking the border and ran.

Cerberus smashed the barbed wire and stake right in front of his eyes and smashed them, then thrust three of his heads into Vikir's back.

[Kong! Kong! Keong!]

What could be more powerful than a hound chasing its prey?

Cerberus opens his mouth in triumph.

The distance now narrowed right in front of him. Soon. Soon you will be able to chew the flesh and bite the bones of your prey.

...Thump!

If only it hadn't been for the floor that suddenly went down.

Pook-

Suddenly, the floor collapsed.

Cerberus threw himself into a pit covered with dry straw to make it indistinguishable from the plain.

Falling into the trap, Cerberus lost his balance, but he landed on the ground and tried to jump back over the pit.

......But that was impossible.

Fufufufufu!

This is because numerous wooden spears stuck upside down on the floor stabbed her body.

[Sweet!]

A tearing scream erupted from each of Cerberus' three heads.

At the bottom of the pit Vikir had dug, there were countless wooden spears protruding.

Of course, most of the wooden spears could not pierce Cerberus' hard skin and broke, but some wooden spears penetrated

Cerberus' body and left fatal wounds.

It was the lower abdomen on the inside of the side, where the arrowhead-shaped wound had been deeply dug.

“Welcome to the cradle of the sword.”

Vikir briefly congratulated himself.

Originally, this trap was made in preparation for being chased by other monsters such as hellhounds.

They were installed just to impede movement or a little.

Now I'm making quite an unexpected income.

But that's it

Bubbly......

Cerberus snapped and broke the wooden spears stuck in his side and mouth, and his whole body trembled violently.

A mad rage, but it was something else that made Cerberus' body tremble before that.

Blood Bean!

Vikir boiled the bloodbean beans and soaked the wooden spear in the water so that the energy soaked into the tip of the spear.

Cerberus is also a canine monster. A large amount of chocolate energy permeates directly into the body through the blood of the wound.

However, like a high-ranking monster, he did not fall down at once.

Foam at the mouth, burning excrement dripping from the anus, and the thick smell of chocolate coffee.

But even so, the three heads stand upright and stare at Vikir.

Vikir shook his sack and took out all the Bloody Beans.

Tick! Tick tick! Sudden!

Beans fly towards Cerberus's three gaping jaws.

Most of the beans thrown by Vikir landed in Cerberus's mouth, which was slowed down by his spear.

As a result, Cerberus' movement gradually slows down.

Dduduk! Pop!

Eventually, Cerberus broke several wooden spears stuck in his body and drove Vikir to the corner of his pit.

It was around the time the sack of Blood Bean Beans was empty.

Cerberus has become a wreck, but he still has the strength to bite his prey by the neck with a final leap.

“.......”

Knowing that, Vikir, who had been driven to a dead end, looked extremely prudent.

Before long, Cerberus moved.

Vikir also lunges forward, clutching one of his wooden spears.

...Pod!

The wooden spear thrown by the hunter flew through the air and grazed Cerberus' body.

The wooden spear, which seemed to be slightly stuck in the wound on the side, was pulled out helplessly.

If it wasn't for the original arrow mark, it would have bounced off at all.

Cerberus bared his teeth at Vikir.

Cerberus' six eyes burned even more intensely at the thought that he would soon see the end of his prey that had been so annoying.

......But.

Breetle!

Cerberus, who was running, staggered his body for an instant.

Cerberus, who suddenly lost his balance, panicked, but calmly took a step forward again.

Stagger-

However, the second step was also slightly out of focus.

The same goes for the third step. In the fourth step, it even nearly fell over with its legs bent in a strange direction, and in the fifth step fell.

And in the sixth step, he dragged his body forward once, and in the seventh step, he fell flat on the floor without even crawling.

Only seven times.

The number of steps Cerberus took while approaching Vikir.

That was his last.

...Cheeky!

The three heads, foam bubbling at the corners of their mouths, fell down and never moved again.

Only then did Vikir sit down leaning against the cliff.

“......There is something worth hiding.”

The hunter's gaze is directed at the wooden spear he threw earlier.

A wooden spear that just grazed Cerberus.

However, the wooden spear is a little different from other wooden spears.

Attached to the tip of the spear were two small but sharp spikes.

At the end of this dry thorn, you can see that there is a dark aura.

A snake's venom that makes it difficult to even walk.

The Bloody Mamba's posion was still flowing through it.

Chapter 12

The Gluttonous Flies (1)

◆

Droopy Cerberus.

Greasy vomit flowed out of his mouth at the same time.

Tsutsutsutsutsu...

Immediately after Cerberus' death, the spirit from his body got absorbed Vikir's body.

This mysterious energy, called karma, karma, experience, etc., makes the body and spirit of those who defeat monsters even more noble.

“It must be difficult to carry this.”

Vikir tried to move Cerberus' corpse, but gave up.

And he decided to just leave Cerberus' body here.

Anyway, the cause of death was clear, and there were many guide dogs who saw Vikir shaving a wooden spear in this hideout, so there were many people who could prove it.

So, all he did was to remove a few important parts and entrails and bury them in a secret place.

...More than anything.

“It's not important right now.”

Vikir peered beyond Cerberus' corpse into the deeper forest he had come from.

Cerberus is basically a gatekeeper-type monster born with the habit of defending his territory.

Regardless of whether he had been pushed all the way here by the barbarians, it was clear that there was probably a 'dungeon' guarded by Cerberus nearby.

A dungeon is a cave-like place where treasures were usually present, but most of them are also the habitat of powerful high-ranking monsters.

“Cerberus is dead, so it's likely no other monster is there.”

In general, monsters are attracted to strong demonic energy, so there is a high possibility that relics with strong demonic energy existed in the dungeon where Cerberus was.

To be honest, Cerberus is not a monster that just lived anywhere.

Vikir searched the outside of the borders, keenly alerted to the usual spirit of Baskerville's hounds.

Hellhound and quite a few monsters fled far away just by lsmell of Cerberus.

Vikir's eyes trace back the footprints and marks of Cerberus, buried in the withered soil, rotting leaves, damp roots and dismal darkness.

As I walked through the withered thorns, burned roots, and decayed old trees, the depths of the flood were soon revealed.

Dungeon.

It was a low-lying crypt between large mounds of earth.

From above, it looked inconspicuous.

It was not made by Cerberus, and it is assumed that it has been there for quite some time.

Of course, this place was also a place in Vikir's memory. It will be discovered in the next 10 years or so.

“......But I think it was an empty back then.”

But now it is different.

The smell of demons hidden behind the rotten smell.

An inexperienced hunter might miss it, but Vikir managed to sense it.

...Clattering!

Vikir broke the parched mound and slipped down into the crypt.

Eventually, you will see a dungeon made of reddish soil and rocks.

A vein of ruby protruded out of the mound, as if it was connected to the Le Rogue Mountain, a tributary of the Le Rogue Mountains.

As he entered the darkness of the cave, he saw a deep, winding passageway.

A place so dark and deep that you have to feel it with your hands.

But surprisingly, the inside of the dungeon was wide and bright.

There was a fairly spacious stone chamber, and a ruby stone the size of a fist protruded around it, emitting a red light.

A stone chamber stained red like blood by the ruby light.

Vikir looked at his own shadow that was cast on the wall of the stone chamber.

“......Is it a dungeon with nothing?”

The stone chamber was just empty.

No, it wasn't quite empty.

At the end of the place where Vikir's long shadow reached, two skeletons were scattered.

A skeleton with cuts all over its body cut and broken as if it had been stabbed by a knife.

Looking closely, the inside of the ruby-colored had marks of a fight.

Judging by the marks, it must have been a very long time.

Yet Vikir found a page of handwriting written on the side of the skeleton.

[ First of all, it's okay if you don't know my name. Just call me 'Gain'.

Do I really need to stain this paper with my name?

After thinking about it several times, I write down a few characters for the purpose of preventing

future generations from making the same mistake as me. ]

It was an unusual diary from the start.

Vikir continued to read the text, relying on the red light.

After some time, Vikir noticed that these letters were written in a old script descended from the Baskerville family.

“Is he the ancestors of Baskerville?”

It was a reasonable inference.

[ This stone chamber is an ancient dungeon that has been talked about as a legend within the family.

My brother and I found this place by chance, went through countless trials to explore it, and

eventually reached this room.

It turns out that this dungeon once had a fairly tough difficulty level.

Although now it remains only as an empty and lonely crypt.

And it is presumed that the person who wrote this memoir and the skeleton scattered here must

have been twin brothers.

My brother and I killed countless monsters and arrived at this place.

However, the last task we received in this stone chamber kept our brothers on their feet. For a

whopping 3 years!

Vikir raised his head.

What is the “task” they are talking about?

The question was soon resolved.

It was because I could see the writings engraved on the stone wall in the direction where the skeleton's skull was facing.

[ One comes in, two come in, and one goes out. ]

It was a strange riddle.

Vikir looked at the notes again.

[ My brother and I pondered over this gloomy phrase for a long time.

However, considering that this dungeon has been passed down as a legend in the Baskerville

family, the meaning is clear.

We don't know what it means only one of us can achieve what he wants from this dungeon?

We brothers who entered the dungeon.

They were originally one when they were conceived in their mother's womb, but split into two

when they came out into the world.

And to get what they want out of this dungeon, they must become one again.

Realistically, the bodies of the twins could not be joined as one, so they had to kill each other to

remain as one. ]

It is the custom of the Baskerville family to instigate rivalry between siblings.

The two brothers started fighting each other for a long time, and the match ended with the death

of the younger brother.

“Then, does the younger brother here become 'Abel'?”

Cain and Abel.

The older brother who had to kill his younger brother in order to be 'chosen'.

Vikir thought as he looked at the skeletons scattered on the floor.

A skeleton that was almost weathered even in a windless stone chamber, no matter how long it had been dead.

However, the content of the manuscript was quite unexpected.

[ I killed my brother after a fierce battle. Now, I am the only one left in this stone chamber.

However, despite this, there was no change in the stone chamber.

A handwriting that gradually becomes colored with madness.

The handwriting also became more and more crooked, and in the end, Vikir had to understand the meaning of the letters at an almost decipherable level.

[ Even though it was obviously two to one, I didn't get anything!

You can't get out without getting anything!

Nothing! Nothing!

However, as for the last handwriting, it was returned in a neat handwriting, probably written after

a long time had passed.

I'll stop wasting time.

If there are brave descendants who will visit this place in the distant future, I would like to

you to give up.

Get out of here right now

It is said that nothing can be obtained in this devil's den, which only deceives and mocks people. ]

In the end, what he wanted to say was clear.

He passed through all the barriers and came here, but it was dog hair.

And latecomers are also encouraged to go back the way they came from without losing their strength.

...But Vikir thought differently.

“I'm not a twin.”

Despite the fact that Vikir is not a twin, the content of the assignment is still valid.

That means that Cain and Abel, who were here, misinterpreted the contents of the text.

“When I came in, I was one, but when you came in, there were two, so when you go out, you have to become one again?”

Baskerville looked at the cave behind him.

It was a jet black without a single strand of light.

And in front of it was a stone chamber where there was light.

Before long, Vikir turned his head to look at the skull.

What hangs over the end of the skull is its own shadow. Shadow!

“......Right.”

Vikir raised his fist.

Then he smashed the large ruby ore that lit up the stone chamber red with his fist and shattered it.

Clink!

When the ruby shatters, the faint magic within it also disappears.

The inside of the stone chamber was plunged into darkness for an instant.

OK.

Ku-gu-gu-gu-gu-kwak!

A strange thing happened.

The stone wall on one side of the stone chamber had collapsed.

The wall was so thick that the thickness alone could reach tens of meters.

It is so large that you would never think of it as a door.

Vikir nodded.

The answer to the riddle was simple 'shadow'.

When you enter, you are completely alone in the passage of darkness, but the moment you enter the stone chamber illuminated by ruby light, the shadows separate.

And when the ruby is removed and complete darkness comes, the shadow returns to the body.

When they become one, the final stage of the stone chamber will be opened.

Vikir cautiously reached out in front of him.

Fortunately, the space beyond the stone wall was a flat, single road, and there were no traps.

Cain and Abel would have sorted out the swarming monsters long ago, so all that remains is to check the dungeon's rewards.

Before long, something cold touched Vikir's fingertips.

It's the handle of a sword.

The sword was firmly stuck vertically into the rock, and an inscription was inscribed in front of it.

Vikir fumbled with his fingertips and read the words.

'Only the blood of the Baskervilles is this '...''Will I be able to pull out.'

The text mentions the last name Baskerville and Carl's first name.

And the moment he learned the name of the knife, a shock like a thunderbolt hit Vikir.

“......Was this an artifact that found here?”

Chapter 13

The Gluttonous Flies (2)

◆

'Only the lineage of the Baskervilles will be able to select this 'Beelzebub'.'

The text mentions the last name of Baskerville and Devil's first name.

“......Was this an artifact found here?”

Vikir traced the shape of the sword with extremely fine beams of light from broken ruby shards.

A black awl with an elongated snout protruding from a three-bead-shaped knife stand, round and reddish like a ruby.

The rugged handle area is glistening green and looks like a large fly.

Vikir knew the identity of this artifact.

As a child in his previous life, he clearly remembers seeing it in an illustration on a page in a myth book.

'Beelzebub, the gluttonous fly'

It is long to explain the origin of this sword.

To summarize briefly.

In the mythology of the distant past, there were demonic constellations called the 'Seven Disasters', unprecedented demonic beasts that invaded this continent, and all humans on the entire continent joined forces to defeat these demonic constellations.

And the remains of these seven demonic constellations were left in this world in any form, whether material or notional, and despite being in a position where they could no longer interfere with the law of cause and effect, they retained some of the power they had in life.

One of them was this sword, Beelzebub.

The heads of seven families, including the first head of the Baskerville family, each defeated one demon constellation.

For this reason, the remains of Beelzebub were kept in the Baskerville family's estate, and the strong demonic energy emitted by this artifact drew powerful monsters nearby. It is an old legend that few people believe in now.

'But the legend was true, and later this sword would fall into the hands of the demons.'

This forgotten artifact suddenly appeared on the battlefield one day and drove countless humans to their deaths.

Even among the demons, the owner of this sword continued to change, and perhaps the number of demons far exceeded the number of people killed by this sword.

...But now the situation is a little different.

Beelzebub's artifact came into Vikir's hands.

In my previous life, I was robbed by demons and didn't even know it was stolen, but that won't be the case now.

Buzz buzz buzz-

The sword began to resonate with the mana emitted by Vikir. The sound of the wings of a fly is loud in my ears.

Vikir stretched out his hand and caressed it, and the sword, Beelzebub, began to be absorbed into the palm of his hand as if it were part of Vikir's body.

...Pod!

As Vikir stretches out his hand for strength, black cracks from the artery side of his wrist.

Beelzebub would thus hide quietly inside Vikir's body, and when he wanted, it would spring out and serve as a spare sword.

However.

Beelzebub is a strange sword made from the corpse of a demon constellation.

This is not the end of this supernatural ability.

...Growl!

As soon as Beelzebub settled inside Vikir's suddenly felt very weak.

“......What is this.”

Vikir was a little taken aback.

In my previous life, he was used to starving for a week and eating everything in one meal.

When he went out into the field, he often stayed in hiding drinking only water for a month.

A warrior that has been trained so harshly can endure things like this easily.

Even in a body of a child there was no way he would be this weak.

...Growl!

Once more, his stomach twists as if in a fit of rage.

Vikir realized that this extreme hunger was not normal.

“Are you asking for something?”

That's right.

Beelzebub agitated Vikir with the buzz of wings.

Sniff-

Perhaps his sense of smell has also become sensitive, and he smells delicious somewhere.

It's the smell of demons. An appetizing smell wafted from outside the dungeon.

Vikir crawled out of the dungeon and walked into the forest.

As he approached the border area and returns to where he came from, his smell grew stronger.

The first thing he encountered was the corpse of a hellhound.

Beelzebub didn't even call, but he stuck out first.

As it should be, a hound that exposes its teeth without being ordered by its owner must be punished.

But Vikir made an exception this time.

Because the hunger he shared with it was so intense.

'Looks like he's starved for a long time.'

The corpse on which Beelzebub was embedded and the soil around it were very dry and twisted.

No, perhaps it is because of Beelzebub's mad hunger that the entire Le Rogue Mountains are made up of dead trees and parched soil?

Then, how much food did he need to supply to appease this in the future?

“.......”

Vikir shook his head and brushed away his thoughts.

Beelzebub's power was enough to bear the price.

Yet.

The Beelzebub that Vikir knew began to reveal its power.

Gulp- gulp- gulp- gulp- gulp- gulp-

The Hellhound's corpse, Beelzebub stuck in the neck, began to suck blood at an astounding rate.

Blood and gut juices enter Vikir through Beelzebub's awl pipe.

The hungry was filled.

...Sparkle!

Vikir noticed that one of Beelzebub's three eyeballs glowed exceptionally red.

'I got the skill.'

Yes. Vikir's intuition is correct.

Beelzebub, a gluttonous fly, had the power to steal the other person's unique characteristics or specialties while alive.

The width of absorption was close to infinity, and countless people were deprived of all the achievements they had made throughout their lives to Beelzebub and turned into incompetent people.

Unfortunately, this is harmful , so there is no such ripple effect.

Only 3 skills can be stolen from the opponent.

Vikir's Beelzebub gained a skill by sucking the blood of a hellhound.

<Beelzebub, a gluttonous fly>

-1 slot: Bleeding – Hellhound (B+)

-2 slot: none

-3 slot: none

An ability that is only manifested by Vikir's will.

Whoever is stung by this awl will feel the full mortal power of the hounds of hell.

In general, even shallow and minor wounds that do not bleed will always draw blood over time, and bleeding lasts much longer than normal wounds.

Meanwhile.

Jagged jagged-

Beelzebub sucked the hellhound's corpse until it was almost mummified before it fell.

The skill was taken away right away, but it seemed that he was simply hungry.

Vikir also felt his hunger subside somewhat.

...Growl!

But even so, he was still hungry.

The delicious smell that passed my nose was still wafting from far away.

Vikir hurriedly got out of the forest.

Eventually, a familiar boundary line appears.

Cradle.

You can see the space where the children of the Baskervilles take their exams.

When he crossed the border, he saw a hole he had dug under a rock in the distance.

Fortunately, it seems that the supervision of the guide dogs has not come yet.

Well, no matter how 'cradle' it is, the area is quite large. The supervision of the guide dogs would not have reached all parts of the test site.

Furthermore, since he was just sitting in the pit for a long time, it is clear that Vikir was already classified as a safe surveillance target and his surveillance was neglected.

Vikir crossed the boundary and went down to the hideout and removed all the soil and fallen leaves that had been lightly covered.

Before long, an appetizing piece of meat appears.

Cerberus. It was spread out as it was when it died.

Buzz buzz buzz-

Beelzebub, who smells the fat meat, is very fond of it and dies.

The sound of the wings of a fly grew louder.

Soon after, Beelzebub set his fangs into Cerberus' corpse and began to gorge himself on meat and organs.

But Vikir stopped Beelzebub.

“Wah- Whoa- This is proof of practical evaluation. If you damage it too much, it will be difficult to explain when you do an autopsy later.”

Still, Beelzebub doesn't care and pushes in from the snout.

Vikir's expression turned grim.

“No!”

Match!

Vikir hit the back of his hand violently.

He hit the back of his own hand.

Keeing......

Beelzebub finally noticed and removed the fangs from Cerberus' corpse.

Vikir saw new blood and abilities running through the arteries on the back of his hand.

<Beelzebub, a gluttonous fly>/ Awl

-1 slot: Burn (Fire) -Cerberus (A+)

-2 slot: Bleeding – Hellhound (B+)

-Slot 3: High-speed regeneration -Norbegicus the Rat (F)

Is it because Cerberus is a more powerful monster?

1 slot was occupied by the blood of Cerberus.

Hellhound pushed to 2 slots.

And absurdly, the 3rd slot had the blood of a rat.

Perhaps under Cerberus' corpse, the bones and hides of a rat that had been eaten were strewn about.

'Looks like I can delete the previous skill if I catch a stronger monster.'

Vikir laughed as he saw that among the three arteries that pulsated on his wrist, the artery where the rat's blood flowed had shrunk in particular.

For now, Vikir decided to leave it alone, as it would be better to have something rather than leave it empty.

Above all, it was a great harvest to obtain the 'Burn' skill of Cerberus, the guardian of hell.

Now, the person stabbed by this will be burned that never heals naturally by the flames of the oil world possessed by the hell watcher Cerberus.

Once you get stabbed, you have to live with the burning pain until you die.

Considering that one of the worst pains that humans can feel is burning pain, it must have been much worse than the bleeding skill that a hellhound possessed.

“Now I have everything I can get on this mountain.”

There's not much to do now.

Just relax like this until the end of the practical evaluation, submit the body of Cerberus to the guide dogs and receive first place evaluation, and that's it.

And perhaps Vikir will be rewarded for this.

“.......”

Vikir closed his eyes and checked his body.

As a wizard, he had already accumulated 4 mana circles.

The number of Baskerville teeth that can be drawn with his sword is three. No, maybe four now.

This is the stage of looking at the beginning of a graduate from the highest level of sword expert.

'If it is evaluated lightly, it is the highest level of expert, and if it is evaluated generously, it is a beginner level graduate.'

In practice, it is right to see it as an expert because it is half lower than my ability.

In his last life, no matter how much mana he accumulated and how skilled he was in combat, he couldn't draw more than 4 teeth because of the limitations of the swordsmanship he had learned.

For reference, the current Hugo has 7 teeth, and the Hugo before returning knew a swordsmanship that could draw 9 teeth.

Baskerville Type 9.

This is a swordsmanship that only extends to the family head and his direct descendant, the eldest son who will succeed the family, and the bastard son who will assist him.

It was a noble and sophisticated swordsmanship that was on a different level from the 4th formula that Vikir had learned.

But now it's different.

“......10 meals.”

Baskerville Type 10. Ten teeth.

The ultimate state that no Baskerville in this world could reach.

A legendary swordsmanship textbook that contained the teachings of the first head of the family who were said to have subdued the demonic constellation belonging to the Seven Disasters in the distant past.

Vikir knew where the treasure was.

'I don't have to go far.'

Unexpectedly, it is rotting in a very close place, among miscellaneous books that are so common and close that anyone can easily read them.

Who will give it to you?

Hugo Le Baskerville, the head of the Baskerville family.

He will hand it over to Vikir himself.

He couldn't even imagine how much the value of the job book he handed over was.

Chapter 14

Solitary (1)

◆

Practical evaluation was over.

As the hounds came back.

Usually, hounds receive the monster corpse as a spoil.

The same was true of the children of the Baskervilles.

They acquired shields, swords, necklaces, etc. made from the parts of the corpses of the monsters.

Through this opportunity, the young hounds would grow stronger.

The exam that had been tense until the written test was over disappeared as if it had been washed after the ranks were set.

Perhaps because of the experience of rolling together in extreme conditions for a long time, an unknown and strange brotherly love was emerging throughout the class.

Of course, despite this, there were still some siblings who didn't get along well, but most of them solved their problems during the practical exam or died, so unexpectedly, infighting rarely occurred in the class.

In this way, for a few days a year, a relaxed atmosphere pervaded the Baskervilles after the practical exam.

◆

Hugo Le Baskerville, head of the Baskerville family, was receiving a report from Butler Barrymore.

“......Who caught what?”

It is almost unheard of for a superhuman who has risen to the level of a sword master to doubt his own body.

But at this moment, Hugo was clearly doubting his ears.

Deacon Barrymore read the report again in a clear, excited voice.

“Vikir van Baskerville in the class of 8. Crossed the boundary line and entered the forbidden zone during practical evaluation. Successfully hunted down Cerberus, a monster of danger grade A+. That is all.”

It's the second time he talking about, but it still sounded ridiculous.

An 8-year-old child went out to the forbidden area and came back alive.

Actually, this alone is great enough.

Just being able to draw a map or listen to testimonies that help them guess the topography and ecosystem outside the Unsealed Zone is a tremendous achievement.

However, this unprecedented 8-year-old child went into hell and returned to life unharmed, and even brought back Cerberus, the guard dog of hell!

“......Cerberus is a high-ranking monster that even the family guardian knights feel burdened to deal with.”

Hugo stroked his beard with a puzzled expression.

However, the detailed report that followed was even more absurd.

Hugo reread the report once and put down his reading glasses.

“He lured Cerberus into a trap and stabbed him with his throat spear? Do you think this makes sense?”

“Originally, it was an object that was injured by barbarians, and there is also information that poison was applied to the throat, Lord.”

“No matter how injured it is, it is the same. What poison was strong enough to send Cerberus away? Where else did he say?”

“That is...... Nothing else was recorded in the hunting log. I was going to ask the young master, but he said he was tired and went right back to the dorm.”

At Barrymore's words, Hugo put on a dazed expression for a moment, then chuckled.

“The young man is already puzzled but information is power, and power is value. Self-worth is what you have to raise and protect.”

Hugo turned his gaze back to the report.

It is admirable that Vikir did not immediately reveal the poison that caught Cerberus, but it is also admirable that he did not take Cerberus' corpse directly to the guide dogs, but covered it with soil and concealed it until the practical evaluation was over.

Deacon Barrymore admired.

“His patience is truly amazing. When I was an eight-year-old, I would do anything to be praised by adults and respected by my siblings. If I had caught Cerberus at the age of 8, I would have turned it over to the Guardian Knights right away. To get praise and attention.”

“Ha. If I did, I would end up looking like old Santiago.”

Hugo refering to a fisherman from a legend of the distant past.

He went out to sea and caught a huge monster fish, but while he was tying the fish to a boat and dragging it, he met a group of sharks, took all his flesh, and returned home with only a huge bone.

“If Vikir had caught Cerberus and started dragging that huge corpse around, he would have been the target of many brothers. He could have been killed if it wasn't enough that he was deprived of all his achievements.”

After hearing Hugo's words, Barrymore felt a chill running down his spine at the bloody family customs of the Baskervilles.

“To be honest, I was very surprised. It is not a middle name of 'le' or 'la', but a talented person like this is born among the youngsters who have a middle name of Van.”

“I'm different from the previous family heads. Bloodline should not be considered important when raising hounds. There are ugly dogs of good blood, and there are good dogs of poor blood. I don't care if it's a son from an imperial woman or a son from a street prostitute. As long as you have enough talent and courage.”

Hugo's eyes, muttering in a low voice, are looking out the window at the distant spire.

His second son.

Barrymore noticed what Hugo was thinking when he looked at the spire, who was in training at the top of the spire.

“It is said that even among dogs of good blood, there are ugly ones. Will you understand?”

“......I'm sorry.”

Hugo waved his hand.

“It fine. I'm the only one who loses if I have to be upset because of my stupid son. I just need a diversion.”

His gaze fell out of the window, this time to the report.

Barrymore nodded his head when he realized his master's intentions.

“I'll call the Master Vikir.”

◆

It was several hours later that Vikir stood in front of Hugo.

Hugo still did not beat around the bush.

He just asked it.

“How did you catch Cerberus?”

“I put chocolate on his throat.”

It was the same with Vikir.

Single sentence and an immediate answer.

There was no flab or grease in Hugo's conversation with Vikir.

Hugo's eyes widened.

“Is it chocolate?”

“Chocolate is poison to canine monsters.”

“Huh. Is that why you asked for chocolate the other day?”

“Yes.”

Vikir gave a short answer.

After thinking for a while, Hugo opened his mouth again.

“If true, the value of the information is quite great. It will be useful when subjugating canine monsters. There will be many advantages in trade with the information guild when raising dispatch results.”

“I think so too.”

The corner of Hugo's mouth went up slightly at Vikir's nonchalant reply.

Hugo asked in a presumably cold voice.

He said, “I heard that when the butler asked, he did not answer properly about hunting Cerberus.”

“You're right. Because he is not my master.”

“Then who is your master?”

To Hugo's question, Vikir answered again calmly.

“I belong to a family, so wouldn't the owner of the family be you?”

At that, Hugo finally nodded his head and smiled contentedly.

“You learned well. As a reward, the carcass of the monster you caught will belong to you in its entirety.”

Cerberus, a monster of danger grade A+. Its corpse was worth the cost.

Teeth and claws were used as weapons, organs and flesh as health food, and bones and hide as armor.

There is nothing to throw away from the corpses of high-ranking monsters.

It was a great reward to receive all of this in its entirety.

Furthermore, Hugo gave Vikir another prize.

“Since you ranked first in both writing and practical skills, the expectations of your family are high. If there is anything you want, tell me.”

“Didn't you already hand over the corpse of Cerberus?”

“That is my idea. I want to hear what you want.”

Vikir opened his eyes a little wide.

Hugo's words were somewhat surprising.

This is because he never had a history of asking his children for their thoughts.

He just give orders. Who would ask a dogs what they thought?

But these variables are always welcome.

Thinking it would make things easier, Vikir voiced his opinion.

“I want to go into the Inner Library.”

“......!”

At those words, Hugo's eyes narrowed.

The Inner Library is a huge library located deep inside the fortress of the Baskerville family, and it is large enough to rival the largest library in the world, the House of Morgue.

Hugo put his chin on his chin and pondered for a moment. It's rare for him.

“......Hmm. Go all the way. It is a place that only those of the pure blood can enter. Did you know and ask?”

At those words, Vikir widened his eyes.

A look that he didn't know at all.

'I didn't know about it because I didn't have anything to go into the library in my previous life.'

Culture, swordsmanship, and other knowledge were enough to be provided in classes within the family.

He lived content with the reality and did not show any desire to learn more.

That was the dog's virtue and was tamed that way.

'......I didn't know. If it doesn't work, I'll just do it another way.'

Vikir quickly bit his foot. Well, it doesn't matter. It's enough to sneak in under cover of night.

But things turned out easier than expected.

“You may go.”

Hugo's judgment was quick.

Before Vikir could put on a dazed expression, Hugo continued.

“I can't give you too much time. Will ten days be enough?”

“All it takes is one day.”

There is no need alert Hugo by staying in the library for a long time.

Hugo looked down at Vikir with a faint smile.

“What book do you want to read in just one day?”

“I learned about 'family history' during a liberal arts class and just wanted to know more about it.”

He just mentioned any book in moderation,

but Hugo must have liked Vikir's answer quite a bit.

“Family history. Feel so good. It's good to be proud by studying the honorable history of your family.”

If you see him talking about pride that he didn't even mention.

Hugo even recommended a book for Vikir to read.

“The depths of the Inner Library , If you look in the middle row of the library in the 6th control area, there is a swordsmanship manual called 'Baskerville 6th Form'. Read it.”

Vikir couldn't believe his ears when he heard that.

The world's Hugo recommends a swordsmanship textbook?

4 forms, which is the limit that Van's surname can go up to, how many 6 meals?

Baskerville sword forms.

This swordsmanship, which allowed him to draw six teeth, could only be mastered by the elite among executives and direct descendants within the family.

Hugo has now allowed it to Vikir. Even if it's a very brief reading.

Considering that the current Hugo had seven teeth, and the Hugo before the return knew how to produce nine teeth, Hugo's current treatment was truly unconventional.

Compared to the four forms Vikir had learned before returning, 6th was a powerful swordsmanship that was on a different level.

But.

Vikir, was aiming for something else, would not be very impressed.

'......It's just meat.'

A foolish idea that would make others faint if they heard it.

But I'm not stupid enough to go out of the way to show it off.

“Thank you. I will definitely read it and live up to your expectations.”

Vikir bowed his head and thanked Hugo.

He was a very humble and polite greeting, seemingly impeccable.

Of course, if he had known what kind of evil lurked inside him, Hugo would have stopped Vikir even if he had to burn the library.

“.......”

Thinking that he has finished all his business, Hugo just indifferently turned his head away.

Having obtained access to the Inner Library, Vikir greeted politely until the end and then turned around and left the room.

And.

He set out on his way to the most precious treasure in all of the Baskervilles.

Chapter 17

Solitary (4)

◆

“That's it.”

Vikir closed the book.

He had memorized the entire book, word for word.

He had memorized it so intensely that he could recite it with his eyes closed, even backwards.

And. The results were soon visible.

Ssshhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!

Vikir drew a sword in the air, just as he had learned in the book.

The first tooth was drawn sharply.

Then the second, then the third.

So far, so good for an eight-year-old.

Kirik!

Then the fourth tooth appeared. It was the Baskerville Fourth, my specialty before regression.

But.

...Pot!

Vikir's hand drew one more sharp trajectory, beyond the Baskerville Fourth.

The Fifth Tooth. It was a little smaller and blunt, but it was definitely a fifth tooth.

Baskerville Fifth.

And there it was, in Vikir's hands, unsteadily recreated!

“...In the world.”

Vikir repeated the gesture he had just made several times.

The result: success.

The trajectory of the sword was not quite right, given the child's small hands and short arms, but it was there nonetheless.

The fifth tooth was growing.

“...Where's the knife?”

If I had a knife right now, I would have tried to aura it.

But it's unlikely there's a knife in the library.

But that doesn't mean I can't unleash Beelzebub from his slumber in the artery of my wrist.

Well, whatever.

I was so happy it almost brought tears to my eyes.

Something burning in my chest, rising to the top of my lungs.

Vikir desperately tried to calm this overwhelming feeling.

“Now, as long as I have the mana to support me, I can definitely ascend to the level of my previous life.”

In terms of swordsmanship alone, he had already mastered something much stronger and more refined than his previous life.

His swordsmanship was not limited to the fifth level, but could be enhanced to the tenth level, so his future possibilities were endless.

Vikir closed his eyes and checked the mana in his body.

The mana hall that had been enlarged by the Styx River was still slowly accumulating mana.

Although it was impossible to determine the exact level of his cultivation, it was clear that his cultivation had risen to the next level.

“...Graduator!”

Vikir jumped from Sword Expert to Graduator.

With the ability to create a liquid aura at the tip of their blades, Graduators are a step up from Sword Expert.

Instead of just the tip, Graduator can envelop the entire blade in an aura that is liquid, dense, and quite malleable in shape.

When the liquid aura blade of a Graduator collides with the gaseous aura blade of a Sword Expert, the result is as clear as water vapor colliding with water.

Graduators are combatants whose physical prowess exceeds human limits.

Their strength is the measure of a House's prestige and, by implication, the Empire's military might.

Vikir reached this level at the age of 30 before his regression.

...After the regression, Vikir is now only 8 years old.

That's a huge step up from where he was before.

A level that most swordsmen can only dream of reaching in their lifetime.

As a mage, he's probably on par with a fourth-circle master.

Perhaps in the entirety of the Baskerville family's nearly one hundred years of existence, there would be no one else of his age who had achieved this level of accomplishment.

“ ... Moreover. The atmosphere of swordplay has definitely changed.”

The sword technique that Vikir had been using before was the 'Stabbing Fang' sword technique, which was basically what the hounds of the Baskervilles were trained in.

Stabbing Fang Sword Technique. Four of them.

Vikir had pierced through countless defenses with his four fangs, piercing the enemy's heart like an awl.

Still, the stabbing fang swordsmanship was risky.

While you can quickly become strong enough to be useful in combat, there are clear limits to your growth.

In exchange for the certainty of killing your opponent, you also took a lot of risks.

It is this 'stabbing fang' swordsmanship that is best taught to hounds for use as a discard card.

However, there is something different about the swordsmanship Vikir has learned this time.

It's called the Lurking Ambush, and it's sinister and painful, moving slowly and without revealing its power or aggression.

The melody of the sword seems graceful and dignified, as if nothing is going on.

But underneath it all lies a malicious intent to inflict the worst pain on the opponent.

Once you've succeeded in stabbing, you'll be met with an unrelenting barrage of brutal combo attacks that will make you feel like you'd be better off dead.

A frenzied onslaught, while still being able to protect yourself, is the perfect swordsmanship of this whole style, the Lurking Ambush.

“Perfect for hiding power.”

Vikir muttered quietly.

At first glance, the Lurking Ambush Strike bore a striking resemblance to a stabbing fang.

So it shouldn't be too difficult to hide their swordsmanship.

After all, it's called 'ambush' in the first place.

Vikir glanced around, making sure that no one was watching.

His heart was pounding with the exhilaration of reaching a higher level.

Buzzing.

The sound of a fly's wings in his ears.

I glance down at my wrist and see Beelzebub pointing the tip of a black awl at me.

“Get in there.”

Vikir scolded, not daring to show his teeth.

On the other hand, he was coldly calculating how much this Beelzebub would affect his current performance.

Vikir van Baskerville.

Age 8.

A swordsmanship that can reliably reveal four teeth, and an aura that has materialized to the level of a thin substance, could be said to be at the beginning of the Graduator.

Combine that with the experience of a lifetime of battle, a fifth tooth that can be drawn unsteadily, and the power of the magic sword Beelzebub, which can absorb the skills of monsters, and you've got yourself a force to be reckoned with.

'If I put my mind to it, I should be able to take on an intermediate Graduator somehow.

A 100% chance of assassination, a 50% chance of hand-to-hand combat.

“...The question is, how far do you reveal your skills?”

Who's going to believe you when you say you're a Graduator at just 8 years old?

It would be foolish to show off your skills.

In the real world, you're supposed to keep 30% of your power hidden.

“....”

Vikir paused for a moment to consider the appropriate behavior for an eight-year-old child.

It didn't take him long to come up with an answer.

Just enough to build up Hugo's anticipation, but not so much as to put his enemies on edge.

You don't have to hide your power and live in fear.

Rather, it's the right amount of power that gives you a chance to slip under Hugo's radar.

“A provincial assignment, for example, or a place at the Academy.”

As soon as Vikir leaves the library, he will have to report his findings to Hugo.

And he's already done the calculations on how he's going to pose on the proof table.

And now.

Vikir took a pair of reading magnifiers from his pocket and stared at the window for a long time.

Tsutsutsutsuts...

The cover of the 'Lurking Ambush' swordsmanship manual gradually turned black under the harsh light of the magnifying glass.

Crackle!

Soon, embers.

Vikir stares down at the burning book.

With that, the sword book that contained the ten Baskerville formulas was gone from this world forever.

It remained only in Vikir's mind.

In the distance, he heard servants scurrying about.

“What is that smell!”

“Sniff, sniff, grab and go!”

“It's not even under a preservation spell, ugh!”

The servants rushed over with buckets of water and were met by an apologetic Vikir.

“Sorry. I left my magnifying glass everywhere.... If it's something that must be reported, I'll be sure to tell the butler.”

The servants waved their hands in dismissal.

“Ah, well, that's not something for the Master to apologize for.”

“It's our fault for not keeping you straight.”

“At least it's a good thing you're in a place with a bunch of janitors, hehe.”

The servants seemed to take note of the 'if it must be reported' part of Vikir's words.

Vikir looked at the ashes on the floor.

“Well, it wasn't worth much, so I suppose it's better to pretend it never happened, and as you all know, the butler is quite busy these days with the ruby mine dispute with the Morgue family, so who has time for such a trivial matter?”

The servants nodded eagerly at that.

“Aha! Yes, that's what I thought.”

“Well, we lowlifes always want to make our masters feel comfortable.”

“As long as you look the other way, we're fine.”

Even they are glad to be spared the annoying report.

“I see. I'm afraid I'm going to have a lot of work to do cleaning up the library, but I'll make sure the burned books are filled with appropriate transcriptions since I remember the contents.”

Vikir made sure to finish and turned away.

“You are a good man. You've thought of the servants, and I'm sure others will enjoy this tale.”

“Huh! Hey, you're supposed to tell them about the book!”

“Just praise him, he's nice and impressive!”

My hearing has become more acute as I've gotten better.

I could hear the servants chattering softly behind me, but I didn't pay much attention.

He needed to rehearse how he would respond to Hugo's summons as soon as he left the library.

Chapter 18

Bared Teeth (1)

◆

“So. Did you have a bad day?”

Hugo Le Baskerville.

He summoned Vikir to his office as he emerged from his study.

He had cleared his schedule to the point of waiting for Vikir's arrival, and he was obviously looking forward to it.

Aside from his first and second sons, Vikir had never seen him care so much about his children.

But that's no reason to get carried away or panic. The old Vikir had been almost as old as Hugo now.

“A little bit.”

“Ho-ho.”

Hugo's eyes light up.

He's only been in the library for a day, and he can't possibly have gained anything.

Most of the other Baskervilles his age are just getting their feet wet with mana and haven't even had a chance to play a real game yet.

Under such circumstances, what could a child of only eight years of age possibly get out of seeing a high-level sword book?

But Hugo looked at the son in front of him, whose birth he didn't even know, with an unexplained sense of anticipation that even he didn't know the source of.

“What did you feel and understand in the library?”

“...It was, um... warm, and... pointy, and... sharp, and... squishy, and... squishy? Something like that?”

“....”

Hugo ran a hand through his hair for a moment.

A child's answer is always hard to understand.

But could it be the intuition of a master? Hugo suddenly understood something in Vikir's string of words.

“...No way.”

Hugo shook his head weakly, even as he muttered to himself.

Aura.

A sign that one had truly entered the world of swords.

A realm that no ordinary swordsman could enter, not even in death.

A level that even the prodigies of Ironblade Baskerville could only reach at the age of fifteen by training nonstop.

That is the realm of the 'Sword Expert Beginner'.

Hugo frowned once more.

A child of only eight years old. What was he expecting now?

And yet.

Hugo couldn't take his eyes off his son's magical face in front of him.

What if.

The anticipation of what might be made Hugo impatient and forced him to open his mouth.

“ ...Can you show this father what it is?”

All humans in Baskerville are reluctant to reveal their true prowess to one another.

It's almost instinctive, even among parents and siblings.

That's why Hugo chooses a cautious tone, even when dealing with his 8-year-old son.

But Hugo's worries are dispersed so easily by Vikir's cheerful answer.

“Of course.”

Baskerville Street's performance hall.

A small child stands alone in the center of this wide-open plain, surrounded by a crowd of people.

Vikir's eyes are closed as he holds a short sword long enough to match his size.

When Hugo decides to test Vikir's level, a crowd of people flock to the stage to watch the spectacle.

“Did he say he was underwater for eight minutes in the Styx?”

“Well, he strangled two venomous snakes in their cradles.”

“And for this practical, he's captured a Cerberus.”

Surprisingly, Hugo didn't deter the onlookers.

He just stares at Vikir in the center of the stage.

Butler Barrymore, standing beside Hugo, asked.

“My lord. How do you plan to test the Master's skills?”

“ ...I plan to pit him against a proper monster.”

Hugo was cold to the core.

To unleash a monster against a mere eight-year-old.

Next. Vikir's opponent arrived.

The creature brought by the Guardian Knights was a large, green-skinned monster.

<Orc>

Danger Rating: C

Size: 2 meters

Found in: Enemies and the Black Mountains Valley

A species designated as a pseudo-humanoid due to its human-like appearance and intelligence.

Due to their strong bodies, low intelligence, and excellent fertility, they live in groups and are no less dangerous than barbarians.

Orc. A demonic creature with combat strength comparable to that of four or five unarmed adult men.

Their entire bodies are made up of lean muscle, and they are naturally strong, immune, and resilient.

Captured alive by Baskerville, this orc was ready to hate and rage against the entire world, as he had once been a member of a warlike tribe.

The people around him began to murmur.

“Hmm. To say the least, an orc is a bit.... for an 8-year-old.”

“If it's an orc, you'd have to be at least 15 years old to deal with it.”

“Well, if there's still time, the guardian knights will step in.”

Even if they were Ironblooded Baskervillians, most of them didn't understand this matchup.

“....”

But Hugo didn't say anything, and the match went ahead.

And then.

...Clang!

The orc was freed from his restraints and released into the center of the arena.

Pushed back by the spears and swords of the Guardian Knights, the orc made his way to the center, drooling, teeth and gums bared.

There stood Vikir, sword in hand.

[Kaaaah!]

The orc lunged at Vikir with both hands open.

An eight-year-old child, an easy kill, and it caught him off guard.

But Vikir ducks low and avoids the orc's two hands.

It was a skillful move, exploiting the difference in weight and height.

“Huh?”

Hugo's eyes widen in amusement. The other Baskervilles' gazes were similarly amused.

But before the surprise could sink in, Vikir connected with his next move.

Bam!

He spun around, sword in hand.

He may be an 8-year-old child, but he weighs a lot.

Vikir's full weight was on the blade, and it sliced right through the orc's wrist.

[Grrrrr!?]

The orc didn't realize what had happened for a moment.

It's understandable, as the opponent in front of him suddenly disappeared, and his wrist was sliced off.

But before he could realize it, the next reality hit him hard.

After slicing off the orc's wrist and slipping out from under his groin, Vikir proceeded to cut off his ankle as well.

Thud!

By the time the orc realizes that his wrists have been cut off, his ankles have been sliced off and he's fallen to the ground.

A silence falls around them.

Everyone in Baskerville stared wide-eyed.

“...He's eight years old?”

“How is that guy physically strong? He looks like an old man.”

“I can't believe he can do that without raising his mana. What was I doing at that age....”

The number of people surrounding the performance hall grows by the moment.

Even the guardian knights and servants have come to watch.

But.

“....”

Hugo is the only one who remains speechless.

Of course, Vikir understood Hugo's reaction.

'You haven't shown me what you've uncovered in the library yet, I suppose.'

'What you just did to the orc's wrists and ankles was really just physical.'

I haven't even shown you what I learned in the library yet.

And now.

Vikir took a deep breath and flicked his sword lightly.

It's a fairly heavy short sword for a child, but in Vikir's hands, it swings like a puppy dog.

As if that weren't amazing enough, Vikir pulled off another astonishing move.

...Pow!

The tip of the blade glows faintly.

Everyone in Baskerville, realizing the identity of the light, gasped in unison.

“Aura Sword!”

The gaseous aura that symbolized the Sword Expert.

It was emanating from the tip of Vikir's sword like a ghostly fire.

The aura crackled as if blood was being burned for firewood.

An emblem of the Baskervilles, a concentration of life force.

The orc instinctively recoils in fear and backs away.

He tries to heal the wounds on his wrists and ankles with the orc's unique skill, Rapid Regeneration.

<Binge Fly 'Beelzebub'>/ Awl

-1 slot: Burn – Cerberus (A+)

-2 slot: Bleed – Hellhound (B+)

Slot -3: Fast Regeneration – Norvegicus (F)

Unfortunately, due to the power of Beelzebub within Vikir's body, this was not possible.

The Hellhound's Bleed skill overpowered the Orc's Rapid Regeneration skill.

Now the Orc would feel the full mortal force of the Hellhound's teeth.

Shallow, minor wounds that would normally not bleed will surely draw blood in time, and will bleed for much longer than normal.

If you slit your wrist or ankle, it's a guarantee.

Gulp...gulp...gulp...gulp...

The blood on the shortsword slowly disappears.

The Shortsword, imbued with the power of Beelzebub, lusted after the Orc's blood like a greedy monkfish, and the Orc was forced to offer it up as tribute over and over again, unable to resist.

And in that situation.

Boom!

Vikir's sword swung.

And all those gathered in the ballroom saw.

A single, ghastly fang emerging from thin air.

The first ceremony of Baskerville.

A single 'stabbing fang' appeared and sank deep into the nape of the orc's neck.

Naturally, the orc's breathing was instantly cut off.

With the agony of burning in hell.

Vikir displayed the kind of innocence one might expect from a 15-year-old in Baskerville.

Naturally, words were spoken around him.

“Crazy. I didn't even feel mana when I was eight.”

“I could barely form a ball of mana in the palm of my hand.”

“That kid looks like a perfect Expert Beginner, holy sh*t, is that even possible?”

Eight years old, when the youngest Sword Expert ever was 14.

This was unheard of even in Baskerville, a place of sword geniuses.

Butler Barrymore said with a mixture of shock and amusement.

“...Co, congratulations, my lord. A rare genius has emerged, a blessing for the family.”

“...Hmm.”

Hugo nodded, expressionless.

But Barrymore looked. The corner of Hugo's mouth, hidden beneath his mustache, twitched upward.

He could never get enough of his child's praise, so he chimed in a little more.

“An orc who can fight four or five full-grown men and not be overpowered. My God, an eight-year-old killing an orc like that with such ease. No family in the empire will ever have such a genius again...”

“Hmph. Enough, butler.”

Hugo interrupted Barrymore as if he were a stranger.

Then he opened his mouth with an uncomfortable expression.

“Apparently, the orcs are a little strange.”

“What?”

“Orcs are characterized by great regenerative powers, but that guy just lost a lot of blood. A sudden loss of blood in large quantities inevitably dulls them. Was that Vikir guy's sword poisoned or something?”

“Ah, that's unlikely, it's just an ordinary sword that was checked and handed over by the Guardian Knights.”

“Hmph. Then the orc must have been weakened a lot.”

The man was never one to take compliments lightly.

Barrymore smiled faintly and shrugged.

“Whatever. It was true that Baskerville had a rare genius on its hands.”

A young warrior who, at the tender age of eight, had become a perfect Sword Expert beginner.

When everyone, including Hugo, was quite surprised by this accomplishment.

“Wait a minute.”

Vikir caught everyone's attention.

Hugo started to turn away, but stopped and looked at Vikir.

Their gazes locked together.

Vikir spoke in a low voice.

“Is there anything bigger than an orc?”

He asks and doubles back.

Chapter 20

Camus Morgue (1)

◆

Ten men have ten lives, a hundred men have a hundred lives.

A person's life is unique and cannot be measured by a single formula.

But.

In Baskerville, the Ironborn, a person's life can be schematized and organized like a formula.

A typical formula is as follows

Sword Expert junior = 1 mage circle.

Sword Expert Intermediate = 2 Mage Circles

Sword Expert Advanced = Mage 3 circles

Graduator Low = Mage 4 circles

Graduator Intermediate = Mage 5 circles

Graduator Advanced = Mage 6 circles

Swordmaster = Wizard 7th circle

Sword mastery has been replaced by magical mastery.

In addition, the young hounds of Baskerville are not allowed to eat at an age when others would.

Their training is grueling, with every moment a firing squad.

In the process of digesting them, they usually go through a series of schematic growth spurts.

To reformulate it, it goes like this

Sword Expert Lower = 15 years old

Sword Expert Intermediate=18 years old

Sword Expert Advanced=20 years old

Gradient Lower = 30

Gradient Intermediate=35

Gradualtor Advanced=40

Swordmaster=?

Most young hounds of House Baskerville progress according to the following formula.

Children of House Baskerville typically first become in touch with mana around the age of seven or eight, at which point they can, at best, concentrate it in their hands and feel its warmth.

It's not until around age 15 that they can truly channel mana into a sword and emit an aura.

This is called the lower level of Sword Expert.

Most members of the Baskerville family learn a sword technique called the Baskerville Style, which is divided into three levels: first, second, and third ....

It starts with Baskerville 1, which is the level where you can draw a single tooth with the trajectory of the blade tip, then Baskerville 2, where you can draw two teeth, and then 3, 4, and 5, where you can draw three teeth....

Considering that most 15-year-old Baskervilles who reach the rank of Sword Expert are trained in Baskerville 1 swordplay, the following formula is established

Sword Expert Low = 1 Baskerville, 1 Tooth

Sword Expert Intermediate = Baskerville 2, two teeth

Sword Expert Advanced = 3 Baskerville, 3 Teeth

Gradator Low = 4 Baskerville, 4 Teeth

Gradient Intermediate = 5 Baskerville, 5 Teeth

Gradator Adv = 6 Baskerville, 6 Teeth

Swordmaster=7th Baskerville, 7 teeth

However, the elite of the elite are those who can master more than five styles of swordsmanship.

That is, only the true heirs of the House.

It is no secret that the current patriarch, Hugo Le Baskerville, can draw the Seven Teeth.

It is also no secret that his eldest son, now away on assignment in the far reaches of the country, can draw five teeth, and his second son, now in training, can draw four.

On the other hand, those with “van” surnames, such as bastards and illegitimate children, who are not recognized as legitimate, cannot learn more than five sword techniques, no matter how much mana they have accumulated or how old they are.

As a result, there is a definite limit to the number of teeth they can draw, even when they become a Gradient.

But no one is complaining about this.

No one. None. None. None.

For the swordsmanship of the Baskervilles was so great, and the mastery of the four styles was enough to make the world tremble.

...But.

There is.

Even within the great Baskervilles, there are Irregulars who occasionally deviate from the formula.

The bad ones are the hounds that don't follow the formalized progression and fall through the cracks.

These were nothing special, really. They were disposed of on the spot.

Those who die in training and disappear into the experience of their brothers, those who die or go missing on a mission and become nothing more than numbers on a damage report, those who are assassinated for family interests, and those who are rarely soldiers....

The casualties of the Baskervilles are many, but they become fewer with each passing year.

The older they get, the more seasoned they become.

However.

There are few, if any, Irregulars who deviate from the formula in a somewhat different way.

Even within the Baskervilles, a family of geniuses, there are those who are recognized as geniuses.

Such was the case with Osiris Le Baskerville, Hugo Le Baskerville' eldest son and head of household.

A little sunshine who will lead the Baskervilles in the future. A genius, by all accounts.

Until now, Osiris has been the greatest genius in the family.

But lately, a rumor has been spreading.

A mother-of-pearl cloud floating in the infant star. A tiny sun that floated beneath the sun.

Rumors circulated within the family that another genius had emerged to succeed Osiris Le Baskerville.

Vikir van Baskerville. Eight years old.

A prodigy who, according to the patriarch himself, Hugo Lé Baskerville, recently reached the rank of Sword Expert Intermediate.

A swordsmanship that could draw two teeth and a mana that would be two circles in mage terms.

He has perfected at the tender age of eight what his siblings would have to wait until they were eighteen to accomplish.

So much so, that whenever three or more of them got together, even the most disinterested of Baskervilles, they were talking about Vikir.

“...Yes, you mean there's such a kid?”

“Where's he from? Is it the van's surname? Hmm, so we don't even know where it came from.”

“Well, it's worth keeping, if not, then early....”

He listened with interest, or indifference, sometimes weighing his own interests.

And with that, Vikir had already bared his sharp fangs.

Meanwhile.

“Stupid people.”

Vikir himself, the subject of the rumor, was not concerned with the gaze or reputation of those around him.

He already knew where the family's power struggles and dirty tricks were headed.

How could he not? He had spent the last few decades as a dog dealer, bouncing from one line to the next.

...Chulpuduk! Chulpuduk!

Vikir thought as he watched the haggis fall to the table.

'I was only going to show two teeth anyway, I've had enough of this.'

Now that we've clearly exposed the true colors, we may be able to utilize some of the House's infrastructure on our own.

As I've said before, it's good to be recognized in moderation if you want to make sure you stay off Hugo's radar.

Vikir sat in the far corner of the dining room and began to nibble at his haggis.

As the salty, fishy gruel slides down his throat, he thinks about many things.

First, about her true skill set.

“Currently, my official skills are Baskerville 2nd Class and Sword Expert Intermediate.”

However, Vikir's true strength is already at the level of a Graduator Low, and in terms of swordsmanship, a Fourth Teeth Baskerville.

With his profound cultivation in the Great Library, he is on the verge of reaching Intermediate Graduator.

If he continues on this path, he should be able to break through to the fifth level of swordsmanship without difficulty.

“I'll reach the upper Graduator before I turn 17.”

By then, my swordsmanship will be able to reach the Sixth Form. Unlike before the regression, when you were stuck at just four.

What's more.

...Wiggle!

The spoon that was unwrapping the haggis suddenly flinched.

Beelzebub, lurking in the artery of his right wrist, had moved.

<Binge Fly 'Beelzebub'>/ Awl

-1 slot: Burn – Cerberus (A+)

-2 slot: Bleed – Hellhound (B+)

Slot -3: Super Regeneration – Troll (C+)

Beelzebub removes the Rats from slot 3 and fills the void by taking the skills of the recently killed Troll.

His opponent was bleeding, he was regenerating. It was a terrible combination.

Add this ability to the mix, and he'd probably be even more formidable than the average Graduator.

Vikir thought to himself as he continued to devour his haggis.

It was his sixth serving already, and he felt that his appetite had only grown stronger since absorbing Beelzebub.

Then.

“...Hey, hey.”

A voice called out from behind him, and Vikir turned his head.

“?”

Unexpected figures stood behind him.

The triplets. Highbro Le Baskerville, Middlebro Le Baskerville, and Lowbro Le Baskerville.

The trio that would come to be known as the Trident of Baskerville stood behind Vikir.

Vikir's brow furrowed.

“Look at these as*holes?”

Why bother asking? The harsh words come right out.

Vikir narrowed his eyes, and the triplets instinctively reacted with fear.

Is there anything in the world easier to handle than a frightened dog?

Vikir clutched the spoon he was using to scoop up the haggis, and the triplets immediately waved it away.

“Oh, no, not that one!”

“We just want...!”

“That, that, that, that, that, catching the troll and Cerberus was cool!”

...?

Vikir frowned, not realizing what was going on.

“Is this a two-faced tactic or some kind of trick?”

But looking at the trio in front of me, I don't see any signs of advanced psychological warfare.

As I stare at them, I can't help but feel a chill run down my spine.

...Boom!

Vikir had just finished preparing to send a spoon flying toward the foreheads of the three puppies.

“Master.”

Another voice came from beside him.

He turned to see Butler Barrymore standing at attention.

He had appeared out of nowhere and addressed Vikir in his usual polite tone.

“My lord seeks you.”

Hugo Le Baskerville.

He was now seated on a couch by the window in a state of great irritation.

“Is the butler here yet?”

The maid inclined her head groggily at Hugo's question in search of Barrymore.

“I looked under the window and it looked like they were just coming into the lobby on the first floor, with Master Vikir.”

“They should be coming up any minute now.”

Hugo nodded, then shifted his gaze to the side of the couch.

On the couch next to it sat a middle-aged man with a handsome mustache.

Adolf Morgue.

A delegate from House Morgue, a martial family known as the rival house of Ironblood Baskerville.

The younger brother of Raspane Morgue, the head of House Morgue, he is a key figure in House Morgue, always present as the acting head of the house whenever there is an outside event.

Adolf lifted the teacup in front of him and drank.

Then he looked directly at Hugo with a wry smile.

“I hope this year's annual event goes off without a hitch.”

The annual event Adolf was referring to was the friendly tournament between Baskerville and Morgue.

The Morgue and the Baskervilles train together once a year, in accordance with a decree from the previous Emperor, who said that “magic and swords are complementary.”

Though it was only for children between the ages of eight and fifteen, it was a show of force for the imperial family.

Even then, the atmosphere was frosty, with Hugo, the current Lord of Baskerville, and Raspane, the current Lord of Morgue, at odds over the ownership of a newly discovered ruby mine in the middle of their territory.

It was in this atmosphere that Adolf, the younger brother of the Morgue family, came to visit.

The purpose of the visit is said to be to socialize through an annual event, but... it remains to be seen if that is really the case.

Hugo shrugged it off.

“It's just a joint exercise, it's always been that way.”

“Heh heh heh. Didn't we have two children seriously injured last year, one from Baskerville and one from Morgue?”

“They survived, and were treated in time. How can you call that a loss?”

Hugo's nonchalant words brought a line of blood to Adolf's forehead.

After a moment's grimace, he coughed a few times and changed the subject.

“Hmmm. Hum. So, let's talk about this joint exercise, shall we? Oh, by the way!”

Just as he was about to cut to the chase, Adolf had a sudden thought.

“I heard that there's a supernova over Baskerville, and I'd really like to see it, I'm looking forward to it.”

“ ...I'm just calling it up now anyway.”

Hugo replied, feigning nonchalance.

But the observant Adolf didn't miss the slightest twitch of the corners of Hugo's mouth.

“That lizard man responds to his child's praise. That's unusual.”

It is a surprise in its own way. Adolf thought for a moment that he should go back and report to his lord, but then he continued.

“It is a great blessing for the Empire to have a once in a hundred year genius in Baskerville.”

“I would not go so far as to say that.”

Hugo bowed, at least formally.

However, Adolf's next words were quite provocative.

“Well, it's a double whammy, actually, because we have a once in a hundred year genius in the Morgue family.”

Hugo's eyebrows shot up at that.

Adolf smiled politely, then motioned toward the door to the parlor off to one side of the room.

“Come in, little Camus,” he said, “and say hello to the head of House Baskerville.”

Then, as if by magic, the door opened of its own accord.

In walked a small girl, trailed by servants.

Her hair flaming red, her eyes sparkling like rubies.

A fair face with a small nose, full lips, and white, even teeth.

Camus Morgue.

The girl, who had just turned eight years old, walked over and stood beside Adolf without a trace of embarrassment.

Hugo's brow furrowed slightly.

A supernova of the Morgue family, born only once every hundred years or so.

A girl who could hear the sound of genius even within the prestigious Morgue, where only magical geniuses gathered.

Camus Morgue.

The sight of her clutching at the hem of her uncle's cloak, her eyes shining brightly, made even the mighty Hugo soften his expression a little.

But cuteness aside, Adolf's statement was quite provocative.

“We also have an 8-year-old genius. Let's see your level of eight-year-old genius.”

The Morgue family had come to play.

'...Hey. You're not worthy of such a flirtatious provocation.'

Hugo tried to turn his head away as if he wasn't worth the trouble.

The Camus Morgue bombshell pinned his head back.

“Are you the thief who stole our ruby mine?”

Chapter 22

Camus Morgue (3)

◆

“I guess the Morgue don't teach you not to envy what belongs to others?”

Vikir's words as he entered the chamber changed the mood once again.

Adolf's expression, which had been subtly amused, hardened.

Camus also glares at Vikir with an angry expression.

Hugo, on the other hand, wore the same subtle expression that Adolf had been wearing all this time.

“....”

“....”

A showdown between two self-respecting geniuses.

The once-in-a-hundred-years supernovae of the two sides stare at each other in the center of the room.

Vikir studied Camus Morgue in front of him.

Red hair, sparkling ruby eyes, a sharp nose, chubby cheeks, a few freckles, and an innocent expression.

“Is this the Camus Morgue I know?”

Her childhood face and her adult face overlap.

If you take away the baby chub from that face, take away the haggardness, and add a few more years to it, you'll see a face ... that Vikir knows.

The Ironblood Empress of House Morgue.

She was known as the undisputed genius of Morgue, a magical family that has produced many of the greatest mages in history.

In addition to her magical prowess, she also possessed a stunning beauty that captivated the hearts of every man in her social circle, and she was skilled at using her beauty to her advantage.

With a figure that could go in one place and come out another, Camus could wrap even the highest ranking royalty in a skirt, making her the embodiment of power.

He did not hesitate to marry for convenience several times, and each time the prestige of the House of Morgue greatly increased.

In her prime, when she ruled as the Lord Chancellor, she slaughtered countless demons and barbarians in Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, skewering them and burning them with fire to establish a border of blood and ashes.

In her later years, she was referred to by the enormous title of “Heavenly Empress”.

“Dude, what did you just say?”

...But that's in the distant future. For now, he's just an eight-year-old kid.

The Camus asked Vikir in an angry voice.

“Why is the ruby mine yours! It's ours!”

Adolf laughed and Hugo frowned at the sight.

But Vikir dismissed Camus's protests with a single word.

“You must have traveled a long way to smoke this.”

Hugo laughed and Adolf frowned at the sight.

Meanwhile.

The Camus gritted his teeth, realizing that his weapon of choice was a child.

So he changed his demeanor and reverted to his logical self.

Saaaaah...

A chill ran through the girl's body.

Dropping her innocent expression, she spoke in a cold voice.

“Since you seem to dislike talking, let me logically explain why this ruby mine belongs to Morgue.”

Camus took out a map and analyzed the mine's topography.

“The only surface mines that can produce rubies are within our family, which means that the Baskervilles can't mine them on their own anyway, and it makes good business sense for the Baskervilles to give us the mining rights to the ruby ore beneath the estate in exchange for a percentage of the estate's rent.”

She is the only child of a prominent mage family who has never been overcome by logic before.

Her logic would make even grown men flinch, much less people her own age.

But Camus's pride was soon challenged.

“The mineral ruby is commonly used in magic. There is no reason for Baskerville to mine them, and it would be a great tragedy for House Morgue to have a fool in our midst who would open up our lands for rent.”

Camus stared blankly at Vikir's argument.

For the first time in his life, he had met someone whose logic didn't make sense to him, and it was someone his own age!

Weren't most men his age dull and stupid? Camus couldn't help but feel a little confused.

...Meanwhile.

Camus's and Vikir's arguments were not those of mere eight-year-olds.

Both had a firm grasp on the logic of the Morgues and Baskervilles, and Adolf and Hugo could not help but watch with interest.

Camus narrowed his eyes.

“Well, that's curious. I've never met anyone like you before. I don't know anyone my age who can talk to me.”

“I go outside a lot.”

“...Excuse me. I've been outside a lot already, if you mean inspecting the estate. What makes you think you know anything about my life?”

“Actually, I have no interest in your life, the problem is Ruby. If you want to change the subject, do it alone.”

Vikir's stoic demeanor is replaced by a glint in Camus's eye.

“You're the first guy I've ever met who's been this indifferent to me!” is the classic, clichéd, yet timeless sentiment.

I just did that.

She's a direct descendant of House Morgue, and she's been the recipient of countless favors.

Where else would she go to receive such a blatant pat on the back from someone her own age?

Moreover, this is a stage he cannot afford to lose, an argument he cannot afford to lose.

My pride has never been diminished.

Camus asked pointedly.

“The mine is in Morgue territory, so the mining rights belong to Morgue!”

“The vein runs beneath Baskerville's territory, so the mining rights belong to Baskerville.”

“I thought Baskerville was not interested in rubies!”

“That's right, they only care about their territory, which is why they don't want you to come in. Is that hard to understand?”

Morgue is interested in the ruby, and Baskerville is interested in the territory. There's no way they can agree on anything.

The adults standing behind the children didn't see eye to eye with them, so the dispute was far from resolved.

Then.

Camus's ruby eyes sparkled.

“Very well, I'll make sure you know where the ruby ore belongs!”

The Camus picked up a brush and ink from his desk.

He began to draw on the floor.

A large circle centered on Vikir, and a larger circle centered on Camus.

The two circles touched each other.

Then, Camus made a big wall of paper to separate the two circles.

(The wall of paper was so large that two servants had to hold it up on each side.)

Then Camus on the other side of the paper wall said.

“This is your land, and this is my land.”

“....”

Vikir made no reply.

Only Hugo and Adolf watched with interest as the two eight-year-olds argued.

Then.

...Boom!

The wall of paper was torn apart.

Camus tore through the paper wall and stuck his arm through.

A white, chubby arm broke through the paper wall and entered Vikir's land.

The camel asked Vikir.

“Now, whose arm is this?”

Adolf's face lit up when he heard the answer.

Hugo's face crumpled.

The camel's analogy was clear.

Even though his arm had crossed the boundary, he still owned it, and so did the ruby vein.

It was the wisdom of his ancestors, who, long ago, when the persimmons on their persimmon tree grew over their neighbor's fence, went to claim them.

But.

“...Hmm. Who does this arm belong to?”

Vikir is not a very likable character.

Chin!

A strong grip that doesn't look like it belongs to an eight-year-old grabs a white, chubby forearm.

Before Camus can squeal, Vikir is the first to speak.

“He's mine now.”

Instantly, an immense sense of power radiates from Vikir.

It wasn't the kind of power that comes from drawing on mana, but the kind of power that comes from existence itself.

It was an overwhelming force that only seasoned hunters from the Age of Destruction could exude.

It was enough to make even Adolf and Hugo cringe for a moment.

Not to mention Camus, who was only eight years old.

“...What?”

Camus tried to swat his hand away, but to no avail.

Boom.

The wall of paper ripped open, and Vikir yanked on Camus's arm.

The distance between them was now close enough for their noses to touch.

“...!”

For a moment, Camus's gaze wavered.

It's the first time he's ever seen another child this close. Not of the same gender, but of the opposite one.

On the other side of the wall, the face of the first boy outside of his clan was incredibly familiar and yet strange at the same time.

Dark hair, dark eyes, white skin.

And a body odor unlike any he'd ever smelled before, and a breath that was almost too quiet to be heard.

For a moment, Camus felt a jolt that seemed to knock the wind out of him.

It was a very foreign experience for the eight-year-old, who hadn't had much experience wandering outside of the clan.

“He looks cute.”

Camus thought, momentarily forgetting the gravity of the situation.

Is that why?

He made the mistake of blushing and backing away from an important meeting.

“My, why am I yours, woo, you're hilarious!”

It's hard to tell if the attack landed because he's looking down at the floor.

Adolf and Hugo watched the scene with subtle expressions.

“Humph.”

“Hum, hum.”

Important diplomatic matters mixed with the tender sensibilities of eight-year-olds made for a very awkward atmosphere that was neither theirs nor mine.

...Just then.

Vikir's words broke the ice.

“Who says you're mine?”

At the same time, Vikir's grip tightened.

Camus was pulled firmly back towards Vikir.

Before she could scream in surprise, Vikir's other hand moved.

“Your arm is mine.”

As he spoke, Vikir plucked something from his waistband like lightning.

It was a sharpened dagger.

It was a shocking sight that made Camus, Adolf, and even the usually poker-faced Hugo hiccup.

Chapter 24

Camus Morgue (5)

◆

“Aaah!”

Camus summoned fire and ice, lightning and boulders, and began pounding the ground.

Vikir narrowly avoided all of them, gradually moving closer and closer to the border with the other side of the performance hall.

“You bastard, don't run away, stick to me!”

Camus shouted, trembling. It seemed to regain some of the confidence it had lost when it was forced to close the distance.

However, the three bumps on his forehead made her look anything but cute to others.

Vikir raised his palm and tapped his forehead three times as he moved to avoid the magic.

The smirk on Vikir's face was enough to make Camus lose his cool.

“I'm not going to let you off easy, you little bastard, not even if you beg!”

As Camus took his final leap, Vikir stopped running.

And that's when Vikir's clever calculations paid off.

...Boom!

The 15-year-old Baskerville and Morgue, who had been fighting in the next room, clashed fiercely.

Swords broke and magic burst, sending shards flying in all directions.

The 15-year-old Morgue used a massive fire spell that shredded and scattered flames in all directions.

Even Vikir and Camus were caught in its path.

...Boom!

An explosion. And cries of horror.

“Ouch! It's Camus!”

“Oh my God, Camus!”

“No! It's ...!”

The mages watching the tournament from the sidelines were stunned.

But even if it was an accident, it was a fairly minor one.

The flames from the nearby training grounds didn't pose much of a threat.

However.

“Gah!”

Camus screamed as he looked down to see that most of the hem of his clothes had been burned away.

As she hastily stripped off her still-sizzling clothes, she became an underwear breeze in the middle of the training grounds.

Luckily, the flames, smoke, and dust around her hadn't yet revealed her nakedness to others, but... was sure a gust of wind would do it in a few seconds.

Thinking the damage was minor, the guardians outside didn't barge in.

Only a few worried voices could be heard.

“Oh, no, not at this rate...!”

The teary, snotty face is not enough, even the underwear-like body is exposed in front of everyone. What an embarrassment!

'What can I do, what can I do, what can I do...'

If I show this kind of behavior, I will lose my dignity in the family.

I had once been kicked out of the house, naked, for talking back to my mother, so the trauma was even more intense.

“Nu, can someone... someone come!”

Camus crouched down, covering his bare skin with his hands as best he could.

Worried about the terrible humiliation that would come in a few seconds.

But then ... just then.

Flutter!

Camus felt the fabric wrapped around his entire body.

It was heavy, but soft fabric.

Raising his head, he saw a black blood-red robe covering his entire body.

“Wear that.”

Vikir said. He stood in a blur of underwear in front of Camus.

Camus stuttered.

“...You, huh?”

At that, Vikir shrugged.

“It's a privilege of children to be naked for all to see and not have their honor tarnished.”

The idea that it's a disgrace to show what's underneath the clothes is rampant among both genders, but... those are the stories of adults.

Little kids running around naked is not a big deal or an emotional issue or a flaw. Kids can be kids.

...Of course, the child may have a different opinion, but at least that's what Vikir thought.

After helping Camus, Vikir got up from his spot.

Then.

Camus pointed at Vikir's face and stuttered.

“Yaah... you, you are bleeding, you are bleeding!”

Vikir raised his hand and wiped the blood from his forehead.

Apparently, when the magic had been dispersed, the shards of the sword had been dispersed as well.

It wasn't a fatal wound, but it was blood anyway, and in a fight between eight-year-olds, blood is the difference between victory and defeat.

And now.

Whirring-!

A gust of wind blows in, sweeping away the dust and smoke from the stage.

It reveals a dazed Camus, covered in Baskerville's training clothes, and a bleeding, naked Vikir.

It's unclear what happened in the dirt, but everyone could tell that the mood between them was no longer one for fighting.

“....”

The look in Camus's eyes, in particular, tells everyone that the battle is completely over.

That dazed gaze was like a blank slate....

Meanwhile.

The other Baskervilles looked at the naked youngster, who stood tall and proud.

“Ho-ho, did you lose to the Morgue woman, or did you win, I can't tell.”

“By the way, the young one is very good. He must have been favored by the River Styx.”

“Of course, all those lean muscles all over his body. You must be keeping up with your training schedule.”

The fight between the eight-year-olds, which had been impressive in many ways, ended somewhat sourly with the loss of Camus.

◆

After the friendly competition was over.

Hugo pulled Vikir aside in the corner of the arena.

As they walked to the chamber, Hugo turned to Vikir and asked.

“How was the battle with the young lady from Morgue?”

“It was interesting. It reminded me of the purpose of the event.”

“A battle with a wizard is quite different from a battle between swordsmen.”

“I'll keep learning.”

Hugo and Vikir chatting away.

If anyone else in the family had seen this, they would have been quite surprised.

Hugo wasn't the type to talk to his children like this.

And Vikir was also feeling quite out of place in this moment.

'What is this, was he always like this?'

I don't actually remember much of Hugo as a child.

He was always cold, strict, and cruel.

Rumor has it that the reason he was so screwed up was due to the bitter loss of his first wife and eldest daughter.

'...Well, that's none of my business now.'

While Vikir mulled this over in his mind, Hugo asked his next question in a blunt tone.

“What do you think of the ruby mine?”

Hugo's core question, a continuation of the argument from before the friendly competition.

At the time, Camus's logic had been, “We can't mine the rubies in Baskerville anyway, so we'll take the mining rights for pennies on the dollar,” which was also Morgue's demand.

Baskerville, then, has no choice but to give a realistic answer.

Turning to Hugo, who was looking at him with some anticipation, Vikir replied.

“I think it's better to give it away.”

Hugo's eyes widened slightly at that.

“You're giving away the mining rights to the ruby mine?”

“Yes.”

“On what basis?”

Hugo asked again, and Vikir answered without hesitation.

“Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, through which the ruby mines flow, are downstream of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain. A little further up, powerful demons and barbarians abound, and I know this because I recently crossed the border into the Forbidden Zone on a practical assessment.”

Vikir said, remembering the arrow marks in Cerberus' side.

Meanwhile, Hugo's expression was brightening, albeit subtly.

“Hmm. So?”

“And the Baskervilles have made it a point to expand their borders by opening up those backwoods. If we can use the Morgue to our advantage, we can minimize the damage to the Baskervilles' frontier.”

Hugo's eyes glowed blue at that.

“Hoo-hoo-hoo, that's the answer.”

He understood Vikir's point.

If the ruby mining rights were given away, the Morgue would put a significant number of men downstream in Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

Baskerville would then be able to open up the wilderness next to them and drive any demons or barbarians that lived there back to Morgue.

When you take territory from demons or barbarians, you must dry up their seeds so that the natives will never seek revenge.

Cutting Root.

I must kill all the demons and barbarians in the land, as well as chase down and kill all those who escape, and then I can take full possession of the land.

Return to the land.

This is because it prevents the departed from gaining strength and returning to take revenge.

But it's a long and painful process to completely exterminate fleeing prey.

So Hugo decided to clear the land and drive all the fleeing demons and barbarians to Morgue's ruby mines.

“Hahaha, the rubies will be even redder with Morgue's blood. You will regret entering our territory, child of Raspane.”

Hugo was pleased with Vikir's answer.

The Morgue had gotten the ruby, Baskerville had gotten the territory, and the meeting had ended cordially.

“Very well done. A ploy that fits my plan perfectly.”

Hugo said, stroking Vikir's head.

Vikir thought.

'Of course it was. The plan came from your head in the first place.'

Vikir knew this well, for before the regression, he had served as a hound to drive demons and barbarians toward the Morgue.

For now, however, he must simply lower his eyes and answer politely.

“Still, I think we should carefully monitor the movements of any Morgue who have entered our territory, just in case.”

“There is no need to worry about that. I have been slowly increasing the number of hounds I have sent there for some time now.”

Hugo's answer came as a surprise. Not that the plan was surprising, but that he'd bothered to tell Vikir about it.

Vikir was stunned to realize that Hugo's gaze had softened to the color of tanned leather.

Just as they were about to enter the chamber.

“My Lord.”

A voice called out to Hugo from behind.

Where he turned, Adolf Morgue stood.

And beside him, he saw Camus, whose eyes were still red.

The way it was clutching at the hem of his uncle's cloak, staring at him, seemed oddly familiar.

Hugo narrowed his eyes.

“Acting Lord Morgue, what is it, and do you still have business?”

“I have one very important business to attend to.”

“Well, let's go inside and finish it.”

Hugo opened the door and stepped into the chamber.

Adolf followed him in and sat down on the couch.

“....”

Camus still didn't say anything.

He merely glanced at Vikir before entering, then dropped his gaze to the floor and walked away.

He still wore the blood robe Vikir had given him after the duel, wrapped tightly around his body.

Adolf said to Hugo.

“The truth is, Morgue has been putting a lot of thought into resolving the ruby mine issue amicably, and the rent for the manor is just one of many issues.”

“So what, the price of me opening up the lands.”

“What about the marriage pact?”

Hugo's brow furrowed slightly at Adolf's offhand remark.

But it wasn't a frown.

Hugo leaned forward and asked.

“Marriage pact?”

“Yes. A marriage between a man and a woman from Morgue and Baskerville.”

Opening up the lands to another family for money might not look good, so let's paint a good picture by creating a marriage relationship.

But a marriage between Morgue and Baskerville, known for their long-standing rivalry, is an awkward and outrageous proposition.

Hugo chuckled at the suggestion, which he hadn't even considered.

“I see. And who does it link to whom?”

“How about this one's eldest daughter and that one's eldest son?”

Adolf turned his head to look at Camus.

Just then, Camus's head snapped up in surprise.

It's a sign of the times.

“He's my nephew,” he said, “but he's a great kid. Beauty for beauty, intelligence for intelligence, strength for strength, nothing is missing, and I think she would make a good companion for the little sunshine of Baskerville.”

But Hugo didn't care about any of that.

“Hmph. My firstborn is twenty this year. I thought there was quite a difference in age?”

“Eight and twenty. It's only a seventeen-year difference, isn't it? That's easily overcome.”

“Adolf was forty years old this year, wasn't he? Do you think he could meet a seventeen-year-old?”

“....”

Adolf suddenly became very quiet.

Hugo threw up his hands.

“Besides, my eldest son is already engaged to be married.”

“Is that so, and when...?”

“It's a prenatal marriage. You don't even know.”

Hugo's answer gave Adolf a troubled look.

Just then.

Suddenly, Camus raised his head and shouted.

“I will not marry anyone weaker than my mother!”

Her tone was quite confident.

Adolf and Hugo's gazes turned to her.

They hadn't even asked for the child's wishes.

Adolf smiled gently and stroked the camel's head.

“My dear, if you refuse to marry someone weaker than your mother, you will be a virgin for most of your life. Or you'll have to find a man with a huge age gap.”

“I'm looking at possibilities, and I don't want a huge age gap. I like people my own age or younger, and there were a lot of people my age in the audience earlier!”

Adolf shrugged at Camus's comment, as if he had nothing to say.

Then Hugo looked at Camus with a hint of irritation.

“Kid, this isn't a buffet.”

“I know, and I'm not interested in picking and choosing.”

With that, Camus looks up and stares off into the distance.

There, standing in the distance, was Vikir.

Hugo is stroking his chin with his hand when he realizes where Camus's gaze is headed.

“No! You!”

Adolf jumped up and covered the Camus's eyes.

“He has the surname of Van, not Les, and you're a dragon from the creek, after all!”

Adolf whispers in Camus's ear, but Hugo, who is now a superhuman, can't help but hear the whispers.

“Hmmm. That's true, but it's kind of pissing me off.”

Hugo mumbles a little to himself.

Then he turns to Vikir, who is standing next to him.

“Well, when it comes to marriage, it's what you think that counts. What about you, my son?”

Without hesitation, Vikir answered.

“If you say so, I will obey.”

It was a loyal answer.

Hugo laughed heartily at that, and Adolf's face contorted in bewilderment.

If you ask me to do it, marriage is not a timely process.

What a disrespectful way to treat Morgue's only child!

Hugo was even openly scratching Adolf's insides.

“In Baskerville, there's no such thing as direct lineage. Inferior things come from the family name of Les, and superior things come from the family name of Van.”

“ ... Is that what the Lord would say, my friend?”

Adolf looked down at Vikir with a smile on his face.

But the smile was cold and hard.

“I didn't get a good look at you in the training grounds earlier, do you mind if I take a good look at you?”

Vikir finally managed to look up at Adolf, who stood before him.

Sixth Circle Master. A powerhouse at the very top of the Mage House Morgue.

A delegate to the Great House and a master of words who is often the go-to person for diplomatic and political matters.

“And known as a terrible nephew fool.”

Vikir is alone, mulling over the pre-regression character data.

Adolf leaned closer and whispered in Vikir's ear.

“Child, I don't mean for you to hear this, but.... To be the husband of our Camus, you must be of a certain age. It's just a matter of opinion within the family, and personally, I don't think you're even close to being the right man for Baskerville.”

The words were spoken with a hint of bravado.

As is characteristic of politicians, Hugo's temper is quite high for a man who had just taken a jab at Camus.

But.

“....”

Under Adolf's pressure, Vikir doesn't move an inch, just stands there with an expressionless face.

In fact, Adolf's brow furrows.

“Why don't you answer me? Are you listening to me?”

Finally, Vikir's mouth opened.

“You said it wasn't for me to hear, so I didn't listen.”

Chapter 30

Special Law of Vikir (3)

◆

-Vikir Special Law, Article 1, Paragraph 1-.

-The person who pulls this stake (hereinafter referred to as “the stake”) shall be paid 100,000,000 gold immediately, as determined by Deputy Vikir Van Baskerville.

A law made and enforced by the young Deputy Magistrate at the age of fifteen, upon his first appointment.

No one in the legislature objected to this law being made.

No one in the legislature objected to the law being enacted, because they had no idea what it was for or what it was intended to do.

The citizens looked dumbfounded.

“What, you're going to give us 100 million?”

“You've got to be kidding me. One hundred million gold is four years' worth of rust rods for ordinary people.”

“You're offering 100 million for a wooden stick?”

“What's this for, a show?”

People chattered. They all stare at Vikir with unreadable expressions.

And that included Chihuahua Baskerville and other officials from the Enforcement Division.

The chatter only increased slightly, but when no one stepped forward, Vikir spoke again.

“Anyone else?”

No one answered the question.

By this time, Vikir had picked up his quill and scribbled a few more words on the notice.

-Vikir's Special Law, Article 1, Section 2-.

-The person who pulls this stake (hereinafter referred to as the “stake”) shall be paid an additional 900,000,000 gold, as determined by the Deputy Magistrate, Vikir Van Baskerville.

One hundred million gold and nine hundred million more.

“Whoever pulls this stake will be paid one billion gold in cash.”

A billion gold! That's a sum of money that no ordinary man can touch until he dies.

The people began to laugh.

“This is ridiculous.”

“Are you kidding me? What kind of fool would do this?”

“Hey, kid, don't play around, let's go in!”

“This is pretty funny now that I look at it, isn't it some kind of stand-up comedy?”

The people gathered in the square were stunned by the absurdity of the situation.

Some of them even openly call Vikir a clown.

But Vikir remains nonchalant.

“Is anyone here?”

He asks, and he hears a few laughing responses from around him.

The faces of the enforcement officials, including Chihuahua Baskerville, turn bright red.

“Why is the embarrassment on us!”

The officials in the back are fidgeting, unable to withstand the taunts of the citizens.

Vikir nonchalantly raises his brush.

-Article 1, paragraph 3 of the Vikir Special Law-.

-To the person who pulls this stake (hereinafter referred to as “the stake”), there shall be paid an additional 9,000,000,000 gold, as determined by the Deputy Magistrate, Vikir Van Baskerville.

A total of ten billion.

At the mention of this sum, the room fell silent at once.

A deathly silence.

“Whoever pulls this stake will be paid 10 billion gold in cash.”

Article 3 of the Special Law of Vikir was proclaimed.

The stares and sneering taunts are gone, and the central square is silent, as if nothing is alive.

The absence of sound, despite the huge crowds of people, gave me chills.

Chihuahua Baskerville and all the officials of the Executive Office were momentarily overwhelmed by the silence on such a massive scale.

But Vikir remained nonchalant.

“Is anyone there?”

This time, no one answered the question.

The citizens stared, unable to laugh or talk.

“What, what is this? What's going on?”

“Are you really offering 10 billion? Should we leave?”

“Are you crazy? You know what you'll get if you leave.”

“Look at that knife in his waistband. I don't want to be executed for being a rich bastard.”

You never know.

Why is this young deputy magistrate, who has just been appointed, doing this?

No one in the room had any idea why anyone would want to burn 10 billion dollars on a stake that anyone could easily pull out.

“Could it be that the stake is really heavy, so heavy that a normal person can't even pull it out?”

“Not likely. I've seen government employees carrying them around.”

“Hey, don't go out there! They've got something else up their sleeve!”

“In times like this, it's best to stay out of it.”

It's quiet in the square, with only the occasional shouting match.

“....”

Then Vikir picked up his brush again.

He was about to create Article 4 of the Special Law.

“I... let me try!”

From the crowd, a palm the size of a small film rose.

It was a girl in shabby clothes, a basket of wilted flowers in her hand.

She had a limp, and her face was pockmarked with spots that suggested malnutrition.

She raises her hand and steps forward, only to be stopped by a gracious old man.

Presumably a neighbour.

“Hey, Judy, aren't you Judy! You don't know what you're doing out here!”

“Grandpa, I'm fine, my mum's sick and I've got to do something, there's no flowers for the bullies these days....”

“You naive boy, you'll get stabbed if you step in at a time like this! You shouldn't be so ignorant of the world....”

“Hehe. If anything happens to me, please do me a favour, mum.”

Judy stepped out into the square, avoiding the disapproving neighbour's grandfather.

Vikir looked down at Judy with a cold stare.

“Pull it out.”

Judy clutched her hair as tightly as she could.

The citizens looked at the little girl with uneasy eyes.

Partly pitying, partly mocking, partly intrigued to see what would happen to the poor little thing in the next few seconds.

Meanwhile, Judy was breaking out in a cold sweat.

'Oh, come on, they're going to have to kill me,' she thought, 'I've been a laughing stock in public like this... and they're going to have to give me a few bucks.'

How much would it cost to be a clown in front of so many people?

'I hope I can get a basket of flowers for it.'

Then I can take a steaming bowl of meat porridge to my sick mum.

Judy stretched out her hand under Vikir's cold gaze.

Her trembling little hand gripped the stake.

And then.

...Snap!

The stake was pulled out.

The stake was light enough to be pulled out with the strength of a girl who hadn't even eaten blood porridge.

“....”

Judy was baffled by the ease with which the stake was pulled out.

So was the crowd watching, and so were the officials from the Enforcement Office.

“Pulled it.”

“I got it.”

“Pulled it.”

“He's got it.”

The chatter around me grows louder.

What will happen to the girl who pulled the stake now?

That was the initial concern, the one that had the crowd gathered here on the edge of their seats.

And then.

“....”

Vikir raised his hand.

He moved his hand to his waistband. It was where the hilt of his sword dangled.

Seeing it, Judy squeezed her eyes shut.

“He's being executed.”

She didn't know what the crime was, but it was probably some sort of insult to nobility, some sort of insolence, some sort of greed, some sort of vice.

In that brief moment, Judy thought of all the people she cared about. Who would take care of her mum if she left like this?

Just then.

“No!”

A near-terminal scream erupted.

A skinny woman burst through the crowd.

Her clothes were rags, her body skeletal and skinned, and she looked like she was dying, but somehow she found the strength to pull Judy into her arms and kneel before Vikir.

“My lord, please, please have mercy!”

Judy's mother. She fell at Vikir's feet with Judy and began to plead.

“The lowly dared to be arrogant, not guessing the intentions of the High. Please forgive me just once, I'm a good... child, I'm a good girl, I've survived my father's death, I've fed my sick mother, and I've been selling flowers on the streets day after day, even though I'm sick....”

The mother began to sob uncontrollably.

“Please forgive us... lowly things like us don't even dare to be pressed with the blood of your sword... please turn a blind eye just this once, please....”

The mother slashed her forehead on the ground, begging for her daughter's life.

At her cries, the crowd began to get angry.

“...Ma, that's good! What did Judy do wrong!”

“There was never another girl in this market as sincere and good as Judy!”

“What did that mother and daughter do wrong!”

“Who are you to persecute Judy when you have the power!”

The atmosphere in the square turned nasty.

The crowd, which had been as quiet as death, began to boil.

The officials, including Chihuahua, shuffle their feet nervously in what looks like a riot at any moment.

...Then.

Vikir reached for Judy.

His hand passed over the hilt of his sword and clutched the leather hilt behind it.

Tsk-tsk.

Vikir thrust the heavy leather sack in front of Judy's eyes.

Judy stares, dumbfounded, at the sack and then at Vikir's face.

Then, with trembling hands, she takes the sack and hands it over.

She pulls on the straps of this incredibly heavy leather sack.

...Pow!

A blindingly bright golden glow emanates from within the sack.

Gold coins. Countless, countless, countless.

For a moment, the room falls silent again.

Judy, her mother, the countless others watching the poor mother and daughter, all fell silent in unison.

Vikir spoke.

“Ten billion gold.”

The words were like some kind of oracle.

Judy and her mother were simply kneeling there, dumbfounded, in front of a sum of money they had never seen, heard, or imagined.

And it was the same for everyone watching.

“This is how the ... law works.”

By this time, Vikir had declared to all the citizens filling the square.

“It will be upheld.”

Chapter 32

The Social Club (1)

◆

A large high-rise hotel in the centre of Underdog City.

On the 69th and 70th floors, a large club is located.

'Burning suspension'

An exclusive social club where the best and brightest of Underdog City gather.

It's where the rich and powerful gather to burn off their youth.

Champagnes costing as much as 100 million gold a bottle were being flown in, and fast-paced, upbeat music was blaring.

Hookahs of an unknown variety send up clouds of smoke and colourful lights bathe them in colour.

The atmosphere was so lavish and extravagant that it could have been an imperial court ball.

“Here, pile it up!”

“Bring it all in!”

“Let's build a tower today!”

A room tucked away in the deepest recesses of the club.

Seven young apprentices were hanging out in this room, which costs 10 million gold for six hours and is only accessible to VVIPs.

Champagne, costing more than 100 million gold a bottle, is being brought in on ice.

In the centre of a large table, champagne glasses were stacked high in a pyramid.

At the bottom, 100 glasses are arranged in the shape of a 10*10 square.

On top are 81 champagne glasses in a 9*9 shape.

On top of that, 64 champagne glasses in the shape of 8*8.

49 on top of that, 36 on top of that, 25 on top of that, 16 on top of that, 9 on top of that, 4 on top of that...

One last glass of champagne was placed on top, completing the pyramid-shaped champagne tower.

The seven assembled masters chuckle and pour the 100 million gold champagne, Donquixote Perignon 666, from the bottle into the top champagne glass.

And then.

Cackle cackle...

After filling the top glass, the champagne begins to drip into the lower glasses, gradually filling them up.

When the bottle of champagne was halfway empty, the masters ruthlessly threw it away and ordered a new one.

And so on.

The champagne that filled the glasses at the top would trickle down and fill the glasses below.

Thus the 385 glasses that made up the tower of champagne were all full.

The master laughed and said

“Hey, drink what you spill on the table.”

Just then, the waiters standing at the entrance to the room rushed over.

“Thank you, brothers.”

“Thanks to you, I've tasted such precious liquor, and I'm properly pampered.”

“We will serve you with all our souls today.”

The waiters smile and lick the drops of champagne that have spilled onto the table.

The masters chuckle and sprinkle gold coins on their faces.

“This is the trickle-down effect.”

Champagne dripping from the top, filling the glasses below, soaking the table, and seven men laughing at the sight of it.

These men were the core members of the local government's Youth Autonomy Committee.

It's just a civilian organisation made up of second- and third-generation local tohu, yujiu, and sedo, but their influence in the community cannot be ignored.

They had enough money and power to hold some low-level government positions, but they were still aristocrats, lording it over the common people.

They had lived in the region for a long time, so they were aware of the situation around them.

As such, the Baskervilles also gave them some power and allowed them to handle troublesome matters on their own.

In exchange for a small amount of tribute and taxes, they were granted some autonomy by the Baskervilles.

...In fact, historically speaking, all of the masters here are descendants of families that were defeated and relegated to the margins of the Empire's central power struggles.

With the exception of the Baskervilles, who have been sent by the Emperor to expand the borders of the Empire, all of them are nothing special.

But the young people gathered here don't seem to think so.

“It's better to be the head of a snake than the tail of a dragon.”

“It's better to play here, away from the prying eyes of the imperial family?”

“Yes. I went to a club in the Imperial Capital the other day, and it was much more luxurious here.”

“Besides, we're guarded by those Baskervilles. How safe are we?”

“Giggle giggle – aren't the Baskervilles our hounds at this point?”

The masters were not without their faults.

While the Baskervilles were preoccupied with expanding their borders, they were rotting away inside.

So where did the money come from to pay for all this luxury and debauchery?

The main source of income for local tax collectors is actually quite modest.

At best, the water taxes from the reservoirs that water the fields, road use taxes, tolls, and the proceeds from the sale of livestock... are just a small amount of money to pay the butlers and serfs.

Both the money going out and the money coming in are small, but... in fact they had a hidden source of income.

Illegal slave auctions.

This is the kidnapping, imprisonment, and sale of unauthorised persons into slavery.

In recent years, the Baskervilles' aggressive territorial expansion has displaced an increasing number of barbarian peoples, so they've been sneaking around the world, luring them in with tricks or kidnapping them by force to sell them.

In other words, they would work for free for the Baskervilles and pick up the crumbs.

With no taxes and a steady flow of business, money naturally accumulates.

With the black money they earned, the masters were able to spend their youth on fire.

They can't put it in the bank because it's illegally earned, so they burn it all in cash machines.

“The champagne tower is full! Go let the kids in! Bring in the good ones.”

They sent the waiters away for a while.

Then we started chattering amongst ourselves.

“By the way,” I said, “it's so nice to have an uptight family like the Messinadnaros gone. We can have fun without all the prying eyes.”

“Actually, that's the way it should be. We're playing with our own money.”

“Good thing we framed them and sent them packing, huh?”

“Let's not let them be members in the future.”

They smoked bubbling hookahs and looked languid.

One of them suddenly looked up.

“By the way. By the way, have you guys heard about the new deputy?”

“Uh, yeah, I put in a request for an interview. He's got the Barnes surname.”

“Hmm. Well, if he's a half-breed, he must be a bastard.”

“You should feel honoured to be called by us.”

“Cackle, cackle, he's going to come running.”

They always did something called “taming the junior bureaucrats” when new deputy commissioners came in.

It's not a big deal, it's just a little bit of an extravagant party to dazzle them.

It was like putting a leash on a dog, saying, “If you're going to follow us, you're going to listen to us.” The masters would chuckle.

The masters chuckled.

“His name is Vikir. Have you ever heard of him?”

“I don't know, I've never heard of him.”

“She's 15. They say this is her first time out of the family.”

“What? Isn't she a total brat?”

“Yeah, he's a brat. He's got a huge drinking problem the first time he came to city hall. He must be a bit of a wreck.”

“C'mon, if you think he'll fit in with us.”

Then one of the masters had a brilliant idea.

“Why don't we tease him a little bit, while we're at it?”

He extended his index finger and explained his plan.

“Later, we'll have a big party and invite him over. We'll get the best liquor, we'll get all the girls, and we'll have a good, old-fashioned fuck.”

“And?”

“And then later, after the party, we'll make him pay for the drinks.”

The masters burst out laughing.

“Okay, okay, that sounds like fun.”

“Don't you think his eyes will pop out when he sees you begging?”

“You need to realise that your eldest son is spending this much money to entertain you. If you take it for granted, you'll go away.”

“I don't think a 15-year-old civil servant would have the money, and he wouldn't be able to find a place to get it because he'd be reprimanded if he reported it to his family.”

“Then you can say it was a joke and pay him back later.”

The masters had a plan for the new deputy bureaucrat, and how to roast him.

Just then.

“Gentlemen, the girls are here-!”

A waiter burst through the door with a huge grin on his face.

Soon, numerous women peeked into the club room, amazed at the luxury.

Some of them were familiar faces, and the masters waved at them.

“Hey, you're back again?”

“After all that?”

“Send him away. We're happy for you, ugh.”

“Why? I thought she was pretty.”

“Hey, come over here and sit down this time!”

One by one, the women entered the room.

...See?

At the end of the line of girls, there was a strange one.

A boy, maybe in his early teens? A very young looking boy.

He followed the women into the room from the back of the queue, and it was so natural that the waiters didn't even bother to stop him.

The seven masters scanned the women, cracking crude jokes, and finally spotted the boy.

“But what's with him? Did you bring a male waiter? Well, he looks cute.”

“Oh, don't you know him?”

“No, I don't.”

The teachers, the waiters, and the women all look puzzled.

What is this kid doing here?

One of the waiters raises his eyebrows.

“He walked in so boldly that no one thought anything of it. How dare you, you little shack, tell me where...!”

But he couldn't quite reach out to grab the boy by the hair.

Oops.

The sound of something thick and hard breaking.

The waiter suddenly realised that his wrist had been turned in a strange direction.

“Ugh!”

The boy had just broken a grown man's thick forearm with sheer brute force.

“What, what, you!”

Three or four waiters pounced at once, but it took less than a second before they were all on the floor.

The masters' faces hardened slightly.

“What's with you, kid? What are you doing here? Do you know who your brothers are?”

“I know.”

The boy's voice was devoid of any emotion.

“They're the idiots from Xiangcheng.”

No respect, no fear, no cowering, not even a hint of contempt.

The masters were stunned for a moment.

Then, with a single, hearty laugh.

“That's right. We're the idiots from Xiangcheng.”

“He must know who we are.”

“Then we only need to know who he is.”

“Kid, who are you?”

The masters were debating whether this was funny or not.

But it was.

The boy's next words wiped the smiles off their faces.

“Vikir.”

The new Deputy Magistrate.

Vikir van Baskerville is here.

The apprentices slid their feet off the table.

Then he rose to his feet and asked.

“Vice... Exarch? What brings you here....?”

“You called for me.”

At Vikir's words, the masters exchanged another blank look.

Then.

“Wahahahahaha- this is hot, Deputy! I didn't think you'd come so soon!”

The mood is not good.

Moreover, the masters had just been insulted, and their pride had been bruised.

“Shall we start taming the new recruits right away?”

“Sure. Let's buy some liquor.”

“What if we roast them, boil them, sit them down, and then ask them to pay for their drinks later at the end of the party...?”

But... their cute little plan didn't quite work out.

...Thud!

Vikir slammed his hand on the table.

And.

Tsk, tsk, tsk...

The black aura of the Baskervilles emanated from him.

The mana in Vikir's body radiated through his hand and into the table.

A ferocious resonance, a violent vibration.

Boom, boom, boom, boom...

On the table, in the glasses, the champagne suddenly began to boil.

And then.

The great tower of champagne in the centre of the room changed.

...Pow!

A single glass at the top of the champagne tower suddenly exploded.

Numerous glass shards and champagne drops sparkled and scattered below.

...Boom!

...Clink! ...clink!

...Clink! ...clink! ...clink! ...clink!

...Clink! ...clink! ...clink! ...clink! ...clink! ...clink!

The four glasses that were downstairs,

nine glasses downstairs,

16 glasses downstairs,

and 25 glasses downstairs,

36 glasses downstairs,

49 glasses downstairs,

64 glasses downstairs,

81 glasses downstairs,

100 glasses below that, all exploding and shattering one after the other.

The champagne tower had collapsed.

It didn't collapse from the bottom, it exploded backwards from the top.

Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.

Countless glass shards and champagne drops rained down on the VVIP room.

Under the rain, the masters of Sedoga could only say one thing.

“We were going to pay for the ....”

Chapter 38

Sponsored (1)

◆

The club Burning Suspension has closed its doors.

Not just closed, but burned to the ground.

Vikir burned down the entire hotel building that housed Burning Suspension.

...Roar!

The club's Burning Suspension, an enormous pyre of firewood.

The great den of devils, where the second and third generations of Sedoga gathered for the ultimate in luxury and pleasure, was burned to the ground in front of all the citizens.

Despite the fact that it was night, the city was as bright as day from the light emitted by the burning suspension.

A few slacker youths milled about in front of the club, their eyes full of regret.

“What's the matter, pigs?”

They fled with their tails between their legs as the pit bull knights lined up in front of the burning building.

Vikir hadn't just burned down the club.

The VVIPs who came in and out of the place, the seven children of the seven families who spent the most money and played the most extravagantly, were laid out in front of the burning club.

Only their heads remained.

Their severed heads bore the marks of torture.

Underneath, a long list of accusations of misdeeds they had committed in their lifetimes.

At dawn the next day, Vikir announced the executioner's position.

Without a spokesperson, he stepped out into the square.

“Before the law, caste is meaningless. Everyone is subject to the law.”

The tone was nonchalant, but the impact was enormous.

Public opinion of Vikir was either favorable or extremely favorable.

The unfavorable were few and far between.

Everyone in the city of Underdog, in groups of three or more, hailed Vikir as a great ruler.

Of course, the native families who lost their pampered offspring would not stand idly by.

The House of Montblanc, the House of Pierre, the House of Louis Vuitton, the House of Channel, the House of Ferragamo, the House of Hermès, and the House of Prada each sent a letter of protest to the Court.

But Vikir was adamant.

“Not only were they involved in all sorts of crimes, but they were directly involved in the most taboo of imperial crimes, the 'illegal slave trade'. There can be no other consequence but death.”

The imperial emperor treated the illegal slave trade as a felony of the highest quality.

This was because most of the slaves traded illegally were barbarians from outside the Empire.

Of course, this is not because the Emperor is concerned about the human rights of barbarians outside the Empire.

He is wary of the phenomenon of privateering, where another war is fought to capture them.

In order for local nobles to engage in privateering, they would have to recruit private soldiers, which could be done by treasonous conspiracy.

There was a risk that a slave hunt, conducted secretly and out of sight of the imperial court, could turn into a rebellion or coup.

Indeed, the fact that several large-scale rebellions of a few years earlier had their roots in troops organized for slave hunting was evidence of this.

So the emperor nominally said

“It is inevitable that war will create slaves, but it is not permissible to wage war to create slaves.”

From then on, illegal slave trade was treated with the same weight as treason, a first-degree felony in the Empire.

Vikir cut to the chase.

“I have obtained all the notes issued by the seven executed prisoners, all the books they kept, all the cash they spent. These events are being duly investigated by the Baskervilles and will be reported to the Imperial Court.”

To summarize: “Yes, if you refute, you are a traitor.”

After this conversation, the seven families stopped protesting.

Now was not the time to sulk with Vikir over their anger and grief at the loss of their son.

He couldn't afford to do that when his family was about to be disgraced.

In the end, the heads of the seven haughty families came to the ruler's office in person, an unprecedented occurrence, kneeling and begging for forgiveness.

They were forced to bow down to the man who killed their sons and beg for their family's survival.

This is the price they pay for mis-educating their children.

They crouched, foreheads on the marble floor, but... Vikir was relentless.

“I have already examined all the black ledgers in the Burning Suspension. Those guilty will be summoned soon and their treatment will be determined according to their crimes.”

The results, if written down, would fill countless pages.

But here are the key findings.

Paragraph 1. All property of the Montblanc, Pierre, Louis Vuitton, Channel, Ferragamo, Hermes, and Prada families shall be confiscated and placed in the treasury.

*Only those properties that have been earned through illegal activities should be confiscated, but at this point it is virtually impossible to distinguish between legal and illegal properties, so they are confiscated in full.

Section 2. The House of Montblanc, the House of Pierre, the House of Louis Vuitton, the House of Channel, the House of Ferragamo, the House of Hermes, and the House of Prada shall be destroyed for treason.

The reference point is the seven people executed on January 0.

Section 3. The members of the House of Montblanc, the House of Pierre, the House of Louis Vuitton, the House of Channel, the House of Ferragamo, the House of Hermes, and the House of Prada who are involved in this case shall be punished by double the sentence under the special provisions of the Noblesse Oblige.

Paragraphs 1 and 2 do not overlap.

It can also be summarized in three short lines.

-You.

-That's it.

-Fucked.

The blood hasn't dried on the floor of the execution chamber in a while, thanks to the arrival of a new deputy magistrate.

The foul blood of the vermin that had been feeding on the city.

“The flower beds will be richer for it.”

Vikir muttered to himself as he looked at the flowerbeds at the foot of the death chamber and the flowers that bloomed there.

The white lilies that the Chihuahua had so carefully tended had turned into red lilies.

...Whatever.

The ruling circles in the provincial capitol, who had been dictating policy decisions at every turn, dropped their heads in silence, and the provincial tribesmen, who had been farting around, now shuddered at the mere shadow of a government official.

The seven indigenous families who might have been able to play a power game with Vikir were uprooted and effectively exterminated.

Moreover, rumors that Vikir held some of the Baskervilles' military authority had gained traction in other cities.

Who in the world wouldn't hold their breath in the presence of a Baskerville military commander?

There were no longer any underdog cities that stood in Vikir's way.

On the contrary, a new group of people was emerging to give him wings.

“Indeed, the viciousness of the Seven Native Houses has crossed the line.”

“If you're going to accuse the new Deputy of cruelty at the hands of the old, you might as well accuse me first.”

“New flesh does not come from begging and pleading. Rotten flesh must be cut out. You deserved it.”

One after another, clean signers who had been penalized for their honesty, or nobles who had been dismissed for being too clean, or who had been forced to live in foster homes, declared their support for Vikir.

They had no power or wealth, but they were honored and trusted by the common people, known as “intellectuals,” “teachers,” and “mentors.”

Their support for Vikir's bold reforms grew as more and more Confucian intellectuals followed suit.

As a watershed moment, Vikir reinterpreted all past precedents and freed all wrongfully convicted prisoners and prisoners of conscience.

As a result of this process, the massive manpower required to uncover the truth of the past led to a massive hiring spree of additional government employees and contractors, which significantly reduced the unemployment rate in the underdog city.

The shortfall in the payroll budget was covered by the tax revenues generated by the crackdown on the illegal underground economy.

This has prompted the citizens of Underdog City to organize daily mass protests in front of the city hall.

<Deputy Mayor Vikir to stay in office permanently!

<We strongly urge! Deputy Vikir to stay in the city of Underdog forever!

<I love you, Vikir>.

It was a protest for the love of it.

◆

Mr. Chihuahua's secretary is single-minded.

The distrust and disdain that had greeted Vikir's arrival had been washed away.

“Are you at work, sir? Here's your coffee.”

“If you're the head of the office, mind your own business. You don't need to bring me coffee.”

“This is a personal thank you. Didn't you save me from being stabbed by a clown the other day?”

“Then a cup of coffee is too salty for a lifesaver.”

“It's not too salty, it's two primes of sugar and ten thousand of water.”

The two have gotten to know each other well enough that they now joke around like this.

Vikir is currently teaching the Chihuahua how to write.

More precisely, how to mimic different typefaces.

With that handwriting, Vikir is creating new laws and updating old ones.

Vikir was making new laws and updating old ones: developing the ruby mines with Morgue, stabilizing the price of agricultural products, rewarding those who did good work for the fief, giving slaves immunity from taxes when they did good work, developing backward areas equally, institutionally guaranteeing the benefits of following laws with penalties for breaking them, taxing merchants outside the fief, raising taxes on the wealthy, lowering taxes on the poor, dispelling superstitions, nationalizing land, and more....

Of the laws that would be enacted in the future, Vikir cherry-picked the ones that had worked well and refined them to fit the current social climate.

Naturally, the legislators were impressed with Vikir's knowledge of the law, and scratched their heads even more.

The city of Underdog was going from strength to strength.

“...Are you really 15 years old?”

Vikir chewed on the Chihuahua's question in awe.

With that, Vikir began the most important task of the day.

“Secretary.”

“Yes.”

The Chihuahua trotted over and stood beside him.

Vikir continued in his nonchalant tone.

“Is there any Tio left in the dungeon right now?”

Chapter 41

Morgue’s United Front (2)

◆

“Farewell, I'll leave you to your administrative duties!”

Vikir left the city hall of Underdog City with a chihuahua salute.

Leading a single black horse toward the outskirts of the estate, Vikir was followed by another black horse, Phil.

“Good to see you again, Master.”

He was Lord Baskerville of Staffordshire, a knight of the Knights of the Pit Bull.

He'd been in charge of Vikir's training once, and had stood by his side when they'd taken down an illegal slave auction house.

“How is Uncle Boston Terrier?”

“Yes, he's still alive, and ever since that day at the slave auction, he's been urging me to bring Master Vikir into the Pitbull Knights. He's also insisted that I do the same.”

“What?”

“To never let the Wolfhound Knights take him away from me, never!”

Staffordshire chuckled as he finished.

Vikir nodded in agreement.

They led the servants, supplies, and other entourage that followed them to the Red Awl Mountain on the outskirts of the estate.

As the name suggests, a red mountain juts out steeply from the ground.

At its base was a wide, flat basin that accentuated the mountain's pointedness.

Here, near the trunk of the great tributary to Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, the river is rich in sediment and the land is fertile, and farming is quite profitable.

Crops of sugar cane, cotton, and tobacco were growing, and these were the main products of Baskerville's estate.

And as you make your way across this vast expanse of farmland, you'll see strata lined with reddish veins ahead.

Here and there in the seismically fractured sections of the strata is a glint of red light: the ruby veins.

There, men from the Morgue family were digging for rubies.

Simple forts of wood and stone rose high above the ground.

From now on, the Baskervilles would have to be vigilant, as the Morgue had leased the area to them.

Vikir's sharp eyes scanned the farmland to the rear and the mining fields to the front.

He didn't see anything illegal going on.

Just the usual scene of slaves tending and harvesting crops, or digging with pickaxes.

The Morgue Clan hadn't violated any treaties, either, perhaps because of the Baskervilles' emissaries.

Staffordshire explained to Vikir in a low voice.

“This mission is nominally an inspection of our lands and goodwill, but....”

“I know. That it is an outpost for the extermination of the barbarians behind the mountains.”

Otherwise, there would be no reason for Baskerville's knights to be following so closely behind.

The Baskervilles had entered Morgue's territory, disguised as a routine manor inspection party.

The Morgans, of course, were aware of this.

For some time now, Morgue's armed forces have also been gathering here, disguised as miners.

Now Morgue and Baskerville will join forces to crush the barbarians.

The barbarians, unaware that a large force of swordsmen and wizards from both houses has gathered here, will rush in as usual, plundering crops and slaves, and that will be the beginning of the end.

Staffordshire said.

“I hear that there are one deputy and twelve senators from the Light Party in Morgue, and one deputy and nineteen senators from the Dark Party, and it seems that there are other wizards who are not senators.”

“The Morgue Clan has put its money where its mouth is.”

While the Morgue Clan has made this much of a commitment, the Baskervilles have, at best, brought a few dozen lay knights, with Vikir, a member of the House of Representatives.

It didn't matter, though, because the real elite of the Baskervilles were lying in ambush on the other side of the mountains, and that had also been agreed upon with Morgue.

Vikir was really here to inspect the estate and socialize.

'Well, if Hugo's right, it would be nice to be able to examine the ecology of the barbarians.

Soon, the Baskervilles began to traverse the mining district.

Everywhere they looked, they saw coal mines, and they saw palisades, stockades, and watchtowers rising high above them.

Just then.

“Hmm?”

Vikir slowed his horse as he spotted something.

His nose caught the scent of burning.

The smell of meat roasted to the limit and then charred to blackness.

As if on cue, the horses are frightened and hesitate.

Ahead of me, I see something perpendicular to the ground.

It was long and pointed, sprouting vertically from the ground and reaching for the sky.

And in the middle of it was something.

Vikir kicked his hesitant horse in the back and pushed forward.

The identity of the strange sculptures was now clear.

It was a giant skewer of iron.

Only one being could have created such a thing, an iron skewer forged from the trace elements of iron contained in the soil.

“A mage.”

It's not surprising to see something like this in the grounds of the Morgue family, who are known for their mage sect.

However, the things pierced by the skewers and nailed to the ground are quite alien.

Skulls. And charred flesh.

The bodies impaled on the skewers had all been burned to death.

The bodies were mixed and matched, demonic and human alike, and some of them had been burned to the bone, leaving nothing but empty skewers.

Whirling.

With each gust of wind, the skewered corpses crumble into black powder.

...Gross!

A lump of charcoal, unknown to the barbarians or the demons, falls from the skewer and scatters ash on the ground.

“You've been warned.”

Staffordshire said, looking up at all the things that had been impaled on the skewer and burned to death.

This must be a warning to the demons and barbarians of Morgoth.

And Vikir already knew of one person who did this.

'...You must have grown up, then.

Vikir was reminiscing in his mind.

“Who's there!”

“Stand down!”

“Identify yourself!”

Ankaljin shouts came from the watchtower up ahead.

Vikir looks up and sees three women descending from the top of the watchtower.

Elderly women, treading on thin air as if it were a staircase.

Fiery red hair, dresses out of place in a murderous fortress.

Vikir already knew their identities from his knowledge before the regression.

“Highsis, Middlesis, and Lowsis, triplets of Morgoth.”

Sixteen wives of the year.

Each a master of water, grass, and earth magic, and the synergy of the three of them together?

Born on the same day and at the same hour, they were called the Three Flowers of Morgoth.

However, the world called them something different.

Samhwa

It means “three plagues.”

Each one of them was said to have an insane personality, and together, they were said to be unstoppable.

They were notorious in Baskerville for their pride and arrogance.

It's no wonder they're the ones who ruin the friendly competition every year.

To top it all off, they have strong magical skills that make up for their nasty personalities.

And here they were, the three sisters of Morgoth, guarding the gateway fortress to Morgoth territory.

Vikir stepped forward and spoke.

“We are emissaries of House Baskerville.”

Highsis, at the head of the line, smirks.

“So?”

“So, we're here to inspect the estate and exchange goodwill. Open the gates of the fortress.”

“Not now. I've sent a report to those in charge, so wait.”

The horse said wait, not wait and see.

Vikir asked.

“How long do we have to wait?”

“I don't know, maybe tomorrow? Ho-ho-ho-”

It was more than a plea, it was an argument.

Vikir's eyes narrowed.

“In what name are you preventing Baskerville from entering Baskerville's land? You are arrogant for a tenant.”

“What? You call me a tenant? Don't you know the Tenant Protection Act? That's a law of your own making? Don't you even know your own family's laws?”

“If that's the law, I've already changed it. I've already amended it to allow me to evict true tenants.”

“....”

Vikir urged his horse forward a little more while Highsis was speechless.

“I am the deputy magistrate of the city of Underdog. I am here by appointment, and this is the last time I will speak to you.”

“....”

“Open the door.”

Hearing Vikir's words, the three Morgue sisters exchanged glances for a moment.

Then the eldest, Highsis, smirked.

“I've heard that there's a younger one in the city of Underdog.”

“Oh, but what are we going to do about it?”

“If it's a young rascal, we've had enough of them!”

The three sisters drew mana into their palms.

And then.

...Quack, quack, quack!

Water, grass, and earth magic unfolded, and Baskerville crashed down in front of them.

Vikir frowned slightly and reared his horse back.

The three sisters' laughter rang out from beyond the billowing mushroom cloud.

“Giggle, giggle-we'll wait for you, you ignorant swordsmen!”

“Not even Baskerville dares to enter Morgue's land!”

“Shall these sisters see what a supernova a Baskerville is?”

Then Staffordshire came to Vikir's side and said.

“I don't think we should tell them.”

Vikir was thinking the same thing.

Just then.

“How dare you bitches who don't even know the subject speak in front of anyone!”

“You're a fool!”

“You're a fool!”

Three shouts erupted from the Baskervilles' emissary.

Soon, three familiar faces emerged from the dirt.

Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro.

The Baskervilles' triplets, who had been at the back of the delegation, stepped forward.

They stood side by side, now friendly again, and glared at the three Morgue sisters as they descended.

They snorted.

“Don't you know the subject?”

“So you guys are higher up than us?”

“Don't you dare.”

But the three brothers denied their words.

“Not us.”

“Not us.”

“Not us.”

“Then who?”

“Who?”

“Who?”

The three siblings turned their heads in unison at the question.

“This is our Baskerville street sign!”

The direction the three brothers stare in awe and fear.

That's where Vikir was standing.

Chapter 42

Morgue’s United Front (3)

◆

Vikir thought.

'?'

What kind of situation is this?

For the first time since his return, something unexpected had happened.

The three infamous young Baskervilles, who would come to be known as Hugo's Trident, had begun pretending to be friendly with Vikir.

The trio had even crossed the line of fire several times before Vikir regressed, and crucially, it was their fault that he was captured and executed at the last minute.

...But what about now?

The High, Middle, and Low Brothers stood in a circle around Vikir.

Whereas before they had surrounded him to harass him, now they were surrounding him to protect him.

“He's the poster boy for our line, you can't let him fight just anyone. He has to pull his weight.”

“Protect.”

“Protect.”

Lowbro even turned his head and winked at Vikir.

Vikir was even more bewildered.

“I just got my finger chopped off, and this is what he's going to do?”

But this wasn't the first time Vikir had encountered this behavior from the triplets.

“Certainly, they've been noticeably more civilized since the last time they hunted a troll in front of everyone.”

Maybe even before that. Maybe since he'd killed a Cerberus in his first practical assessment at the age of eight?

I knew something was off when I walked up to Vikir while he was scarfing down a haggis and pretended to be friendly.

Vikir had spent his entire life avoiding the attention of his siblings.

They were too weak and young to be worthy of his attention.

But this indifference must have caused a mutation in the triplets' minds.

After all, it was in the Baskervilles' nature to follow the philosophy of the strongest.

What's more, they seemed to be under a strange illusion.

“Leave this place to us, Vikir. We'll repay you for recommending us to the Academy.”

“Leave it to us, Vikir. We'll repay you.”

“Leave it to us, Vikir. We'll make it up to you.”

The triplets speak with determination.

Vikir suddenly remembered his conversation with Hugo not long ago.

He had mentioned the triplets without thinking when asked who he was close to, and it had apparently impressed them.

Vikir decided to keep his mouth shut.

“....”

It's always cute to see a kid who thinks he's doing something great.

(Plus, these triplets have a fucked-up personality, so that's one cute thing about them.)

Vikir thought for a moment.

“They could be useful.”

These triplets will surely grow up to be very useful killing machines.

They might not have the brains to make their own decisions, but they certainly knew how to do what they were told.

They've been used for all sorts of sneaky and dirty jobs, so they've proven to be both skilled and loyal.

Hounds, literally. Fiercely obedient to their master's command.

And that was something Vikir knew all too well, having been bitten by their teeth.

Finally, Vikir gritted his teeth in defeat.

“I'll give you a chance, brothers.”

The triplets' faces lit up.

They stood in front of Vikir, looking even more pleased than when they'd received Hugo's praise at the end-of-the-month review.

“Well, if they're going to go to all that trouble, why shouldn't I?”

Vikir decided to stay in the background for now.

Next.

The three sisters of Morgue and the three brothers of Baskerville were about to face off.

The three sisters of Morgue and the three brothers of Baskerville had already met at several annual events, and they had a reputation for getting along very badly.

The three sisters struck first.

“What a bunch of idiots, all you know how to do is stick together in threes.”

Lowsis was the first to bring her hands to the ground.

With her powerful Water Realm magic, she formed countless water droplets and began to shoot them out.

Puff-puff-puff!

The force of the water droplets flying at high speed was powerful.

It was said that falling water could take a long time to pierce through rocks, but the mana-laden droplets she was sending out could pierce through rocks in an instant.

The ground is devastated.

The droplets of water that Lowsis unleashed pierced countless holes in the ground, drenching the earth with moisture.

Middlesis followed suit.

She specializes in powerful earth magic, and with a sweep of her hands, she gathers the loose soil together.

Crunch, crunch, crunch.

At Middlesis's command, the waterlogged and deformable soil formed an earth wall that surrounded the three sisters.

What's more, sharp rocks protruded from its surface like blades, allowing for both defense and offense.

Finally, the eldest sister, Highsis, stepped forward.

Specializing in powerful grass magic, she flicked her hands together and pulled the grass seeds from beneath the ground.

Thick plant stalks sprouted and vines grew, feeding on the waters of Lowsis and the soil of Middlesis.

Land, water, and plant life worked in synergy to make Morgue's fortifications stronger and stronger, while at the same time putting pressure on their enemies.

Indeed, these are the qualities that have earned it the name “The Three Flowers of Morgue.”

But Baskerville's three brothers were no slouches either.

“Heh, heh, heh, heh, what are we going to do with all that grass and no meat?”

“What are you going to do?”

“What are we going to do?”

Hive was the first to jump up.

A pale aura of gaseous form drew out a single sharp tooth and slammed it into the dirt wall in front of him.

Then.

...Pow! Pow!

The earthen wall cracked open, revealing the inside.

It was only one circle of magic, so its defense was obviously limited.

The blades of Middle Bro and Low Bro followed suit, slashing down.

The high-speed rotating auras vaporized the flying water droplets and shredded the plant stalks.

Clang! Clang! Pow!

Sword and magic clashed ferociously.

The magic was drawing in more mana, recreating the power of the elements more strongly, and the sword was exploding with firewood from the mana and life force in his body.

Which is stronger, magic or sword?

It was an ever-present debate between the neighboring realms of Morgue and Baskerville.

And at the forefront of that debate today stood these three sisters and three brothers.

Each of the six was fighting to prove their family's banner.

“....”

Watching on, Vikir was bored to tears.

After all, what tension could there be in a battle between three first-class mages who could only use first-circle magic and three lowly Sword Expert juniors who had just mastered the first form of Baskerville?

What's more, Vikir is a cripple from across the river, with no real attachment or brotherhood to the Baskervilles.

“I wish they'd all just die.”

It's an extremely cynical attitude.

But the other knights of Baskerville, with the exception of Vikir, had a different attitude.

They all seemed to be quite excited, even if they didn't say so.

Staffordshire turned to Vikir, who had a sullen expression on his face.

“Aren't you having fun?”

“What?”

“Isn't it a competition of talent and potential among young dreamers who will one day carry the family name in tow?”

“If you put it that way, I'm a dreamer.”

“Master, you're already... and you're not fit to play in that age group.”

“It's just a waste of time. I must pass quickly, I have a meeting with the head of the fort to discuss....”

But Vikir couldn't finish his sentence.

Quack, quack, quack!

A powerful explosion ripped through the area.

“Kaaaah!”

“Ugh!”

The three sisters of the Morgue family and the three brothers of the Baskerville family were all stunned.

Flames roared, consuming everything around them.

Skewers of steel rose from the ground, turning the area into a field of thorns.

Puff, puff, puff!

The skewered wall of earth collapses in an instant.

The searing heat burned away the water and vegetation before Baskerville pushed back the triplets' blades and sent them flying.

A line of fire and iron, red and black, separates the Morgans from the Baskervilles in an instant.

The magic was so powerful that even the other Baskervilles, who had been watching the children's fight with amusement, half-sheathed their swords in surprise.

Crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle!

In the blink of an eye, the surrounding cotton fields turned into an inferno.

The Baskerville triplets barely made it beyond the wall of fire.

But their hair was already charred to a crisp.

“Hey, what the hell, you almost burned me!”

“What the hell!”

“What!”

The triplets jerked their heads up to protest Morgue's overreach.

But Morgue's three sisters on the other side of the room were treated even worse.

Not only are they scorched by the flames, but they've been skewered, scratched and torn all over.

Crawling on the floor, Highsis, Middlesis, and Lowsis had dark horror in their eyes.

“Hmph, hmph... I almost died just now....”

“If you had dodged a little later, you would have died, hmph-”

“Sisters- I'm scared-”

Seeing them stutter, the Baskerville triplets quickly shut their mouths to protest.

Morgue was unrelenting, even against his own family.

All heads turned toward the direction the fire magic had come from.

Then, from beyond the barrier of fire, came a calm voice.

“...What is this?”

A cold voice, but somehow familiar.

And with it, an enforcer of iron skewers and hot flames.

The distant nickname that would later come to be known as Jian Tian Muhu.

Morgue's mistress, who would come to be known as the Queen of Fire and Skewers, or the Queen of Red and Black.

'...But she is still young.

Vikir looked up.

An eight-year-old girl in a blur of memories.

And now, a fully grown fifteen-year-old girl.

Camus Morgue.

She looked down at him, reunited after seven years.

Chapter 44

The Fiancée (2)

◆

The fortifications of Morgue came into view.

Huge earthen walls stood in a circle, dotted with wooden and iron watchtowers.

Camus and Vikir were walking around the fortress, talking about this and that.

“The barbarians are raiding the ruby mines and plundering the native slaves and crops. They're taking the slaves not to save their own people, but to sell them as slaves elsewhere.”

“Exactly. There are many barbarian tribes, and they do not consider each other kin, so they would not hesitate to sell criminals of their own tribe or captives of other tribes into slavery.”

“I see, and I'm glad I don't have to answer the stupid question of why barbarians fight amongst themselves.”

Camus reached out and gestured to the mud wall in front of them.

“These walls were built by Earth and Iron mages for a month.”

The size of the wall was enormous.

If ordinary people had built it, it would have taken a year, not a month.

It would have taken hundreds of men to build it.

Vikir moved closer to the earthen wall.

Then he saw something strange.

There was a grid of steel beams embedded in the hardened earth wall, but they were only visible to Vikir because of the holes in the wall.

The earthen wall was pockmarked with holes that looked like the surface of a biscuit.

Hundreds of them.

Vikir studied the size of the holes.

They looked to be about three centimeters in diameter.

“...The marks of the Ballak.”

Vikir's sharp eyes were identifying the enemy, the famous barbarian tribe beyond the Black Mountains.

Camus nodded.

“The Ballak are the most troublesome. Their arrows carry a powerful aura, and many a man has been killed by them while standing guard at night. They can punch through an earthen wall two or three meters thick, so do you have what it takes to defeat them?”

“Even shield magic won't stop it. They fly so fast.”

“Yes. That's why my uncle almost got himself in trouble once, not long ago.”

The camel smirked.

Not long ago, he said, he'd been sniped at while searching for Mad King Adolf himself.

“I think the arrow pierced his shield, and it freaked him out. He was lucky to escape with his life, but his pride must have been bruised.”

“Come to think of it, my lord,” said Vikir, “you had a similar experience, and I heard that you had a scar on the bridge of your nose.”

Vikir remembered the scar on the bridge of Hugo's nose.

Wounding Swordmaster Hugo and Class 6 Master Adolf, Ballak's archery was indeed something to be wary of.

“It seems the barbarians have some talent. Who is it?”

“I think it's a woman, but she's too far away to make out her identity, and they wear black paint on their faces, so it's hard to memorize.”

Camus threw up his hands in annoyance.

“Anyway. The Ballak are the most threatening, even though they only number about three hundred, and the next most threatening, the Rokoko, are ten times less numerous.”

A warlike tribe, the Ballak.

They are a nomadic, plundering, warlike barbarian people who belong neither here nor there.

They have been on the move for unknown reasons in the last seven years, and have come into increasing conflict with Baskerville.

The Morgue, who have recently leased some of Baskerville's territory to develop ruby mines, are equally annoyed with Ballak.

Camus looked out over the water on the distant horizon and spoke.

“The Morgue have their fingers crossed, but... barbarian raids are so stealthy that it's hard to detect them. Besides, we have a gap in our vigilance about once a month.”

“Gaps?”

Vikir asked, and Camus arched an eyebrow.

“The Morgue are a matriarchal society, so women are overwhelmingly in charge. Even the wizards who stand guard are women.”

“But what does that have to do with the gap?”

“Well, about once a month, .... Because there's magic.”

“But you're mages, aren't you?”

Vikir asked, and the camo opened his mouth for a moment, then chuckled.

“You've got a bit of a stupid side to you, don't you?”

“...?”

“Okay. I like it. Bonus points for being a man's man.”

It took Vikir a few slaps on the shoulder before he understood what the camo meant.

Just then.

“Booyo!”

In the distance, someone was looking for the camo.

A female wizard rushed to the cage and bowed before him.

“The hermitage's search party has captured a barbarian scout alive!”

A prisoner had been taken.

◆

The one being dragged away in ropes was a man with brown skin and black hair.

From the tattoos on his body, Vikir could guess his tribe.

“You're from the shaman tribe, Rokoko.”

I don't know how he ended up here, but his fate is already sealed.

Camus Morgue.

She faced her captive with a fearsome aura.

“Did you get any information?”

The mages beside her cringed.

“We're not talking, for now.”

“What about mind magic?”

“It doesn't work. The powerful spell makes it impossible to read their memories.”

The camouflage turned away.

He walked over and stood in front of his captive.

“You raided Morgue's fortress once before and took some slaves.”

“....”

“Among those slaves was a Morgue woman. She is my half-sister. Her name is Rosie.”

Camus glared at Rokoko's captive with searing eyes.

“What did you do with her?”

The captive's tightly closed mouth slowly opened.

“?????.”

At the word, the camo raised an eyebrow.

“Interpretation. Where is the barbarian returnee?”

But no one answered him.

They just glanced at each other uneasily.

One wizard spoke up apologetically.

“They were all killed or taken away when the barbarians attacked, Vice-Captain.”

“Then there is no one to translate his words?”

“For the moment, no.”

It was an awkward moment.

Everyone had a puzzled look on their faces.

“I speak a little Rokoko.”

Vikir stepped forward.

Camus stared at him, wide-eyed.

“You can do that, too? What are you not good at?”

“Not very well. I just know the basic vocabulary.”

Vikir stood in front of Camus.

Camus asked.

“Ask him where my half-brother is. The girl you kidnapped in the last raid. She has red hair, red eyes, and unusually white skin. She's about 12 years old.”

Vikir nodded, then turned to Rokoko's captive in front of him.

“?? ???? ?? ??????”

A short reply came back.

“???”

Vikir's expression hardened for a moment.

Then he turned to the camel and shook his head.

“He's dead.”

At that, the faces of all the Morgue turned grim.

He had expected death when he was kidnapped, but hearing it was a different story.

Then, Camus stepped forward.

She growled in a low voice at her captive.

“When this war is over, your language will be the language of hell.”

Those were the last words the prisoner heard.

Camus said.

“The delegate from the Light Party is being treated now. The Delegate of the Dark Party is now inspecting the opposite estate, and I, Camus Morgue, a member of the Council and Deputy Fortressmaster, will make the judgment here.”

That was the end of the summary trial.

And now.

With a flick of his hand, Camus drew a circle of magic in the air.

Then.

...Poof!

A large iron skewer sprouted from the ground.

The iron elements hidden among the earth elements came together and exploded, and the skewer that formed impaled Rokoko's prisoner in one fell swoop.

From groin to crown.

The prisoner struggled, unable to even scream.

He was nailed high up in the air, impaled on a metal skewer.

Flames began to crackle beneath him.

Crackle!

The skewer burns. In the blink of an eye, the camouflage had burned Rokoko's captive to death.

All the slaves who saw it looked at it in fear.

It was the same with the people of Morgue.

Purr, purr, purr, purr, purr!

The sound of someone being skewered and burned to a crisp.

Black powder scattered in the wind along with the smell of burning meat.

In front of that terrifying fire, the camel smiled nonchalantly.

“Let's go.”

She grabbed Vikir from beside her and they were out of there in no time.

Everyone around them could only stare after them with a faint sense of dread.

◆

Meanwhile.

Back behind the earthen wall, Vikir was a little surprised.

Not that he was surprised to see a man skewered alive and burning.

Vikir had spent decades rolling on the battlefields before his return, and had seen much worse.

It was the expression on the camo's face that startled Vikir.

“...Blah, blah, blah!”

The camel had gone to a place where no one was around, and now it was crying.

His face contorted, his eyes red, tears streaming down his chubby cheeks.

Vikir's mouth was half open in disbelief.

Oh, my God, to see the weather goddess crying.

Of course, she had seen it when she was eight years old, but it felt very different now that she was 15.

'But I'm still 15,' I thought.

After staring at the crying camel for a while, Vikir finally spoke up.

“...Why are you crying?”

“Why would I cry!”

The camel screeched and looked around for anyone to hear.

Vikir closed his mouth for a moment, then opened it again.

“You must have been very close to your brother.”

“I was. She was very protective of me, an innocent, good child, not fit for Morgue.”

After speaking, Camus squatted down against the earthen wall.

They were about the same height, but somehow she seemed much smaller now.

Vikir thought to himself.

“Don't be so sad, he must have gone in peace.”

When Vikir offered his awkward words of comfort, the camel snapped back.

“Who do you think you are?”

The question was a mixture of anger and sadness.

Vikir noticed.

The camel understood him.

“I'm a genius. I can't talk, so I can't listen.”

“....”

“Tell me straight. Tell me if I heard right.”

Vikir could only nod with a heavy expression at Camus' words.

Rokoko's captive's last words hadn't been “dead.”

“Eaten.”

The Rokoko are a tribe of shamans and cannibals.

It is their custom to eat their captives.

Hearing Vikir's confirmation, Camus began to tear up again.

“...I'm sorry. I'm sorry I couldn't protect you. I'm sorry for you.”

Camus cried and cried.

Vikir stood still beside her and remained silent.

Surprised that Camus Morgue, the queen of red and black, of fire and skewers, would hide such a thing behind her mask.

...And after some time had passed.

Camus rose from her seat.

She dabbed at her cheeks with her sleeve, wiping away the dried tears.

She returned to her original cold expression.

She looked at Vikir, who stood off to the side.

“That wasn't so bad.”

“...?”

“I would have killed him if he'd shown any flimsy sympathy.”

There was no way a lowly threat from a fifteen-year-old girl was going to have any effect on a hundred-year-old man who'd seen it all, but Vikir gave a grim nod anyway.

...Whatever.

Sometimes it's comforting to just be there.

Not knowing what to do with a 15-year-old girl who was crying, staying still had paid off this time.

Next, Camus patted Vikir on the chest.

“No time to mourn, boy. We need to recover and get revenge as soon as possible.”

“....”

“Come with me. There's something we need to do together.”

The camo sounded quite determined.

Chapter 45

The Fiancée (3)

◆

Seven years ago.

There was an eight year old girl in the Morgue family who was broken.

Camus Morgue.

The youngest member of House Morgue, a renowned mage family.

Her extraordinary talents were evident from the earliest days.

The young children of Morgue gathered for a lesson in magic.

“Now, the road to Magehood is hard. As you look into the abyss, the abyss looks into you. You must always be careful and cautious because if you look into the depths, you might be eaten by a giant demon.”

When the children heard the tutor's words, each of them felt a vague sense of fear and terror.

Only one. Camouflage snorted.

“Nonsense.”

The tutor furrows her brow.

“Mr. Camouflage, why do you say it's nonsense?”

“You said that when I look into the abyss, the abyss looks into me. That's bullshit.”

Camouflage gives you a stern look.

“The Abyss of Mado is so wide and deep that no human mind can comprehend it.”

“....”

“Because I look into the abyss, the abyss looks into me? Nonsense. Just because an ant can see me doesn't mean I can see the ant, and the abyss doesn't know I'm looking into it, and it doesn't care. It doesn't care, so being afraid of the abyss looking into you is overly self-conscious.”

“....”

“Well, maybe once you get to a certain level, but don't instill fear in kids who can't even handle their mana yet.”

At that, the tutor fell silent.

The tutor's jaw dropped.

In all the years he'd been able to reach Class 5 and roll five mana circles, he'd never once fallen into the abyss of Mado.

Unless, of course, you're knocking on the door of Class 7, the ultimate in Mado.

When the tedious lesson was over, the camel shook himself out of his seat and stood up.

“What's my uncle up to?”

The only person in the family who understood his talent and whom he felt comfortable confiding in.

Camus favored her younger brother, Adolf Morgue, even more than her mother, Raspane Morgue, the head of the household.

Then.

Camus overheard her mother, Raspane, and her uncle, Adolf, talking in the parlor.

“You say that a ruby vein runs underground on the Baskerville family estate?”

“Yes, sister. It looks like a collision is inevitable.”

“That's a big deal, Hugo, and I don't want to have to bow down to that bastard... Plus, that's where the barbarians are raging, so does that make it a three-way war?”

“Well, for one thing, the lode runs into the Baskervilles' territory, so we're at a legal disadvantage. Also, your barbarians are a group that the Baskervilles have been struggling with for years, so a local conflict would be very damaging to the family in more ways than one....”

Raspane and Adolf looked grave.

Then Camus stepped forward.

“I'll take a look.”

Raspane and Adolf gasped in surprise.

“Does he know what's wrong with this...!”

“Wait. Sister. Let's hear what the kid has to say. He's a genius, you know, and maybe he can point out something the grown-ups don't see.”

This is why the camel likes his uncle Adolf.

Raspane and Adolf nodded in disbelief at what the camel was saying.

“Hmmm. Let's give it a try, shall we?”

“After that, let's solidify our cooperation and push for joint development? Hmm. Not a bad idea.”

It's hard to believe they came from the mind of an 8-year-old.

And then.

“And wouldn't it be great if we also discussed the issue of nepotism? I like the idea of in-laws going into business together, rather than just bowing out.”

A.k.a. the 'prenup strategy'. Camus had another good suggestion.

Raspane's eyes lit up and he asked.

“You mean a pact with the Baskervilles? Who do you think we should send?”

“Well, what about the triplets, Highsis, Middlesis, and Lowsis, who are useless to anyone?”

Camus answered nonchalantly, not giving it much thought.

Morgue immediately begins to negotiate.

Adolf took Camus with him to Baskerville, and Camus used his status as a child to talk to Hugo.

He used his status as a child to speak to Hugo, comparing the underground veins to his hands and forearms.

But. For the first time in his life, Camo had to suffer a bitter defeat.

'That one'.

From the opposing camp came an eight-year-old kid.

I don't know the logic behind it, but he was definitely outgunned.

The camel was so angry that he started crying and almost lost his mind.

I've never experienced anything like this in my life.

No one else, not even his 8-year-old peers, not even teenagers, had ever done this to him.

Not even adults.

Everything in the world had always gone the way he wanted it to, and he had never been caught off guard.

But that day was different.

Everything had gone against Camus's will.

And the reason for this was the dark-haired boy she had met that day, 'the one'.

“If it weren't for you...!”

So the camel was furious. He wanted to show the first person he'd ever met his true colors.

So he challenged him to a fight in the training grounds, where swords and magic clashed.

He fought with all his might.

But the creature was cowardly and dodged the blows.

...Crackle! ...Crackle, crackle, crackle!

He flicked his fingers at his forehead, as if he was just playing around.

And it really hurt, too, as I kept getting hit.

His face zoomed in for a close-up.

I felt blinded by anger. You feel like it's just you and him in the world.

All I could think about was punching him in the face.

...Right then.

Boom!

There was an accident in the next room.

There was a huge explosion and my clothes were burned to a crisp.

I hastily tried to hide behind the dust and smoke, but it only saved me a few seconds of nakedness.

It was only then that she became worried.

There are tons of people here besides me and 'him'.

What an embarrassment!

Morgue's supernova, her genius, her next big thing, the person she respected and trusted, all in one moment, naked in front of everyone.

Even eight-year-olds have their virginity. He has his pride.

Camus fought desperately to keep the tears from falling.

He was about to be stripped naked in front of all the kids his age who had always looked down on him.

Especially when the sneaky sisters Highsis, Middlesis, and Lowsis were in the next room!

I didn't want to cry naked in front of them. They would make fun of me for the rest of my life.

'...But what can I do?

But there was no way out of this situation.

Soon the dust would settle and she would be the laughing stock of the world.

“I should die.”

Camus thought to himself.

...Just then.

Flutter!

His vision went black.

Something heavy but warm and cozy covered the camel's naked body.

She looked up and saw “him” right in front of her.

He had removed his own clothes and covered her, leaving her naked.

“Isn't he ashamed?”

The camel thought so, but 'he' didn't seem to think so.

He flaunted his nakedness for all to see. Without a trace of shame.

The camel felt his heart pound in his chest as he stared at his naked body.

The first time he'd ever seen his number, the first time he'd ever suffered a defeat, the first time he'd ever seen a confident demeanor, the first time he'd ever seen the naked body of someone his own age.

So many firsts were jumbled together in Camus's mind.

For the first time in her life, her good hair stood on end, and so did the time that flowed around her.

For what seemed like an eternity, she stared at him.

Secretly thinking to herself that it was a good thing that she had brought out the 'marriage pact strategy' before she left the clan.

And then, one after another.

He was pitted against his uncle.

The camel had always liked and followed his uncle, but for that moment, he thought he was being unfair.

“He's a grown man, and he's persecuting a child.”

She had always been grateful to her uncle for treating her like an adult, but not as much as she was at this moment.

What?

'The kid' continued to challenge his uncle.

An indomitable spirit that refused to back down in the face of such a stark disparity in skill.

Camus felt mixed feelings.

He knew of his uncle's strength and greatness, but he couldn't stop his gaze from drifting to....

Inwardly, he was surprised that he was hoping for such a ridiculous situation, that 'that guy' would defeat his uncle.

And then.

The fantasy became a reality.

In a situation that even the strongest camo thought was hopeless, 'the one' surprisingly overcame his uncle.

Chirp chirp chirp...

A broken water jar, a stream of water, and a dazed uncle.

The camo cheered at this shocking outcome.

It even jumped up and down in place.

Her uncle looked shocked and expressed his disappointment, but it was none of her business.

She had always despised the frivolous laughing and jumping of 8-year-olds her age, but before she knew it, she was laughing and jumping like a normal 8-year-old.

After the negotiation went well.

Arriving home, the camel went to bed.

The stuffed animal she always hugged when she went to sleep, she decided to put it aside.

“I'm not a child anymore.”

Instead, her usual cuddle had changed.

Baskerville's black blood.

The cloak that “he” had wrapped her in became her first love.

Camus slept in it every night, always burying his face in it as he fell asleep.

The smell of musty sweat was somehow thought to be a good thing, and I slept better with my nose buried in it.

Sometimes my heart would suddenly thump in my chest, other times I would feel a tingling sensation all over my body, and other times I would nibble my collar with my teeth on a sudden impulse.

When the nanny would suggest doing the laundry, Camus would raise his hand and firmly stop her.

“These things aren't worth washing.”

After that, she never washed it.

And so the seasons changed, and a few birthday cakes came and went, and the camel always thought the same thing.

“Where would she be now, what would she be doing, and how tall would she be?”

And just like that, the little girl became a lady.

She went to the ruby mines all the time because she loved rubies, but she never saw 'him'.

She had only heard rumors on the wind that he had gone on a long training run.

And time passed.

One day, Camus heard a rumor.

There was a fairly large city on the edge of the Baskerville estate, adjacent to the Morgue estate.

It was rumored that a young deputy had been appointed there.

Apparently, he caused several major accidents upon his arrival.

Of course, by accidents, I don't really mean accidents, I mean mega-achievements.

Upon hearing that he had burned 10 billion on a single stick, the camel slapped his knee.

“You've grown up.”

She made her way over to Gajusil.

“What, you want me to send you on a joint operation with the Baskervilles?”

“Yes, mom. Right now.”

Camouflage pawed at her patriarch, Raspane, as they made their way to the Baskervilles' estate.

Before doing so, he made sure to identify the new deputy magistrate of Underdog City as his partner in the joint operation.

And a day before the Baskervilles were due to arrive.

Camo had made all the arrangements.

The fort's watchtower, with its many beautiful cotton blossoms, was chosen as the meeting place.

A little embarrassed, he kept Morgue's prying eyes as far back as possible.

There, among the white flowers and their delicate scent, the seven-year wait would end.

The camel went to bed with a puffed-up chest.

...And that day.

The camel was furious.

He had picked an atmospheric spot, but it was already in shambles.

His sisters, who had been so disrespectful when he was younger, and who now dared not even breathe in his presence when he was older, had ruined it.

“What the ... do you think you're doing?”

Camus asked with infernal fury.

The aftermath of Romantic's destruction was horrifying.

Morgue's three sisters sobbed, unable to speak English.

“Kaa, Camus, my sisters are...”

“Woohoo, we just wanted to keep the intruders out....”

“Well, they started the fight!”

But Camus's mood was already low.

The reunion he'd been waiting seven years for had been ruined.

“Camo, are you talking to me, sisters?”

“Hic! No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!”

“Get out of the way. If you don't want to be like that.”

The camel didn't really intend to kill the three sisters, but he did intend to spank them really badly.

But he didn't have to, because they scurried away on their own.

Then.

Camus reined in his horse and stood in front of 'him'.

“Welcome, partner.”

Seeing him again after seven years, he didn't look much different than when they first met.

He wasn't much taller than her, as if he was still growing, but his face had changed slightly.

His jawline was more defined, and his nose was more prominent.

It was better than the version that had been glorified and beautified in Camus's imagination.

'You've grown a lot. Mmm. You've grown.

The camel nodded. His face flushed red of its own accord.

Why did the naked body under the blood wind of the eight-year-old suddenly appear in his mind?

“...Mo, has your body changed a lot?”

It was a camouflage that didn't use any magic, but it was unnecessarily hot.

Chapter 47

The Husband Hunt (2)

◆

Ping!

The sound of a hole in the air.

An arrow flew through the air with a crash and stuck in the dirt wall.

Boom!

The hard baked earth wall exploded with a loud bang, leaving a huge hole.

A soldier who was taking cover behind it was instantly killed by the arrow.

“????? ??????”

“????? ?? ??????? ????”

“???? ????”

Booming voices echo from the edge of the jungle.

Ballak. A tribe of brown-skinned savages.

They had swords and bows in their hands and were attacking Morgue's fortress.

Ping-.

An arrow flies, and a soldier is sent tumbling down the ramparts.

In the blink of an eye, Ballak's barbarian warriors overturned all the skirmishers and scrambled up the ramparts.

Boom, boom, boom!

They set fire to the cotton fields below the walls and dragged the barbarian slaves with them.

Thump, thump, thump!

The barking of dogs everywhere.

The Barbarians of Ballak rode their great wolves in groups of two or three, and in their hands they carried nooses of strong rope.

These were thrown into the air, and a slave, always a woman, a man, and a child, was taken alive.

It was like a hunt.

The surprise was so swift that the fortress was in an uproar.

Flames were everywhere, soldiers were dying, and many slaves were being dragged alive.

And in the midst of it all, Vikir descended.

Some of the barbarian women's eyes lit up when they saw him.

“???? ????”

“?? ?? ???”

“???? ????? ???? ???????”

They tossed the nooses into the air, swung them up, and hurled them at Vikir's throat in unison.

And with that.

Tut-tut-tut.

The three-strand rope noose snaps around Vikir's neck.

The barbarian warriors kicked at the mounted wolf's loins, driving it like a horse.

But.

...Crack!

The wolf was forced to stop running.

Vikir was standing there, unmoving.

Thud.

The rope noose tightened around his neck, but Vikir didn't budge.

Next, Vikir twisted the noose with his hands and gave it a firm squeeze.

Quack, quack, quack!

The wolf and the three barbarian female warriors sprawled across the floor.

The faces of the barbarian men around them twisted.

They shouted something and pointed their bows at Vikir.

Beep, beep, beep.

Arrows of incredible speed. In unison, they lunged for Vikir.

But Vikir's hand was much faster.

...Whoosh!

Vikir quickly drew his longsword and imbued it with an aura.

The liquid aura of the Gradient symbolized a single point on the tip of the blade.

Papapapap!

Vikir drew a figure of eight with the tip of his blade, slicing all the flying arrows in half.

The barbarians shrank back in horror at the sight of Vikir's aura.

They couldn't help but notice. This manipulative power could only be seen by those who touched some singularity.

Vikir squinted, taking in the group of Ballak before him.

Brown skin. Hair of varying shades of silver, gray, and black.

Faces painted black, collars with thorns around their necks, riding on the backs of large wolves and using bows as their primary weapons.

“Just like I remembered before the regression.”

I've faced Ballak's warriors many times before.

They are not only belligerent, but each warrior is highly skilled.

It is fortunate that this is a plain with a fortress, for if we turned against them in the middle of a dark jungle, we would have had a hard time.

'Before we set out, Hugo assured me that we were not to engage until we were joined by the main body.'

This was Baskerville territory, but it was leased to Morgue, so Vikir had no reason to risk his life in dispute with them.

“....”

“....”

Vikir pressed the barbarian warriors with just the right amount of momentum, and they didn't hesitate to charge at him.

They had seen the ghostly swordsmanship Vikir had displayed just moments before.

Then.

...Boom!

There was a loud explosion, followed by searing flames.

An earthen wall collapsed, and a girl stepped out from behind it.

The one who would one day be called an enemy and the Queen of Black.

Camus Morgue, she glared at the barbarian warriors of Ballak with bloodshot eyes.

“Die!”

Camus crossed her hands.

Quadra-casting, four offensive spells manifested and began to shake the battlefield upside down.

Powerful blasts of fire and wind, steel and rock, drove firestorms and rock showers.

Ballak's barbarian warriors were biting the wolves back, signaling loudly among themselves.

Perhaps it was time to retreat.

Camus kept the invaders at bay, but glanced back at Vikir.

Her gaze was drawn to the few drops of black liquid on the tip of Vikir's blade.

“You were a Gradient? That's amazing.”

Camus was genuinely impressed.

What kind of mastery was a Gradient?

An exalted realm that ordinary people couldn't reach even after a lifetime of training.

Even the people of Baskerville, who were said to be swordsmanship geniuses, could only reach it by the time they were thirty.

“I see. You are the only man I can recognize.”

Camus smirked and stepped up to Vikir's side.

She had taken a defensive stance, as if she thought Vikir was tired of projecting his aura.

“Stay back, it's dangerous.”

Stepping in front of Vikir, the camo created a wall of steel and rock while summoning icicles of fire and ice to pound the field.

Three circles of magic, even a quadruple cast.

Truly a Morgue genius, a talent worthy of a kick in the ass at age 15.

“I will avenge my brother's death!”

Camus summoned all the mana in his body and hurled it at the barbarians.

But.

The battlefield is a place where even the most genius of talents can't let their guard down.

...Pow!

Camus frowned at the stinging sensation at the nape of his neck.

“An arrow?”

But if it was an arrow, he would be dead before he had a chance to think about it.

He reached up and pulled the thing out of his nape.

Something so small and thin it could have slipped through the shields floating in the air.

It was a cactus needle.

PING-

Camus felt his head spin.

The thorns must have been laced with paralyzing poison.

“????! ??? ???? ?????!”

I see one of the barbarian warriors pointing at the camel and jumping up and down with glee.

Apparently, he was the one who shot the tranquilizer needle.

And now.

Whirly-lic-

The barbarian warrior threw the lasso he was holding at the camel.

It looks like he intends to capture the camel alive.

But.

Jaws-

The lasso was intercepted halfway.

Vikir reached out and caught the lasso halfway.

Kukuk...

The barbarian warrior and Vikir began to struggle.

The other man tugged at the noose with all his might, but the already superhuman Vikir was no match for his strength.

Boom!

The barbarian warrior was thrown off the wolf's back and sprawled on the ground.

“That's at least a half-wit.”

Vikir shook his head as he watched the Ballak warrior roll around on his back.

Vikir looked back at Camus.

“I think we should retreat from here.”

“What? But the farmlands and the prisoners?”

“It would be better to refrain from engaging them until we have rejoined the main body of the Baskervilles.”

The camo looked conflicted.

Rationally, it would be better to back off moderately here.

But.

She had just lost her beloved half-brother, and in the heat of the moment, her emotions got the better of her judgment.

He was taken alive by a savage tribe. He must have suffered terrible pain and terror until the moment of his death.

The image of her brother flashed through her mind, and her fists tightened.

Just then.

PING-!

A sharp piercing sound came from somewhere.

Vikir instinctively jerked his head back.

An arrow whizzes past the nape of his neck, sending him flying into the city wall.

Boom!

The blow was strong enough to pierce the ear of the rampart.

“...!”

Vikir jerked his head back.

A lone female warrior stared back at him, perched on the back of a large wolf.

Black hair mingled with silver, tipped with triangular ears, and a face smeared with ash.

She threw her lasso right at Vikir, as if she knew he would dodge it.

The snake-like lasso swooped down, aiming for Vikir's throat at an exquisite angle.

“....”

Vikir didn't react, instead calmly reaching for his sword.

The black aura that symbolized the Baskervilles drew four teeth in the air.

The noose snapped in half in midair.

Just then.

“Danger!”

There was a hand on Vikir's back.

He turned his head to see a camouflage of stiffened bodies pushing against Vikir's back.

And behind him, the barbarian man who had fallen off the wolf's back earlier, tugging at the noose through clenched teeth.

I thought he'd be a half-wit, but he's stronger than I thought.

The noose was wrapped tightly around the camel's waist, and the barbarian took off running with the paralyzing poison.

'...So this is what happens.'

Vikir sighed softly.

A momentary lapse in judgment is costly.

Morgue's next patriarch would learn this the hard way.

“Even in her original history, she was kidnapped by barbarian tribes once.”

Even before the regression.

As a young man, Camouflage was captured as a prisoner of war and taken away as a hostage.

Of course, it wasn't long before she returned home, slaughtering barbarian tribes.

It was during this time that she became known as the Queen of Enemies and Black.

“But I still have to do my job.”

Even though it's not Baskerville's business, Vikir has formed a strategic alliance with Morgue.

Vikir quickly unleashes her aura.

Ka-ang!

The silver-haired female warrior's weapon blocked Vikir's path.

“...Bow?”

Vikir's eyes narrowed as he realized the identity of the thing blocking his sword.

The Ballak female warrior in front of him had swung her bow with its full length, blocking Vikir's blade.

Then.

Vikir locked eyes with the woman before him.

A strange sense of disquiet washed over him.

“You look familiar.”

Just as Vikir was about to rummage through his memory.

The warrior spoke up.

“You said you'd see ... again, didn't you?”

She spoke in broken Imperial.

Chapter 48

The Husband Hunt (3)

◆

Vikir thought.

“She looks familiar.”

The woman before him must have seen him before.

...But she didn't have long to think about it.

Pfft.

The next moment, the warrior's long legs flew out and kicked Vikir in the stomach.

A tingling sensation down his spine, an unbelievable weight.

There was no way she could have pulled off such a move without using her aura.

Vikir somersaulted a couple of times in the air before landing on his feet.

“Mastery.”

The barbarian warrior before him was no ordinary bet.

With the charcoal black paint on her face, it was impossible to make out her features, but she looked to be in her late teens, early twenties at least.

It would be difficult to fight her while hiding her skills.

Vikir lowered his stance and was about to prepare to fight.

The female warrior's mouth opened.

“You said we'd see each other again, didn't you?”

She spoke in broken Imperial.

Vikir suddenly remembered where he had seen this barbarian warrior before.

The girl who had once been kept in a cage like a beast during a raid on an illegal slave auction in Underdog City.

She was destined to be turned into flesh by perverted nobles.

Vikir had helped her escape by turning the auction house upside down and opening the cage door.

He even gave her a potion.

“You return the favor.”

The barbarian girl shook her head at Vikir's scowl.

“Me. A slave, avenging my capture. Morgue. Nothing to do with you.”

Apparently, House Morgue had something to do with this barbarian girl's captivity by the slavers.

Not surprising, since the Morgue have been at odds with the barbarians over the development of their ruby mines.

Perhaps this latest raid was in retaliation for the barbarian girl's capture by the slavers and her subsequent treatment.

Vikir narrowed his eyes.

“That said, she's a pretty high ranking girl.”

And then. The barbarian girl jerked her chin at the wolf in the distance.

The wolf had a lassoed camel tied around its waist.

“For what you've done. We pay him back. We. The woman. The next leader. We take them.”

Ballak and Morgue faced off. The girl swung her bow, knocking the wolves around her back.

The signal to retreat.

All of Ballak's warriors began to fall back in unison. As if their purpose was over with the capture of the camouflage.

The barbarian girl looked slightly troubled, then turned to Vikir.

“If you want your girl back, follow me.”

“...Do you speak Imperial?”

Vikir continued to speak to her, hoping to gather some more clues, to buy a little time.

But that was it.

As soon as the words were out of her mouth, the barbarian girl turned and disappeared into the jungle.

Vikir was about to give chase.

Beep, beep, beep.

It was impossible because of the countless showers of arrows falling down.

'Should I reveal my ...power?

If he unleashed all of his hidden power, he might be able to break through that rain of arrows.

But.

“Camo!”

That was impossible, as Adolf, leading his soldiers, charged into the battlefield.

Vikir took a few steps back to avoid the arrows.

With so many eyes on him, he couldn't afford to show his strength.

“Give me my nephew!”

Enraged, Adolf cast a great spell, turning the earth upside down.

But Ballak's warriors were fast and skilled.

The vanguard easily sidestepped Adolf's magic and disappeared over the water, while the laggards scattered in countless directions to confuse the pursuit.

In the end, Ballak's raiders fled into the jungle, most of them, leaving only a few casualties behind.

“This, this nonsense...!”

Adolf stood dumbfounded.

So did the mages who had brought reinforcements.

It took less than three minutes for the Morgans to respond to the emergency signal announcing the invasion, but the Ballak assault was so methodical and swift that it would have been all over in that time.

The raiders were well organized and caught the inexperienced camo off guard.

Slaves and crops would have been one thing, but the kidnapping of the next head of the family was a big deal.

“How can this be good!”

Adolf stamped his foot as he watched the sun set over the water.

The waters of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain were terrifying, but they became even more dangerous after dark.

Entering the waters at night was suicide, and even the wizards of Morgoth were not easily pursued.

One wrong move could mean annihilation.

...Just then.

“We can still catch up.”

Vikir stepped forward.

He gazed into the depths of the water.

“I've been in there when I was a kid.”

A lie, of course. He'd only been in there once, briefly, when he was eight years old.

But Vikir had searched, scouted, and slaughtered countless times before his return, and he knew most of the geography underwater.

Meanwhile, the wizards of Morgue were dumbfounded by Vikir's words.

One wizard raised his eyebrows and spoke up.

“Entering the Black Mountains with a dark enemy is suicide....”

But he didn't finish his sentence.

“Those who won't go, go. I will not trouble you later.”

Adolf Morgue, his eyes bloodshot, stood before Vikir.

He had recognized Vikir's extraordinary abilities.

With that, Adolf bent down at the waist to be eye level with Vikir.

...Boom!

Adolf squeezed Vikir's hand with both of his hands, and he said desperately.

“Please, I beg you. Help me save my niece.”

Vikir nodded.

The raiders from earlier had obviously thrown their nooses at him, and it was the camel who had returned the favor.

A debt must be paid, and without another word, Vikir turned and walked into the tangled jungle of roots.

“Maybe this is my chance to get out from under Hugo's control.”

They say a crisis is an opportunity, and Vikir thought he might be able to use this to his advantage.

Dusk fell.

The earth spider was losing.

◆

The watery terrain between the enemy and the Black Mountains is littered with all manner of fiends, poisonous plants, and traps.

Bone-sucking mosquitoes, venomous thorns, spiders that walk without making a sound, narrow, deep cliffs between rocks hidden by fallen leaves.

A normal person wouldn't be able to survive even a few hours in these waters, and the situation isn't much different for beings who have reached the pinnacle of nothingness.

What's more, the nights are so deep and dark that even barbarians are reluctant to pass through them.

All sorts of dangerous things are awakened from their daytime slumber.

So it's no wonder that even the bravest of Morgue's warriors wouldn't dare venture into the murky waters.

...But.

In the jungle, among all these potential killers, there was a being who seemed to be weaving in and out of them with incredible speed.

Vikir. Vikir van Baskerville.

He burned blades of grass to scare away poisonous insects, crossed cliffs hidden beneath dirt and fallen leaves, and rubbed animal feces on his clothes to hide his scent and creep.

All in a series of extremely skillful movements.

The Morgue and Baskervilles who followed could only hold their tongues.

“Are all ... Baskerville boys like that?”

“Of course not, you're a special case.”

Staffordshire shrugged at Adolf's quizzical look.

But Vikir, who is actually leading the way, is nonchalant.

“It was a universal tracking technique in the Age of Destruction.”

Swordsmen of that era weren't just good at swordfighting.

There was nothing they couldn't do: foraging, scouting, searching, hiding, ambushing, assassinating, pharmaceutical, healing, and cooking.

It was a time of survival.

SPOT!

Vikir halved a rotting log in his path and stepped through it.

The aura of the Gradient, vibrating and spinning at lightning speed at the tip of his blade, sliced through everything in an instant.

Everyone was truly in awe of Vikir's ability to find and remove obstacles, both large and small, single-handedly.

Especially the Baskervilles' triplets, who followed closely behind him.

“Cool.”

“Cool.”

“Delicious.”

The third one stuttered a bit after his finger was cut off and reattached, but they were all on the same page.

Then.

...Stop!

Vikir, who had been walking ahead, halted.

Looking at the bare footprints in the damp mud, Vikir checked the direction of the wind, then ducked low and circled behind a bush.

To hide his scent.

The warriors of Morgue and Baskerville followed Vikir back behind the bushes.

Then they saw a faint glimmer of light.

Ballak's hunters were gathered around a small campfire.

Rustle – ding – ding – ding

In the forest at night, even the smallest sounds of human movement can be as loud as thunder.

Furthermore, the Ballak hunters had scattered dry leaves and sticks around their makeshift campsite.

They had scattered them around their makeshift camp so that they would be heard.

Vikir pondered for a moment how to muffle the sound as they approached.

Then.

“...Silence.”

Adolf chanted the words with a terse syllable.

Instantly, a translucent aura enveloped everyone's feet.

Then, to my surprise, there was no sound as they walked.

This is magic, and Adolf's magic specializes in support.

Vikir had once been an assassin himself, and he knew what a ridiculously deceptive perk it was to be silent when approaching a target.

Soon, the pursuers were close to their target.

“?? ?????? ?? ????”

“????? ?? ???? ?????? ???? ??? ??.”

“??? ???? ???? ????? ???? ???”

The hunters rested, unaware that they had become the hunted.

Vikir picked out his targets by the faint light of the remaining fire.

Up ahead, he saw the barbarian girl who had parried his sword and kicked him earlier.

She was barking out orders as if she were the leader of the group.

The barbarian man who had shot the tranquilizer needle and thrown the lasso earlier grumbles as he follows her instructions.

And so on and so forth, until, in the center of the gathering of Ballak's barbarian warriors, the final target was located.

Camus Morgue.

She could be seen kneeling, naked.

Her hands and feet are tied to stakes driven into the ground behind her, and a collar is around her neck.

The good news is that there are no signs of beatings or other abuse.

The camel was cursing something at the barbarians and didn't seem particularly fazed.

Vikir let out a small sigh.

“No wonder he's naked every time I see him.”

Just then.

...Jaw!

Someone touched Vikir's shoulder.

He turned to see Adolf Morgue standing there.

Immediately, he spoke, his complexion and voice hardened.

“I will never forget this favor, nephew.”

The title ... seemed a little odd, but now was not the time to point it out.

No 2 of the Mado Sect.

It looks like Mado Star Adolf is about to reveal his true power.

Chapter 49

The Husband Hunt (4)

◆

The dark forest was eerily silent.

The silent forest was eerily dark.

The sky was like a handful of coarse salt scattered across a black carpet, but not a single ray of its countless stars could penetrate the dense canopy of vines, roots, and leaves to reach the bottom of this watery mess.

Not a single grasshopper whined around him.

Crackle, crackle, crackle.

The eerie sound of faint embers gnawing at the firewood.

“....”

Camus Morgue. She was bound and gagged, glaring at the barbarians of Ballak.

With her powers of observation and memorization, she had been able to pick up some of the names and ranks of her attackers while being dragged here.

Beyond the faint warmth and light of the campfire, she could see the silhouettes of the barbarians.

The supposed leader is a girl of about seventeen.

Her name is Aiyen.

Her hair is a mix of silver and black, her ears are pointed and triangular, and her face is charcoal-black.

But one thing is for sure: she's good.

She was powerful enough to hold off Vikir, a lowly Gradient.

Beside her, a man grumbled as he added wood to the fire.

The man who had shot himself with the tranquilizer needle was named Ahun, and his back was still aching from Vikir's attack earlier.

The other women and men were also there, most of them around 17 or 18 years old.

They had not made a large bonfire, but had thrown ashes on top of the fire to make a gentle roaring fire, and were sitting around it in a circle.

“I didn't catch the husband feeling.”

“I liked that girl I met earlier.”

“Maybe we'll catch him again someday.”

The three women warriors chattered amongst themselves.

Camus could hear, if not speak, the barbarian language, so he could get a sense of what was going on in their conversation.

The savages of Ballak always go on “husband hunts,” “saxi hunts,” “son-in-law hunts,” and “daughter-in-law hunts” around this time of year.

The targets are other tribes and sometimes even empire borders.

The reason for this practice of finding spouses in different areas is simple. To avoid genetic diseases caused by inbreeding and to bring in fresh blood from outside.

This is why most warriors who go out to find a mate want a superior seed.

Once they've kidnapped the right person, if they're good enough, they'll start making children, and if they're not, they'll enslave or kill them.

They especially welcome women, because women are more important than men when it comes to calling the population.

Is that why? The savage boy, who goes by the name Ahun, has been staring at the camel for a while now and smiling wickedly.

“The men of the tribe must be happy, having captured such a fine female.”

Understanding Ahun's words, Camus gritted his teeth.

“You want me to take the seed of your barbarians? I'll die for that!”

Camus immediately tried to bite her tongue, but Ahun was quicker to gag her.

Ahun chuckled and stuck an arrowhead under Camus's chin.

“Perhaps this cheeky slave needs an education.”

He was just about to touch the camel's body.

...Jaw!

Someone stepped in front of Ahun.

Aiyen. A female warrior leading a young Ballak hunting party.

She pressed the nock of her bow to Ahun's sternum.

“Get out.”

Aiyen's words were short.

Ahun's brow furrowed.

“What the hell, boss. I got him.”

“Bullshit. Just a little less.”

“What do you mean, I shot the tranquilizer needle and lassoed him!”

“Who did that for you?”

Ai Yan asked coldly, leaving Ah Hoon speechless for a moment.

She continued.

“You would have been dead if I hadn't interrupted that 'boy with the sword' earlier.”

She is referring to Vikir.

Ahun began to tremble as Aiyen mentioned the situation earlier.

He cried out in frustration.

“So, you're saying that this female belongs to you?”

“Of course.”

“The boss is a woman!”

“What does it matter?”

At Ai Yan's retort, Ah Hoon fell silent, as if he were speechless.

Then, frosty blue flesh began to erupt from Ai Yan's entire body.

A silvery aura emanated from the bow she was clutching.

Upon seeing it, the camel's eyes widened.

That was the liquid aura, the symbol of the Gradient.

Although it was faint, it clearly revealed the prowess of a lower-ranked Graduator.

A 17-year-old grader. There were geniuses like that in the world besides Vikir and himself.

Whether Camus was surprised or not, Aiyen didn't seem to mind at all.

Ahun, meanwhile, bowed low before Aiyen's power.

“Come at me whenever you want. I'll beat you to a bloody pulp.”

“...An kouwa.”

“No?”

“...No. Whatever. I give up. She's yours.”

Ahun shook his head, a mixture of anger and bitterness.

Aiyen tore her gaze away from Ahun and looked back at Camus.

He didn't particularly feel that she had saved him.

Neither did he.

“Good eyes, good constitution. You must have good blood.”

Aiyen looked at the camel with the eyes of a thorough merchant.

“I, too, was once captured and sold into slavery by your empire, especially the Morgue.”

“....”

“And so it will be with you.”

After speaking, Aiyen closes his eyes for a moment, seemingly remembering someone.

“Only, you will not be as fortunate as I was.”

Opening his eyes, Aiyen grits his teeth and stares into Camus's eyes.

“I will take my time, slowly, bone by bone, soul by soul. I will make it a daily routine for you to lick your tongue between my toes....”

But Ai Yan was unable to finish her sentence.

...Quack!

A loud explosion erupted from the bushes behind them.

“Die, beastly savages.”

The voice sounded like a death sentence.

At the same time, ice picks flew out, piercing through Ballak's hunting birds.

In less than a second, three or four of the hunters in the rear were dead.

Behind them was Adolf Morgue, a reddish mana stalk.

Soon, Morgue and Baskerville's pursuers were on the battlefield.

“I'll repay your debt.”

Baskerville of Staffordshire and the triplets of the Baskerville family slashed at several Ballak hunters with their swords.

Morgue's wizards were desperate.

Numerous offensive spells were flying, creating a blaze of light and sound.

...?

Somehow, the Ballak hunters were unable to respond.

Despite the vast disparity in power, if they focused on planning and fleeing rather than fighting back, they should be able to minimize the damage.

But why?

Ballak's hunting party, and the wolves they ride, are greatly perplexed and restless.

It was as if they were more worried about Morgue and Baskerville's surprise than they were about the lights and sounds they were creating.

“Ugh! These lunatics are making such a ruckus in the waters of the night!”

Ahun jumped back in surprise.

His uneasy gaze was fixed not on the swords and magic raging around him, but on the darkness of the water beyond.

It was the same for their leader, Aiyen.

“....”

Aiyen moved quickly.

The first thing she did was not to respond to Morgue's magic or Baskerville's sword, but to kick up sand to extinguish the campfire.

Once the faint glow was gone, Ballak's hunting birds made their move.

They mounted the wolves' backs, firing arrows as they retreated deeper into the water.

“They're fleeing. Don't leave a single one alive!”

Staffordshire shouted to the Baskervilles' hounds, spurring them on in pursuit.

And through the infernal darkness, a shadow approached the camo.

Vikir. In a flash, he cut the rope and noose from the stake and freed the camel.

The camel, still paralyzed by the paralyzing poison, recognized Vikir's face.

“It's ...! It's you!”

“Shhh.”

In the blink of an eye, Vikir had the camel in his arms and was falling backwards.

No. He tried to pull away.

If it weren't for the silver shadow that appeared out of nowhere.

“I knew you'd come, 'boy with the sword'.”

Aiyen was facing Vikir squarely.

Her eyes scanned Vikir's entire body as she spoke.

“A strong body to cover such a distance in such a short time.”

“....”

“A strong mind to see through the darkness of the water.”

“....”

“The hot innocence to risk his life to save the woman he loves.”

“...?”

Vikir frowned.

Why did he have to listen to this barbarian woman's assessment of him right now?

Vikir was just about to dodge past her to the rear.

Aiyen points a finger at the camel in Vikir's arms.

“I will not ask about the past.”

The corners of her mouth curved in a gentle arc.

“Pass.”

Chapter 50

The Husband Hunt (5)

◆

Vikir wrinkled the bridge of his nose.

“...Passed?”

I don't know what the hell that means.

But there was no time to ponder that.

Vikir searched his memory and guessed the identity of the barbarian girl in front of him.

Information about the Barbarian tribe of Ballak flashes through his mind before he regresses.

#Ballak #Civilized barbarians #Live in the highlands of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain #Population between 300 and 500 #Wolf-riding, bow-wielding hunter-gatherers #Friendship with the Empire is very low #Warriors of both sexes #Every single member of the tribe is highly militant....

After reviewing the many podiums, I'm starting to get the picture.

The Ballak were a barbarian tribe with few known personalities, though some of their names were known far beyond the borders of the mountain range.

The first name that comes to mind is Adonai the Archer, one of the greatest warriors the Ballak have ever known.

He was one of the Empire's “Three Outer Calamities,” and a chieftain at the height of Ballak's power.

He was so famous that he single-handedly declared war on the Empire, sniping and killing 542 Gradients during the 100-day war.

The number of casualties among the rank-and-file soldiers was uncountable.

The Empire suffered untold losses in the short span of 100 days, and from then on, the enemy and the Black Mountains were categorized as “extralegal” territory, and all-out war was avoided.

It's a much devalued account in the Empire's history books, but a remarkable one all the same.

'...But this is not the age of the Adonai.'

Vikir thought for a moment.

Adonai was from a whole generation before.

A great man so long ago that even Vikir had only heard of him in history books.

The archer Adonai had disappeared from the scene when the Baskervilles had just migrated to the Western Front and established themselves as pioneers, and he had presumably died around that time.

The current patriarch of the Baskervilles, Hugo Le Baskerville, hadn't even been born yet.

So, who else could have been of the same age and as famous?

'If it's relatively recent, it's... the 'Fox of the Night' who fought a ten-day battle against the Baskervilles and the Morgans, killing 32 people before disappearing.'

When Vikir was a boy, Baskerville and Morgue had joined forces to wipe out their enemies and the barbarians of the Black Mountains.

One of Ballak's archers, who played a prominent role in those wars, was known as the Night Fox.

Not much else was known about her, only that she was female.

In the span of ten days, she had killed sixteen Gradient-class swordsmen in Baskerville, ten fourth-class mages in Morgue, and six fifth-class mages.

Vikir was too young to see the devastation with his own eyes, but he could guess at the aftermath, as many of his instructors at the Hound level had died.

“And it was the same in this life.”

The creature that had left scars on the bridge of Sword Star Hugo's nose and on Adolf's chest in a territorial dispute not long ago was probably the Night Fox.

'...But she doesn't look the right age to be a night fox.'

It was clear that her current age was at least in her early thirties, and most likely in her mid-thirties.

Even if she was an archery genius, she must have lived and practiced for quite a long time to be able to wound a Swordmaster and a Class 6 mage.

The barbarian girl in front of him was probably only in her late teens.

Although her skills were impressive, she was far too weak to be a Night Fox.

'It's not in the history books, and I've never heard of her.

So what was this, some kind of bloodline from the Night Fox?

Not much was written about the Ballak in the history books, and even the local Baskervilles who fought them knew little about them.

If the Night Fox, who might now be leading the Ballak, had left any blood, it could be this girl in front of him.

“So much for the barbarian researcher.”

Vikir had thought a lot in such a short time.

Just then.

...Hook!

The sound of a wind blowing in from somewhere.

It was too faint to be the sound of an arrow.

But the hunter's senses, trained through the ages of destruction, would not allow for a gap as thin as a hair.

Boom!

Vikir swung the hem of the bloodwind to stop it in its tracks.

It was a cactus thorn, a stinger laced with paralyzing poison.

The same ones that had poisoned the camo before.

“...What! How did you stop it!?”

An exclamation of horror echoes across the water.

Ahun, hiding beneath the roots of a tree, was panicking, his mouth clamped shut.

Vikir debated whether or not to fight back, then withdrew his aura.

All that mattered now was getting the camel in his arms to safety, and by extension, erasing his massive debt to the Morgue Clan.

“Just be patient, I'll take you to your uncle soon enough...?”

But Vikir did not finish his sentence.

The camel in his arms was looking up into his face with a blank expression.

His complexion was flushed and he was out of breath. His heart was beating too fast.

“Has it been poisoned with something other than paralyzing venom?”

Vikir asked the camel, sensing something was wrong.

“Poisoned?”

“...I think so.”

If so, this is bad news.

Vikir hurriedly retreated.

Aiyen drew his bow with lightning speed, but he couldn't catch Vikir as he darted backward.

Whirligig-!

The rope snares fly again.

The female warriors of Ballak have been relentless in their pursuit of Vikir.

But.

Kiririk-grrrr!

Vikir, too, has unleashed his auras, slicing through the lassos.

With so many eyes on him, he was only able to display the swordsmanship and aura of a lower level Gradient, but that was enough to overwhelm the common warriors of Ballak.

But.

Ping-ping!

Aiyen's arrows were so powerful that even Vikir had to be careful.

The good news is that Aiyen's arrows are deflected by Vikir's rapid fire.

Arrows aimed precisely at Vikir's legs, and the occasional noose flying by.

Add to that the fact that Vikir is carrying a camel in his arms, and you've got a recipe for trouble.

Meanwhile, the camel clutches at the hem of Vikir's robe in a show of understanding.

“...Ugh, I never thought I'd be an embarrassing heroine who only grabs ankles.”

“Heroine, you're so self-conscious.”

Vikir scooped the camel up and kept falling backwards.

Just then.

Quack, quack, quack!

A loud explosion puts a giant wall of ice between Ballak's warriors and Vikir.

Suddenly, a massive wall of ice surrounded them, trapping them all.

Adolf Morgue.

Morgue is a delegate to the Mage Council, leading the great party known as the Ming Party.

One of the highest ranking members of the Imperial Magisterium.

His power, looking beyond the sixth class to the seventh, was unbridled.

“Stand down, nephew.”

He drew a number line in the air, calculating complex formulas.

The volume of ice, the specific gravity of ice, the latent heat of melting ice, the amount of mana remaining, and the fatigue of magic tools are multiplied and divided.

And the results are frightening.

Boom, boom, boom!

The entire sea of water began to freeze.

As if an ice age had come, hail and snowflakes scattered through the air, and the ankles of those fleeing were frozen to the ground.

Ballak's barbarian warriors and their wolves were hardy, so their frozen legs would not be cut off.

But there was nothing to be done about being pinned to the ground.

“Bite them all to death.”

Baskerville's hounds' teeth sank into the defenseless Ballak warriors.

Morgue's wizards joined in, and screams began to erupt from everywhere.

By then, Adolf had taken the camo from Vikir.

“My nephew, are you all right?”

Adolf called out anxiously to the camel, who was still covered in Vikir's blood.

At the same time, detoxification magic appeared.

...Pow!

CURE POISON.

It was a very high class magic, and not just anyone could use it.

Adolf succeeded in removing some of the paralyzing poison from the camel's body.

“That's a lot of paralyzing poison, and it's going to be hard to get it all out. You're going to have to lie down for a few months, and when we get back, we'll start by visiting the Holy House of Quovadis.”

Even Adolf's strength could not remove the poison.

Afterward, the camel recovered from the paralyzing poison and leapt to his feet.

And then?

...Boom!

He rushed to his less paralyzed leg and hugged Vikir around the neck.

“You saved me again!”

Adolf's expression behind him turned to one of frustration and sullenness.

“Nephew, here's your uncle.”

“Why is my uncle here now, I'm going to tell my mom everything!”

“....”

At this, Adolf grew even more sullen.

At that moment, Vikir pushed the camo away from him and spoke to Adolf.

“My lord. It seems that the camouflage is poisoned with other poisons as well. From what I heard earlier....”

“Hmm? I don't recall any other poison besides the paralyzing one?”

“...?”

What? I thought it was clear earlier....

But not if it's not Adolf.

Vikir was just about to turn to look at the camo.

Charalak!

Another rope lasso flew in.

This one wasn't like the last one.

It was much more sophisticated, with a strange, writhing motion. It was like watching a live snake.

“...!”

Vikir frowned, striking the noose with the back of his sword.

Aiyen. Holding the end of the noose, she glared at him with a determined expression.

Not at Vikir, to be precise, but at the camo.

“You'd better be caught quietly, we're running out of time.”

Slurred Imperial, Vikir thought, puzzled.

“No time?”

What does this mean? Did he misspeak because he was not fluent in Imperial?

Even now, the Morgue and the Baskervilles are overwhelming Ballak. It is only Ballak

time.

Bombastic sounds, bright lights, and high-pitched screams echoed from everywhere.

Sssssssss...

The water reacts to the untimely disturbance.

Leaves slowly rustled.

Just then,

“...Came!

It's finally here!”

Ahun, who was carrying the longsword, shouted in a seizure.

All the Ballak warriors who heard it stopped moving for a moment.

“...?”

Vikir scratched his head.

Even the keen senses of a hunter who has lived through an age of destruction can't pick up on anything.

Only.

A buzzing.

Beelzebub, lurking within the arteries of his wrist, was warning him furiously.

“It's coming!”

“Madam Eight-Legs!”

“She's coming, she's coming!”

Ballak's barbarians are hardy souls, whose faces never change in the face of the most severe torture.

To see them so terrified now was indeed a grave sign.

....

...And now.

Something peeks out from the darkness.

A heavier, darker blackness, casting its shadow across the water.

This moment,

drawn by the light and commotion of battle.

An unknown horror was coming.

Chapter 51

The Husband Hunt (6)

◆

....

Something peered out of the darkness.

A darker, heavier darkness, casting its shadow across the water.

Deeper, thicker, heavier, darker, it is 'it'!

It had surely been drawn to the lights and commotion of the battlefield by Baskerville and the Morgue.

“Here comes Madam Eight-Legs.”

Ballak's warriors are visibly panicking.

The warriors of Morgue and Baskerville realize the gravity of the situation, as do the warriors who are not known for their fearlessness.

Vikir, in particular, already had some idea of what was peering out from beyond the darkness.

He had seen, heard, and experienced countless incidents in the jungles of the Black Mountains with the enemy before his return.

And Vikir remembered the words of an old native he had once stumbled upon while drifting in an unfortunate time.

'Madam with eight legs'.

A piece of ghostly legend.

It was a tale of untold horrors that lurked at the bottom of the water, in the depths of rotting root holes.

“...Shhh. Don't make a sound.”

Vikir placed his hand over the camel's lips in his arms and whispered in its ear.

“You may not be able to see very well, but you have sensitive ears and skin, old man.”

Light and sound. He's sensitive to them.

Jahak... Jaharak...

Beyond the tangled skeins of roots in the floodwaters, a noise sounded otherworldly.

It sounded like the uncomfortable groan of an old man, or the last gasp of a drowning man in a swamp.

Rustling, rustling, rustling.

Soon there was the sound of bristly, dense fur being swept everywhere.

From the sound of it, the thing that was now approaching must be of immense size.

Even the mighty Adolf Morgue was at a loss as to what species this creature lurking in the darkness belonged to.

“It must be a new creature that hasn't been seen before, but how could such a monster be undiscovered?”

Adolf's questions were legitimate.

But Vikir, who knew how large and vast the enemy and the Black Mountain's waters were, had nothing to say.

He merely recited the information from his pre-reversion knowledge, information that had been refined and perfected over the course of several more editions, even in the version Adolf now knew.

“Madam Eight-Legs. An annihilation-level demon. One that will grow into an even more terrifying monster in the next decade.”

Risk Level S.

Dangerous enough that a single entity is capable of destroying a nation.

If we were to fight it head-on, we would have no chance.

Even here, in its home base of Suhai, it's not even at night!

...Gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp.

Something sticky is dripping down from above, onto the leaves, fallen branches, and human heads.

The drops of slime falling simultaneously from various locations created the illusion of drizzling rain.

....

Static.

Perfect static.

There hadn't been a sound of a grasshopper in the water since before.

And now this.

The veteran swordsmen of Baskerville, the seasoned wizards of Morgue, and the fierce barbarian warriors of Ballak had all been reduced to nothing more than grasshoppers.

All were frozen in place, unable to breathe.

Praying that the great nightmare in the sky would pass quickly.

Just then.

“Kaaaaaah!”

A tearing scream came from the air.

Vikir turned his head quickly.

There, standing there, was Camus, his eyes narrowed in horror.

“It's not ..., is it?”

She made an X with her hands as if to say, “No more embarrassment.”

Vikir breathes a sigh of relief.

It's Ahun of Ballak who's letting out a new scream.

“My, my head! Madame's poison!”

Ahun was running around, shaking out his hair.

Was it because he quickly cut it off with a knife?

Tsutsutsutsuts...

On the ground, Ahun's hair is melting away.

But dodging the onrushing water didn't save him from the tsunami that followed.

“It” began to respond to his screams.

A thick darkness descended upon the Ballak warriors.

Aiyen quickly grabbed Ahun by the back of the neck and ran.

“You fool! If you weren't the eldest son of a shaman, I'd be all over you!”

Ahun cowered, unable to utter a word as Iyen growled.

Soon, Ballak's warriors began to scatter, spreading out across the water.

“Let us run!”

At Adolf's words, Morgue and Baskerville's pursuers retreated.

But there was a slight difference in the way the Ballak, Morgue, and Baskerville alliance retreated.

Ballak's warriors fled individually, with none of them running in the same direction.

The Morgue and Baskervilles, on the other hand, fled in unison.

This slight difference helped determine the “it” factor.

Passasasak-

The sound of blade-like leaves bending so easily.

A huge pile of fur was breaking through the dense foliage and thorns, heading this way.

...Into the room at breakneck speed!

Puck! Thump! Thump...

Dull noises came from all directions.

It was the sound of swordsmen and mages being crushed by an unidentified attack.

“What the hell is that?”

Adolf exclaimed as he ran, scooping up his camel.

Staffordshire, too, runs forward, carrying the Baskerville triplets in his arms.

The triplets, who had just been knocked out by an unknown attacker, were bleeding from the corners of their mouths, their eyes wide open and glaring at the “it” behind them.

Just then.

“That's it.”

Vikir paused.

At this rate, we're all going to die.

Whirr-

Vikir spins around in his seat.

Camus sees him and cries out.

“Rain, Vikir! What!”

She gasps in surprise.

Facing the camel, Vikir doesn't turn around, but waves his hand briefly.

“Let me buy you some time.”

“It” is not an opponent that can be fought by hiding its power.

And this crisis was an opportunity, a golden moment to legally slip off Hugo's radar.

Vikir instinctively sensed that the time had come to realize a plan he had long thought of.

Death. And camouflage.

Once a hound in the field is dead, all surveillance and control over it ceases.

In his mind, he had already memorized the theories of the Baskerville Tenth Sword Art. His mana and aura are slowly recovering to the level of his previous life.

All she needs is time. A place away from prying eyes.

This is the perfect place to hide and improve, so that when the time is right, she can leave and return to her family.

“No! Vikir, please come back!”

The camel cries out.

Vikir turns his back on the plaintive cry.

In the distant future, when he is no match for Hugo, or at least when he is able to hide and control his skills perfectly, he will return to his family and perhaps be treated as a hero.

At least he could claim to have sacrificed himself for the sake of Morgue's feast.

Vikir straightened his posture.

“Do your best, or die.”

He had no intention of giving it his all against an opponent who would likely die anyway.

It was just a matter of how much she could produce.

Vikir stood in front of 'It' in an almost sacrificial manner.

'If we go on like this, we'll all die,' 'I'll stop it for a while, so everyone run away,' 'Tell my family that I was brave at the end,' ... and other lines that Vikir didn't bother to say.

They must have gotten through without me.

“...Nephew.”

Adolf bit his lip, a grim expression on his face.

He bites his lip so tightly that it bleeds from the corner of his mouth, but he must return to his family as soon as possible to save his poisoned niece.

“Master ....”

Staffordshire, also carrying the injured triplets, looked back at Vikir with trembling eyes.

Finally, Camus.

“....”

She stretched out her hands toward Vikir, her face covered in tears and snot, her expression now speechless, her throat hoarse from exhaustion.

Only to be blocked from moving forward by Adolf's strong forearm.

“Go.”

Vikir turned his back on everyone and drew his sword.

Then.

“Do not let my niece's sacrifice be in vain!”

Adolf cried out, spitting up blood.

With that, the survivors of the Morgans and Baskervilles began to run away from 'it'.

“....”

Vikir watched them all move away.

And with that.

Passa Passa Passa.

The fast-approaching 'thing' broke through the darkness and leaned forward toward Vikir.

At the same time.

Vikir unleashes all the power he's been holding back.

Mana, fed by the waters of the River Styx.

An aura made even more refined by his newfound mastery of Baskerville-style High Swordsmanship.

In addition, the rare magic sword Beelzebub pierced my wrist, revealing long teeth.

...Puff-puff-puff!

A pitch-black aura, red as blood and dark as the abyss, began to rampage like a demon from Beelzebub's tip.

It quickly formed five gigantic teeth and clamped down on 'it'.

Jaaaahhhhh!

The monster let out a startled yell. A scream, tight with pain.

Quack, quack, quack!

There was a flash of light like a giant sun falling.

Vikir's aura surged with power, forcing dawn into the dark waters.

He didn't see Adolf and Staffordshire, who were concentrating on running forward, but... Camus and the triplets, who were being carried by them and looking backward, saw through the exploding beam of light.

...Flash!

Vikir's ridiculous power exploding the aura of a Gradual Intermediate.

Chapter 56

The Hunter and the Hunted (2)

◆

“....”

Vikir was speechless on the wolf's back.

Aiyen, riding in front of him, glanced up and down the length of his back, watching him closely.

“Did it hurt?”

“....”

“Are you angry?”

“....”

Aiyen turns his head all the way back to look at Vikir.

To which Vikir only replies bluntly.

“Look ahead.”

The wolf Aiyen was driving caught on a root and lurched once.

Aiyen quickly jerked his head back to the front and drove the wolf on.

All the while, he kept glancing back to see if Vikir was bothering him.

At this point, it was hard to tell who was master and who was slave.

Eventually, as the roots disappeared and a wide open plain emerged, Aiyen slowed the wolf.

He turned back to Vikir, still on the wolf's back, and spoke.

“I had no choice. Ahun is a stubborn, relentless creature, and this was the only way to prevent his petty retribution.”

“....”

“...Why aren't you talking, huh?”

At his master's continued prodding, Vikir replied shortly.

“It hurts.”

And it did. The inside of his mouth is covered in crusts of blood, and it hurts just to open it.

Then. Aiyen's body flinched for a moment.

She slowly turned her head to look at Vikir.

“Does it hurt a lot?”

Aiyen looked at Vikir's neck.

The white skin was smeared with red marks from the dog collar.

“....”

Aiyen stared at the mark for a moment.

Then she bent her head toward Vikir and ran her tongue across the scar on his neck.

Vikir jerked his head back in disgust, and Aiyen, for a moment, realizing what she had done, backed away in anger.

Vikir frowned.

'Do barbarians normally lick each other's wounds?

'Animals of the dog family do.

Ballak's warriors are friendly with wolves, so this behavior may be commonplace.

But Vikir was a civilized man, and it was awkward.

“Besides, licking the wound with your tongue is dangerous, as it leaves room for infection.”

So Vikir was prepared to firmly refuse if Aiyen tried to lick the wound on his neck again.

However.

“....”

Aiyen doesn't say anything, just tilts her head.

For some reason, the tips of his pointed ears were colored bright red.

◆

Like all Ballak warriors, Aiyen was basically a simple person.

Her spirits were quickly lifted when Vikir returned to his usual behavior, except that he was less talkative due to his illness.

Now in a better mood, Aiyen offered Vikir a gift to apologize for her earlier slap.

“Is there anything you want from me, anything I can do for you that's within my power, just tell me one thing.”

Vikir didn't hesitate to answer.

“Teach me how to shoot a bow.”

“...A. Bow.”

I wondered if he had something else on his mind. The answer came back a little muffled.

Aiyen looked a little disappointed at Vikir's immediate response.

“Yeah. Bow is good. Bow....”

Aiyen mumbled for a moment, then a grim smile curved his lips.

“Good. Since we're out hunting, I'll teach you how to shoot a bow, too. You're probably better with a bow than a sword anyway.”

With that, Aiyen moved behind Vikir and hugged him tightly against his chest.

Aiyen's body pressed tightly against his, the weight of it pressing down on Vikir's spine.

Vikir grunted through the pain.

“ ...Do I really have to learn in this position?”

“It's best to learn everything with your body. Do you have a problem with that?”

It was hard for Vikir, whose body was broken, to resist.

Then. Aiyen pulled out a spare bow and placed it in Vikir's hand.

The unfamiliar feel of it in his hand brought back memories for a moment.

Vikir was quite proficient with a bow, as part of the education of the young hounds of Ironblood Baskerville was an introduction to armory.

And the swordsmen of the Age of Destruction actually knew how to use almost every other weapon to some degree, not just swords.

Vikir had already mastered the basics of archery.

...A minor, really.

“But not enough to go out and show off.”

Before his regression, he'd been pretty good with a bow, but not to the point where he could actually use it in combat.

At best, he could take down small prey that could be cleaned and eaten immediately.

But here in Ballak, where all the people are masters of the art of archery, he might be able to reach new heights.

Is it the desire to take down the big prey?

Aiyen had been teaching Vikir archery since the beginning of the day.

“We'll need the help of a wolf pup for this hunt.”

Aiyen was eager for this hunt.

Ballak's 300 members need at least 200 kilograms of meat to survive the day.

What's more, the warriors' recent hunting performance has been poor, and there are many people in the tribe who are starving.

“Your life will be easier if you make your mark here.”

At Aiyen's words, Vikir nodded.

Just then.

“...!”

Aiyen's wolf, Bakira, suddenly stopped running.

It had spotted its prey.

Aiyen bent down and grabbed a handful of dirt from where Bakira was sniffing.

A mixture of rotting sawdust and fallen leaves, moss and sand.

The soil was slightly damp, and it smelled sharp and raw.

Aiyen said with conviction.

“It must be oxbane.”

Vikir knew the creature Aiyen spoke of.

<Oxbear>.

Danger Rating: A

Size: 5 meters

Found in: Ridge 7, Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain

-A very large bear with two huge horns.

A carnivorous bear, the strongest terrestrial predator, and a perfect killing machine, it is considered the strongest and pinnacle of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain 7th Ridge ecosystem.

It has few natural enemies, except for its own kind.

The bear carries two water buffalo horns on its head.

Its entire body is covered in thick muscle, fat, and bristly fur.

A monster I had encountered many times before during my training within the clan.

However, the ones roaming around here now must possess a different level of strength and life force than the ones that were captured in the cages inside the clan, waiting to be killed.

“This must be their territory from here on out.”

Aiyen turned his head to follow the direction of the scent.

Oxbears deliberately sprayed their poisonous urine to discourage prey and warn rivals.

The scent would have sent any lesser predator running for cover, but not Aiyen, the hunting leader of the younger Ballak.

Vikir, too, had the calm composure of the worn and tattered hound he had been before his regression.

Aiyen smirked at the sight.

“Not scared?”

“Not really.”

“It's good to see you've got some balls for a kid from the Empire. An Oxbear is a threat to even the most experienced hunters of the Ballak.”

Aiyen seemed to like Vikir's demeanor all the more.

Soon, Aiyen and Vikir were facing the wind, tracking the scent.

Aiyen pursued his prey with animal instincts.

Sometimes he could smell it better than Bakira, the wolf.

Vikir, too, was skilled at tracking, but only when it came to fleeing humans.

“Good chance.”

Vikir looked over his shoulder at Aiyen's skilled monster tracking.

And then.

It wasn't long before they spotted their target at the top of a rolling hillside lined with tall bushes and short shrubs.

I see a large oxbear making its way through the brush.

Two fiercely curved horns, fur far thicker and denser than I'd ever known, flesh and muscle clinging together in an impossibly tight knot.

The oxbear, which appeared to be very old, stood about eight meters tall, larger than any oxbear Vikir had seen before his regression.

“...That's enough to raise my risk rating.”

When Vikir muttered that, he was done talking.

It's hard to go head-to-head with a creature of that size.

It would have been better to back off now and move on to other prey.

But Aiyen didn't back down.

“Let's go after it.”

She clung to Vikir's side.

Vikir gritted his teeth against a faint ache.

“A beast of that size will be hard to beat. Apparently he's unusually strong for an oxbear.”

“Fool. Who said we'd catch him?”

Vikir looked puzzled at Aiyen's comment.

She replied with a smirk.

“If there's a female bear, there's no shortage of male bears. Look.”

Before she could finish, a response came from beyond the thicket.

Another oxbear had approached the previous oxbear.

Apparently, the giant oxbear that Vikir and Aiyen had first spotted was a female.

The new male oxbear was relatively small.

It was barely over four meters tall at best, and must have weighed nearly twice as much.

Could she be in heat?

As the female oxbear moves her massive body, the male oxbear sneaks up on her and sniffs her fur.

Then he starts nuzzling her chest and back.

“Okay, that's the real prey.”

Aiyen grinned and pressed Vikir's chest and back against the bush.

Vikir watched the grooming of the male and female oxbears and felt the strength of Aiyen's grip on his arms.

Passasac...

Hidden in the bushes, Aiyen's body pressed closer to Vikir's.

His breath, wet and hot, brushed against his earlobe.

The skin of every inch of her body, toned and soft, pressed against Vikir's back.

The pounding of her heart against his back made him tense up like an athlete.

Naturally, Vikir could only think one thought.

“That's a lot of weight.”

Chapter 57

The Hunter and The Hunted (3)

◆

“When there are sows, there are no shortage of bulls.”

Vikir understood now why Aiyen had said this.

Vikir and Aiyen are currently lurking in front of a den deep in the jungle.

The den they are watching closely contains a large female oxbear and a small male oxbear.

The two oxbears have been mating nonstop for three days.

The female's strength and desire were immense.

She blocked the entrance to the nest with her huge beak and pushed down on the exhausted male to prevent him from escaping.

He, too, had good seeds and was able to satisfy her intense thirst for a couple of days, but by the third day he was running out of strength and often made dying noises.

Females are the strongest of their kind, and their appetites are unusually voracious.

She had a long hibernation ahead of her, so she didn't let go of him for a moment to make sure she was going to get pregnant and hibernate.

When he gives it all out and spreads out, she climbs on top of him, grooms him all over, and brings him back to his feet.

And then she'd do it all over again, over and over again.

Vikir sighed softly.

“I don't know what I'm doing.”

Vikir's arms are filled with the carp, salmon, berries, mushrooms, and other things he's just caught.

Aiyen, too, had gathered up various supplies and laid them out in front of the cave.

These were not for Vikir and Aiyen to eat. They were for the oxbears mating in that den.

They had been helping the oxbears mate for the past three days.

When a hungry female came out to forage for food, Aiyen and Vikir would provide her with these small bits of food so that she could mate as quickly and as often as possible.

The female oxbear would carefully examine them for poison, then take them back to the males and feed them to restore their strength.

Aiyen smiled wryly.

“Those berries and mushrooms are a short-term boost. But in the long run, they're terrible for you. They raise the body's heat rapidly and then drop it rapidly again.”

Vikir knew the benefits of those ingredients.

Taking them makes you temporarily stronger, but it saps and burns your life force, which is not good for your health.

And the female Oxbear seemed to know this and still take them.

The male Oxbear also seems to recognize the benefits of these mushrooms and berries, but he can't do much to satisfy her needs right now.

He can only eat.

Sometimes during the feeding, if Vikir accidentally left a scent or a trail, the female oxbear would come out of her den, alert and wary.

She was old and had poor eyesight, but her ears seemed to make up for it.

[Crouch!]

She tore at the thick logs around her with her claws and pulled rocks apart.

A giant tree that must have been hundreds of years old was snapped in half, and the rocks that supported the small hill were shattered.

After ravaging the area for a while, the female, satisfied that there were no more signs of intruders around her, went back into the den and climbed on top of the exhausted male.

Vikir, hiding behind a bush, muttered quietly.

“I don't know if it's a warning to the intruder or the male.”

Such a display of strength would scare off the intruder, but it would also make it impossible for a cowardly male to escape.

Vikir now understood why Aiyen had chosen a large, powerful female to pursue first.

The stronger and larger the female, the more likely she was to be able to keep the male at a distance.

Meanwhile.

Lurking hunters need to eat, too.

Aiyen calculated the direction of the wind and set about making a meal that would not carry the scent to the oxbears.

Clear water boiled in a coconut shell with crayfish from the waterfall. The only other additions were a handful of salt and a bunch of dried seaweed.

Aiyen offered Vikir some of his clear water.

He pushed all the lobsters, even the plump ones, in front of Vikir.

It was a sight that made it hard to tell who was the master and who was the slave.

“Eat a lot, so you can feel better.”

Aiyen shoved a considerable amount of food in front of Vikir's nose.

Vikir thought she looked a bit like a camel.

...Pow!

The red lobster's body snaps in half.

The hard shell cracked open, revealing plump white flesh.

The yellow and blue guts were steaming hot.

Vikir chewed on the crayfish's head.

“By the way, they mate like crazy.”

For three days, the oxbears barely left their burrows.

The constant vibrations of the burrow and the mingled moans of the males and females inside must have been exhausting for those who had been watching for three days.

Aiyen's eyes light up with mischief at Vikir.

“Isn't that what you deserve?”

“...What?”

“I thought all Ballak men were supposed to do that, but not Imperial men?”

Vikir frowned.

Aiyen's words were so unreliable after what had happened.

Hadn't he once taken her word for it and pissed in the middle of nowhere and been humiliated by his tribe?

But Aiyen continues to tease Vikir.

“You can't do that?”

“....”

“Well, maybe you can't because you come from the land of the sandman.”

“Who's a sandman.”

“Then can you do that?”

“....”

“Can you do it? Can you do it?”

Aiyen was getting annoying.

Vikir knew that getting caught up in her pace would be a headache, so he chose to ignore her completely.

What a cheeky slave.

...Just then.

[CRACK!]

A cry unlike any other erupted.

“...!”

The playfulness drained from Aiyen's face.

She bounced to her feet, quickly grabbed her bow and arrow, and began to peer over the bush.

The playful seventeen-year-old girl of just moments ago was nowhere to be seen.

Only the sharp-shooting hunter remained.

[Grrrr...]

Bakira, Aiyen's partner wolf, had bared her teeth as well.

Vikir, too, dropped his lobster claws and rose to his feet, crouching beside Aiyen.

A commotion was from the den containing the two oxbears.

[Gwooow! Gwooow! Gwooow!]

The female, who had been gentle with the male up until this point, gagged a few times and suddenly changed her demeanor.

She bared her teeth at him and threatened him with her hidden nails.

The male was taken aback by her sudden change in demeanor, but remained lying on the ground, apparently trusting his bond with her.

He seems to want to stay in his big, cozy nest for a while longer.

But she wasn't about to let him keep squirming and pressing against her.

...Bam!

A dull noise.

The female slammed her front paw with the force of several tons.

Teeth snapped and blood spurted.

A slap on the ear jolted the male to his feet.

He scrambled out of the den on shaky legs.

Aiyen called out in triumph.

“Looks like the female is convinced that she's fertile.”

Now that she's successfully conceived, she doesn't need to squeeze the male's seeds.

It's a world of carnivorous bears.

After mating, the opposite sex is simply a competing predator that has invaded their territory.

[Boom!]

The female roared once more at the fleeing male. The male is confused and scrambling for his life.

The male scurries away from the female's lair in a daze.

To avoid being eaten, he had to run away as fast as he could while she wasn't in a bad mood.

His legs are shaking and his movements are slurred and slippery.

Her fur was matted and had lost much of its shine.

His nose and eyes were dry, and all the fat that had once been plump on his back, belly, flanks, and thighs had been burned away.

His cheeks were already visibly puffy from the slap he had just received.

And at the sight of such a male oxbear, the eyes of Aiyen, the hunter of the Ballak, glittered.

“Follow me, slave.”

“....”

Aiyen, a male oxbearer, and Vikir, a slave to his mistress.

This was the beginning of the real hunt.

Chapter 58

The Hunter and the Hunted (4)

◆

Aiyen and Vikir tracked the oxbear male with caution.

It was obvious that his nerves were as sharp as his body was weakened. This was evident by the water scattered in his path.

“You have to take advantage of the moment when your target is as weak as possible.”

Vikir nodded as Aiyen applied frog venom to his arrowhead.

...When is the enemy most fragile?

It's when they're sleeping, especially after several vigorous copulations.

Aiyen looked at the oxbear feces on the floor and nodded.

“Judging by the viscosity and consistency, he's in very bad shape.”

“He'll probably sleep soundly tonight.”

“Of course he will, he hasn't slept a wink for the past three days and is drained of energy. He'll probably retreat to a dark, deep corner where he doesn't normally go.”

Aiyen was right.

The oxbear was aware of its condition, and it was heading deeper and deeper into the dense floodwaters.

Dense jungle. Fallen trees hung between the living, creating a maze of trees.

The leaves were turning red and yellow, making it difficult to discern direction.

Tracking the animals was made even more difficult by the fact that their tracks could be washed away in as little as half a day if it rained.

But Aiyen never loses sight of his target.

The way the branches bend, the way the grass is trampled, the depth of the soil, the chirping of the grasshoppers around him.

To a seasoned hunter, these are all signposts.

“Where an oxbear has passed, you won't hear a mouse or insect for a while.”

As if in agreement, the wolf Bakira lets out a low howl.

Bakira had been tracking a scent from earlier, the faint scent of sweet-smelling berries, a faint scent that the human nose could not detect.

The scented berries had been stuffed into the stomachs of carp and salmon by the Aiyen and tossed to Oxbear as food.

So that Oxbear would breathe it in and carry it with him everywhere he went.

“....”

Meanwhile, Vikir had watched the Aayen's skillful tracking from start to finish.

Some parts he didn't know, some parts he did.

What he knew, he would review; what he didn't know, he would learn.

Then.

Up in the trees, Aiyen looked down at the forest at the bottom of the hill and stretched out a finger.

Sure enough, there it was, a male oxbear stumbling along.

He could probably catch it if he pounced on it right now, but he was cautious nonetheless.

“Well, we'll have to put off the hunt for a while.”

“Why is that?”

Vikir asked, and Aiyen grunted and frowned.

“That oxbear has crossed the borders of the swamp. There are scary creatures that live in the swamp, so we can't go in there.”

“ Scary creatures?”

Vikir was about to ask what it was.

...Mate!

Aiyen's two palms flew out and slapped Vikir on both cheeks.

The cheeks flushed red in an instant. As Vikir stood there dazed, Aiyen smirked.

“This is the creature.”

Aiyen held out one palm in front of Vikir.

In the center of his palm was a dead mosquito.

Bakira, the wolf, growled lowly and pawed at the mosquito's corpse in warning.

Aiyen warned with a serious expression.

“There are three types of mosquitoes in that swamp. One is the blood-sucking mosquito. These are not very threatening. But... bone-sucking mosquitoes and flesh-sucking mosquitoes, you have to be careful.”

This was something Vikir knew as well.

Of all the mosquitoes in the waters of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, the bone-suckers were the most dangerous.

They swarm over anything that moves, turning the body of a living creature into a leather bag of blood and guts in an instant.

In fact, Vikir had seen what the bone-sucking mosquitoes had done to a colleague a few times before, so he understood the gravity of Aiyen's situation.

...But there's one thing he doesn't understand.

“But. Why won't you take your hand away from your cheek?”

Aiyen's other hand was still on Vikir's cheek.

Aiyen flinched slightly at Vikir's question, but then answered in a brusque manner.

“Do I have to take it off?”

Aiyen was now openly pinching the flesh of Vikir's cheek.

Vikir frowned.

“...What are you doing?”

“Why, I'm the master. Do you have a problem with me touching mine?”

Vikir's mouth was half open in disbelief.

But it would be futile to rebel against Aiyen now, not when he was so ill.

“You're so soft.”

“....”

So I'll just have to put up with this humiliating childish treatment for a while.

◆

On the night.

Aiyen settled down on the cliffside directly overlooking Oxbear's burrow.

“They'll strike at first light tomorrow.”

Oxbear is nocturnal, so fighting him now would be a disadvantage.

It was wisest to strike when the sun rose and he fell asleep.

Aiyen and Vikir built a simple hut on a solid rocky area.

A few branches, a leather cloth, and some broad leaves made a tent large enough for three or four people.

Blow into it and white smoke billows out.

This is what the indigenous people of Ballak call the “cold valley,” a valley where even in May, the snow still hasn't melted.

“It's so cold here, even the mosquitoes can't come.”

Aiyen climbed into the tent and lay down.

He lifted his leathers and turned to Vikir, who stood outside the tent.

“Come in here.”

“....”

Vikir was silent for a moment.

He looked around and saw the harshness of the environment.

The ground is cold and the soil is bad.

Trees couldn't grow much, so where they had grown and died, only bushes and weeds sprouted in their place.

With short shrubs rising up like a grate, it was not a bad place to camp for the night, as long as you were careful of the cold.

Rustle...

Vikir stepped inside the tent.

Aiyen had dug a shallow pit in the new floor and piled leaves and swordfire in it.

Crackle!

A small fire blossomed.

The light from the teepee warmed the confined space.

True to its name, the valley became very cold at night.

His face and arms were hot in front of the fire, but his back, head, legs, and toes were immediately icy.

Beyond the crackling embers, Vikir thought of many things.

The friends and companions he'd left behind in the Age of Destruction, all those faces.

People he could see again whenever he chose, people he would never see again.

Meanwhile, in the sea of fog outside the tent, dead trees, like human bones, rose and sank.

Vikir is lost in thought over the dying embers of the fire.

“Boom!”

A sound breaks his reverie.

He turns to find Aiyen buried in Bakira's fur, inhaling something.

It was a strong liquor, so strong that you could tell its strength by the smell alone.

From a leather pouch, Aiyen smoked a wide slice of jerky, slathered in white fat, and ate it as a late-night snack.

It looked like buttered bread, but the flavor and calorie count would be far different.

After a long pause, Aiyen looked back at Vikir.

“You should eat it, it's good for you.”

“...I don't have jerky.”

Vikir replied, and Aiyen waved his hand dismissively.

“Oh well. Don't worry. It is a master's virtue to provide for his slaves. I've even brought you your share.”

“...?”

Vikir cocked his head.

Aiyen's leather pouch had contained only one piece of jerky.

It had just gone into her mouth.

Just in time.

...Jaw!

Aiyen cupped both of Vikir's cheeks in her palms.

Then she shoved her face into his.

“...!”

Vikir didn't even have time to protest.

Aiyen kissed Vikir on the mouth, spilling the liquor and jerky in his mouth.

Gulp!

Vikir swallowed the liquor and meat in one gulp.

“Fuha!”

Only then did Aiyen pull her face away from Vikir's.

She stroked his chin with the back of her hand and smirked.

“You can't chew this jerky with your current jaw. It's very tough.”

“...I'm sure it is.”

Vikir frowns.

The jerky that remained in his mouth was so tough that he had to draw on his mana to chew it.

With Ahun's beating, Vikir hadn't been able to eat anything other than porridge or tree berries, so this was a nice (?) nourishment.

Suddenly.

Aiyen's eyes widened.

Somehow, she had ended up sitting on top of Vikir.

In the cramped confines of the tent, Vikir could do little more than struggle beneath her.

Aiyen's face is flushed red from the firelight.

She stares down at Vikir with an oddly heated smile.

“You can't even rebel, can you?”

“Because it's heavy.”

“It's not heavy.”

“I said it's heavy.”

“I'm not heavy.”

“I said I'm heavy.”

Aiyen was silent for a moment, thinking hard about something, and then he said.

“It's not that I'm heavy, it's that you're weak.”

With that, Aiyen smiled a smile that seemed strangely pleased.

Vikir saw it and gave up on the conversation.

Maybe it's the language, but he can't read her emotions right now.

“The first thing I need to do is recover quickly.”

He had to if he didn't want to be manipulated.

If I could regain my strength, I could easily subdue this little fellow and leave the jungle.

And the best way to do that was to sleep.

Vikir closed his eyes.

Aiyen leaned in close enough to touch his face with the tip of her nose.

“Are you itchy? Put your hand here. It's the place with the most heat. In return, I'll put my hand on yours....”

As Vikir's hand slid between my chest and armpit, Aiyen paused to drape her body over his.

Aiyen's expression quickly turns to bewilderment.

“...Are you asleep?”

The answer came back, too scared to speak.

Doron-.

Vikir had fallen asleep in that brief moment.

He can fall asleep in less than a second when he lies down, a skill that has been practiced by martial artists throughout the Age of Destruction.

“...Huh!”

Aiyen pouted her lips in disbelief.

She slid off Vikir's body as if offended and lay down beside him.

Then she rolled over and crossed her arms, her own hands trapped between his chest and armpits.

“Hmph. How dare you be insolent. A dull slave, inconsiderate of his master.”

Aiyen continued to grumble.

Only Bakira, the wolf with her ears to the ground, is looking at Aiyen with a pitying gaze.

“What is it, why are your eyes open like that?”

[Grrrr-]

“What! What! I was just cold, I wasn't trying to do anything else....”

Just as Aiyen and Bakira were about to argue.

...Bam!

Vikir, who thought he was sleeping, instantly jumped up.

The momentum was enough to make even Aiyen and Bakira flinch in surprise.

“Uh, uh, you didn't sleep...?”

Before Aiyen could open her mouth, Vikir spoke.

“It's coming.”

Something clicked in his senses that hadn't been there for a moment.

Suddenly, Aiyen's and Bakira's expressions stiffened.

Suddenly, an inexplicable wail rips through the night.

[Krrrrrr!]

The oxbear male had attacked this way first.

Chapter 60

The Protagonist of Hunting (1)

◆

The Plunder Festival.

A great festival was held in the village of Ballak.

In fact, every day is a celebration for the Ballak, but on a day like today, when meat is plentiful, it's unusually loud.

When the vines are cut, clear water pours out and pools in a large stone pot.

Into the boiling water were thrown lobsters, freshwater crabs, zaras, turtles, carp, catfish, venison, rabbit, squirrel, snake meat, caterpillars, beetles, ants, frogs, lizards, water grass, berries, mushrooms, and tree roots.

A huge stone pot bubbled in the center of the village.

All the small game that Ballak's hunters have gathered is thrown into it, simmering into a rich broth.

Everyone in the village gets a fair share of the broth.

Larger prey, such as deer and boar, were roasted separately around the stone fire.

Everyone would gather around these large hunks of meat, singing and dancing merrily.

In the midst of all the noise and excitement, it was a huge hunk of meat in the center of the village, even bigger than the stone oven, that caught everyone's attention the most.

An oxbear, a giant, six-legged beast weighing a ton.

Without the bones and fur, the pure meat weighs over 800 kilograms.

This giant hunk of meat was the star of today's hunt.

Naturally, the hunter who captures the oxbear earns the respect, admiration, and gratitude of all the villagers.

That would be Aiyen and Vikir.

“How does it feel to be a hero, slave?”

Vikir didn't say much in response to Aiyen's question.

She smiled and patted Vikir on the back.

“An oxbear is a very honorable prey. They're strong and fierce, but they're also intelligent, unlike boars, whose eyes are dark, whose movements are slow and simple, and who are so scared they shit and scream when they run.”

Aiyen shouted as loudly as he could, hoping someone would hear him.

Then he heard grunting and grunting from beyond the campfire where the meat was roasting.

It was Ahun, who had killed a fairly large boar.

“...Holy sh*t. I don't know how a dying creature could have gotten away with this. He must have gotten incredibly lucky.”

Ahun spat once on the ground and glared at Vikir.

Then Ahun picked up his knife and cut the oxbear's meat into small pieces.

The entrails and blood are perishable, so he immediately puts them in a pot of water to boil, and the flesh is cut into small pieces for fair distribution.

Ahun then handed the meat to the villagers lined up in a row, and then to Vikir, who stood behind him.

...?

Vikir's expression frowned slightly as he accepted the meat.

The size and weight of the pieces of meat given to Vikir were dwarfed by those given to the others.

Even less than what the frail old men and sniveling children had received.

Vikir raised his head to protest.

“What are you doing?”

“...?”

Then Ahun looked up, annoyed. A puzzled look on his face.

Rather disgusted, he retorted.

“What are you talking about, you slave?”

“Why is my meat so little?”

“What? No wonder. Because your honor is so high!”

Ahun bellowed.

Vikir gave him a puzzled look, and Aiyen, beside him, broke out into a wide grin.

“It is a Ballak tradition. The one who contributes the most to the hunt takes the least. In return, he receives an amount of honor equal to the lesser meat. If you can trade honor for meat, you have a great deal.”

Ahun nodded in agreement.

“Damn. Part of me wants to give you a lot of meat, too! But you gotta give credit where credit is due.”

Judging by his grumbling, he really does want to give Vikir a lot of meat.

Well, the less meat he gets, the more honorable he is.

Vikir decided that meat was better than honor that was worthless, but for now he could only nod.

'It doesn't really matter.

Though the meat was scarce, there was enough food to fill his stomach if he so desired.

In fact, the real harvest of this hunt was not meat.

<Gluttonous Fly 'Beelzebub'>/ Awl

-1 slot: Burn – Cerberus (A+)

Slot -2: Sacral Spine – Oxbear (A)

Slot -3: Tight Throat – Infernal Buffalo(A)

New skills gained from capturing Oxbear.

One of the three orbs of the magic sword Beelzebub is imbued with the hardy soul of the male Oxbear you killed last night.

The Hellhound's soul is gone, and the spirit of the stronger, higher-ranked Oxbear is Vikir's new slave.

The skill of Sacral Spine was simple and effective.

By holding your breath, you could increase your weight by nearly a thousand pounds (600 kilograms) in that time.

It's a pretty versatile skill for close combat.

Not only that, but the karma from killing the Oxbear was infused into his body, restoring a significant amount of health to his entire body.

Skills and experience.

Vikir was mentally calculating the results of this hunt.

“C'mon, Ahun. That's quite a kill, don't you think?”

Aiyen broke Vikir's reverie.

She had brought several kilograms of foreleg meat, a jar of blood, and the heart, liver, and gallbladder that were Vikir's share of the bounty, reserved for the best hunters.

Aiyen lifted the meat and waved it in front of Vikir's eyes.

Narrowing her eyes, she spoke with a burdened air.

“Just as important as the hunt is the preparation and preservation of the kill.”

Aiyen wanted to use the grooming as an excuse to stick close to Vikir and interfere.

But there was one thing she didn't know.

Vikir had slaughtered countless demonic carcasses during the Age of Destruction, and his skill at removing their entrails, flesh, bones, and skins to preserve and cook them was almost masterful.

Chuckle, chuckle, chuckle, chuckle...

Vikir soaked the hides in water in a wide bamboo vat and scraped away the fat behind them with a sharp stone knife.

The hides, which came off without a scratch, were set aside for tanning.

When dry, the hides were as hard as planks, but softened after a few beats with oil squeezed from the scaffolding.

The oxbear's flesh, guts, and blood were boiled in a pot, and the oils that floated to the top were skimmed off and used to light the lanterns.

The bones, claws, and teeth were used to make weapons and jewelry.

Meat as a whole was cooked in a variety of ways.

Some cuts were made into jerky, some were boiled into soup, some were boiled into tang, some were lightly poached, some were smoked over charcoal, and some were hung to dry in nodal....

Vikir was particularly good at smoking large pieces of meat whole.

Some of the people who watched Vikir work on the meat were dumbfounded and left their meat to him.

Among them was Aiyen, who had come to learn how to handle the meat.

Vikir tied the large chunks of meat to salted rope and hung them from a branch.

He then dug a pit and let the meat dangle in the center of the pit, and at the bottom of the pit he piled pine needles and oak and apple wood and lit a fire.

Once the fire was blazing, Vikir gathered branches, leaves, and mud to seal the opening of the pit.

After a while, he broke the mud lid, which had hardened under the fire, and pulled the rope to reveal a browned, smoky chunk of meat.

A whole oxbear hind leg was roasted.

The Ballak people raved about the deliciously smoked hind leg barbecue.

Aiyen's eyes widened in amazement as he cut into the meat.

“What the hell can't you do?”

Nothing too extraordinary, given the age of the soul, but certainly surprising, given that the body was no more than fifteen years old.

Vikir watched the younger children eagerly pick at the chunks of meat, blowing on them.

The exuberance of young children is something that puts a smile on anyone's face, regardless of age.

Vikir watched as the people ate the meat he had roasted.

There was a slight quirk in the way the people of Ballak shared their meat.

Those with bad eyes ate the eyes of an oxbear.

Those with bad lungs ate the lungs of the oxbear.

Those with bad legs ate oxblood legs.

Those with bad pancreas ate the pancreas of the oxberry.

The tribesmen seemed to believe that they could cure their ailments by eating the parts of their prey.

“Strange superstition.”

Vikir thought to himself.

“Hey, slave.”

Vikir hears a voice calling to him from the side.

Aiyen, who had slipped away after the dismemberment had begun, was standing behind him when he reappeared.

Cheeks burning, a large bowl of coconut in his hand.

The steaming bowl was filled with a hot, bubbling broth of oil.

Inside was a large chunk of meat, elongated and thick, making it hard to tell what it was.

“Organ?”

I asked, though I couldn't tell exactly what it was because it was floating in a cloud of grease.

Aiyen snorted and said.

“I've taken what the shaman covets with the authority of a hunter, and this is for you to eat, by all means!”

“I have already received a piece of meat, a jar of blood, and some entrails.”

“No, no, no, this is for you to eat!”

Aiyen insisted on feeding Hansako Vikir the meat soup.

Her logic was adamant.

“If your eyes are bad, eat the eyes of your prey; if your heart is bad, eat the heart of your prey; if your hands or feet are bad, eat the forelegs and hind legs of your prey!”

“What part of the oxbear is this?”

When Vikir asked about the identity of the long, thick chunks of meat in the bath, Aiyen only coughed and offered no explanation.

“Hmph, seeing as how you've been sleeping around in the cold, you'll definitely need this, eat some...!”

Aiyen mumbled the last part and swallowed it whole.

Reaction erupted around him instead.

“Woooo- Captain, you're already taking what's yours(?)!”

“Who gives that to a slave for his own good!”

“Ho-ho, the season of long nights is coming soon.”

“That's too blatant! It's obvious what he's up to!”

The young women of the village booed Aiyen in unison.

“Shut up, girls! If you're not happy, you can go out with your lasso and get him!”

Aiyen raises her fist, her eyes glowing, and the heckling dies down.

“....”

Vikir frowned, not quite sure what to make of that.

Well, I'll take what I can get.

Vikir gulped down the hot broth.

He chewed and swallowed every last bit of the coarse meat that had sunk into his stomach as Aiyen kept urging him on.

“This is so tough.”

The texture itself was similar to the haggis she was used to eating in Baskerville, but it was much more savory and chewy than that.

...Gulp!

Vikir's throat gurgled loudly once.

Only then did Aiyen's expression soften.

“I see. Now you're going to give me an excuse.”

Vikir frowned slightly once more.

“I think I've already given you more than your fair share of hunting.”

He couldn't quite figure out what more she wanted here.

Chapter 63

Unfair Trade (1)

◆

Tink-tink-tink-tink-tink-!

Over the clanging of bells, the watchman shouts.

“The outsiders have appeared!”

Something seemed to have happened in the village.

Vikir scrambled to his feet.

“ ...Is it war?”

Beside him, Aiyen turned to look at Vikir with a puzzled expression.

“Are you serious?”

“...?”

When Vikir gave her a puzzled look, Aiyen reached out and stroked her hair once, roughly.

She smiled.

“There's no way in hell there's a bunch of lunatics in these lands who would challenge our Ballak to a fight first.”

That's right. No one would challenge Ballak to a fight unless they were a high level demon.

Outside the borders, there was no one who could stand up to Ballak, except perhaps the Baskervilles or the Morgans.

Even the cannibalistic Lokoro tribe was no match for Ballak.

How could a tribe of only 300 people declare war on the Empire, much less their neighbors?

It would not be an exaggeration to say that Ballak had no one to look out for in the continent, except for 'Madam Eight-Legs', who reigned as a local nightmare.

“...Then who is the intruder?”

Vikir asked, and Aiyen rose from his seat and drew back the curtain at the entrance.

“It would be quicker to see with your own eyes.”

As she spoke, Vikir turned his gaze toward the outside of the barracks.

“...!”

There was a rather unexpected sight.

White-skinned, blond, jet-black, and blue-haired people.

All dressed in clean clothes and speaking in a familiar language, they were clearly Imperials.

“...Houses of Bourgeois.”

Vikir frowned, though only slightly.

The Seven Houses of the Empire.

The Baskervilles, represented by swords, the Morgue, represented by magic, and the other five are the Seven Pillars of the Old Country, sworn to the Emperor's service.

The Bourgeois family was a tycoon family that had amassed a great deal of capital through trade and commerce, and was one of the Seven Families, along with the Holy House of Quovadis and the Poisonous House of Leviathan.

Then.

“It's been a while since you've been here.”

Aiyen's blunt words broke Vikir's reverie.

Her expression was a slight frown.

Merchants from house of Bourgeois are known for doing whatever pays the bills.

They'd probably come this far underborder with supplies to trade with the natives.

Aiyen didn't look too impressed with them.

“This is actually not necessary. They are selling something that is not here, psychologically this makes us feel like we will regret it if we don't buy it...I'm not suited with those kind of merchants.”

And to a certain extent, Vikir agreed with her.

Before the regression, Hugo had a saying about bourgeois families.

“There are fools who think money is power. They've never known what real power is.”

There was an undisguised contempt and irritation in his voice.

He didn't like the idea of the Bourgeois who proudly boasting in the rich land in the capital of the empire while the Baskervilles were fighting bloody frontier battles with barbarians on on the borders of the empire.

What's more, the fact that he's sneaking into their territory and trading with their enemies, the barbarians, doesn't make him look good.

The other families were similar in their dislike of the bourgeois, but it was ironic that they had no choice but to do business with them.

Diplomacy, trade, commerce, real estate, banking, and all other aspects of the empire's monetary economy were influenced by the Bourgeois.

“But how did they get here?”

Vikir looked bewildered.

If the Bourgeois were to send merchants this way from their seats on the ecliptic of the Empire, they would essentially have to pass through the territory of the Baskervilles or the Morgans.

Especially to reach the depths of these border, they would need to procure large amounts of supplies, and that would be impossible without the help of the locals.

There was only one thought in Vikir's mind.

“...Smuggling.”

They had trespassed on the Baskervilles' property and made their way to the border.

And they had most likely smuggled themselves in via Underdog, the city closest to the border.

“....”

They made their way to the center of town and began to unload their cargo while Vikir stood still and watched the merchants of Bourgeois Avenue.

“Now, as usual, it's a five-day market. We came here first, before the other tribes!”

The merchant, who came from a bourgeois family, was a middle-aged man with a long mustache.

Sir Smuggler.

He had a gentle and kindly appearance, but the greedy gaze in his eyes was unpleasantly scanning the bodies of the young Ballak maidens on display.

Soon, the merchants began to pull various items from their packs and distribute them to the natives around them.

They were cheap glass beads, brooches, whistles, perfumes and cosmetics of shiny materials, and, to my surprise, the Ballak warriors accepted them with a twinkle in their eyes.

“Here, free, free, try these!”

The merchants gave away all sorts of goodies to the locals.

The middle-aged women and older men were especially excited.

“Here are some glass beads that you can put in your bed to help you have good dreams, please take one.”

“Here are some perfumes, ladies!”

“There are also cosmetics, cosmetics!”

The glass beads not only sparkled, but also gave off a nice scent.

Neither did the perfume nor the cosmetics.

The natives were accepting them, as well as me, because they are hard to smell in the barren jungle.

Soon, the merchants who had attracted people by handing out freebies began to sell their products in earnest.

They were mostly grains and vegetables, things that could not be grown in the jungle.

The prices the traders demanded from the native Ballak, who did not use currency, varied.

Animal skins, bones, teeth, rare parts such as gums and antlers, and forest products such as precious mushrooms, spices, and medicinal herbs.

Sometimes, gemstones or gold.

When Vikir saw it, he thought to himself.

“What a rip-off.”

Indeed, the natives of Ballak were trading their diamonds for the merchants' corn.

For the natives of Ballak, it was a profitable trade, turning worthless rocks into edible grain, but for Vikir, who knew how much they were worth..., it was unbelievable.

Then.

“Wait!”

Aiyen stepped forward.

Her eyes flickered between the diamonds and the corn.

Then she stood between the girl with the diamonds and the merchant with the corn.

“This is an unfair trade,” she said, “it's ridiculous to trade a diamond for a kernel of corn.”

As Vikir listened to her, he thought, “Right!”

Aiyen had some bones to pick, and he should be able to stop this unfair trade.

But.

“...You should get at least two bags of corn.”

After speaking, Aiyen looked back at Vikir and gave him a victory sign with his finger.

Vikir sighed lightly.

She may be an accomplished warrior, but she knows nothing of the world outside the Empire.

The natives of Ballak were a bit rough around the edges, trying to devalue the merchants' wares, but well, ... Vikir thought.

“Hmmm. Hmmm. This radish isn't very sweet. I don't think I can trade for a pearl clam, at least I'll take two radishes.”

“Damn it, did you bring this cabbage too? It's wilted and bug-eaten in so many places! This is why I can't give you a whole pair of antlers. You'll have to take one!”

“Do you know how hard I've been drying these otter skins, you should give me at least two more potatoes!”

Everyone is a haggler.

In the empire, the value of crabs, antlers, otter pelts, pearl shells, diamonds, wolf teeth, and bear bones are traded for sweet potatoes, potatoes, corn, radishes, barley, cabbage, and more.

“Oh no, we can't afford to lose to Ballak's warriors.”

“Well, I'm afraid you can't keep raising the price of your goods like this, but I can't help it. I'll meet your demands this time, Nene. You're a good bargainer~”

“We don't have anything to offer, either.”

The merchants quickly take the natives' goods, even though they are grumbling.

Soon enough, the agricultural products-potatoes, sweet potatoes, corn, cabbage, radishes, carrots, barley, and rice-are gone, along with cheap glass beads, brooches, and perfume.

In their place were deer antlers, mushrooms, sea turtles, ivory, bones and skins of all kinds, peony, reishi, matsutake, jewelry, gold, and the hatchlings and eggs of small and rare beasts.

The merchants pretended to be calm as they looked at the goods piled high on their carts, but inwardly they were jumping for joy.

I wonder how many tens of thousands of times this is.

When the trade was finally over, the merchants' demeanor became arrogant.

They saw more goods than they could carry in their carts, and now they began to accept goods based on their merit.

Then.

A girl stepped forward.

She could not have been more than twelve years old. She was pretty, with dark hair and dark eyes.

She carried several plump caterpillars, carefully roasted on twigs.

They were a delicious and prized food among the Ballak natives.

The girl held out the caterpillar skewers and said to the merchants of Bourgeois Street.

“Excuse me, can I get a glass bead?”

But the merchants' attitude was cold.

“There's a glass bead, but what's that?”

“This is the caterpillar of a sunbeetle.”

Several of the younger Ballak children looked at the skewer of caterpillars the girl was holding and gave her an envious glance.

The caterpillar was a rare insect that tasted unusually like a mixture of milk and egg yolk, and it was worth a lot of money.

However, the merchants of Bourgeois Avenue looked at the girl's caterpillar skewer with disdain.

“...Wow, you're not giving this to me to eat, are you?”

“Haha, kid, that's for you brown-skinned people. White people don't eat that stuff.”

“That's why you're black as a dung beetle. Hahaha!”

“Why don't you give me something else instead of that, like showing me up your skirt.”

They taunt, sneer, and sexually harass the girl in an imperial language she can't understand.

Boom!

One of the vendors shoves a skewer of caterpillars out of the girl's hand.

She drops the caterpillars to the floor.

She couldn't understand what the merchants were saying, but she could at least guess the meaning of their jeers, scorn, mockery, and lustful glances.

Just then.

...Jaw!

A boy picked up a skewer of caterpillars that had fallen to the floor and devoured them in one bite.

Vikir.

He stood in front of the merchants, gulping down the caterpillars in his mouth.

His face and body were covered in black charcoal dust, as if he had just spent the night in an open fire.

“....”

The girl looked up at Vikir, panicking.

Vikir patted her on the head, then turned to look at the merchants.

He spoke in a fluent Imperial tongue that stunned the merchants in front of him for a moment.

“This trade is invalid.”

Chapter 67

Blood Relatives (1)

◆

The four seasons of the jungle are quite distinct.

Summer. Crazy summer. Winter. Crazy winter.

Beyond the vast expanse of water, beyond the forest, the seasons have changed many times.

And here, in a quiet meadow at the beginning of the season.

...Puck!

A dull noise is heard.

A Ballak warrior, probably in his late teens, winced, clutching his nose.

“Oh, my nosebone!”

He grunted, his nose dripping with blood. It was Ahun.

And in front of him stood an impassive-looking man with an extended fist.

Tall, black hair cropped casually, cold eyes, and pale skin.

Vikir stared down at Ahun with a grim expression.

“That's enough hand-to-hand combat.”

His task complete, Vikir turned away without another word.

Ahun grabbed his companion's hand to help him to his feet.

As Vikir walked away, Ahun spat at the back of his head.

“You bastard, you've become more and more of a monster since you've been restored.”

The others around him snickered.

“You used to be a great fighter. Nowadays, your bow skills are amazing. From what I've heard, you're on par with Captain Aiyen.”

“Oh, I don't see how I can compare to Captain Aiyen, and judging by his fist just now, he's not that great.”

“Yeah, yeah, yeah. Ahun's nose was bleeding, but that's something I can handle.”

As his coworkers exchanged giggles, Ahun spoke in a low voice.

“...It didn't hit.”

“What?”

“The fist. I didn't get hit.”

Ahun felt a chill run down his spine.

Sure enough, Vikir had extended his fist. And stopped in front of his face.

The pressure of the wind that followed was enough to make Ahun's nose bleed and his bones jolt.

“ ... You did this with just the wind from your outstretched fist?”

The others' mouths dropped open in disbelief.

They can only stare blankly back at Vikir's back, now a tiny vanishing point in the distance.

◆

Vikir just turned seventeen this year.

His face has aged a lot.

His short stature grew with each passing day, and his chubby cheeks grew thinner.

The 24 months in the water did a lot for Vikir.

Not only has his body fully recovered, but he is much stronger in body and spirit.

Realizing that Ahun and the other warriors his age were no longer glaring at him, Vikir showed his true strength.

...Pow!

The magic sword Beelzebub pierced through the arteries of his wrist.

The blade had grown thicker and longer. Beelzebub could now pull out nearly a meter.

Vikir swung it around, testing out slashes and thrusts.

...Snap! Qua-qua-qua!

The boulder in front of him split in two, and the boulder next to him was pierced with a hole.

Vikir's swordsmanship was quite advanced, considering that it was generally more difficult to deliver a slashing blow than a thrusting one.

As soon as Vikir destroyed the two boulders, he sent four more flying.

A total of six boulders were destroyed almost simultaneously.

Torn, cracked, pierced, impaled, sliced, and split.

It was the fierce teeth of a hunting dog that destroyed the rocks.

“The sixth teeth.”

You have mastered the Sixth Teeth of Baskerville.

The six teeth that had been rampaging just a moment ago sank back into his wrist, and Vikir cooled the sweat that covered his body.

The boiling mana in his body is now spinning at high speed in six circles.

With this, Vikir had reached the upper levels of the Perfect Gradient.

'But I still can't get past the Master's wall.

Masters are something.

Even though I'm a graduate, I've only just gotten there, and at this rate, I'm not even close to where I was in my previous life.

It was the forty-year-old Vikir, before his regression, who was unable to break through the Master's barrier and ended up at the very top of the Graduate.

It sounds like a pun, but there was definitely a middle wall between the peak of the graduate and the Swordmaster that needed to be crossed.

“'Superior Graduate.”

The ability to manipulate liquid auras that were so thick and sticky that they felt like solids.

Only by reaching this level could one fully regain the power of their previous life. You will also be able to break through the walls of masters.

But aside from reaching the peak of the Graduate, Vikir was confident that he could fight and defeat a Graduate in real life.

One weight class above. An ability that allowed him to kill stronger opponents.

This was thanks to the protection of the River Styx, which made his bones and flesh tough and hard, the magic sword Beelzebub, and the archery and assassination skills he learned from the barbarian warriors of Ballak.

“ ... To the peak of the graduate at full power?”

But I wouldn't say I'm really good at pushing that hard.

And since my real goal is Hugo Le Baskerville, Sword Master of the House of Baskerville, I'll have to work harder anyway.

With that, Vikir returned to the village.

At the entrance to the village, young hunters who were about to go out hunting were waiting for the blessing of the shaman Ah'Heman.

They still had dark charcoal dust on their faces.

It's a ritual that prevents the spirits of the prey they kill from remembering their faces.

“....”

Ah'Heman stood wordlessly, glaring at Vikir as if he didn't like the late arrival.

But that didn't stop him from giving his blessing to Vikir, who always performed the best when he was out hunting.

Malmanama. If he didn't bless Vikir, and he performed well on his own, it would only prove that the shaman's blessing meant nothing.

Next, Ah'Heman quickly dusted Vikir's face with charcoal powder, which he did so sloppily that Vikir's white skin showed through in spots.

“...Well, the hunting gods will be with you.”

“...Thank you.”

Vikir didn't really need Ah'Heman blessing, either, so they parted on good terms.

Meanwhile.

Aiyen was receiving reports from the returning shift hunters before they went out on the hunt.

She listened quietly, with a rare look of seriousness on her face.

Vikir approached Aiyen and asked.

“Aren't you going hunting?”

“Mmm. Maybe later.”

It was unusual for Aiyen to reject Vikir.

Usually, she would approach Vikir before he could ask or suggest anything, but today she was serious.

“...?”

Vikir was a little puzzled, but didn't press the issue.

Soon, armed with a worn longsword, bow, and arrows, Vikir sets off into the depths of the marsh without a single wolf to follow.

The other hunters pay him little attention, as his simple attire, equipment, and short stature allow him to outperform most other hunting parties.

Except for one, ...Aiyen.

“Is he gone?”

Aiyen turned to see that Vikir had completely disappeared.

The subordinate who had been reporting nodded and spoke up again.

“Shall I report back in detail?”

“Yes. Do so.”

Aiyen listened, and the subordinate resumed his report.

“To summarize, four things. First, the rainy season is coming.”

Earlier, the search party had passed by a stream and spotted an unusual creature.

It was a fish called a “lungfish.”

These fish have lungs that allow them to breathe through their lungs, which allows them to stay out of the water for quite some time.

Flapping their fins and crawling through the mud, they sleep in deep wet mud during the dry season, only to wake up as the rainy season approaches and the moisture in the air increases.

Ballak hunters don't eat meat without scales because they consider it unclean, so they don't specifically hunt lungfish, but their presence means that the rainy season is coming.

The rainy season brought many bad things, such as flooded rivers and plagues, so they needed to be prepared.

“Secondly, we found suspicious strangers.”

Aiyen narrowed his eyes at the next report.

They were white-skinned Imperials.

He wondered if they were remnants of the merchant and mercenary groups he'd exterminated two years ago, but of course they weren't.

They came in quietly and went out quietly, and the only thing they did was release something at the river's source.

A red liquid in a glass jar.

The suspicious men poured it into the river and then slipped back through the jungle.

Ballak's warriors captured one of the dogs, who immediately consumed the poison they had hidden in his mouth and killed himself.

All he left behind was a dagger with the markings of a single, large snake on it.

Aiyen clutched it in her arms. He would ask Vikir what it was later.

If Vikir knew anything, he would surely know about this sigil.

“Third, an updated report on the Rokoko.”

The subordinate continued his report.

The Rokoko were a rival tribe to the Ballak, and just as all of the Ballak were excellent archers, all of the Rokoko were shamans.

Masters of curses and spells, they went by the name of black magic in the Empire.

Aiyen frowned.

Reports indicated that the Rokoko tribe had made few appearances in Ballak territory lately.

This was strange, considering they outnumbered the Ballak by nearly ten to one.

Then came the final report.

“Fourth, a search party from Morgue.”

It was this fourth report that caught Aiyen's attention the most.

“Have they come again?”

“Yes. They're more frequent than before.”

“And their commander? The same?”

“Yes. It's 'her' again.”

Aiyen's face crumpled at his subordinate's report.

For the past two years, Morgue's search parties had been tirelessly scouring the surface.

And the leader of the search party has remained the same.

Camus Morgue.

She was almost there.

Chapter 75

The Hound of the Night (2)

◆

St. Mecca, population 160,000, a resort town with dense forests and clean waters. One of the central cities directly under the control of House Quovadis.

People walk solemnly and reverently along the white marble paved streets.

Whenever a bell rings from the tall clock tower, everyone stops in their tracks and prays to the holy tablet on the roof of the Quovadis' official residence in the distance.

If a gold coin fell to the ground, it was not picked up, and order and security were kept very strictly by the citizens' own rituals.

“...Where would I live suffocated?”

Vikir stood on the roof of a tall tower and looked down.

Women walked around with white cloths wrapped around their bodies, exposing only their eyes. The men did the same.

For religious reasons, lust and greed are strictly controlled.

No nudity, no fashion, it's all white and monochromatic.

It's a far different atmosphere from the Ballak village, a tribe that lives freely in the jungle with most of their bodies exposed.

Having lived there for the past two years, Vikir found the atmosphere of St. Mecca stuffy and uncomfortable.

After waiting for darkness to fall, he headed to a slum on the outskirts of the city, far from the center.

Broken windows, cracked walls, low-lying areas with stagnant water and steep staircases.

Slum scenes are similar everywhere. It's the same in cities under the power of Quovadis the Faithful.

The people here are especially harsh, as Saint Quovadis banishes sinners from the center of the city and sends them to the outskirts.

People who hadn't committed felonies worthy of jail time, but had committed misdemeanors that wouldn't allow them to enter the center.

They were weeded out by the checkpoints and paladins that dotted the city's pathways.

Vikir climbed a steep flight of stairs and entered the slums on the higher ground.

It was the most remote and darkest of the slums.

Then, from beyond the darkness, the bell rang twelve times, signaling midnight.

By this time, few people were passing by, but those who remained in the streets all bowed down to the ground to show their respect to the Quovadis.

And when they did, only the Hound of the Night did not.

Moving through the noise of the night, Vikir went to the well and pulled out a vial.

It was the Red Death, the essence of the plague, drawn from the blood, sweat, and tears of Aheul.

Vikir poured the liquid into the well.

He released the Red Death into the heart of the Quovadis.

“It is an extremely infectious plague, and sooner or later there will be a reaction.”

The Red Death has an incubation period of up to ten days and a minimum of one day.

Once inside the body, it can take as little as a day to develop, three days if it comes into contact with mucous membranes, and usually a week if it is spread through breathing or skin contact.

'It's the realm of the faithful, so hopefully we can cure it before anyone dies.

Vikir thought for a moment about when to move on to the next design.

Then.

“...!”

Vikir made eye contact with a group of children approaching from the other side of the well.

They were on their way to catch bugs, and they were carrying buckets, dragonfly traps, and sugar water.

The oldest child, the one in front of him, peered over and asked.

“Is anyone there?”

The children stopped in front of the well and shouted. They can barely see Vikir, who blends perfectly into the darkness.

It's a dark, moonless night, and Vikir is masked.

He'd never be recognized, but he had to be careful.

Next, Vikir's eyes glowed with life.

A crimson glow blasted through the gas mask's glasses.

[I will curse this well.]

The children shuddered at Vikir's words and sank to the ground in a heap. They even pissed themselves.

Vikir warned them sternly.

[Anyone who drinks from this well will surely die].

It's unnecessary, but it's a consideration.

He didn't want the children to get caught up in it.

“Hiiiit! It's a ghost! It's a demon!”

“The well is cursed!”

“Ew! I'll never drink it!”

The children scurried away in a huff.

After Vikir checked several times to make sure that all the popular pretenders were gone, he buried something in the dirt near the well.

It was a marker left by the intruders who had flooded in some time ago.

It was the mark of Leviathan the Extremist.

Vikir knew immediately that the Leviathans were responsible for unleashing the Red Death on the surface.

“Let's see you guys fight to the death.”

The religious Quovadis and the ultra-orthodox Leviathan had been at odds for generations.

What would happen if the Red Death spread to Quovadis's home base?

Since it's Quovadis's home base, suppressing it would be quick, but after that would be the problem.

“We need to move fast.”

I can already see a few people coming up to draw water from the well.

We need to get the Quovadis out before there are any innocent civilian casualties.

The sooner I can fulfill my promise to Aiyen.

◆

The Hound of the Night worked diligently, visiting the official residence of the Holy Prophet Quovadis in the heart of Saint Mecca.

Despite the late hour, several wagons were parked in front of the compound.

It's true what they say, sickness does not sleep at night.

Even at this moment, there were many people who wanted to visit the holy man to heal themselves.

Most of them were nobles and wealthy people who had arrived in fancy carriages, and they were all knocking on the saint's door, their well-groomed clothes contrasting with their sickly faces.

“We heard that you are on retreat here! Please open the door for us, we want to greet you!”

“Oh saint, I knew you were here, and I have come to ask you to take a look at my illness just once!”

“Please let me see him, saint!”

It seems that word has gotten around that Saint Dolores, the direct descendant of Quovadis and the owner of a small household, is currently here in St. Mecca.

Saint Dolores, the pride of the Quovadis family, is currently a sophomore at the Imperial Academy, where she is the Vice President of the Student Council.

Rumors that she was resting here during the academy's vacation period had drawn nobles and noblemen from far and wide.

They were all highborn nobles, rich men with lots of money.

Over the clamor of knocking and shouting, a voice came from inside the door.

“...Who are you and what brings you to me at this late hour?”

The voice was gentle and feminine, but with a hint of power.

The voice of a saint, perhaps.

The nobles and the rich were thrilled to hear the voice of the famous Saint Dolores herself.

But it doesn't last long, and they quickly answer.

“I am the son-in-law of the House of Alpons, the eldest son of the House of Jonathan, which has produced knights of great distinction from generation to generation, and the son-in-law of the House of Dortmund, and I have the House of Dotte as my brother above, and the House of Franz as my sister below...!”

“I am the general manager of the Ipsen Guild Union, which is a subcontractor to the Bourgeois family, and I am in my fifth year as president of the Ipsen Town Council, and I am also an honorary knight, having recently been knighted by the Empire and having served for two years as a squire to the prestigious Count Les Baskervilles, a Boston terrier...!”

“If I may speak for myself, I am the second son of House Childs, and if you can cure me of my ailments, I can bestow upon you the entirety of the fertile granary lands far from the main house of the Quovadis, as well as a villa on the warm shores of the south and a fleet of private carriages...!”

But.

No man, no matter how powerful, no matter how rich, could open the gates of Quovadis.

St. Dolores kept the door firmly closed and refused to open it to anyone.

“I don't see how your status and wealth are any reason for me to open the gates to your ambitious vision.”

Not the noble, not the rich. They all went home, exhausted, after proclaiming at the top of their lungs how wonderful they were and how much they could pay for a cure.

And then, as the night wore on. The line had disappeared and Vikir was the last one standing at the door of the government office.

It was so quiet you couldn't tell if anyone was behind the door.

Standing in front of it, Vikir knocked politely.

Sure enough, this time he heard the saint's voice.

“Who are you, and what brings you to me at this late hour?”

Vikir thought for a moment.

The men who'd been listing their identities at the top of their lungs just moments before had all come up empty.

“That is not the taste of a saint.”

Vikir knows who Saint Dolores is.

He'd seen her on the front lines, on the bloodiest of battlefields, before he was turned back.

The intense look of treating the wounded covered in blood.

Her white robes stained with blood, her white holy power bursting from her.

The sight, even from a distance, was holy and sublime.

Finally, Vikir spoke briefly.

“...It's just a lost lamb.”

For a moment, there was silence beyond the door.

Vikir waited.

And then.

A click.

The door to the Quovadis of the Faithful, which had been firmly closed and opened to no one, opened.

Chapter 78

The Saintess (2)

◆

“...You. Who the hell are you?”

Dolores asked in an uncertain tone.

The being who had suddenly appeared one day and warned him of the misfortune of the Quovadis family.

A lonely man, dressed in strange clothes, but with a clear and pure spirit.

“Who are you, and how do you know all these things?”

Dolores's voice began to tremble.

Normally, among the guests who come to the House to feed themselves, there are always those who are well versed in the ways of the world.

But few of them could predict the future with such accuracy.

Even more so, they have the distinction of being early warners of an epidemic that hasn't even been reported yet.

Naturally, Dolores and Mozgus couldn't help but wonder about the identity of this strange visitor to the Quovadis family.

“......Ooh, great! Doesn't the saintess ask? Who are you?”

Mozgus also asks, dangerously fiddling with a small teapot that looks like it will be crumpled at any moment.

It's like he's pressuring me to respect the saintess's authority, but he's really just curious.

Dolores and Mozgus both look at Vikir's face, their eyes shining.

In response, Vikir answered briefly.

“Hound of the Night.”

At that, both priests' expressions become slightly subtle.

“...Night Hound. That's a rather ominous name.”

“Even when you give yourself a nickname, you wear it as if it were a piece of clothing. How very blasphemous.”

Dolores and Mozgus snorted.

Vikir remained silent after that, saying nothing else.

Naturally, Mozgus hurried things along.

“...Whatever is going on......everything he said is possible, Night Hound. We need to investigate the plague as soon as possible, report back to our patriarch, and take measures at the clan level.”

There was a sense of urgency in the chapel.

Dolores formally asked Archbishop Mozgus to organize a crusade to relieve the plague.

She also formally reported to her biological father, Cardinal Humbert, whose monastery was not far away.

Today, Dolores' decision would reach the ears of Lord Nabokov I, patriarch of the Quovadis and Pope of the Church of Runes.

It was a big deal.

Mozgus scurried off to tell the saint's will.

Meanwhile, Dolores was staring at Vikir with wide-eyed wonder.

Vikir, in turn, met Dolores's gaze calmly.

Vikir did not bother to tell the holy woman the story of House Baskerville and House Morgue.

To do so would reveal that the Red Death was first released in the waters of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

In fact, the Baskervilles and Morgue have the most to gain if the Red Death is released into the waters of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

The barbarian tribes play a crucial role in Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain ecosystem, and the loss of these largely predatory creatures would cause subordinate demons to overpopulate, leading to monster waves and a spike in civilian casualties.

Vikir recalled the past.

Before the regression, over 40% of the barbarians had been exterminated as the Red Death gradually spread.

This caused the demon population to skyrocket, and the political influence of the Morgue and Baskervilles on the border grew.

Hugo used this political influence to grow his family's power even further, and once again, many hounds were lost.

Vikir was one of them.

Well, whatever.

Keeping the Ballak alive is all about getting revenge on Leviathan the Extremist and Bourgeois the Tycoon, which in turn is about getting revenge on your comrades who died in Baskerville the Ironblade.

It's a chain of events, by design.

Vikir closed his eyes in silence, contemplating what was to come.

Meanwhile. Saint Dolores stared at Vikir as he did so.

“...A lost puppy, exhausted and lonely.”

Why do these thoughts come to mind for a man who calls himself a hound?

Why did the man who had brought down the mighty Mozgus and the paladins under his control look so small and pitiful?

He smelled of blood, of the wailing of a broken soul, and the sound of blood.

Sorrow, hatred, and loneliness. And a man walking a thorny ascetic path, carrying all these burdens alone.

He had the aura of a prophet or a seeker.

Suddenly, I remembered the words he had muttered in his deep throat.

“Theology is essentially a process of understanding human beings, so this is inevitable.”

There is no doubt that the person who knows this passage of the old scripture, which even the theology experts do not know well, is not a Rune follower.

He must be a follower of the runes, practicing the doctrine on the front lines of suffering, in the lowest, most intense places.

'There's no way he could remember and recite those words otherwise.'

At least that's what Dolores thought.

She is a young, immature sixteen-year-old girl with the qualities of a saintess who can read the souls of others.

Is that why? Her misconceptions about Vikir were gaining weight.

But whether she does or not, Vikir is merely waiting for the appearance of the holy water that can extinguish the Red Death.

“....”

“....”

A man and a woman look into each other's faces with different thoughts.

The tea that hadn't even been touched was quietly cooling down.

◆

Later.

Vikir hurried to the slums of St. Mecca.

Saint Dolores, Inquisitor Mozgus, and dozens of paladins and priests followed.

“Is there really a plague in this place?”

Dolores said, out of breath as she climbed the steep stairs.

The paladins escorting her seemed to be in disbelief as well.

But there was no hesitation in Vikir's gait as he ran forward like a scout at the head of the pack.

Finally, landing on a high roof high above the city of Dahl, Vikir glanced from chimney to chimney.

Despite the fact that the weather wasn't too cold, the chimneys of several houses were wreathed in smoke from wood-burning stoves.

Vikir looked for houses with smoke rising from their chimneys.

As it turned out, some of the houses with smoke rising from their chimneys were already experiencing an outbreak of the Red Death.

The first symptoms of the Red Death are usually chills and fever.

This is followed by intense pain throughout the body, followed by vomiting and diarrhea.

Patients shudder at the sight of red spots that slowly appear on their skin.

The chills naturally lead them to shove firewood into the chimney.

But just because there was no smoke rising from the chimney didn't mean there were no patients.

In the slums, many families didn't have enough firewood, and most of them were wrapped in dirty blankets to keep the chills at bay.

Dolores wept at the sight of their suffering.

“Alas, poor people, do not worry. Rune's great love will heal you.”

Without hesitation, she touched the bodies of the plague victims, saying prayers and blessings.

Vikir stood still behind her, assessing their condition.

“Thank goodness there are no children.”

It was worth it to scare the children at the well. There were no children among the patients.

Because Vikir had come in such a hurry, they were all early cases with only mild pain.

They were all primary cases, infected by drinking water, and secondary cases, infected by the saliva or feces of primary cases.

The disease had to be stopped early, while there were no deaths.

Saint Dolores gathered the patients in the central square and prayed to God.

[Light of my life, flame of my life, my sins, my soul, look down upon the young and poor gathered here...]

The saint recited the prayer in a clear voice.

And then.

A single tear fell from Dolores's eye and rolled down her cheek.

She looked so vulnerable, so holy, so somehow sublime.

It was the look of a beautiful girl, but without the slightest hint of lust or lustfulness.

Soon, a single tear, broken by contact with the floor, began to work miracles.

...Pow!

It emitted a white, holy light and instantly wiped away the red stains from the bodies of the patients in front of her.

With a single drop of her tears and a single line of prayer, five or six patients were freed from the red death.

“Oooh! Thank you, saint! Thank you!”

“You are my savior.”

“I'm healed, I'm cured, my God, it's a miracle!”

The villagers, who had been shivering with chills and gagging just before, jump up and jump as if they hadn't suffered from a plague.

Dolores smiles as wide as she's ever cried when she sees her patients regain their strength.

And there was a man behind her who stared at her smile.

“That's it. That's what I need.”

It was Vikir, hoping for a miracle from the holy water.

Chapter 79

The Saintess (3)

◆

Some time had passed.

Saintess of Rune Dolores Quovadis has been thinking to herself since she received the report of the growing number of patients.

“Curing them with divine power is a temporary solution. We can't stop the new patients from coming.”

That's because it doesn't cure the source of the plague.

The patients keep showing up because somewhere in this slum, a well is contaminated with the plague.

The wells often followed the water table beneath the ground, and as a result, it was impossible to completely eradicate the plague without purifying the water source.

“The number of reported wells in this slum is 42, plus unreported wells dug by the villagers themselves....”

Dolores worried.

If this happens, there is no choice but to concentrate the divine power to one well that leads to the deepest place.

The essence of pure water.

Concentrate and focus the divine power, make it the size of a pill, release it into the water, and it will purify the entire slum along the underground waterways.

So the priests of Quovadis immediately began clinical trials.

Divine Essence to purify the water, clinical trials 1a through 3c.

If they all pass, the plague of the slums will be eradicated.

While the priests of Quovadis Family gathered their divine powers to create the Essence, Dolores tended to the more pressing cases.

“A terrible plague indeed.”

This red death, once contracted and cured, was a disease that could return again and again.

The incubation period was extremely short, but the time to death was very long.

What's more, it felt like an artificial compilation of the worst aspects of all the plagues in history.

The malice itself.

It was an extremely virulent plague that was deliberately created to torment humans, causing the patient as much pain as possible for as long as possible.

“ ... This is not the time for this. We need to cure one more person.”

Even now, more patients were streaming into the infirmary.

Dolores was on her feet within a few minutes of sitting in the chair.

A moment.

A ping.

She stumbled slightly as she stepped onto the floor.

It was overwork to the point that she, who was born with mild anemia and full divine power, felt tired.

“I can do this, though.”

Dolores dragged her exhausted body out of the barracks, her holy power slightly restored.

She couldn't wait to comfort the suffering patients as soon as possible.

Then.

“Ouch! A saintess has come out!”

“Oh, what a holy figure!”

“Saintess, we are with you!”

“From now on, you have nothing to worry about, Runmen!”

There were men following Dolores as she headed toward the slums.

High nobles, or the scions of high nobles.

They had knocked on the door of the Quovadis not long ago and had been refused a meeting.

“...What brings you here?”

Dolores asked.

Beautiful blonde hair, clear blue eyes, flawless skin, and a clear voice.

Just hearing her voice was enough to make the men in the room shiver.

And then the male competition began.

“I, too, have followed the saint to this place to offer my services!”

“How could a noble lady be sent to such a filthy, lowly place alone!”

“We brought only three carts filled with donations and relief supplies. Please tell the beggars to gather! Hot ha! Today is the day they ride.”

“I would go to any place more shabby than this if the saintess was there!”

The young men talked eagerly, each trying to win Dolores' favor.

But the coldness in Dolores's eyes as she received their envious glances was unbearable.

When Dolores walked toward the front without answering, the young men thought they had her permission to follow.

“Thanks to the saint, I've never been to a place like this before. I've only seen backward neighborhoods like this in books, but it's a refreshing experience.”

“Haha, I thought that only skinny, dirty people would live in the slums, but there are still people living there. I didn't realize it. I guess you have to experience things to know them.”

“But looking at the kids walking around, they're wearing nicer clothes and shoes than I thought. Are they really poor? They don't look that different from the kids in the middle class neighborhood. Hmm, aren't they a little too extravagant, these people.”

“Oh, I don't know if I'm paying too much for this donation. I wonder if these people will lose the will to stand on their own.......”

They had their servants bring in carts full of donations and relief supplies.

Eventually, Dolores arrived at the temporary barracks where the patients were gathered.

Boldly, she slipped through the curtain and went inside.

But the young men following her pause and hesitate.

“Is it safe? There must be a lot of plague victims in here.”

“Ugh. If they move it, I'll have to.... I'm a third generation nobles”

“It doesn't matter, the saint will fix it!”

“The brave get the beautiful! I'm coming!”

Some of them turn away in fear.

Some took a deep breath and bravely stepped out into the barracks.

Those who followed Dolores into the barracks had to cover their noses as they gagged.

The smell of sweat, blood, vomit, piss, and shit everywhere, the foul breath and body odor of unwashed patients, and the air unpleasantly warmed by elevated body temperatures.

Visions of red death floated like ghosts through the thick vapor of filth.

The stench and foul heat, combined with the moans and cries that came from everywhere, made the barracks seem like a living tomb itself.

“Uh...... uh uh uh...... ”

Where did the second and third generation of nobles, young people who inherited inheritance at a young age and became wealthy, encounter such a terrible and desperate sight?

...Chulp!

Water poop poured out by the patient next to him fell to the floor.

The shards splattered and stuck to their shoes and pants, and they ran out of the barracks, screaming at the top of their lungs.

“Ew! It stinks! It's filthy! How dare you...!?”

“How much do these shoes cost!”

“Priests! Priests! Treat me first! Treat me first! Get out! I'm plagued!”

“Open the door! Tell them to get out of the way! I'm getting out of here!”

Before she could take a breath of the air in the barracks, the entire group of young men fled.

Saintess Dolores looked at them with a pitying gaze.

“...I knew it.”

Dolores' beauty had long been well known.

Within her family, outside of it, and at the Academy.

Wherever she went, the eyes of men followed.

No man dared openly flirt with the noble saintess, but she couldn't help being the object of his gaze, as if she was always yearning for something.

Whenever she went out to volunteer during the academy's vacations, or during her free time, there were always men like that following her.

They were disgusted by the sight of the sick, sometimes openly expressing their contempt and disgust.

Sometimes they would secretly turn the sick away behind their backs.

So Dolores distrusted the men who followed her because of her beauty.

If she were to become ugly, if her body were to be covered in such filth and stench, wouldn't they evaporate around her?

And it is disrespectful to leave it and come to the sacred relief site with a special heart.

In the fierce scene of life and death, there should be only one mind, the mind of the patient.

Absolute goodness. Pure selflessness. Dogmatic sacrifice and service. Kindness and affection.

These are the things closest to the grace and love of God.

St. Dolores set her heart on being a martyr and a seeker.

She entered the depths of the barracks with an even more reverent attitude.

The deeper she went into the barracks, the more foul odors and unclean heat she encountered.

Cries and groans of agony mingled with the dancing of the red death, creating a grisly scene.

Dolores drew on what little holy power and stamina she had left and made her way to the farthest reaches of the barracks, to the quarantine area where the sickest patients were kept.

From here, even veteran priests would struggle.

And then.

“...!”

Dolores's eyes went wide.

The innermost barracks, where he'd expected to find nothing but misery and desolation, was surprisingly alive with activity.

Sure, the suffering patients were still there, but....

“Hurry up and get more saline!”

“Yikes, it seems that divine power isn't the only skill in the real world, hurry up and get me a scalpel!”

“...Ohhh. What a skill.”

The surrounding priests are all admiring with their mouths half open.

It was a very different attitude from the overworked and depressed officers in the other barracks.

The hardest places bring out the most vibrant life.

A man fighting alone in the dirtiest, fiercest, most inhospitable places.

Even though he is covered with filth all over his body, he examines the patient's condition without any hesitation and silently gives first aid despite the curses and curses he spat out carelessly out of pain.

The Hound of the Night.

He was bustling among the patients, directing the priests.

Chapter 81

The Saintess (5)

◆

The priests of Quovadis have come together and prayed day and night, and all of Phase III has been successful.

The essence of divine power, capable of cleansing a large area of plagues with a single drop.

Three drops of this extremely concentrated holy water were made as a backup.

Plany de la Verge (Saintess's Tears).

Just one drop was enough to uproot all the plagues in the slums.

Dolores recited a prayer of blessing and thanksgiving over the three final drops of holy water.

[Behold, all of you. Here is a woman with her only son. Do you know the grief of a mother who sees her son hanging? I, the unfortunate one who had to raise the Son of God, howled from that night to the next, and it is so painful that my heart does not follow me. This day, O my beautiful and excellent son, shall be the most bitter and sorrowful day for me...]

The epic written by the first saintess weeping shines by consoling all the holy sacrifices in this world.

Then three drops of holy water began to emit a bright light.

Archbishop Mozgus bowed respectfully and placed the small glass jar containing them on a tray.

Dozens of bishops then followed him in carrying the holy water.

It was to be stored in a solid underground vault deep inside the official residence of Saint Mecca branch of the Quo Vadis family.

Soon, a crowd of priests gathered in the main building of the Quovadis family to watch the procession.

“....”

Dolores felt the awkwardness and discomfort in the air.

The Holy City of Quovadis had recently been in the midst of a civil war, and here were the two leading factions, the Old Covenant and the New Covenant, all in one place.

The plague, the Red Death, was a huge problem.

Suddenly, a middle-aged man with a grave and sleek appearance looked at Dolores.

“Come closer. My Nymphet, my daughter.”

Dolores hesitated slightly at the words, then lowered her eyes respectfully.

“...Yes, father.”

With that, she walked with slow, small steps to stand in front of the man.

Dolores' eyes took in his face.

'Humbert Humbert L Quovadis.

A man who holds the title of Cardinal, the de facto highest dignity of the Old Order, a position so exalted that there is no place higher except for the Pope.

He reached out and stroked Dolores's head once, lightly.

“You've made a great dedication this time.”

“You are flattering me.”

Dolores was very careful with her father.

It was an uncharacteristic demeanor for a father-daughter duo, but it was also commonplace in large families, so no one thought it odd.

Humbert, on the other hand, recognized Dolores' demure demeanor and nodded.

“Very well. Give me a report on what's been going on.”

“ ... I've been working on a report, can I give it to you right away?”

“'Better say it out loud. Writing is stiff.”

Dolores nodded silently at Humbert's words.

“We'll use the first batch of 'Saint's Tears' to cleanse all the waterways that run underground in St. Mecca.”

“Have you found the source of the plague?”

“Yes. It was an unregistered well high above the slums.”

Dolores was a born investigator.

She was a member of the Academy's detective club when she was a first-year student.

Dolores focused her investigations on slum patients, mostly children, and was able to secure a number of testimonies of ghostly sightings at a well.

When the children claimed that a ghost had cursed the well, Dolores went to investigate.

Sure enough, the well was heavily contaminated with plague, and he found a glass jar in which the killer had allegedly placed the plague bacteria.

What's more.

“And while investigating the area, we found a suspicious object.”

This is where the report stops.

At Humbert's questioning look, Dolores pulled out the evidence, wrapped in a clean cloth.

Humbert's eyes widened at the sight of it.

“Is this ...?”

A single dagger.

With a large snake emblazoned on it, it was unmistakably the symbol of Leviathan.

Also lying next to it was a button.

A golden button with a scythe and hammer on it, clearly the mark of the tycoon bourgeois.

“Where did you get these?”

“They fell in different places by the well.”

Then Cardinal Humbert's eyes dart around rapidly.

In his mind, the cause-and-effect chain was already being put together.

“ ...You said that the structure of the plague seemed to be artificially created.”

To create a plague of this magnitude, not only would it require an intimate knowledge of poisons, but it would also require huge research funds.

BANG!

Cardinal Humbert stomped his foot once, hard.

The white marble floor cracked and the two stone pillars around him crumbled.

“I declare a crusade! How dare you, you lowly vipers, and mistresses dare to blaspheme...... !”

Even the Emperor bows to the will of the Quovadis, so how dare these lowly poison-making, money-grubbing creatures make such a challenge!

Indeed, there was an undercurrent of strife among the seven families of the empire.

“....”

Dolores remained silent, her mouth agape.

Then, something came out of Cardinal Humbert's mouth that made her eyes widen.

“ ...Did you say hound of the night?”

Humbert said, his handsome face contorting.

“He's suspicious, too. Take him in and put him before the Inquisition. Make him spit out everything he knows.”

At this, Dolores visibly panicked.

Her calm, cool demeanor crumbled in an instant.

She looked like any other sixteen-year-old girl and shouted urgently.

“He's not guilty!”

“...?”

Dolores suddenly protested, and Humbert's expression hardened for an instant.

“...Him?”

Humbert looked down at Dolores in disbelief.

“Daughter, what are you saying...?”

Dolores, the daughter who had always moved so dutifully, without a word of protest.

She had been a good daughter who had never gone against her father's wishes since she was born, except for her enemies in the New Order.

But what about now?

“....”

Dolores met Humbert's gaze, her fists clenched and shaking.

It was as if he was determined to defend the existence of the Hound of the Night.

“There's no way a man so dedicated to the poor could be evil!”

Dolores had heard the testimonies of many patients.

A man who stayed up all night to see them, saying over and over again that he was sorry for what he had done.

A man who used divine powers, albeit weak ones, and who gave away all his possessions to his patients.

'Why did he say he was sorry to his patients?'

For not being able to cure them sooner or more? If that was the case, Dolores felt strongly about it.

She had felt sorry for sick people every time. Then others would ask her what she was sorry for. Or rather, why would someone who should be grateful be sorry?

But even so, Dolores was sorry. I always felt sorry for everyone.

And the Hound of the Night understood that. Empathized with her.

She remembered a conversation she'd had with the Night Hound not long ago.

'I was lucky enough to be born with divine powers, but I'm weak in body, mind, and faith. Someone as strong as you should have been born with these powers....'

Why did God choose her to be a saint? There are plenty of other people with strong faith who don't have divine powers. Why did he give her the undeserved title of saint?

The Night Hound turned to Dolores, her head bowed and weeping.

'The very fact that you are so distressed and sorry must be why the gods chose you. It must be the love of the gods you speak of that shines through in the lowest, fiercest places.'

Dolores couldn't help but sigh softly.

The words were comforting, as if spoken by a veteran saint who had seen all the ups and downs.

This advice hit her like a knock on the door from her future self to her present self.

Like a wise old saint from the classical era, or a big sister to emulate and follow.

Watching the hounds of the night, she felt a little like that.

'When I get older, will I be able to say the same words you just said?'

'...Perhaps you will be.'

He answered strangely, giving Dolores a faint glimpse of trust.

The sixteen-year-old girl admired that.

Perhaps that's why she was so adamant about the Hound of the Night's innocence in front of her father, Cardinal Humbert.

But.

“....”

The more vigorously Dolores defended herself, the harder Humbert's expression hardened.

Then Humbert motioned to a number of bishops.

“Prepare for an urgent arrest. We will meet and question him.”

Dolores's pleas were to no avail.

Humbert strode off, his demeanor even more murderous than before, and headed for the chambers where the Hound of the Night was supposed to be staying.

Dolores followed Humbert in a panic.

He was ready to throw himself down and wrap his arms around the Night Hound if he had to.

...But.

“!?”

Everyone standing in front of the cabin couldn't help but open their eyes wide.

Whirring.

An empty cabin. The curtains swallowed the wind coming in through the broken glass window and puffed up like ghosts.

A hound of the night, long gone.

The priest's urgent shouts from downstairs gave away the situation.

“There's trouble! A drop of the saint's tears has gone missing!”

The moment.

“...Aah!”

Dolores opened her mouth in silence.

Now he had a vague idea of why he had come here.

And the vague certainty that now that he had served his purpose, he would never see him again.

As Humbert and the paladins fussed and organized a pursuit party, Dolores stared out the window into the darkness.

The empty rooms, the broken windows, and the cold breeze brought the reality back to him.

...Thud!

His heart sank once more.

It was a different beat than the last.

Chapter 84

The Illiad (1)

◆

It had been several days since Vikir had returned to Ballak's village.

The Red Death had been completely uprooted, but its aftermath was far from over.

Though freed from the horrors of the plague, many were weak from dehydration and upset stomachs, and much nourishment was needed for the sick.

So the unaffected warriors hunted hard for food for their families and friends.

Vikir and Aiyen were among them.

“...Shhh. Found it.”

Aiyen was the first to spot the prey.

Vikir's senses were sharpened, and he knew where it was.

Two years ago, when Aiyen would say, “Look, there it is!” and point to it with his finger, Vikir would say, “Where? I don't see it.”

But now Vikir is almost as good at spotting prey as Aiyen.

The prey Vikir and Aiyen have their eyes on is one they've met before.

Woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo-woo

On a branch, a snake swallows a large jaguar whole.

A mouth as big as a catfish, a bizarrely flat snout, razor-sharp teeth.

<Mushuhushu>

Danger Rating : A+

Size: 32 meters

Found in: Ridge 8, Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain

-Named 'Full-body Intestine Snake'.

A snake whose entire body is made up of intestines.

It boasts a large mouth and appetite that can swallow an elephant in one bite, and legend has it that the giant Mushuhushu, which has lived since time immemorial, can swallow an entire country.

They are famously silent as they crawl across the ground or swim through the water.

At first glance, you wouldn't think it was a snake at all.

Even compared to other common Mushuhushu, this old individual is more than twice as large.

They can reach up to 40 meters in length, weigh more than 5 tons, and have a mid-body bridle of up to 3 meters.

Considering that the average individual stops growing between 25 and 30 meters long, that's a lot of size.

Aiyen carefully examined the snake.

“His name is Ka'ah, and he's a rival to Gustav, the lizard from the swamp far away. There's no other creature in this neighborhood that can match him.”

Aiyen was right to be cautious.

The giant Mushuhushu named Ka'ah was not only huge, but it made no sound when it moved.

Its natural protective coloring, silent movements, and overwhelming strength and size would have been enough to keep it as the dominant force in a region.

But today it had met its match.

Vikir bared his fangs at the snake.

“You're old. It is time to repay the debt of the rainy season.”

Once before, he had raided a Ballak village.

It was a night of torrential rain. He came down the overflowing river and attacked Ballak's warriors.

Vikir had fought it with his Baskerville flesh, but he had been unable to win, and had only been able to chase it away.

By then, the water had risen so much that he too was being swept away.

“Now the water has gone down and he's regained his territory. He must have regained a lot of strength. Look, he's got a big belly.”

Aiyen pointed to the center of the giant python's body.

In addition to the jaguar that had just gone down its throat, the snake's stomach seemed to contain several other beasts.

I could tell by the way the snake's body was bulging in several places in the shape of a necklace of pearls.

Aiyen drew his bow.

“If we catch him, we can get the other meat inside, and since it's tenderized, it'll be perfect for feeding the patients.”

“I agree.”

Vikir nocked an arrow to his bow.

Aiyen gave Vikir a nudge and pulled the string.

“It takes a lot of muscle to draw a bow.”

No wonder, given the tension of the draw.

Archers actually need more arm strength than most blunt-weapon users.

Especially since Aiyen's bow has a unique construction, with five strings and up to ten arrows on the string.

Pulling this off requires at least several hundred kilograms of muscle strength.

Obviously, it's a much harder discipline than wielding a sword or mace.

And then.

Puff-puff-puff.

The aura-laden arrows fly out, aiming for Ka'ah's neck.

[...Shhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!]

By the time Ka'ah realizes it, the arrows are already lodged in her throat.

Pit.

Vikir draws his magic sword, Beelzebub.

Ka'ah immediately closed the distance, aiming for Aiyen, but Vikir had been waiting for that.

Vikir attacked with a barrage of arrows, but as soon as Ka'ah was close enough, Vikir sliced him under the chin with Beelzebub.

Snap.

The hard scales snapped in half and red blood spurted out.

At intermediate to advanced Graduator levels, the aura becomes thick and sticky, almost indistinguishable from blood.

Vikir continues to thrust his blade, dodging Kha'ah's dragon trim as it rampages around him.

At this point, Ka'ah tried to fight back.

[Woosh! Woosh!]

He gagged and threw up something.

Vikir recognized Ka'ah's intentions immediately.

“ ...It vomits out the prey in its stomach to increase its mobility.”

It was a typical attack pattern of snake-like creatures.

Once they have consumed a large meal, they can lie down and remain motionless for months, and if they need to make a quick getaway in the meantime, they will vomit up the food in their stomachs to lighten their bodies so they can escape.

Ka'ah had lost his territory for a while due to the flooding of the river during the rainy season and hadn't been able to feed much.

He has also burned a lot of calories floating down the river and fighting Vikir, so he must be starving.

As such, he's currently consuming a large amount of food to replenish his strength.

With a full stomach, his movements were naturally sluggish and slow.

[Gurgle, gurgle, gurgle].

Ka'ah wanted to vomit out all the huge chunks of meat in her stomach.

That alone would probably shed nearly two tons of weight.

But.

“No way.”

Aiyen's arrow interrupted Ka'ah's vomiting.

She fired another arrow, and another, and another, until it lodged near his uvula.

The target was the jaguar he had just swallowed.

Aiyen's arrows penetrated the scales that Vikir had split open, pierced the tough flesh, and lodged in the jaguar's body in the esophagus beyond.

It was as if giant spikes had pinned the jaguar's carcass to Ka'ah esophagus.

Naturally, the bodies of the other creatures Ka'ah tried to vomit up would only pile up underneath the nailed and immobile jaguar, unable to pass through the esophagus.

In the end, Ka'ah is left with a grotesque bloated neck, unable to expel the contents of her stomach.

Because of that, the movement became more unnatural, and even the view behind it was limited by the hood and ribs that swelled like that of a cobra.

In more ways than one, this was good news for Vikir, who had been aiming for the snake's vital points of attack, the back of the neck and under the chin.

...Kwasak!

Vikir stretched out Beelzebub and severed the end of Ka'a's spine, the nerve cord that connects his neck to his brain.

A gush of cerebral fluid, bone marrow, and blood gushes out.

Baskerville carnivorous, flesh-eating. The six ambush teeth burrowed into Ka'ah's body, relentless and persistent.

Pow, pow, pow, pow! Thud!

Vikir stubbornly pounded and pounded and pounded at the wounds that had been thrust into him.

He dug and dug and dug, tearing flesh, shattering bone, and severing nerve fibers.

Even. Aiyen had been aiming for Ka'ah's rear all this time.

Boom!

Arrow after arrow lodged in the snake's genitals.

“How's she doing?”

“....”

Vikir sighed inwardly at Aiyen's relaxed demeanor even in this critical moment.

And then.

...Thump!

The raging leaven snake, Mushuhushu, slammed its large body into the ground.

It had been a long time since he'd caught a big fish.

◆

The warriors of Ballak have gathered for a raid.

They have been working hard to nourish the sick.

Catfish, salmon, carp, and other fish fattened by the rainy season. Large lobsters and old lobsters from the Salt River. All sorts of nutritious mushrooms, roots, berries, and other ingredients were gathered together to make the soup.

The oxbear subadult that Ahun had caught earlier was his greatest achievement so far.

But the return of Vikir, Aiyen, and the wolf Bakira turns the tables again.

Ahun slapped Vikir on the back and laughed heartily.

“No matter what I do, I can't beat you! Hahaha!”

It took all of Ballak's warriors and wolves to lift and carry the giant snake.

The old king, who had long ruled this corner of the depht, was now reduced to a tattered mass of meat.

The lean meat was roasted, smoked, steamed, and stir-fried.

The bones made into broths, medicines, and other things.

The entrails and blood were boiled in water and made into soup.

The highly nutritious snake meat, stir-fried in oil and roasted until fatty and golden brown, was reliably restoring the patients' strength.

What's more, the meat of the other animals in Ka'ah's stomach was just tender enough to be eaten by the younger patients.

Everyone is grateful to Vikir, showing him respect and love.

But in the midst of all the attention, Vikir had other things on his mind.

“I'm glad I caught Mushuhushu. It paid off.”

The jackpot had been won.

Vikir's eyes lit up as he saw Mushuhushu's soul occupying one of the three orbs of the magic sword Beelzebub.

<Binge Fly 'Beelzebub'>/ Awl

-1 slot: Burn – Cerberus (A+)

Slot -2: Silent Heel – Mushuhushu(A+)

Slot -3: Sacrum – Oxbear(A)

Mushuhushu Kaa's move is in.

Vikir's passive is Silent Hill, which replicates the snake's ability to make no sound when it moves.

“...Silent Heel.”

Even if you're just walking around, you can turn on your heels to create the same effect as if you were walking on eggshells.

This was a deceptive ability that could be incredibly helpful for survival in dephts, and even more so for assassinations, stealth, ambushes, and even journaling.

Furthermore, Vikir's ability to shoot a bow would prove invaluable in the future.

“It must be similar to the sound-killing skill that Adolf the Mad used in the past.”

Once, when Adolf attacked Ballak's hunting party to retrieve a Camus, silencing magic came in very handy.

Vikir nodded as he watched the beads at the base of Beelzebub's hilt glow red from the spirit of Mushuhushu.

Just then.

A voice drew everyone's attention, including Vikir's.

“The shaman has finished his ritual!”

The sentry shouted, and the mood in the village suddenly turned sour.

The Red Death had just begun, and the mysterious Ah'Heman, who had entered the temple to offer sacrifices and heal the sick, had finally emerged.

Chapter 85

The Illiad (2)

◆

Ah'Heman stepped down from the altar after a long ceremony.

His body was drenched in sweat from the nonstop sacrifices he had been making for the past few days.

As he descended from the altar, he saw that the entire village was deserted and laughed.

“ ... Must have gotten the plague by now.”

In truth, he had known beforehand that the Red Death was coming to Ballak.

Stranger things have happened. After all, it was Ah'Heman himself who helped Leviathan unleash the Red Death on the jungle.

In fact, he had been in contact with the outside world for quite some time.

Whether it's helping the Leviathans conduct clinical trials of new drugs or poisons on unknowing natives in the water, or aiding and abetting bourgeois families in their unfair trade practices.

In exchange for Ah'Heman's secret supply of natives to test poisons and medicines on, the Leviathans would freely give him new poisons or new medicines, which in turn would establish the authority of the shaman.

The shaman's authority was established by secretly releasing a poison to poison a target and then using the medicine to cure the target to gain their trust.

Sickness and medicine.

If someone didn't obey him, he would secretly poison them and make them sick.

Not only does this poison the patient, but also his friends and family.

In the close-knit atmosphere of the Ballak, this was only natural.

Only when the patient's life seemed to be in danger would Ah'Heman step in.

He would perform a convincing ritual, unleash a potion, and cure the patient, and his family and friends would become his devoted followers.

The man's authority is unquestioned, and his family and friends bow before him.

Recently, he has felt the shaman's authority waning, and he is on the verge of a crisis.

The younger ones, including the chief's daughter, Aiyen, had never been sick or poisoned before, so they didn't know how to respect the shaman's authority.

This had been made worse by the recent arrival of the Stranger, an unwelcome newcomer from the Empire.

Young people would go hunting without the blessings of the shaman, and other rituals were considered unnecessary and superstitious.

Then came a proposal from the Leviathan family.

“I'm thinking of conducting a large-scale pestilence experiment on the water.”

Ah'Heman swallowed hard at the words of the Leviathan's messenger, who was shrouded in a black cloak.

The Leviathan's messenger gave him the pathogen of the Red Plague and his antidote.

He was to spread the plague when the time was right, and the antidote when the time was right.

Through this trial, Leviathan hoped to control the population of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain natives and accumulate clinicopathological data to break new ground.

By actively cooperating, Ah'Heman sought to elevate the authority of the shaman on the land.

So he secretly unleashed the Red Death into the river and drowned countless people in it.

Now that the plague has struck and everyone is wandering in the wilderness, he will make a grand entrance, release the antidote, put the situation to rest, and enjoy the power of a chieftain.

Even the cocky youngsters who had looked down on him would now look up to him with respect and awe.

'...I've even infected my granddaughter, just in case there was any doubt.'

The situation was perfect: he had made his own granddaughter a plague victim to avoid suspicion that he had deliberately released the poison and set himself up.

This was Ah'Heman's idea.

...?

As he walked to the center of town, he couldn't help but scratch his head.

The village is overwhelmingly deserted.

The sick, their families, and friends are inherently vulnerable, looking for a place to lean on.

They must have pinned all their hopes on the ritualist, but no one came to greet them.

“Are they all gone already?”

Ah'Heman frowned. Had the plague been stronger than expected and killed all the Ballak?

That would be a problem. They should only be sick to the point of death. One must be alive to become a follower.

Ah'Heman stitched the sack containing the antidote he'd made in Leviathan to his side, then quickly crossed the town square.

But the barracks around him were deserted.

Only a frog croaked in a drained pool on the floor.

Then.

Ah'Heman froze in place.

Thick smoke was rising from a corner of the village.

And he could see every face he knew huddled there.

All the people of Ballak were there, all together.

Laughing and chatting merrily, picking at the heaps of meat.

“????”

Ah'Heman's mouth dropped open.

How? How could they be so well, when he'd surely seen them in the throes of red death just moments before?

He rubbed his eyes with the back of his hand, but it didn't change anything.

What's more, the woman in front of him, stirring the boiling pot with a ladle, is none other than his granddaughter, Aheul!

Ah'Heman's jaw drops even further when he realizes that his granddaughter is completely healed.

He turns his back on the unbelievable.

He runs at the moonlight, crosses the village boundary, and heads for the water source-the same river where he released the Red Death.

“...Huck, huck!”

Running like the wind, he arrived at the water source in the blink of an eye and was once again horrified.

The water source, which should have been contaminated by the Red Death, was still flowing with clear water.

The white salt sandbar is still there, as are the carp swimming up the waterfall.

Monkeys that should have been infected and killed by the Red Death are hopping around in the trees, and the children of the other tribes who came to catch the carp look healthy.

There was no sign of death anywhere.

“'No way, no how, how...!'”

Ah'Heman pulled at his hair.

The moment.

“Why, are you surprised to see so many of them alive?”

There was a jab that cut deep into his lungs.

He turned his head, furious.

Then a boy appeared behind him.

Vikir. His red eyes glowed at Ah'Heman.

◆

Meanwhile.

Vikir had led all of Ballak's warriors here, including Aiyen and Ahun.

Aiyen remembered clearly what Vikir had told them.

“As soon as the ritual is over, Ah'Heman will check on the villagers, and when he sees that they are well, he will run right back here.”

Because he was the one who sprayed the red death across the jungle.

Vikir had heard of Ah'Heman's misdeeds before his regression.

He couldn't remember Ah'Heman's name, but he could at least recall that he had a contact in Ballak who had spread the Red Death, and that the contact was an old man in the position of shaman.

“The enemy and half the natives of the Black Mountains were killed then.”

To fulfill his greed, Ah'Heman waited for the plague to reach its peak.

He planned to appear at just the right time and become the savior of the entire jungle.

But Ah'Heman missed the mark.

The plague had spread out of control, and most of the patients were dying in droves.

The carnage that followed was so horrific that it was recorded in the history of the empire.

It was the helpless and weak civilians who were dying at the hands of the vested interests.

Though the proper use of poison and medicine is a shaman's means of control, Ah'Heman had crossed the line. And for a long time.

“...What is it?”

Ah'Heman glared at Vikir with wary eyes, but he did nothing.

All of Ballak's warriors had already surrounded him.

Young and old alike, they were all staring at him. With murderous eyes.

It was maddening to Ahmed, who expected to be looked upon with respect.

“How did they cure the plague?”

Ah'Heman was at a loss for words.

Then.

Someone stepped in front of him.

His face went white as he recognized the man.

The Night Fox, chieftain of the Ballak. Akwilla stared down at Ah'Heman with a fierce glare.

She held a piece of paper in her hand, an official document that she had personally obtained last night when she traveled to the Empire.

“Holy House Quovadis has declared a crusade against Extremist Leviathan, accusing him of artificially developing and releasing a plague known as the Red Death. This is a declaration demanding the truth about the Red Death.”

“Is that so, and why did you send it to me...?”

“Shaman. You think it's strange, don't you, why the plague that the Leviathans have been studying has broken out here in Dephts?”

“I, I, I don't know. I just came out of the altar holding a sacrifice for the complete recovery of the tribe members.......”

Then Akwilla raised her hand, interrupting Ah'Heman.

She exchanged a glance with Vikir beside her before speaking.

“None of that. I'd like to see what's in that sack at your waist.”

Chapter 86

The Illiad (3)

◆

Ah'Heman was panicking.

His plan to release the antidote as soon as he finished the ritual, cure everyone, and become the hero of Ballak had been derailed from the start.

He had hoped to earn everyone's respect, but it hadn't worked out that way.

Most of Ballak's warriors looked at him with disdain.

“...?”

But he was still puzzled.

He didn't know how the Red Death had been cured, but should he be receiving such hostile stares just because the shaman's ritual hadn't worked?

It didn't help, but the reactions were too cold for that.

But.

Ah'Heman's questions were answered by Akwilla's next words.

“None of that is necessary. I want to see what's in that sack at your waist.”

For a moment, his heart sank.

Ah'Heman barely held on to his mind, which was slipping away.

What could it be? Why would the chief want to see the sack at his waist, and at this time?

It's hard to say unless you know something.

“...Did you even notice?”

As the person responsible for spreading the red death in the waters, it was bound to make his stomach burn.

Turning to Ah'Heman, Akwilla urged him on.

“What are you doing? Get that sack out of my sight.”

The chief's authority is absolute. Once the order is given, there is no appeal.

But the old shaman was so flustered that he denied the chief's authority.

“I can't show you this, I can't show you this!”

He was so flustered that he didn't know what he was talking about.

But the consequences were heavy.

Before he could finish, the faces of all the warriors stiffened.

The younger warriors sighed and shook their heads, and the older ones furrowed their brows.

The warriors' respect and loyalty to their chieftain runs deep, regardless of generation, so there was no way Ah'Heman could look good.

“He's a creep, and I'm going to take this opportunity to make him pay!”

An impatient Aiyen stepped forward.

“Open that sack at once!”

Someone stepped forward before her.

Ahun. Ahman's grandson, he was the first to step forward and open his palm in front of Ah'Heman.

While Aiyen stood stunned by the unexpected sight, Ahun turned to Ah'Heman and spoke firmly.

“There can be no disobedience to the chieftain's word, and if you do not open that sack immediately....”

Ahun said, pulling an arrow from his waistband and nocking it.

Then Ah'Heman's thick eyebrows shot up.

“You rascal!”

“....”

But Ahun's eyes never wavered.

Something must have changed in his mind as he watched helplessly as his sister Aheul died of the Red Death.

Soon, many of the warriors were booing at Ah'Heman.

“Give us the sack now!”

“Show us what's inside!”

“You traitor, you're the culprit!”

As the accusations poured in, Ah'Heman's face contorted more and more horribly.

Then.

“Come on, look! Look what's inside!”

He snatched the sack from his waistband.

Then he flung it into the river that flowed beside the fire.

Many of the warriors paused for a moment.

An eerie silence.

Ah'Heman looked back at Akwilla with a triumphant smile.

“Oops! This old man had tremor, so he dropped his sack into the river...... ?”

He stammered out an excuse, then paused.

Something was about to go wrong.

As if on cue, the warriors chattered amongst themselves and glanced to one side.

There was Vikir, arms crossed and mouth closed.

Akwilla looked back at him and said.

“Indeed. You were right. You really are throwing the sack into the river.”

“...What?”

Ah'Heman opens his mouth in disbelief.

Just then.

“Chief, I found it!”

Suddenly, someone's head pops up from the surface of the river.

A Ballak warrior, who had been lurking in the water earlier, quickly scoops up the leather sack that Ah'Heman had dumped.

The sack, though waterlogged, was still half full.

“Huh! No!”

Ah'Heman jerked, but the sack was already soaked by the time he reached Akwilla's hand.

“....”

Akwilla peered into the sack.

It was half-floating in the water, but full of white powder.

Akwilla turned to Ah'Heman.

“This is the antidote for the Red Death.”

“....”

“Why is this coming out of your hand?”

Ah'Heman mouthed the words, but didn't answer.

Then Akwilla nodded again.

“Indeed. You were right again.”

This time, she looked back at Vikir.

When Ah'Heman shook his head, Akwilla threw the white powder on the ground.

“It's just flour, it doesn't do anything.”

“What!”

“I told you that you would believe this to be an antidote, and by the looks of your surprise, I'm right.”

Ah'Heman's expression turns to disbelief as he realizes that the powder he's holding is just flour.

“That can't be right, that must be the antidote....”

“You have been deceived by the Leviathan family.”

Vikir said, stepping forward.

The Leviathans had used a foolish native spy to spread the plague without an antidote.

I saw through his power lust and ambition.

The mood of the warriors grew somber as everything Vikir had said before came true.

Ah'Heman made a desperate plea.

“I, I don't know, it's just flour, just like he said!”

“Then why did you hesitate earlier when I asked you to show me the sack, and why did you come to this water source where the Red Death first began?”

“Shut up, why should I tell you that!”

Vikir demanded, and Ah'Heman raised the lump in his throat.

But the situation wasn't going to get any easier for him.

The situation was not in his favor, however, because Vikir provided even more incriminating evidence.

From Vikir's arms came two letters.

There were two handwritings on them, one in terrible cursive and unrecognizable, the other in a fairly neat typeface.

Vikir opened his mouth to speak.

“These are the letters between the Leviathans and you.”

The evidence was conclusive.

One of the two letters was unmistakably written in Ah'Heman's handwriting.

The eyes of all the warriors alternated between the letters and Ah'Heman.

Ah'Heman shouted in frustration.

“It's a lie! I never wrote that letter!”

But no one believed him.

Several old elders testified that the handwriting on the letter was indeed Ah'Heman's.

“Aaahhhhhhh! It's true! I'm innocent! He's framing me!”

Ah'Heman pointed at Vikir and jumped up and down.

But Vikir, the target of the scolding, just laughs quietly to himself.

Because the accusation is true.

“And here I am, thanks to my Chihuahua.”

Vikir recalls an incident from two years ago.

'Mr. Chihuahua writes very well.'

'Nothing. Since I was born, I haven't seen anyone who handles handwriting better than me. Every time the archons ask me to sign it, so I'm good at imitating other people's handwriting.......'

'Can't I learn to do that?

'Of course I can teach you, it would be my honor!

'Thank you. Then I'll ask you whenever I have time.'

It was rewarding to learn the art of handwriting forged from him diligently when I was a deputy magistrate in Underdog City.

It was a skill that would come in handy when it came to propaganda.

'Originally, agitation is easy and explanation is difficult.'

Vikir stared at Ah'Heman, who was genuinely pacing in frustration.

Meanwhile, Akwilla spoke up.

“We should see if anyone in the Leviathan family has this handwriting.”

But that would be a tall order. It would be impossible to investigate one of the seven great houses of the Empire.

So, naturally, the mood within Ballak turned toward denouncing Ah'Heman.

“Traitor!”

“You almost got my wife killed!”

“And my children!”

“Kill him, hang him!”

Public opinion was turning very badly.

Even Ahun, his grandson, was giving him the cold shoulder, and there wasn't a single person here who was on his side.

Ah'Heman gritted his teeth.

There was no proof anyway.

If the white powder in the sack turned out to be just flour, there was no point in executing him if he insisted on denying it until the end.

Holding out, however dirty and deadly, was the only way to stay alive.

“...Enough, everyone, you're overreacting.”

That was the mood before Chief Akwilla opened his mouth.

Every warrior turned to look at him. Ah'Heman did the same.

Akwilla coughed a few times before speaking.

“If you look closely, there is no evidence. Everyone, I hope that this will no longer harm the shaman's honor. Isn't he a public servant who has been dedicated to the tribe for a long time.”

Then there was a murmur from all around.

Aiyen spoke up in exultation.

“Mother, no, Chief, do you mean to tell me that you're going to sweep this under the rug...?”

“Enough! Respect the shaman's authority! He has far more years of experience and dedication to the tribe than you do! Be polite!”

At Akwilla's stern words, Aiyen clamped his mouth shut.

Many of the warriors looked disgruntled, but the chieftain's words were absolute, and none of them spoke.

Ah'Heman, the one being defended, looked dumbfounded.

Why would the chieftain, who had so much disliked him, take his side?

But since this was the only way out, he could only bow flat to Akwilla.

“I can only be grateful for your kindness and wisdom.”

“It is nothing. It is only natural if you honor the traditions of your ancestors.”

Ah'Heman nodded, as if impressed.

Just then, Akwilla's eyes glowed deeply once more.

“How dare you allow young things who know nothing to tarnish your high honor?”

“Yes, thank you, Chief.”

“You have nothing to thank me for. You have a reputation to uphold, not only in our tribe, but in the entire Dephts.”

“Yes. What....”

“The honor and pride you carry on your shoulders must be very heavy, Cancer.”

“Yeah...?”

“So today, you were framed for something without evidence, so the wounds in your heart must be very great. No wonder. Because that supreme pride has been damaged.”

“...?”

Ah'Heman felt a little uneasy at the thick coating of gold.

As if on cue, Akwilla turned to face him.

“I am about to give my friend of many years, my valued colleague, the spiritual teacher of all the young men gathered here, the opportunity to defend his innocence, his honor, his pride! Do any of you have any complaints!”

“None ah-!”

Everyone who has guessed Akwilla's intentions cries out at once.

Vikir, who had heard it all before, stepped forward with a calm expression.

“...?”

Ah'Heman stumbles backwards as Vikir steps in front of him.

He looked like he didn't know what was going on.

Finally, Akwilla spoke firmly to him.

“If you are truly innocent, use this opportunity to defend the honor and pride you have earned. After all I've done for you, you won't take it away from me, will you?”

“ ...And you say opportunity?”

Anxiety flickers in Ah'Heman's eyes as he asks cautiously.

Then, Akwilla spoke.

“I command the Illiad.”

The Illiad was Ballak's unique way of resolving disagreements, using force to end the conflict in the winner's favor.

The color drained from Ah'Heman's face as he heard this.

Vikir, on the other hand, laughed quietly.

Evidence, proof, it didn't really matter.

It was all just paving the way for this game.

Chapter 87

The Illiad (4)

◆

“This, the Illiad?”

Ah'Heman's expression hardened.

“The Illiad is a contest between warrior and warrior. It is a final, life-and-death struggle for honor in which neither side can back down.”

The chieftain Akwilla smiled gently and turned to Ah'Heman.

“Ah'Heman, great shaman of Ballak, you are a being of high pride and shining honor, a defender of time-honored traditions, as I have said before. Will you allow such pride, honor, and tradition to be compromised?”

Ah'Heman could not help but grit his teeth.

He wondered why the chieftain, who had always thought of him as an eyesore, had elevated him.

It was all part of laying the groundwork to make the Iliad irresistible.

The veteran chieftain, Akwilla, is determined to use this opportunity to remove the power of the shamans, who have taken over the chieftaincy.

He has been using his daughter, Aiyen, to incite the young people to overthrow superstitions and old habits to keep the shamans in check.

His grandson, Ahun, didn't take sides either.

“Grandfather. You always said we should honor tradition. The Iliad is our Ballak tradition.”

“Shut your mouth, I know that!”

Ah'Heman gritted his teeth and turned his head.

Before him stood Vikir, his expression grim.

The enslaved prisoner of war had been transformed into a local hero in an instant.

In less than two years, a ragtag outsider had filled the position that Ah'Heman had longed for all his life.

Ah'Heman felt his clothes turn inside out.

His anger at Vikir flared up like a pillar of fire in an oil field.

“Good! I understand! I demand the Iliad from you!”

Hearing Ah'Heman's proclamation, Vikir nodded without a word.

It was a sign of acceptance.

Patriarch Akwilla spoke in a low voice that only Vikir could hear.

“Do you think you win...?”

“If you ask me to do it, I'll do it.”

Vikir has been a hound of the Baskervilles for over fifty years, before and after his regression.

He was used to being someone else's sword.

Akwilla smiled with satisfaction at Vikir's answer.

It felt as reassuring as a sharp knife in his hand.

“Very well, I believe you, son-in-law.”

“...?”

For a moment, Vikir thought he saw a reflection of Adolf Morgue in Akwilla.

Then, all the warriors, young and old, united to fight.

A place where two warriors would fight for their souls.

All the warriors watched, their hands sweating.

Ah'Heman thought to himself.

“That's right. This is good. I'll take this opportunity to shake off all my bitterness and reclaim my place.”

He raised his searing eyes and glared at Vikir.

As if everything would go back to normal if only that thing in front of him were gone.

“The date is the full moon in three days,” Ah'Heman shouted like boiling magma deep inside an active volcano.

“The date is the night of the full moon in three days, the place is here, and I formally challenge you to the Iliad!”

For a moment, the warriors were stunned by the ferocity of Ah'Heman's words.

However, Vikir, who was the target of the killing, was so indifferent.

Only.

“Three days. Let's do it now.”

It's like he's just trying to get a chore done.

The warriors were once again impressed by Vikir's relaxed demeanor.

Ah'Heman, on the other hand, broke out in a cold sweat.

Three days of stealthy preparation had been undone.

Vikir knows this, which is why he hasn't given Ah'Heman time to think.

“That's what shamans do.”

He's trying to slow down the Iliad with his usual bravado, but it's no use.

Vikir, too, is a worn and tattered old man who has seen it all, but he is no match for Ah'Heman.

In fact, as a man who has lived through an age of destruction, he is superior to the old shaman in the art of conspiracy.

“The Iliad gives the challenger the right to choose the date and place, by tradition, doesn't it?”

At Vikir's words, Ah'Heman makes a pained sound.

He's the one who's always been vocal about the need to honor tradition, so he's at a loss for words when tradition is brought up in this situation.

Self-absorbed and self-absorbed, his own words are weighing him down.

Seeing this, Aiyen chuckled.

“As expected, Ah'Heman's is Ah'Heman.”

Aiyen muttered something accusatory, then turned his head to the side.

He saw his loyal subordinate, trusted ally, and close friend, the wolf Bakira, sitting stoically beside him.

Aiyen stroked Bakira's fluffy ears and leaned in close to whisper quietly.

“Go to the village and tell them to prepare to welcome the winner of the Iliad.”

The instructions were for those who remained in the village to prepare a reception for Vikir.

But.

“Don't do that.”

Vikir turned to Aiyen.

When Aiyen's eyes narrowed, Vikir turned his head and replied.

“If you get your hopes up, you'll always get the opposite result.”

It's hard to prepare for variables when you're so sure.

Vikir watched Ah'Heman grit his teeth in the distance.

He was a shaman, so there were many surprises in battle.

Vikir had fought countless shamans, warlocks, alchemists, and the like throughout the Age of Destruction, and almost every time, there had been a surprise counterattack.

In the end, Vikir was always the victor, but they always had a hand they kept hidden just before they died, and Vikir was used to that.

“I don't let my guard down even one percent.”

A hound does his best to catch a rabbit.

This is especially true when the prey is an old raccoon.

Vikir reviewed all the information he had before the regression, checking off each of the possible contingencies.

Seeing Vikir's cautiousness, Aiyen became cautious as well.

She wanted to be as helpful as possible, so she told him everything she knew about Ah'Heman.

There came a point in the story where Vikir's ears perked up for a moment.

“Wait a minute. Tell me about that part again.”

Seeing Vikir's interest, Aiyen opened his mouth excitedly.

“Which part are you referring to, Ah'Heman's taste in underwear colors? According to the boy in charge of the laundry, he prefers tight, leopard-print pelts....”

“ ...Before that.”

“Oh, you mean his birth background?”

Aiyen whispered to Vikir, repeating what she had heard from Akwilla.

At this point, it was a secret that no one knew except for Akwilla, Aiyen, and Ah'Heman himself.

“Ah'Heman is not a native of Ballak. He was originally a member of another tribe and was kidnapped as a child. He was probably around the same age as you, Vikir.”

Vikir was a little surprised to hear that.

He'd thought he'd been a native Ballak for generations before tradition got in the way, but he was actually an outsider.

I was even more surprised by what Aiyen said next.

“He went around saying that he was captured for son-in-law hunting, but...... In fact, he was taken as a slave. To the shaman at the time who enjoyed sodomy.”

Perhaps because he was an outsider who had been taken as a slave as a teenager, Ah'Heman saw himself in Vikir.

It was a kind of homophobia. ...

Since Vikir, who had been like that, followed all the ideal routes and became a hero respected by everyone, Ah'Heman's stomach was bound to get even worse.

“Anyway. He was a sex slave, waiting for an opportunity, and one day he killed a shaman and took his powers.”

Aiyen went on to recount the bloody struggle Ah'Heman went through afterward to fit into Ballak's society.

“He had no place in a Ballak society that valued physical strength, and he was despised for killing the shaman who had raised him, so he would do anything to be accepted by his people.”

He took on all the village's odd jobs, from scavenging human and wolf feces to driving in dangerous game and serving as bait.

It was not uncommon for him to rise at the crack of dawn and hold the shoes of the previous chieftain in his arms, warming them with his body heat.

At that time, to impress Akwilla, who was still a child, he put her on his back and crawled on all fours, imitating a dog.

And by the time ... he was accepted as a member of the tribe's society, his gray hair had already grayed.

As an old man, he couldn't help but notice the privileges of his youth that he hadn't been able to enjoy.

The blood, violence, and impulses that had been pent up in his youth, unleashed to their fullest extent, rose to the surface with a sense of compensation.

And so he sought to overthrow the authority of his chieftain, Akwilla, and devour Ballak, and the entire jungle.

Outside the walls, he even joined hands with the Imperial House of Leviathan!

Meanwhile, Vikir suddenly had a question.

“...So, what tribe was Ah'Heman originally from?”

“Hmmm. I don't know about that.”

Vikir nodded at Aiyen's answer.

It doesn't really matter at this point.

Meanwhile, Ah'Heman had been fidgeting nervously since earlier.

It only intensified when Vikir entered the battlefield for the Iliad.

Like a seasoned hound, Vikir takes his time, slowly, gradually, tightening the leash on his prey with each step.

Prepared for every eventuality, Vikir heads into battle.

But before the Iliad could unfold, a deadly twist occurred that even the mighty Vikir could not have anticipated.

...Boom!

A foot stamped the ground once behind him.

And then someone grabbed Vikir's wrist and yanked him backward.

Vikir turned his head.

“...!”

Lips brush against Vikir's lips.

Aiyen, whose head has shrunk in the last two years, stares up at Vikir with a ravenous gaze.

“Win and come back. I'll give you something better.”

She smirked and shoved Vikir in the chest.

Vikir thought about saying something in Moorish, but decided otherwise.

This isn't the most important thing right now.

Now.

...Cha-ang!

Beelzebub slices through the artery in his wrist, revealing his black teeth.

It was the moment when the leash of the Iron-Blooded Sword's Hound was released.

Chapter 88

The Illiad (5)

◆

The sword forests of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain are terrible.

Every leaf on every tree is a razor-sharp blade, and there is nothing that is not deadly, from the thorny bark to the roots.

And now, in the midst of this infernal jungle, two men were fighting for their lives.

Vikir and Ah'Heman.

They faced each other with swords at their hips and bows strapped to their backs.

A crowd of spectators formed a wide circle around them.

Though obscured by the dense foliage and vines, the Ballak warriors with good eyes and ears could see the fight hundreds of meters away.

Ah'Heman gritted his teeth.

“ ...You've only been running for two years.”

Vikir had only been acclimatized to the depht for two years.

He, on the other hand, was used to dealing with the terrain, a body that had lived here for nearly 70 years.

Some of the younger hunters were not even close.

“I'll make you regret choosing the jungle for the Iliad instead of the plains.”

Ah'Heman moved quickly through the jungle.

He ducked into a tree-root vine for cover and nocked an arrow to his bow.

“Hooray. Here's a good one.”

He crouched down and found something beneath the roots.

It was a large centipede with a red body and black legs.

He pulled out an arrow and nocked it in the centipede's head.

The centipede's head shattered, spilling its venomous brain matter onto the arrowhead.

Ah'Heman has also laid out vines on the ground that are translucent and hard to see, but unbreakable and strong enough to cut through.

If your opponent jumps on one, they're sure to get cut, and if they're lucky, they might even get their ankle amputated.

I also spread dry sand and fallen leaves over the muddy pit, where the ground is soft and you're bound to get stuck, and I dropped a few honeycombs, where the fierce bees are sleeping, ready to wake them up at any moment.

“Just wait and see.”

Ah'Heman gripped the poisoned arrow in his hand tightly, waiting for Vikir's figure to emerge from the dense foliage.

Just then.

“...Who are you waiting for?”

The cold voice touches his ears and he freezes.

A shudder rippled through his body.

He turns his head, barely holding on to his falling heart, and sees Vikir's expressionless face looming behind him.

“Uh, how!”

How did he get this far without making a sound?

But Ah'Heman can't bring himself to ask the question out loud.

Vikir has sliced the awl in his hand to the side.

Hit.

Vikir sliced through all the ankle-cutting vines that Ah'Heman had set up.

He scrambled backwards to get away from it, stepped in a puddle of mud he had hidden, and was up to his waist in water, dropping a few beehives in the process.

Weeeeeeeeeee-.

The homeless wasps vented their anger at Ah'Heman in the mud pit.

Vikir quietly backed away, while Ah'Heman flailed his hands in the mud, trying to swat the bees away.

Ah'Heman narrowly escapes death by diving into the mud for a long time.

But his body was already swollen with bee stings.

Meanwhile. Ah'Heman had just crawled out of the mud when Vikir climbed up a tree trunk and yawned.

“What the fuck!”

Ah'Heman hung the arrow in protest.

The centipede venom had been washed away when he fell into the mud, but the sharpness of the arrowhead was intimidating enough.

Boom.

The mud on the bowstring flies off in all directions.

A powerful arrow shot vertically, aimed at Vikir.

But.

Boom.

A crimson slash flew out, slicing Ah'Heman's arrow in two.

Before he could react, Vikir vanished like a ghost and landed on Ah'Heman's back.

Ah'Heman's eyes were gouged out, bleeding profusely.

Vikir's speed was one thing, but... if there was something more amazing.

“No sound!?”

Vikir was moving so fast, yet there was no sound.

Obviously, Vikir was moving at a tremendous speed in front of me, but I couldn't hear anything.

His feet crunching through the grass, splashing through the mud, breaking branches, stomping over stones and logs.

All of these sounds are inaudible. Or if they did, they were so faint that they were drowned out by the buzzing of grasshoppers around them.

“Mu, what tricks are you playing, you bastard!”

Ah'Heman fired arrow after arrow, but they only managed to hit a few Aman orangutans in the trees.

Then, Vikir's magic sword, Beelzebub, began to spit out a black aura.

The liquid aura, sticky as honey and tainted with blood, was an unmistakable indication of the Graduator's advanced level.

Ah'Heman was stunned by the level of aura that even Ballak's most seasoned veteran warriors could not easily manifest.

'This kid was this strong!'

It's a fighting power that doesn't match his age at all.

Ah'Heman was only too eager to retreat backwards.

But the hound's six teeth never let go of its prey.

Carnivorous, Baskerville.

Six ambush teeth lurked and leapt out, tearing at Ah'Heman's entire body.

What's more, wherever the blade's teeth grazed, a searing sting followed.

Moreover, a hot burning pain always visited the place where the teeth of the blade brushed past.

The infernal flames, visible only to Vikir's eyes, were burning directly into Ah'Heman's soul.

“Aaaahhhh!”

Ah'Heman shuddered in unintelligible pain.

It was natural to feel pain when one's flesh is cut by a sword, but the pain from Vikir's blade was strangely intense.

He had been struck by swords, spears, and arrows countless times in his nearly seventy years of life, but he had never felt such pain.

It was as if he had been cut open with a flaming knife, flesh by flesh, and even now the flames were burning through his skin, consuming his flesh and fat.

Of course, the Ballak warriors watching the spectacle were unaware of any of this, and could only squeal at the slightest cut, showing their contempt for Ah'Heman.

“Ugh!”

Ah'Heman eventually dropped the pretense.

Honor, pride, tradition, none of that matters now.

Ballak's warriors booed as Ah'Heman fled in disgrace, having challenged the younger warrior first.

Woo-woo-woo!

The chorus of accusations and jeers from across the dense foliage made it seem as if the entire jungle was condemning him.

He backed away in a huff and turned to fire another arrow at Vikir.

But he hadn't thought of that.

Vikir, too, had spent the last two years studying archery with Aiyen, and had become quite a skilled archer.

Ping-!

An arrow flew in a parabolic arc.

...Puck!

The arrow struck right into Ah'Heman's groin.

“Ugh!”

Ahmed's eyes flew open.

He strained his eyes so hard that the flesh around his eyes was torn and tears of blood flowed.

Then, clutching his groin, he collapsed and the leaves in front of him scattered.

Rustle.

Vikir walked out, his face expressionless.

“You coveted an oxbear's genitals, and now you've earned it.”

Two years ago, Vikir had demanded a decoction of the genitals of his hunted prey.

Remembering it, he bit his lip until it bled.

“You're playing with me!”

“I didn't mean to, you're not good enough to be my plaything.”

“Ugh... Ugh!”

With that, Ah'Heman staggered to his feet, dropping the sword and bow in his hand.

“...!”

Vikir felt things take a turn for the worse.

The wind shifted.

Dark mana was gathering around them.

They crackled sinisterly, converging on a single point. The palms of Ah'Heman's hands!

'...Good. A shaman, I see.

Vikir had been expecting a trick up his sleeve.

The man drew a number with his blood-stained palms and chanted a strange incantation.

The next moment, a dark current swept through the area, extending from his hands.

Crackle, crackle, crackle!

Vikir jerked back as he felt several individuals reaching for his ankles.

To his surprise, several figures stood in his way.

They were orangutan carcasses with rotting flesh and exposed bones.

Ah'Heman had used witchcraft to resurrect the corpses of the orangutans he had shot with his arrows earlier.

“It's like this. ...... Right. Was Ah'Heman from the Rokoko tribe?”

Vikir remembered what Aiyen had told him before they had begun the Iliad.

Ah'Heman was essentially an outsider, but it turns out he was from the Rokoko, a tribe of shamans.

Known to the natives of Depht as witchcraft, and to the Empire as a form of black magic, this bizarre practice of resuscitating the dead is one of them.

It was also the specialty of the shamanic Rokoko people.

In his haste, Ah'Heman raised the freshly dead orangutan zombies and skeletons to escort him.

“Heh heh... heh heh heh heh, the Iliad is unorthodox combat, it doesn't mean you have to fight with swords and bows!”

But in the physicality-oriented atmosphere of Ballak, Ah'Heman's behavior was frowned upon by many of the warriors.

It seemed that while all the warriors had little interest in spells, he had been diligently studying and mastering them on his own.

“Go! Go stop him! Buy me time to heal him!”

Ah'Heman called for the orangutans to block Vikir's path.

Orangutans are almost as tall as humans and can weigh up to 100 kilograms, which should be enough to buy them some time as meat shields.

Ah'Heman thought so.

But.

“Hmmm. Not as good as I thought.”

Vikir stamped his foot, still sounding unimpressed.

“...?”

Ah'Heman opens his mouth, wanting something.

Puh-lease!

Something shuts his mouth in an instant.

It's a tremendous impact that knocks him off his feet and onto his back!

The impact ripped the skin off his back, broke his spine, and dislodged all of his internal organs.

Not surprisingly, the orangutan carcasses next to him were also reduced to a pool of blood and crushed to the ground in an instant.

Only Vikir stood back, not making a sound, not making a move.

“????”

Ah'Heman looked up, saliva dripping from the corner of his mouth. Aside from the pain, he is at a loss for words.

His vision flips, and a giant shadow looms over him.

[Grrrr...]

The hulking creature pricked up its ears to see if it could see.

An old female oxbear thrusts her massive forepaws at Ah'Heman.

Chapter 91

The Ghosts of the Ancestors (3)

◆

A Ballak hero who fought the Empire as a single man.

A mythical being who struck fear into the hearts of even the Empire's greatest Swordmasters, unleashing a fury across the continent. The Bowmaster, the most powerful archer who ever lived.

She is Adonai.

Ever since the history of Ballak began to be written down, Adonai, the archer who was known to be the strongest, appeared in front of Akwilla, who was far from learning.

Short gray hair, parched skin on his face, sagging lips and clearly visible teeth.

Every time the black shroud covering the whole body swayed in a black aura, the large bow slung on the back was revealed.

It was a bowstring with a very pointed tip and emitted a very black color.

It had a strange appearance, like two legs of an insect that had been bent and connected.

“....”

Vikir stood still, staring at the Adonai before him.

It had been a long time since he'd been this close to a Master-level being, a being that touched the heights of the Supreme.

The power emanating from Adonai was as wild and vicious as Hugo Le Baskerville's.

Perhaps because he is a Death Knight, it feels even more so.

“...Author is Adonai the Archer.”

Terror of the empire, hero of the barbarians.

It was a strange feeling to see a figure I'd only heard about in jungle mythology.

But my wonder was short-lived.

The next moment, Adonai raised his great black bow.

There were no strings or arrows on the bow.

But as Adonai grasped the air with the opposite hand from the one that held the bow, a cool current of air formed a thin thread from tip to tip of the bow.

It's like a spider spinning a thread.

Sssssss...

To Adonai's surprise, the black air currents connected pole to pole of the bow.

Adonai snapped his fingers once, then released them.

Then, an arrow made of aura was created and nocked on the bowstring, which was also made of aura.

Quack!

Adonai pulled and released the bowstring, and an arrow of dark aura shot out.

“...!”

Vikir narrowed his eyes.

The speed was so fast that even Vikir, a Advance Graduator, couldn't see properly!

It was only through half instinct and half luck that Vikir was able to deflect the arrow by extending the Beelzebub on his wrist as far as it would go.

Boom!

Adonai's arrow flew on a trajectory deflected by Vikir's sword, and it punched a hole in a huge log.

Crunch! Quack!

Not only is the log pierced, but the cliffside rocks behind it crumble with a thunderous crash.

It was a sight to behold, as if they had been scattered by countless blades.

Adonai's arrows are monstrous creatures that devastate their surroundings with just a glance.

It would be unimaginable to face them head-on.

“...Hmm.”

Vikir furrowed his brow and drooled.

Despite the obvious deflection, his wrist was stiff and his arm tingled.

Beyond the torn muscles in his forearm, he must have cracked his wrist bone.

The liquid aura on Beelzebub was also torn to shreds.

Adonai's aura bolts have the density of extremely hard solids, the realm of a master.

No wonder it couldn't be defeated by a Graduator-class liquid aura.

Even.

Tsutsutsutsuts...

The log sniped by Adonai's aura began to wither and die.

The poison was strong enough to kill a giant tree that could have lived for hundreds of years in an instant.

Vikir's attention was drawn once more to the large black bow that Adonai held.

At first glance, it looks impossibly large and long, but it is solid and light, almost weightless.

Pointed at both ends and sprouting horn-like spikes in the middle, it looked like two insect legs glued together.

Vikir realized its identity at a glance.

“...The remains of Madam Eight-Legs.”

When I met Madam Eight-Legs the other day, I confirmed that all eight legs were attached, so it was probably made from fragments of her body before shedding her skin.

This reminded me of something Aiyen had once said.

“'Adonai was the only one who could stand toe-to-toe with the Madame of the Eight Legs. Now that you are a young Ballak, honor him. And pride in being her descendant.”

Adonai remembered that in the past, he had dueled Madam Eight-Legs and won.

The bow was made from her ruins, and her vile poisonous aura was imbued into the bow itself.

The fearsome black bow must have retained its poisonous power long after Adonai died and was buried with her.

“I'm in trouble.”

Vikir clicked his tongue.

He was up against a Swordmaster, or perhaps even a more difficult Bowmaster.

The Death Knight's flaw is that he attacks recklessly and haphazardly, which in close quarters can leave him open and vulnerable, but....

Poof! Pow! Quack quack quack!

In a long-distance fight, it becomes a unified offense.

Adonai fired off a series of aura arrows.

Dark solid auras, even poisonous ones.

They tore through Vikir's black liquid aura, tearing it to shreds.

Vikir loaded his aura onto Beelzebub and swung it long.

Baskerville Carnivore.

Six fangs drew a blackened trail of blood, but even so, it was pushed back.

Even a warrior of the Graduator's rank would be powerless against a master.

A liquid cannot defeat a solid.

However, the reason Vikir was still alive was due to the protection of the Styx River, the strength and mana regeneration of his body, and the power of the monster that the magic sword Beelzebub was sealing.

“...! ...! ...!”

Vikir had gained weight with Oxbear's sacroiliac spell, which allowed him to withstand Adonai's arrows without being knocked back.

But even the six ambush hits from the Baskervilles are not enough to stop Adonai's arrow showers.

Each of Adonai's arrows was stronger, harder, and more numerous than each of Vikir's teeth.

What's more, the aura of her bowstring and arrows never wore out or dropped.

Adonai was simply unleashing an endless barrage of the overflowing negative dimensional energy characteristic of Death Knights.

Boom! Crackle! Puck! Puck!

Deciding that a head-to-head battle was out of the question, Vikir swung his blade sideways to deflect the arrows, but was nonetheless gradually being pushed backward.

The large mana reservoirs of the Graduator were already running low.

The aura radiating from Beelzebub was popping like honey from a hammer whenever it came into contact with Adonai's aura.

Even his shaking wrists told him that he was at his limit.

There were many bad news reports coming from all over the body.

'...At this rate, I'll be an arrow in the quiver.

Vikir tried to move quickly to get out of the way, but Adonai was faster than Vikir,.

Closing the distance would be impossible as the arrows would fly like crazy, and opening the distance would be suicide against a Bowmaster level archer.

A sneak attack might have worked, but there's no way to win a head-to-head fight.

Of course, I don't mean how to win, but how to survive.

'...I need to kill at least Ah'Heman.'

But with Adonai standing firmly in his way, that was impossible.

All the warriors of Ballak fired arrows in unison, but they were all blocked by Adonai's shroud and the body of the black bow.

Just as Vikir was in the midst of thinking.

...Puck!

There was a kick to Vikir's cheek.

“Slave, to the side!”

Aiyen stretched out her long legs and shoved Vikir's head away.

Pow!

A black flash of light flew in a black trajectory to the place where Vikir's head was just a moment ago.

...PIT!

A long, thin gash appears on Aiyen's calf.

Meanwhile, Vikir wiped the blood from his forehead and said.

“Thank you. Better to die of a concussion than an arrow.”

“No time to slack off, here they come again!”

Aiyen reached out and grabbed Vikir by the nape of his neck.

An arrow of black aura struck the ground where Vikir's groin had been just moments before, tearing a deep hole.

“...You're aiming for the groin, too. So much for the rush of the male.”

Vikir smirked at Aiyen's narrowed eyes.

“'Not so fast. To the great Adonai.”

“For now, you're just Ah'Heman's puppet. After you have attained perfection.”

Aiyen quickly fed arrows into his bow.

A dozen arrows flew at breakneck speed, aimed at Adonai.

Then they broke off into different trajectories, each aimed at a different part of Adonai's body.

But.

Puff-puff-puff-puff-puff-puff!

With a flick of his hand, Adonai caught all ten arrows coming from ten different directions.

Woof!

As if that wasn't enough, he clenched his fist tightly, breaking all ten of the arrows and causing them to shatter.

“...Your hands must be big.”

Aiyen gritted her teeth as she saw the arrow fragments falling to the ground behind her.

Then, Adonai raised his black bow.

The bull's-eye was clear. Vikir and Aiyen in front of him.

Boom!

With a sound like a cannonball being fired, a sharp vortex shot out of Adonai's black bow.

It sliced through the air around them like a whirling blade.

Destruction and speed, unavoidable and unstoppable! Vikir and Aiyen prepared for battle.

Then.

Boom!

Someone deflected Adonai's dark power blast with their bare hands.

Kwagigik! Boom!

The frantically spinning blade aura was shattered by pure force.

Adonai's aura arrows turned into black air currents and scattered.

“...!”

Vikir and Aiyen looked up, wide-eyed, at the being that stood before them.

A warrior, dripping with blood from his torn grip, yet standing without missing a beat.

Chieftain Akwilla. Fox of the Night.

She stood here as the representative of the new generation against the representative of the old.

Chapter 92

The Ghosts of the Ancestors (4)

◆

Each of Adonai's arrows was a terrifying weapon.

But there was a hand that caught them and crushed them.

“Stay back.”

Akwilla stepped forward, blocking Vikir and Aiyen.

She had sent the eight Deathknights that stood in her way back to the grave where they belonged, and now she was about to face Adonai, the final pinnacle, the supreme of the Ballak.

Adonai, the leader of the Old Age, and Akwilla, the leader of the New Era.

These two twin pinnacles, each at the pinnacle of archery, now faced each other in a timeless confrontation.

Vikir swallowed a dry saliva.

A battle between two absolute powers, master-level aura users who touch the realm of the Supreme, is not something you see every day.

Even in the Age of Destruction, where the heavens and earth were turned upside down on a daily basis, a battle of this magnitude was not common.

“...What will happen?”

“It's not even worth asking.”

Aiyen beside him answered Vikir's question.

She opened her mouth with a determined expression.

“My mom never loses.”

Aiyen's words exuded confidence.

But the reality was beginning to show otherwise.

Kararak-

Akwilla raised her great bow and pointed it straight ahead.

The thick bowstring was pulled back under tremendous tension, and a powerful arrow was fired.

Boom!

Akwilla shot at Adonai with a silver aura.

The solid aura flew like an arrow made of silver, piercing through the black aura emanating from Adonai's body.

[....]

Adonai immediately counterattacked.

His combat instincts were so sharp that they were firmly embedded in his deceased body.

...Boom!

The black aura emanating from Adonai's body exploded like steam.

The earth around him cracked, sulfurous gas billowing out of the cracks, and the black aura emanating from Adonai's body was black with sulfur, as if it were the flames of hell.

They ascended into the heavens in a maelstrom, and soon the vast expanse of sky was shrouded in dark clouds.

Toward these dark clouds, Akwilla unleashed a barrage of silver flashes.

Silver flashes and black trajectories ferociously devouring each other.

It was so fast that even Aiyen, a novice Graduator, and Vikir, an advanced Graduator, could barely keep up with it.

“'Akwilla, the speed of your bow rivals that of Adonai.”

“My mother's archery skills are world-class, and I don't just mean in terms of accuracy.”

Quite literally, these two living myths were giving future generations of warriors a real lesson.

Akwilla and Adonai's combat is one of precision.

The basics of anticipating your opponent's movements and placing your arrows on a predictable path, while more advanced techniques such as spinning shots that take advantage of the air currents in which your opponent's arrows are flying, and parabolic shots that cause arrows to shoot out of nowhere from above or to the side, are effortlessly executed.

...BANG!

As Akwilla ducked her head, a black arrow flew out and snapped the back of a log behind her.

...Boom!

As soon as Adonai leapt upward, a silver arrow embedded itself in the sandbar he was standing on, sending a tsunami of sand in all directions.

An all-out battle of attrition.

...But as time passed, it was Akwilla who was losing ground.

Spot!

An arrow from Adonai grazes Akwilla's side. The black arrows were slowly, steadily squeezing the air out of Akwilla's lungs.

But it wasn't a matter of skill.

It's because Akwilla needs the limited tools of arrows, and Adonai doesn't.

Sometimes, like Adonai, Akwilla would simply concentrate her aura and send it out without an arrow, but it was so mana-draining that she couldn't use it except in a moment of great urgency.

Adonai, on the other hand, thanks to the negative energy he draws from Hell, can shoot out solid aura arrows of 100% purity.

Even.

“...Even the direction of the wind is unfavorable.”

Vikir frowned.

Adonai had his back to the wind, and Akwilla was facing it head-on.

The winds of the jungle seemed to be favoring Adonai's arrows, giving them more power, while Akwilla's arrows were halved in power.

The difference is becoming increasingly visible in Akwilla's body, which is becoming increasingly covered in scars.

Even Adonai's sniper shots were imbued with the poison of Madam Eight-Legs!

Tsutsutsutsuts...

The wounds on Akwilla's body turned black.

Her complexion was growing pale in contrast.

Ping-ping-ping-ping

Moreover, the arrows that Akwilla had sent out had suddenly begun to go in a completely strange direction.

The wind wrapped around her arrows and sent them flying in different directions, never reaching Adonai.

It was as if the entire jungle was protecting Adonai. Was he really a jungle god?

Vikir wondered. What could he do to reverse the odds?

At this rate, Akwilla would lose, and all of Ballak's warriors would be swept away by the Death Knight hordes.

“ ... Should we kill Ah'Heman first?”

Yes, but to do so would require penetrating Adonai's iron wall, which stands unmoving in place.

What's more, Ah'Heman had not withdrawn all of his Deathknights, but was instead focusing his efforts on controlling several Named-class Deathknights, including Adonai.

Ballak's warriors are struggling against other Death Knights who are only slightly deterred by the sprinkling of salt, but not at all deterred.

“Someone needs to go get the rest of the warriors in town! At this rate, we're going to...!”

Vikir shouts urgently.

Aiyen clamped a hand over his mouth.

“Shhh. We're almost there.”

“...?”

Vikir's eyes narrowed.

Akwilla was getting tired, her arrows flying in strange directions with the headwind.

Adonai, on the other hand, still going strong.

Where in the world did she think she was winning?

But Aiyen, who is a better archer than Vikir, seems to see something else.

Aiyen. She's watching in awe as Akwilla performs a miracle.

“I see it. I do. I see what my mother is seeing.”

“...?”

Vikir could only shake her head.

Then.

It happened suddenly.

...Boom!

A mysterious arrow flew out and lodged in the center of Adonai's back.

A single, authentic arrow twitched.

It came from an unexpected direction, from behind, not from below, not from the latitude, not from the side.

[...?]

Adonai paused for a moment, surely there could only be one person behind him, Ahhe?

But.

Pfft!

Another arrow flew right back at him, hitting him in the back of the head.

And then another.

-Beep, beep, beep!

A huge number of arrows began to fly in from behind.

“Ugh!”

Ah'Heman flattened himself like a bug on the ground.

Several of the arrows flying from behind tore into his backside.

“...!”

Vikir looked up, his mouth half open.

Only now did he see the identity of the arrows coming from behind.

They were the blind arrows Akwilla had been shooting at him a moment ago!

Pipipiping!

Another hail of arrows from behind. Still aimed at Adonai's back!

Whizz, whizz, whizz-!

The fierce wind was carrying Akwilla's arrows back to Adonai.

Only then did Vikir realize the cause of the anomaly.

Akwilla's arrows weren't flying in the wrong direction.

They seemed to have taken a wrong turn, only to surge upward in a whirlwind that raged across the jungle, only to spin around in a full circle and return to where they came from.

Like salmon running up a waterfall back to the place where they were born.

To the center of the black vortex that Adonai is creating, to where the wind begins!

...Puck! ...Puck! Quack!

Adonai's exposed back was instantly transformed into a hedgehog.

After bouncing twice in the wind, the arrow became even more powerful than when it was originally released and struck its target.

Akwilla's arrows, which could pierce rocks and logs, didn't completely penetrate Adonai's powerful body, but they still managed to make a good dent.

Boom!

Another arrow landed on top of the one in Adonai's thigh.

Only then did it manage to pierce Adonai's thigh, causing him to stagger and fall to his knees on the ground.

Akwilla looked up, his complexion weary.

“Great Ancestor, if you were still alive and in good spirits, you would not have made such a simple mistake. It saddens me.”

Akwilla sent the last arrow flying toward the crippled Adonai.

A blind arrow struck him in the back and a sighted arrow in the front.

Adonai was unable to dodge Akwilla's final shot.

Pfft!

An arrow halfway to the back of his head and another halfway to his forehead.

...Boom!

The two arrowheads meet at a single point.

Thud-!

Adonai fell to his knees.

The legend of a previous generation bowed before the myth of a new era.

“....”

Akwilla looked at Adonai, kneeling before him, head bowed.

It didn't really feel like a victory.

Akwilla was at the peak of his powers now, and the Adonai he had just faced had already died of old age and was no longer in the process of being resurrected from the dead.

Moreover, he was a corpse, lacking even basic intelligence, let alone a living mind, so it was hardly a proper match.

“If only Adonai had had the strength of his prime....”

Akwilla shook her head. She could only imagine the horrible consequences.

Then.

“Kaaaaaah!”

A muffled scream.

Ah'Heman was struggling with Adonai's corpse.

The battle was lost, as the Death Knight made from Adonai's corpse had fallen.

The few remaining Deathknights gathered around Ah'Heman, and a far greater number of Ballak warriors surrounded him.

“Now die.”

Aiyen glares at Ah'Heman with disdain.

But.

Ah'Heman's gamble was not yet over.

He has lost almost all of his life and mana, and is crippled from the waist down, but he still hasn't let go of his will to live.

“Don't come!”

Ah'Heman gathered Adonai's body and the bodies of the other ancestors together.

He grabbed a handful of blood from his hands and mouth.

“If you come near, your ancestors will be tainted with my blood!”

Ah'Heman's threat made everyone, including Akwilla, pause for a moment.

Superstition held that a soul tainted with the blood of a traitor would be unable to enter the warrior's paradise.

In his final moments, Ah'Heman had relied on this small superstition to blackmail the others.

At this rate, the souls of the warriors would never be able to go to paradise, not to mention they would have been tricked by him.

The fact that he was so skilled in witchcraft made the situation even more dire.

“....”

Akwilla raised his bow, but Ah'Heman was cunningly hiding behind the bodies of his ancestors.

Thus, all the warriors were unable to act rashly.

For if they did, they might not be able to honor their ancestors forever.

Just then.

“Stand down, everyone.”

Vikir's voice rang out.

All eyes turned to see Vikir raising his bow and aiming an arrow.

However, the arrow was pointed in the wrong direction.

“...What are you going to do?”

Even Akwilla, who had just used the wind to make an unbelievable hit, looked confused.

But. Vikir was confident.

“Climb to a higher place first.”

That was Vikir's last piece of advice.

At the same time.

PING-!

The arrow from Vikir's bow flew in a parabolic arc.

It struck where the logs were stacked on top of each other, the knot of vines holding them together.

...Pow!

Vikir's arrow snaps, and the vine falls to the ground.

And then.

Grrrrr – snap – snap – snap.

As the vines snapped one by one, the heavy logs began to move in unison.

When the wooden barrier dam, which was held in place by vines, collapses, the things on the other side spill out.

Chhhhhhh.

It was a river that swelled during the long rainy season, the waves of a salt river full of melted white salt!

Chapter 93

The Ghosts of the Ancestors (5)

◆

...Boom!

With a loud boom, the dam that held back the water burst.

The wooden boards collapsed and the river began to flood on a massive scale.

“Everyone up in the trees!”

Fortunately, Aiyen was quick to react, and there were few casualties in Ballak.

As the river swept ferociously over everything, Ballak's warriors climbed high into the trees to avoid it.

Those who were too slow to climb the trees managed to hold on to sturdy rocks and ride out the waves.

But. The Death Knights, standing in the distance, were unable to avoid the wave.

Crash! Crash!

The rushing water swept the Death Knights away in one fell swoop.

Of course, the Death Knights were strong enough to withstand the waves, but the problem... wasn't the waves themselves.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsutsuts...

The bodies of the Death Knights gradually turned to black vapor and began to disperse.

This was because the river water that was now flooding was a concentrated salt water.

By nature, the undead are weak to salt, which has the power to purify the unholy.

These salt rivers have long been home to saltwater fish, and even salt that is dissolved in water is effective against the undead.

The Death Knights resisted the salt, but they could not withstand such an overwhelming force.

Sanctification.

One by one, the bodies crumble to dust.

The bodies of their ancestors, returning to where they belonged, swept away by the flowing waters and scattered across the flooded land where they had been born and raised.

“....”

Akwilla swallowed hard at the sight of Adonai's flesh dissolving in the salt water and being swept away.

It was unfortunate that the remains of her distant ancestors could not be properly recovered, but she was glad that the unholy energy had been cleansed.

Most of all, I am glad that the noble bodies of my ancestors were not spattered with the disgusting blood of Ah'Heman.

...And now.

The water level subsided.

It was the end of the rainy season, and the waters were no longer overflowing.

Ballak's warriors descended to the bottom as the water receded.

The water was still up to their ankles, but it didn't interfere with their ability to walk on the ground.

Vikir followed suit as soon as the water level dropped.

Pow! ...pow! ...pow!

With each step, the water rises to his ankles and the wispy grass tickles between his toes.

In the stagnant pools at the bottom, catfish and eels trapped by the current flailed and gasped for air.

Then.

Vikir spotted something.

An object, silently submerged in the water, wafting an eerie aura above the surface.

“Is that ...?”

It was a large bow.

Dark matte. Horns and thorns sprouting like teeth.

This black bow, without even a bowstring, must have been held by Adonai just a moment ago.

A weapon made from the carapace of a Madam Eight-Legs. At first glance, it was an unusual weapon.

Vikir picked it up and handed it to Aiyen beside him.

“....”

Aiyen took it and cradled it in her arms. Then he ran to hand it to Akwilla, who stood in the distance.

Meanwhile.

Ballak's warriors were converging on a single location.

They were heading for a single thorny tree that stood tall in the middle of a wide open plain.

It stood alone, with no other large trees around, and its trunk was densely covered with countless thorns.

The warriors of Ballak stood in a circle around the tree, and in unison they looked up.

Above them, they saw a familiar figure.

“Ugh... Ugh....”

This tenacious old man was hanging on, unable to be swept away by the rising waters of the river.

Just before the water washed over him, he climbed this thorny tree, scraping the ground with his hands and dragging his motionless lower half.

What could have led him to this harrowing path of suras?

The sides of the thorns were sharp as blades, and their tips were pointed like spears.

“Turn it off...... Ahhh...... ”

Ah'Heman reached out a trembling hand and grabbed them.

He couldn't even pick out the relatively blunt thorns in the mad rush of water.

He just had to grab whatever he could get his hands on.

The backs of his hands were punctured, his fingers were zigzagging and tattered, and his knuckles were falling off.

Needless to say, it wasn't just his hands.

The whole body was covered in thorns, cuts, and tears.

His flesh was torn like rags, and his body was dripping with blood.

Salt water and debris filled the gaping wounds, causing hellish pain.

His guts were already disintegrating from being used by high-level Death Knights who were out of their capabilities.

But despite this, the old shaman was still alive.

He continued to reach out and climb the thorns, seemingly frightened, or perhaps even dazed.

He looked as if he had aged decades.

“Sa, save me... please save me....”

As he desperately moved his hands to climb the branches, bits of flesh and guts were dripping down the tree trunk with blood.

The tree turning more and more gray.

Vikir stared at it, lost in thought.

“....”

Ah, well, in retrospect, he was certainly a remarkable man.

He had raised the mythical Adonai of Ballak from the undead, even though all his life force was gone, and he had managed to wield several other Death Knights simultaneously.

'Perhaps if he had only devoted himself to magic, he would have been at the level of Adolf, the Madman of Morgue.'

However, it was a pity that he had awkwardly imitated a warrior to match Ballak's emotions.

Even with a black magic skill of more than six circles, he was still playing the part of a warrior.

But it proved how eager he was to blend into the atmosphere of Ballak.

Vikir turned his gaze back to Ah'Heman.

He climbed the thorns in terror, bleeding.

The sight of him suddenly brings back memories of when he first came to Ballak's village two years ago.

The prisoners of war climbing the thorns and the flames burning beneath them.

Those condemned to the thorn tree were forced to climb it naked, their bodies covered in blood.

They fell to their deaths at the base of the tree, bleeding to death or dying of burns.

Among the dead were men of the house of Baskerville and men of the house of Morgue.

It is especially memorable that in their last moments, they kept their mouths shut, even though their eyes met Vikir's.

“....”

Vikir bowed his head in silence for a moment, then raised it again and looked up at the reddened thorns.

He had heard that it was Ah'Heman who had devised this horrible punishment, and now he was meeting his end by a brutal torture of his own making.

In other words, the real enemy of Ah'Heman was Ah'Heman himself.

Then.

“...I'll finish it.”

There was a hand on Vikir's shoulder.

He turned to see Ahun standing there, his head bowed.

“Please, let me.”

Was it the fact that he'd rejected Vikir's words earlier that bothered him? Ahun looked into Vikir's eyes and asked for a favor.

When Vikir nodded, Ahun stepped forward.

He struck a flint to create embers, and soon spread the oil and a little gunpowder he carried with him at the base of the thorn tree.

Soon, a tiny ember rises and falls on the thorn.

Crackle!

The flames, flickering due to the moisture, soon spread upwards with astonishing speed.

The wet wood burns and emits a great deal of smoke.

Soon, scarlet flames shot up like spears, pursuing Ah'Heman.

Crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle!

The sound of burning wood is loud.

The flames burned toward the top.

The flames and smoke soon engulfed Ah'Heman, who had languished halfway up the thorns.

No screams were heard.

“....”

The warriors of Ballak watched the old shaman's final moments with mixed expressions on their faces.

Recalling the past seventy years, how they had cried and laughed at his every word, every gesture.

Crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle!

The smell of burning meat is thick.

The sound of sizzling fat was everywhere.

Everyone was about to turn away.

“Hee-hee-hee-hee!”

Through the flames and black smoke, something appeared.

The warriors' eyes widened in surprise. Even Akwilla.

There was a skeleton, burning brightly, screaming with open arms.

“Ahhhhhh.”

No shaman, no warrior, born in the body of a Rokoko and living in the mind of a Ballak.

A being whose flesh and the fat beneath it had already burned away.

He shook his flesh, which was already more like charcoal than a body, and screamed at the world.

“You will regret this! You'll regret putting me out like this...! ...! ...!”

The words he spat out after that were muffled.

Not only had his tongue been cooked, but the smoke he'd inhaled had burned through his lungs.

Ah'Heman floundered for several more seconds after that. Disintegrating into black powder like the Death Knights he had summoned.

He lifted his head and tried to see the town beyond the water in the distance.

He couldn't see much of anything through his flame-cooked eyes.

“...Go back.”

Chief Akwilla ordered.

The Ballak warriors returned to the village, their bodies soaked with saltwater and exhaustion.

Vikir and Aiyen did the same, carrying each other slowly back to the village.

A friendly village. A tribe that should be at peace now that its arch-enemy, Ah'Heman, is gone.

...But.

When they returned to the village, the warriors finally understood what Ah'Heman had warned them about.

Why he had laughed so much in his last moments, and why he had turned to look out over the village.

Chapter 98

Madam Eight-Legs (5)

◆

<Madame 'Eight Legs'>

Risk Rating : S

Size : ?

Found in: Ridge 10, Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain

-Nicknamed 'Madame of Dephts'. Her exact race name is unknown.

In the distant past, the most terrible beings that inhabited the depths of the Oil Pole Hell were spiders of immense size, and it is believed that Madam Eight-Legs is a distant descendant that retains the form of those giant spiders that lived in the ancient past.

Their bodies are filled with a disgusting venom, and their webs are stronger than steel, unbreakable by anything but the infernal fires of the Underworld.

Vikir looked up at the giant queen spider before him.

Indeed. Facing this overwhelming force, he understood why Ballak's warriors had been so worried and frightened.

Before leaving Ballak, Akwilla had expressed concern.

“'There is not much known about the Madame. Only the shaman Ah'Heman knew more, but now that he's gone....”

But. There was one thing Akwilla didn't know.

Ah'Heman was from the Rokoko, a tribe of shamans, and as such, he was familiar with the ancient creatures.

And Vikir had recently acquired a number of secret documents from a group of Rokoko who had fled the plague during the Red Death.

Surprisingly, among the documents were important books that the Rokoko shaman hadn't taken with him during his hasty flight from the plague, including a detailed analysis of the creatures of the depht.

It contained information on rare beasts such as the “Swamp Salamander” and the “Bone-Sucking Mosquito,” and the Madame of Depht was no exception.

-We don't know exactly what kind of monster she is.

However, she is similar in appearance to the giant, terrifying spiders of history books from the distant past, and is expected to transform into such a creature as she grows older.

-For now, she lives alone and isolated in a forsaken land between the low hills beyond Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain and the shores of the cold, harsh Sea of Ruin.

But unlike in the old days, when she kept to herself, these days she seems to be thinking about crossing the borders of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

-The Madame of Water is always hungry, and her voracious appetite, combined with her fierce cunning and great strength, means that neither her enemies nor any other creature in the Black Mountain Ecosystem will be able to stop her.

-And neither will we. We must prepare for the nightmare that may soon be upon us. The horrors of water!

Vikir looked at Madam Eight-Legs as he recalled this and other information.

Her plump body expanded and contracted as she exhaled and inhaled.

The black-green poisonous fog that emanated from her body formed a thick veil, beyond which eight red eyes pierced Vikir's entire body.

[Jaaaaack...!]

Madam Eight-Legs reacted first.

She raised her massive forelegs and slammed them into the ground.

...Thud!

The floor wrinkled, and then a huge wave rose up and crashed over Vikir.

Shattered bones, rotting flesh, spider webs, and fecal matter all mixed together in a hot, fermenting mass.

Faced with this wave of disgust, Vikir can only laugh bitterly.

“Good thing I skipped dinner.”

If I had eaten, I would have gotten rid of it.

Even Vikir, who has a strong squeamishness, thinks, “I'm glad I didn't eat dinner.”

Puff puff puff!

Vikir flung himself out of the way of the wave.

He couldn't dodge them casually.

The slightest opening and he'd sink to the bottom of the shifting ground, or get kicked by Madam Eight-Legs' extra kicks.

Vikir leaped upward, landing on the massive ribs of something towering over him.

Karak-

The archery skills taught to you by Aiyen shine through.

Madam Eight-Legs flinched slightly as Vikir's arrow sliced through the air.

She had been wounded herself during the raid on Ballak's village.

It was a minor one, but she had no choice but to react as if it were a nuisance to have hard-to-remove thorns embedded in her body.

Madame ducked slightly backwards to avoid an arrow flying towards her eye.

Sssssss...

An infernal darkness enveloped her like a shroud.

Madame's exhalation turned into a thick poisonous fog, adding an inky blackness to the darkness that almost completely obscured her body.

Rumbling-bang!

If it weren't for the thunderbolt that struck at just the right time.

...Flash!

In an instant, a single bolt of lightning bathed everything in white light.

It was obvious how cunningly Madame had been preparing for her next attack while crouching in the darkness.

The moment she stretches upwards, her silhouette is revealed in the white light.

Boom!

Vikir stabbed an arrow into the gap in the center.

It was like baking beans in a fire.

In that brief moment of light, Vikir was able to see beyond the darkness and put the arrow right on target.

The bull's-eye was Madame's left eye.

CRACK!

The sound of a red glass ball shattering.

The arrow had landed squarely in Madame's skull.

[Jaaaaaah!?]

Madame panicked as one of her eight eyes suddenly burned black.

At that very moment, another thunderbolt struck.

...Flash!

Another bolt of lightning.

The light became a beacon to guide Vikir's second arrow.

Crackle.

Madame's missing eye became two.

The flash of light was followed exactly seven seconds later by a loud boom.

...Boom!

The sound followed slightly later than the light, and by the time it exploded, Vikir was once again preparing for her next attack.

“Two empty left eyeballs.”

Vikir deliberately targeted only the left side of Madame's face.

The two eyeballs on her left side are currently pierced by arrows, so that's her blind spot.

Like a seasoned hound, Vikir made a quick judgment call, and it paid off.

The Madame hesitated as Vikir turned to the left, sensing that she had lost sight of the enemy.

Taking advantage of the moment, Vikir drew his magic sword, Beelzebub, and unleashed a blast of Graduator-grade aura.

Baskervillian Carnivore.

Six teeth blazed with aura as thick as blood.

Quack, quack, quack!

The long slash created a huge crack.

The sound of hard chitinous armor shattering and the squishy flesh inside being torn apart.

Denggeng!

With a loud bang, Madame's left front leg was severed.

[Jaaaaah!]

Madame screamed with her whole body, through the many breathing holes in her body.

But that wasn't the end of it.

Thud!

Vikir's blow cut through the air like a whip, severing not only one of Madame's front legs, but also the mucous sac at the back of her lower belly, where the cobwebs were coming out.

Zzzzzzzzzzzzzz...

The cobwebs began to leak.

I prepared for a follow-up blow as Madame stumbled backwards, dripping with slime.

Once the attack was successful, the hunt was relentless.

Once you have the upper hand, you can't let go.

But.

“...?”

Vikir paused, about to strike.

The old hound's instincts were screaming. Back off now!

Without hesitation, Vikir surrendered to his instincts.

On the battlefield, it is often wiser to listen to instinct than to reason.

Right then.

...Pow!

Vikir's back snapped into a G-shape.

Madame's killing intent had overtaken his instincts.

Where did it come from?

From an unexpected place, another of Madame's legs shot out and slammed into Vikir's body.

“...!”

Vikir saw it clearly as his body buckled under the impact.

The Madame's legs that he had cut off earlier had suddenly regenerated.

And two of them!

[Jarrarak-kick-]

Madame raised her left front leg as if to mock Vikir.

To Vikir's surprise, it was split in two, starting at the same point where it had been severed.

In other words, two new legs had grown from where it had been severed.

Madame's absurdly powerful regenerative powers make such a thing possible.

Her legs had a bizarre structure where the more you cut, the more you grow.

Quack! ...Puck!

Vikir crashed to the ground, buried like garbage in a pile of bones.

Madame's legs turned Vikir's body, which was forged by the blessing of the River Styx, into rags.

The stomach skin was ripped open, all the intestines leaked out, and the right leg was completely cut off.

The bones of his left leg were shattered and bent into a rhomboid, and the impact had blinded him in one eye and ear.

In a single moment, a hero fell.

And Madame, who had reduced countless heroes to rotting lumps of flesh in the past, had done something similar this time.

[Giggle giggle giggle...]

Madame sneers in triumph.

I could see her eyes, of which there were only six left, curling gently into a smirk.

...However.

Madame soon had to retract the mockery from her face.

“I didn't know that, so if you cut off a leg, it becomes two?”

Vikir casually brushed off his seat and stood up.

At the same time.

Tsutsutsutsuts...

Black steam began to rise from Vikir's entire body.

The sound and smell of burning flesh, and black smoke billowing out.

But it wasn't burning flesh, it was regenerating at a staggering rate.

A bog salamander.

The restorative powers of this monstrous amphibian, imbued in the magic sword Beelzebub, had completely rebuilt Vikir's body.

Finally, Vikir spoke.

“ ... But this is within the margin of error.”

With a voice cold enough to make Madame cringe, the hound began to barrel its teeth in earnest.

Chapter 100

Nostalgia (1)

◆

POP!

The sound of a balloon popping echoed through the water.

For a moment, Vikir felt his mind being snapped.

A tremendous impact struck his entire body.

But this time, the seasoned hound didn't step on death's door.

Grabbing onto the broken cord, Vikir gritted his teeth and endured the impact of the fall on his entire body.

He looks up and sees that his limbs are still attached.

Vikir breathes a sigh of relief despite the pain. Now that he knew the outside of his body was intact, it was time to check the inside.

...The inside was in better shape than he expected.

My head was cracked, all my ribs were broken, all my bones were fractured, my legs were bent in weird directions, and my muscles, organs, and blood vessels were torn apart.

The pain and wounds would have killed a normal person several times over, but not Vikir, who possessed extraordinary regenerative powers.

This was an injury that could be repaired with the help of the Bog Salamander's Wraith imprisoned within the magic sword Beelzebub.

“...Exquisite.”

Vikir checked the giant pillow where he had fallen.

It was the decomposed, gassy carcass of a Boggy Bog Salamander.

It had been attacked by swarms of bone-sucking mosquitoes, leaving its tough skin filled with blood, flesh, and soft organs.

The unfortunate salamander had been alive until Vikir climbed the crag, and apparently died while Vikir was at the top of the peak fighting Madame.

The salamander's death and decomposition caused gas to build up in its tough skin, which made it even more puffy, and Vikir fell on top of it.

Needless to say, this didn't soften the impact.

Falling on water is still a shock.

Vikir pushed himself up through the pain.

“At least it didn't have the salamander's bones.”

If the salamander's carcass had a solid skeleton holding it together, Vikir would have been even more traumatized by the impact.

Luckily, the bone-sucking mosquitoes had eaten all of the salamander's bones, so she was spared.

But.

His physical injuries were mostly healed, but he couldn't help the stench.

The impact of Vikir's fall had exploded the salamander's carcass, sending gases, rotting guts, and blood everywhere.

The stench was sickening.

The stench is unimaginable, given that it's the salamander that stinks so badly, and the rotting stench that's added to it.

If you ever get out of here, you'll probably have to stay in the bath for days straight.

...But.

The stench wasn't the issue right now.

Vikir had something else he needed to check first.

“....”

Vikir turned his gaze to the solid rock in the distance.

On it lay a large, bloody chunk of meat.

Madam Eight-Legs, as powerful as she was, apparently didn't have the stamina to withstand the impact of a fall down a cliff.

“Well. You must have sustained quite a few injuries when you raided Ballak's tribe.”

Her entire exoskeleton had been shattered, all her vital organs-bones, lungs, heart-had been spilled to the ground, and many of her legs were bent in grotesque ways.

But amazingly, Madame is still alive.

She barely manages to pull herself upright, shaking her half-exploded and mashed body.

Beneath her, mangled intestines ooze out of her.

“....”

Vikir stretched and walked slowly toward Madame.

Madame. Even a demon of depht can't help but feel fear when they see the shadow of death looming over them.

Madame shuddered as she met Vikir's red eyes.

It was an emotion that coursed through her bones, down to the very core of her exoskeleton. It was fear, 100% pure.

“...Are you afraid?”

[....]

“Are you afraid of death too?”

Vikir laughed dryly, twisting the corners of his mouth where rotten blood had dried.

Madame felt the brains in her shattered skull, torn into pieces, shrinking away.

With each step Vikir took, her heart thudded against the outside of her ribs.

The old madam, whose intelligence and memory had been sharpened by her long life, had imprinted Vikir's current appearance in her mind.

The flickering vision, the approaching terror, the looming death, and the hound, the death dog!

[Zaarak...]

The sound of the beast's cries was small and feeble, like a child's whimper.

Madame staggered backwards, dazed, dazed, dazed.

The burst mucus sac was oozing out of her, but she didn't seem to mind.

Vikir staggered up to her and plunged his awl into her back.

...Pfft!

Beelzebub dug deep into the cracks in the tarnished armor.

Madame shuddered and struggled, but her movements were entirely aimed at escape, and she showed no sign of fighting back.

...Pow! ...pow! ...pow! ...pow!

The awl sank like teeth. Vikir's assault continued.

He had no strength left in his belly, so all he could do was press down with his body weight, but still, he was surely diminishing Madame point by point.

Karma.

The Wraiths of all the Ballak warriors who had died innocently, and the Wraiths of all the natives of all the tribes of the jungle who had died countless times before, were weighing on Vikir's wrist.

The karma she had accumulated up to this point had become experience points, making him stronger... but not as strong as he was at this moment.

The touch of these many Wraiths dragging her down into the depths of the abyss was clearly self-inflicted.

Gulp! Gulp! Gulp! Gulp!

Soon, Madame's soul began to be sucked into the orb of Beelzebub.

<Binge Fly 'Beelzebub'>/ Awl

-1 slot: Burn-Cerberus (A+)

Slot -2: Silent Hill – Monsieur Hushu(A+)

Slot -3: Super Regeneration – Swamp Salamander (A+)

Three formidable creatures of A+ danger.

Their Wraiths originally occupied each of the three orbs beneath Beelzebub's blade, creating a tense power balance.

The new arrival, Madame's Wraith, upset the balance.

Madame's Wraith was the first to seek out the slot that held the Wraith of Cerberus, with whom it had never gotten along with regarding similar territory.

[Grrrr...]

The Wraith of Cerberus, who had long occupied the first slot of the Red Ball, bared its teeth at Madame's intrusion.

As a Wraith, Cerberus still remembers the humiliation of being stripped of his territory by Madame and banished to the Seventh Ridge.

But the hierarchy of the Wraith world is generally not much different from that of the living.

Madame was vicious as a Wraith.

[Cackle! Cackle!]

As in life, Madame took Cerberus's territory and set up a nest in its place.

<Binge Fly 'Beelzebub'>/ Awl

-1 slot: Venomous-Madam Eight-Legs (S)

Slot -2: Silent Hill – Monsieur Hushu (A+)

Slot -3: Super Regeneration – Swamp Salamander (A+)

Finally, Beelzebub's first slot changed owners.

The passive skill that Vikir gained from it was Venom, a poison so concentrated that there was nothing in the world that could match it.

It flowed into Vikir's body and soon dissolved into his red blood.

While harmless to Vikir himself, it would probably be a deadly poison to others.

Meanwhile.

Madame was still fleeing at this moment, frantically shaking the ground.

Despite the fact that part of her soul had become a wraith and fallen prey to Beelzebub, she was still minimally conscious and attempting to escape.

Perhaps it was because her brain had been shattered into many pieces.

Vikir had tried to hold on with his sword in Madame's back pack, but he could not help her fading consciousness.

He hadn't eaten or slept since his recent climb, and his body had been completely rebuilt nearly twice, so he had every reason to be sapped of stamina.

This was especially true now that he had released an aura that had burned through every blood vessel in his body.

A normal swordsman would have been dead or crippled by now.

Thump-thump-thump

From beyond my fading consciousness, I hear the howling of a beast.

“...If it's a pack of dogs, we're in trouble. What other creature in the world would dare to approach this place when Madam Eight-Legs was exuding poisonous energy?”

...Vikir was not in a relaxed enough state to think about that.

Eventually.

Shuffle!

Vikir collapsed on top of Madame's corpse.

....

Sleep took an awful long time, or maybe just a moment.

In the darkness behind his eyelids, he recognizes many faces.

Many faces I'd left behind during my journey through the Age of Destruction, and those I'd met since my return.

Faces of Chihuahua, Cindywendy, Pomeranian, Akwilla, Camus, Aiyen, Dolores, Barrymore, and others rise and fall to the surface without a sound.

Faces from Baskerville, faces from Underdog City, faces from the dephts, faces from Quovadis Street, faces from all over the place, one after the other, without any connection.

Among them were the faces of Hugo and Ah'Heman.

The moment.

“...!”

Vikir scrambled to his feet.

How many days, hours, minutes, or seconds had passed?

He sees a shadowy silhouette hovering over his still-warm body.

He waits for his vision to clear a little more, and then he feels a warm tongue licking his face.

It was Bakira, the wolf, peering into Vikir's face.

And next to it, he could see the face of his constant companion.

Aiyen.

She sat down next to Vikir, looking like she was about to burst into tears.

“Oh my God, Vikir! Are you awake! Can you see me? Hey! Ahun! Over here! Over here!”

“ Vikir! You're alive! I'll get you some medicine right away!”

“Poison! Wash off the poison! Take him to the village!”

The world is silent, except for the slow twitching of Aiyen's mouth, his blurred vision, and the familiar faces gathering around him.

“...Is this a dream?”

With that thought, Vikir blacked out completely.

Chapter 101

Nostalgia (2)

◆

Vikir opened his eyes.

He had slept soundly, without a single nightmare.

He usually slept half-awake, bracing himself for an attack or some other miscellaneous disaster, but this time he slept soundly and defenselessly, as if he were truly dead.

Of course, when I woke up, the wounds on my body had healed nicely.

This was partly due to the regenerative powers of the bog salamander, but also because all sorts of good medicines had healed my body from the inside out.

“...?”

Vikir scrambled to his feet.

He was covered in fluffy fur pelts on a bed of dry straw and a clean cotton quilt.

Herbs and various splints wrapped around his body.

Inside, the layout of the room was vaguely familiar, like something from one of Ballak's barracks.

He glanced down and saw that the room's owner was asleep at Vikir's feet.

It was Aiyen.

Vikir opened his mouth to speak in Moorish.

“...Are you awake?”

A voice came from the barracks entrance.

Akwilla. The night fox stared down at Vikir.

She had aged quite a bit in the few days he hadn't seen her.

Her cheeks were sunken and shadows under her eyes.

The years she had been suppressing by force all this time were flowing again.

Akwilla sat down beside Vikir's bed and glanced over at Aiyen, who slept beside her.

“Aiyen, this one carried you when you fainted. He ran for three days and three nights.”

And that's why Aiyen, who hadn't eaten or slept for days and had run with all his might, now slept at Vikir's feet.

“....”

Vikir was silent for a moment, looking down at Aiyen as he slept, curled up between his toes.

Then Akwilla turned to Vikir.

“What the hell happened to you?”

Vikir hesitated for a moment, then spoke.

“ I tried to kill Madame....”

Madame's complete death. Vikir hadn't seen it through to the end. That's why he only spoke of what came before.

“I didn't think I would be able to overcome it with my own strength, so I dropped it to the bottom of the peak and barely won. Of course, it was quite difficult to drag him out of the deep hole and push him down the cliff...... It's just that I was lucky. It's just a pity that I couldn't definitely cut off Madame's breath.”

Vikir spoke casually, but this was actually quite remarkable.

After all these years of tormenting the natives of Depht, the Madame had finally been defeated by a young hero.

Now the natives no longer had to make sacrifices.

They could use the light at their disposal in the dark of night, and they no longer had to tremble with fear during stormy nights.

This was enough for him to be hailed as the savior of all the tribes on the depht.

As Akwilla listened to Vikir's tale, he remained silent in amazement.

Then she told him what he had been wondering.

“After you fainted, Madame managed to flee the scene. Ballak's warriors followed you, but the poison in the air was too much for them to approach, and it was all they could do to rescue you.”

Whether she intended to or not, Madame had sprayed deadly poison everywhere as she fled.

The fog of poison they created as they volatilized made it impossible for the warriors and wolves to finally cut off her breath.

But.

Akwilla said with a determined look.

“But Madame would be dead by now.”

When Vikir turned his head away, Akwilla insisted.

“She can never last long with that wound.”

He was right. Madame's entire body was crushed, and she had lost many vital organs.

Her vital internal organs, such as her heart, spleen, lungs, and intestines, all protruded out of her body and sagged to the ground, and her exoskeleton was shattered.

Her skull had even split open, tearing her brain into several pieces, making it extremely unlikely that Madame would survive.

There was a reason Akwilla was so certain.

“Moreover. The place Madame fled to is known for being the coldest place in the world, even under the dephts. It's icy there, even in July, and a body that's so emaciated can't survive the harsh climate there.”

In other words. Madame will either die from her injuries, starve from immobility, or freeze to death in the icy cold.

No matter how you look at it, there is no other fate for Madame than death.

Thus, Vikir became the hero of the entire region for killing Madame.

“Hero, you speak too highly of me.”

Vikir shook his head in humility, and Akwilla smiled dryly.

“Is this still too much praise?”

As she spoke, Akwilla swept aside the curtain at the barracks entrance.

And then.

“...!”

Vikir couldn't help but open his eyes wide.

Outside the barracks, an enormous crowd had gathered, at first glance, four figures in size.

They were all kneeling, eyes closed, hands clasped together in prayer.

“We want Vikir, the hero of the depht, to get well. Please send our prayers to....”

Ballak, Rokoko, Renaissance, all the big tribes of Depht, as well as smaller tribes with appearances and attire you've never seen before.

They prayed in different ways, but their requests were the same.

With one heart and one mind, they surrounded Vikir's barracks and offered sacrifices.

And then.

Whoa, whoa, whoa!

At the sight of the awakened Vikir, they stamped their feet, raised their voices, and let out a roar of joy.

The entire tribe was united under Vikir's accomplishment.

◆

That night.

The whole series of processes and events came to a sobering end.

The all-night feast of eating, drinking, and merriment, and the memorial service for the dead, ended simultaneously.

Survivors drink and get drunk in a sense of mission, sadness, relief or joy, and make new resolutions.

And when it was all over, the night fell silent.

“....”

Vikir closed his eyes and checked his body.

'I have it back. Back to my prime before the regression.'

Deep inside him, he could feel his aura bubbling and boiling.

It's so dense that it's now more like a solid than a liquid.

It is the peak of the Graduator, a state that Vikir had reached before his regression.

Added to that was a higher level of Baskerville-style swordsmanship.

The sixth tooth he'd drawn against Madame.

And before he knew it, another, smaller tooth had sprouted behind it.

The Baskerville Seventh.

The seventh tooth, beyond carnivorous.

Vikir's struggle with the Madame resulted in the production of a seventh tooth, albeit a small one.

He doesn't know why, but it's a natural consequence of his deepening understanding of martial arts in times of crisis.

He has fully regained the combat prowess he had before his regression, and has even acquired the 7th Baskerville.

Considering that Vikir's swordsmanship before his regression was only 4 tooth, and the current patriarch of the Baskerville family, Hugo le Baskerville, was 7 dan, this was quite an achievement.

“But Hugo is a Swordmaster.”

Even if they had the same level of swordsmanship, Hugo is a master.

Vikir was a top Graduator, but he hadn't yet broken through the Master's barrier.

'...Still, I've achieved at seventeen what I didn't reach until I was forty, so I've got a long way to go.'

If anyone else knew this, they would faint.

Not even the greatest swordmasters of House Baskerville, who were said to have the best equipment in history, could accomplish this.

Moreover, Vikir was confident that even if he were to go one-on-one with the Swordmaster, he would not be easily overpowered.

“If it's not a duel, but a life-or-death fight, then it's not like we don't have a chance....”

Vikir's eyes shone as he pictured Hugo's face in his mind.

At the same time, the sword Beelzebub, much longer than before, drew its blade from the artery in his wrist.

...Puddle!

The red pattern engraved on the hilt was even more ominous than before.

The reason is...

<Binge Fly 'Beelzebub'>/ Awl

-1 slot: Venomous -Madam Eight-Legs (S)

-Slot 2: Silent Hill – Monsieur Hushu (A+)

Slot -3: Super Regeneration – Swamp Salamander (A+)

The newest addition to the group is a giant wraith.

Madam Eight-Legs.

Since a portion of her soul became a wraith and possessed Beelzebub, this already dangerous weapon has become even more deadly.

Extremely poisonous.

It was imbued with Madame's fearsome malice, capable of killing in the smallest doses.

For a moment, Vikir studied this product of Madame's killing.

Then. Suddenly, Vikir's mind wandered elsewhere.

“Come to think of it, what about...?”

Vikir's gaze fell to the bosom of the black cloak he was wearing.

He slipped his hand into the pocket and felt what he expected.

One soft little ball.

This large black ball bobbed gently in Vikir's hand.

It was the egg that Madam Eight-Legs had laid.

During the battle, Madam Eight-Legs had regained her health by eating her eggs, one by one, and this was the last one she had left.

Vikir scrambled to pick it up.

“I saw it fall and picked it up, but I didn't think it would survive the impact of the fall....”

The egg was quite durable after all.

No matter how many times I hit it with my fist, it bounces back without breaking because it is so elastic.

The others didn't know what this black egg was, so they left it alone for now....

“Hmm, do you think it will hatch?”

Now that it had left its mother's arms, there was a good chance that even if it was a healthy egg, it wouldn't hatch properly.

It could have been a fertile egg in the first place, or it could have been damaged inside.

For now, Vikir kept the egg in his arms.

Maybe one day it could be used for research.

'...I must leave now.'

Vikir lay down in a heap of straw.

He'd seen, heard, and done a lot in the last two years here in Depht.

He had gained experiences that he would never forget.

I've regained my pre-Regression combat strength, and I've learned many important things.

But we can't live here forever.

I still had a lot of work to do before I could return.

'...Someday, when I'm done with all my plans, I'll be able to come back here.'

Just as Vikir was thinking about his future plans.

Thump-thump-thump.

Someone knocked on the barracks' insignia.

The next moment, someone entered the barracks where Vikir was lying.

Whirring.

A dewy night breeze enters and blows out the candles in the barracks.

“...?”

Vikir stared at the shadowy figure beyond the darkness.

Aiyen.

She was staring down at Vikir, her back to the black night sky, a galaxy of countless stars.

...?

“Vikir.”

Aiyen's voice is more serious than ever as she calls out to Vikir.

She was always reticent and serious, but... today, for some reason, she was wearing an unusually reserved expression.

And then.

Aiyen stepped closer to Vikir.

And said in a low voice

“Will you ... help me?”

Chapter 102

Nostalgia (3)

◆

Help me? What, at this late hour of the night?

Vikir raised his upper body. There was nothing covering his upper body beneath the blankets.

Aiyen stared at him.

“Bakira.”

“Bakira?”

Vikir looked puzzled.

Bakira was a wolf who had grown up with Aiyen from a very young age.

She had always wondered how similar they were to Vikir, perhaps because they had similar names, and their blunt personalities.

Aiyen looked into Vikir's eyes and said.

“I think it's time to give Bakira a mate.”

“Is that so?”

“Yes. All males should have a mate when they are old enough.”

Aiyen was silent for a moment as he spoke.

Then, in a small voice, he added

“ ...And so should the females.”

Vikir's brow creased at her words.

Vikir knew that Bakira was in heat.

It wasn't just her, it was all wolves.

Wolves are in estrus all the time for males, but for females, it comes about twice a year, every seven to eight months.

Their vulvas often swell and release a bloody discharge, and lately, both male and female wolves have been keeping me awake at night, howling at the sky.

Vikir asked.

“But what do you want me to help you with?”

Aiyen nodded and answered.

“Do you remember how badly Bakira was hurt during Madame's attack?”

“I know. That's when her right leg....”

“Right, that's because of Madame's poison.”

Aiyen sighed lightly and continued.

“Bakira became a one-legged man. Not even the forelimbs, but the hind legs do that, so they can't mate properly.”

“...I see.”

In the Canidae family, mating is impossible without one hind leg. They can't balance themselves.

It was clear that without artificial help, Bakira would die out naturally.

Aiyen said.

“I want to help Bakira, can you help me?”

“...How can I help?”

Vikir said, dusting himself off and getting to his feet.

Then Aiyen grinned, his face like the color of the moon.

◆

With that, Aiyen led Vikir out of the barracks.

After passing through the village fence and wading a bit into the water, they came to an open meadow.

There, standing on three legs, was Bakira, breathing heavily.

And in front of him, a familiar wolf.

It was a young female who often accompanied Bakira on his hunts and when he returned from them.

Aiyen looked at Bakira in the distance and spoke.

“'Bakira used to be the idol of all the female wolves in the village. He was big, He was a good hunter, and his fur was lustrous.”

But after Madame's attack, everything went to hell.

Bakira lost her right hind leg, leaving her unable to hunt.

But despite this, the female was still interested in him.

“...You know the seeds are fine.”

At Aiyen's words, Vikir remembered her words from the oxbear hunt.

“The Ballak warriors' criteria for choosing a mate is much like the oxbears. An individual with good seed, but young, and if she is wounded and weak, all the better.”

Meanwhile, Bakira moaned softly at the female who had come around her and nuzzled her face.

She licked her tongue carefully over the female's body.

The female licked her fur in return.

Then they wrapped their bodies around each other in the moonlight.

Bakira moved behind her and placed her forelegs on her back.

But then.

...Thud!

One of the legs to support the back is missing, so it just falls to the side.

The female waited patiently with her eyes closed, even as she licked her nose repeatedly with her tongue.

Bakira stood up and climbed back onto the female's body, but this time, without a hind leg, he lost his balance.

Aiyen, watching from afar, narrowed her eyes.

“He's been like that since yesterday.”

“....”

Vikir nodded, too.

He could see what Aiyen was worried about.

Next, Vikir and Aiyen approached Bakira.

Aiyen limped on her right leg, which had been grazed by Adonai's poisoned arrow.

And Bakira, her friend, staggers, having lost her right leg to the Madame.

“Get up and try again.”

Aiyen says to Bakira.

Bakira didn't seem too bothered by Vikir and Ayen's approach.

That's what it means to be a trusted colleague.

The female was still waiting patiently behind them.

Bakira climbed up behind her again.

Aiyen had cut down a log to make a prosthetic leg.

But Bakira's movements were too violent for the prosthetic.

Eventually, Vikir had to hold his lower body to support his weight, and Aiyen had to press the female's hips and legs against his prosthetic to help him get into the right position.

Aiyen slapped Bakira in frustration.

“You idiot! The other side has a mind too, so be more aggressive! Push more! More! You're a male, you're supposed to be stronger!”

As she yelled, Bakira's movements changed slightly.

The female also became more cooperative and receptive.

Eventually, with a scream, the female's purpose was fulfilled.

It's a full moon night. Aiyen and Vikir stand below a female wolf and a male wolf making love.

Bakira and the female wolf clung to each other, unwilling to be separated.

And Vikir and Aiyen had to hold them together.

Then.

Bakira jerked away.

Only a few minutes had passed, but Bakira had gotten off the female's back and was trying to turn around.

Vikir sounded dejected.

“Is it over already? I just put it on.”

“No. Watch.”

Aiyen shook her head.

True to her word, the Bakira was falling off the female's body, but it wasn't.

Bakira turned around and butted up against the female.

It was a unique way for wolves to mate.

It was only after this change in position that Vikir and Aiyen were able to pull away from the two wolves.

Bakira and the female were now well on their way.

Neither Vikir nor Aiyen said a word to each other as they watched the wolves' harsh breathing.

“....”

“....”

There was an awkward air between them.

After a few minutes like that.

Bakira was finally separated from the female.

It is Mother Nature's providence that if there is a union, there is a separation.

So there was no need to be ashamed of the relationship, or regretful about the separation.

They were part of the natural order of things, as natural as the wind blowing, the rain wetting, the sun spinning, the sea surrounding, and the land connecting.

Bakira lay on her belly on the cool grassy floor.

It must have consumed a lot of stamina to stick out your tongue and gasp for not being able to sweat.

The female lay beside him, her eyes glazed over.

“ ... That's it.”

Vikir and Aiyen pulled away from Bakira.

Bakira and the female wolf remained in the meadow, nuzzling each other's faces.

Vikir and Aiyen walked back to the village, leaving the two newly married wolves behind.

It was just beginning to fog up the dawn.

“...Thank you.”

“...You too.”

Vikir waved off Aiyen's thanks.

There was a lingering sense of awkwardness in the conversation.

It hadn't happened in the past two years.

With that, Vikir walked back into the barracks.

He'd been planning to leave, but the thought of it made him feel sick.

The dampness of the barracks in the early morning light felt both familiar and foreign.

Vikir lay down on his straw bunk, but after a while, he couldn't sleep. Perhaps he would have to see the sun rise before he could sleep.

Just then.

A rustle.

The sound of something moving outside the barracks door.

I look up and see a pale shadow peeking over the curtain.

I can just make out the silhouette now.

Aiyen. For some reason, she hasn't gone to her own barracks, but is standing in front of Vikir's, hesitating over something.

“...?”

Vikir considers asking what's going on, but decides against it.

He was tired from helping Bakira mate, and he figured that if she needed anything else, she'd just barge in like she always did.

But.

Aiyen just stood there in front of Vikir's barracks for what seemed like an eternity afterward.

............

After what seemed like an eternity, the shadows slowly thinned.

“Was it an illusion?”

Vikir peered over the veil through closed eyelids.

The dawn dew slowly dried in the distant morning light. The shadow of Aiyen on the banner had vanished completely.

Vikir was already asleep.

Chapter 103

Nostalgia (4)

◆

It has been two months since Madam Eight-Legs disappeared.

Bakira had become a father.

Five wolf pups nurse in their mother's arms, a peaceful sight.

Meanwhile.

“....”

Vikir watched the female wolf nurse her pups.

A black ball was wedged between the squirming pups.

The egg of Madam Eight-Legs. It looked like a large black pearl, but it was smooth and soft to the touch.

Vikir had been trying to get the wolves to hold this egg for the past two months, just in case.

But the wolves' warmth and care hadn't made any difference to the egg.

The only thing that has changed is that the newborn puppies keep nibbling on the soft, fluffy egg and smearing it with their saliva.

Vikir realized that further experiments with Madame's eggs were pointless, and he prepared to embark on his long journey once more.

Back to the Empire. And back to Baskerville.

The return of the Ironblooded Hound.

It was time to return to where he came from.

When Vikir announced his departure from Ballak's village, not only did Ballak's warriors send envoys, but so did all the nearby tribes.

Akwilla did not stop Vikir when he declared his intention to leave. He was not a slave, so why stop him?

Once you're family, you're always family, and even if you're separated by great distances, your ties grow stronger, not weaker.

However, Akwilla invited the envoys from each tribe who had gathered to bid Vikir farewell and held a grand banquet to decorate the celebration.

Everyone at the banquet loved and respected Vikir.

But no one said “see you” or “see you again” to him.

“There are no such words in the Ballak language.”

Akwilla didn't even say anything to Vikir about looking forward to their next meeting.

“See you again” does not exist in the Ballak language.

They believe that once a relationship is formed, it is never broken, and that it transcends time and place.

They were together even when they were apart.

That's why they don't expect to say goodbye.

Akwilla spoke to Vikir in a warm voice.

“'Whenever and wherever you are. You are a Ballak hunter. And you are part of our family. Do not forget that.”

Vikir was silent for a moment.

For some reason, he felt something hot and ticklish stirring in the deepest recesses of his chest.

For the first time, a feeling of belonging settled in Vikir's heart that he hadn't felt in any other place since his return.

It was almost as if leaving Depht and returning to Baskerville was like leaving home and going to a strange place.

Akwilla continued.

“You are a proud Ballak warrior, and a hero to all of Dephts. If you are in trouble, we will help you to the best of our ability, no matter where you are or who you are up against.”

It wasn't just the warriors of Ballak who responded to Akwilla's words.

All the native tribes of the Depht, from the shamanic Rokoko to the berserker Renaissance, cheered Akwilla's words and encouraged Vikir.

“Our hero, call us anytime, we'll come to your aid!”

“Think of us sometimes! We love you!”

“Awesome, Vikir! Go back and take over the empire!”

“May the path of a hero be filled with only blessings...”

Most of all, the young men of Ballak, with whom I had cried, laughed, and slept for the past two years, were the most sad to see Vikir go.

Ahun was the worst of all. He was reduced to tears.

He thumped his chest like a gorilla and shouted.

“Vikir, you can come back anytime! We'll be here waiting for you! And if you have any problems, you can always call us!”

“Brother Vikir. You have to write to me often, you have to, or else I'm going to....”

Beside him, Aheul, who had grown much taller by now, looked at Vikir with a moist gaze.

She handed the departing Vikir a lunchbox wrapped in leaves, having grown so much in the past two years that she could hardly be considered 15 years old.

Inside was a skewer of creamy caterpillars, a precious food.

Vikir's dry smile curved the corners of his mouth.

He couldn't remember laughing much before or after his regression, but here in Depht, he laughed a lot.

He had laughed more in four months here than he had in forty years in his previous life.

“Farewell, Vikir, our hero!”

Without a 'see you later', the warriors of Ballak wave to Vikir with a mixture of amusement and regret in their eyes.

And then.

Vikir left the depht he had been fond of in the midst of everyone's farewell.

....

...No.

Not all of them.

Vikir searched the crowd for a face, but never found it.

Aiyen.

For some reason, she hadn't shown up in town since she'd heard Vikir say he was leaving town.

She didn't even show up for Vikir's farewell ceremony.

Everyone was puzzled because she usually followed Vikir wherever he went.

“...It can't be right.”

Vikir stood outside the village, glanced back at the empty Aiyen barracks, and stood there for a few seconds.

Then he turned on his heel and walked away from his beloved Ballak village.

His steps in the direction of the border of the depht were weak for the first few steps, but then they began to pick up steam.

It's really time to go home now.

◆

Vikir soon left the edge of the depht.

Standing on a high rocky peak, he could see a familiar citadel ahead.

The Crimson Castle.

It was a mining fortress built by the mages of Morgue, to mine the rubies of Red Awl Mountain.

Massive earthen walls, wooden fences, and stone buildings rose crudely but majestically.

It had apparently been hardened over the past two years to keep the natives at bay.

A land of endless veins of crimson ruby, with dark clouds gathering in swirls above.

The landscape still bathed in the ominous colors of red and black.

“...Still mining rubies?”

Vikir walked slowly toward Morgue's citadel.

He was returning after two years.

Suddenly, he remembered the face of Camus Morgue, the former head of the place. Was she still there?

If she had grown up well, she would be a mature woman now, seventeen years old and well within the marriageable age.

But that was the life of a cordinary noble families, and a Camus born into the noble society of Morgue was quite different.

'So, when are you entering the academy? Let's keep up with me. I'm probably going to get early admission by a year or two. It would be so much fun if we could be first years together....'

Suddenly, I remembered how two years ago, she had followed me around and nagged me.

“Did I tell you that I was thinking of applying for early admission to the Academy?”

Two years ago, when she was 15, she had already said that she was thinking about early admission to the Academy, so maybe she was already there.

'You must have forgotten about me.'

At 17, you're a grown up.

An eight-year-old crush would be nothing more than a shy, fading memory.

Vikir smiled dryly and headed out into the wilderness. The wind blew through the cotton fields.

...Just then.

“Hey, slave!”

A voice called out to Vikir from behind.

Turning his head, Vikir saw a silver-black-haired, pointy-eared woman, just turned nineteen, staring at him.

Aiyen. She stood with her back to the cotton wind, her eyes red with tears.

“Are you going?”

“....”

“Really?”

Aiyen asked in a deep voice, and Vikir responded with silence.

Then Aiyen stepped in front of him.

“ ... If you're going to go, take this with you.”

Vikir's eyes widened as he saw Aiyen reach out a trembling hand and give it to him.

“!”

It was a large bow. It was a black bow with a dark light all over it.

A giant bow that Adonai had used in the past.

There was even a bowstring that had never existed.

Vikir realized that the white, tough string on the black bow was made from the tanned silk of Madam Eight-Legs Spider's web.

The same tough spring from which Madame had made and stored her webs had become the string, making the black bow a complete unit.

'Anubis', the strongest bow in Ballak's history, has finally regained its perfect form.

'...I'm sorry I've been missing all this time making it.'

Vikir thought to himself as he looked down at the Black Bow.

...Thud!

Aiyen puts something around Vikir's neck.

A small black necklace.

It is a choker, an object made from the tough hide of an oxbear.

This oxbear was the first catch Aiyen and Vikir had made together.

Aiyen put the necklace around Vikir's neck and spoke in his native voice.

“ ... Don't ever let go of this thing. Anywhere.”

“Understood.”

Vikir nodded, then looked down at Aiyen.

Aiyen looked back up at Vikir.

“....”

“....”

Their positions have changed a lot in the past two years.

When they first met, Aiyen looked down at Vikir and gave him orders.

Now, it's Aiyen who can barely make eye contact with Vikir.

She was a head taller than him then, but now she's a head shorter.

Vikir, who had grown much taller, turned to Aiyen and said.

“You've gotten a lot shorter.”

It was her own joke, her own code for breaking the ice.

But Aiyen didn't respond to such lame jokes.

Just.

Mmm.

She walks in with a swift stride.

Pow!

A fist lands on Vikir's stomach.

Vikir, who was hit in the stomach out of nowhere, swallows a groan and bends over.

...Thud!

Aiyen immediately grabs the choker around Vikir's neck.

The next thing you know, Vikir is being dragged forward by the leash in Aiyen's grasp.

And then.

“...!”

The moment when Vikir, bent at the waist, and Aiyen, choker in hand, are exactly the same height.

Their lips met at the exact same height and pressed together.

....

A second, like an eternity.

How much time had passed.

Aiyen pushed hard against Vikir's chest.

She turned her back to Vikir, who had stopped breathing.

“......See you again.”

It was still an imperfect imperial language.

Chapter 108

The Returned Hero (5)

◆

It hadn't been long since Vikir's return.

Hugo Le Baskerville, the head of the iron-blooded Baskervilles family, made his move immediately upon hearing the news of Vikir's return.

His reaction was so intense that even Vikir himself hadn't not expecting it.

Hugo traveled to the Underdog's City Hall, accompanied by his butler, John Barrymore.

He came straight to the office and asked for Vikir first.

“Where is my son?”

Hugo asked, and the Chihuahua quickly led him into the office.

Vikir barely had time to greet him. Hugo burst through the office door and confronted Vikir, who was just stepping out.

“...!”

Hugo's eyes widened.

Vikir's eyes widened slightly as well.

“You're back.”

“I'm back.”

“Well done.”

“Thank you.”

The conversation is fairly dry and short for a father-son reunion.

However, Barrymore, standing behind them, watched the conversation with amusement and excitement.

“It's been a long time since I've seen my lord so happy.”

No wonder Barrymore thought this.

Hugo hadn't smiled once in the two years since Vikir's disappearance.

Not even the slightest smile.

But now Hugo was looking at Vikir and smiling.

Of course, it was almost impossible to tell, because his face was so cold and stoic.

Meanwhile.

Vikir glanced cautiously at the door to the next room.

Hugo had come in such a hurry that he hadn't hidden the Pomeranian properly.

He'd gotten her into the next room in a hurry, so she should be fine.

Then.

...Jaw!

Hugo clapped Vikir on the shoulder.

“So, how have you been?”

Vikir tensed for a moment.

He'd spent all this time building up his strength in the depht to avoid revealing his true abilities to Hugo.

As a survivor of a age of destruction, Vikir used his skillful mana-hiding techniques to keep his strength in check.

But.

“...?”

Surprisingly, he felt no pressure from Hugo's hand on his shoulder.

There was no indication that he was scanning the mana inside, or trying to get a read on it.

There was even a faint warmth to his voice that seemed out of place.

“What is it?”

Vikir is a little taken aback.

Was he just asking, genuinely curious?

Vikir searched Hugo's gaze again.

But he couldn't read anything in it. Surprise, joy, curiosity, relief?

It was like....

'Sounds like a typical father.'

Vikir furrowed his brow.

'It's one or the other.'

Either Hugo's mind had grown deeper and more sinister than even he could recognize, or his own mind had turned dull.

The night before the regression, when the rain was pouring down in torrents.

He can't forget the feel of so many teeth piercing his body.

How can he forget the man who accused him of being in league with demons and executed him?

A master of hounds, and king of all hounds.

That was Hugo Le Baskerville.

Vikir sharpened his fangs, which were almost dull, again.

And the more he did so, the softer his tone became.

“I've been concentrating on recovering from the wounds I suffered at the hands of monsters while adrift in the depths, and I've managed to establish friendly relations with some of the natives.”

Hugo's complexion brightened a bit.

“I see. You established friendly relations with the barbarians?”

“Yes.”

“That's a good thing.”

Hugo nodded. It was a rather unexpected response, given his morbid dislike of the natives of Depht.

But at Hugo's next words, Vikir could only nod in agreement.

“You must have gotten to know the barbarians well enough to know their location and strength, which would make it easier for you to wipe them out.”

Hugo still regarded the natives as something akin to demons.

Vikir hid a sigh.

“What I've learned from my time with them is that... their power is greater than I thought.”

“Hmm. That's true, especially with the Night Foxes being such a threat.”

“But I've figured out a way to control them.”

“Ho-ho, and what is that?”

Hugo asked, his face lighting up at Vikir's words.

If you ask Vikir, he always has a good answer. Hugo seemed to think so.

And this time, Vikir didn't disappoint.

“The natives of Depht are weak against the Empire's manufactured goods.”

“Manufactured goods?”

“Yes. I have confirmed that merchants from bourgeois families have been sneaking in and trading with the natives of Depht.”

Hugo's expression hardened at the words.

Then he growled in a low voice.

“A bunch of money-grubbers, and now they're trading with foreign enemies? Sooner or later, I'm going to have to cut their heads off....”

“You don't have to worry, father, I've exterminated them all.”

“What?”

“I'm a deputy magistrate in the city of Underdog, and I had them summarily executed under the authority of the acting magistrate, and of course there were no witnesses.”

Hugo's eyes widened again.

Then his gaze dropped to Vikir's, and it was replaced by a look of familiarity, of recognition.

“I see. That's just like my son. This is Baskerville.”

And then, with a gleam in his eye, Hugo asked.

“Yes, it is. You mean the bourgeois have been seducing the barbarians with their petty manufactured goods?”

“Yes. Glass beads and woolen crafts, which are cheap in the Empire, or vegetables and grain, which are precious to them. Exploiting them is a great way to keep them under control, and it's a great diplomatic gain.”

“...Hmm. But isn't that trade, not conquest?”

“It's a way to win without fighting.”

Hugo's expression turned grim for a moment.

“There is no point in fighting. The sword of Baskerville exists to draw blood from the bodies of barbarians.”

What an infernal warmonger. Vikir clucked his tongue inwardly, but didn't let it show.

“Of course barbarians will shed blood.”

“Hmm? But didn't you just say we were trading?”

“I didn't mean to suggest that we make peace with the barbarians.”

“Then?”

Vikir's eyes lit up at Hugo's question.

“I meant to use them as reinforcements for hunting demons.”

Pfft. Hugo's favorite tactic.

Hugo was quite intrigued by the idea.

“Hmmm. Let's lure them in with cheap manufactured goods and slay the demons. It's not so bad, after all, demons are also targets.”

“Yeah. I've already built the infrastructure, you just need to utilize it.”

Vikir did not want the natives of Ballak to be harmed by the Baskervilles.

Now that Madam Eight-Legs was gone, pressuring the Ballak from the west, the Ballak would escape the Baskervilles and move deeper into the watery depths of their original home.

It will no longer have any reason to encounter Baskerville Street.

The Baskervilles can easily fill the void left by Ballak's departure to the west.

Since Hugo is unaware of Madame's existence, he will see Ballak moving west and assume that he is fleeing.

For Vikir, it's a win-win: war is averted and trade is secured.

Finally, Hugo nodded.

“Very well. Then I'll leave the trade with the barbarians to you. Can you do it?”

“If you ask me to, I will do it.”

“Good.”

Hugo smiled with satisfaction at his son's loyalty, which was no different than it had been two years ago-if anything, even stronger.

It was a win-win for Vikir, too, since he would only have to wrap the already laid out board in his own merit.

Then.

“...!”

Hugo added.

“There must be a tribe among the barbarians called the Rokoko.”

“Yes. I know of them.”

“There will be no trade with them. The Rokoko tribe alone will be exterminated.”

Hugo's tone was suddenly ferocious again. He would not compromise on this point.

Vikir could only nod in silence, knowing that arguing back would undo everything they had discussed so far.

Some small talk ensued.

Most of it was similar to what he'd told the Chihuahua.

Hugo sat on the couch and listened to Vikir's report, mostly with a look of satisfaction, but occasionally with a look of surprise.

Finally, he turned to Vikir.

“Since your rescue and subsequent disappearance, we have been able to make enormous diplomatic gains in Morgue. What's more, the imperial court has heard of the tale and has awarded House Baskerville for its chivalry.”

“....”

“All of this was for nothing to a father who had lost his son.”

The more I listen, the more surprising the words become.

Even Butler Barrymore's rabbit eyes behind him echoed Vikir's sentiments.

Finally, Hugo finished.

“But it's good that you're back. It feels like things are finally falling into place.”

“....”

“I suggest that you relinquish your duties as Underdog's Deputy for the time being and get some rest, while we discuss what rewards the House can bestow upon you.”

Vikir replied briefly, then bowed, ending the conversation.

Suddenly, I had a problem.

“...The portrait in the Pomeranian pendant. Should I report it or not?”

Vikir had identified the pendant's original owner as Roxana, Hugo's first wife.

Roxana's daughter, Penelope, and Penelope's daughter, Pomeranian.

We know that Hugo's personality changed after Roxana was killed in action and her daughter, Penelope, was kidnapped in a mysterious accident by the natives of Depht.

This information is reliable because it comes directly from the pre-regression Barrymore.

Should we return this artifact, which presumably belonged to Roxana, to Hugo?

And what about the Pomeranian?

'Nope. Scratch and chew. You can't expect anything from that cold-blooded man.'

Vikir shook his head lightly.

If Hugo had any sisters or daughters, she'd know how he treated female flesh and blood, but... there were none in Baskerville, so his attitude could not be inferred.

'I'm sure he'll say something about women having weak hands for swords and not being needed. You'll be lucky if she doesn't draw her sword and say it has barbarian blood in it.'

Given Hugo's usual sullen nature, it was probably best not to mention Pomeranian.

That's how Vikir judged it.

...But.

Two things happened at once that completely upset Vikir's expectations.

“Aaahhh! Uncle!”

The side door to the next room burst open and the Pomeranian burst out.

“Woow! Uncle! It's raining outside! Thunder! Bam bam bam bam-”

Pomeranian ran into Vikir's arms, covered in tears and snot.

He was the first variable.

And then.

“...!”

Vikir's eyes widened.

The second variable was even more strange than the first.

It was the look on Hugo's face when he saw the Pomeranian.

“...! ...! ...! ...! ...! ...! ...! ...! ...! ...! ...! ...!”

Eyes perfectly circled.

A mouth that had never been seen open like that before.

A face Vikir had never seen in his two lives.

Chapter 110

The Great Banquet (2)

◆

Moonlight shone through the window, illuminating The Shadow's face.

Vikir loosened his grip on her throat.

The face beneath the golden-blonde bob was revealed.

Cindywendy. She had come in person when she heard of Vikir's return.

She winked at Vikir.

“Why don't you just stick to what you're doing, you aren't bad at it.”

“Cut the crap and tell me what you're here for.”

Vikir slid off of Cindywendy's body and sat on the edge of the bed.

She rubbed the back of her neck, which had been so tight just moments before, and smirked.

“Still living without a shoulder. Don't you ever get bored of going in a straight line like that?”

“Before I slap your ass and kick you out. Quick.”

“Wow, he's a big boy. Are you sure you're seventeen? You look like you're forty... or fifty.”

She lay on the bed at an angle, raising only her upper body as if she owned it.

She squinted up at Vikir.

“By the way. You sent a minion after me. How did you know where I was?”

“From the way you've acted in the past. Going to a crooked capitalist, building up trust by telling him of his wealth, and then stealing it all away.”

“Excuse me. I'm a financial planner, and I get paid for my work.”

A flower girl who had once amassed a great deal of wealth thanks to Vikir's special laws.

Thanks to Vikir's protection, which included a bodyguard, she was able to keep her money and lead a safe life.

But it's not just about keeping the money. She didn't know how to spend it or what to call it.

Cindywendy took advantage of that and approached the girl to work as a financial planner.

“She's doing well as a big sister now, and I've already given her a lot of money. Maybe it's because she's so nice and innocent, but she would have been scammed if it was just anyone but me.”

“I've even given him a bodyguard to protect him.”

“Bodyguards? Aren't they just there to protect people? Do they weed out scammers?”

“The bodyguards included financial experts, and I had ordered them to weed out the scammers.”

At that, Cindywendy looked puzzled.

“Those bodyguards... didn't touch anything, so I thought you were completely out of touch with finance. What?”

At her words, Vikir nodded.

“You're right. I even ordered them to let you get close.”

Vikir had thought that if word got out that the flower girl had ten billion, Cindywendy would be the first to approach her.

That was Vikir's bait and switch to lure her in, to locate her.

In the end, the 10 billion dollar bait didn't work out, as Vikir caught her right away at the slave auction, but it did help him locate her later.

After realizing all of this, Cindywendy flopped down on the bed with a dejected look on her face.

“No way. I was wondering how that Chihuahua guy knew where I was and sent the telegram, but I've been playing right into your hands the whole time. I'm dumbfounded.”

“Again.”

“...You're such an as*hole.”

Cindywendy grumbled for a moment, then slipped her hand inside her chest.

A wad of crumpled paper emerged from her chest.

She tossed the stack of papers at Vikir.

“These are the materials you asked for.”

“...Hmm. Next time, put them in the folder.”

Vikir opened the stack of papers from Xin Diwendi.

It was a list of people who would be honored at the Great Banquet tomorrow.

“I knew I'd be invited to the great feast after all my hard work. It's a good thing I did my research beforehand.”

It was to Vikir's credit that Cindywendy had come the night before the Great Banquet.

But.

“But that's only half of it.”

Cindywendy opened her mouth.

When Vikir looked up, Cindywendy pointed to her other breast.

“I'll give you the rest after you pay the information fee.”

“An information fee?”

“Did you think you were going to get it for free?”

At that, Vikir nodded silently.

Then. Vikir pulled something out of his pocket and tossed it to Cindywendy.

...With a pop!

Cindywendy's eyes widened as she caught it.

What landed in her palm was a white, pointed tooth. It was the fang of an oxbear.

She stared at Vikir in disbelief.

“That's it? Are you kidding me?”

Of course, an oxbear's tooth is priceless. They could fetch millions of gold if they were carved into chess pieces.

But if it's an information fee, it's too cheap.

Cindywendy was about to complain, but Vikir cut her short.

“There are thousands, tens of thousands more like it.”

“...?”

Cindywendy stopped what she was about to say and pricked up her ears.

Vikir spoke again.

“If you listen to me, you can get a cartload of them every year.”

He was talking about trade with all the natives of the entire jungle, including the Ballak.

Vikir is now a hero to his enemies and to all the natives who live in the depht of the Black Mountain.

In such a Vikir-led trade, the natives would gladly give up their antlers, gums, shells, truffles, and other precious forest products.

From the Empire's point of view, the trade could not be more beneficial, and the Hierarchy or Guild that would oversee this massive trade would be thrilled.

Mega deal.

If the trade actually takes place, it will open up the distribution of luxury goods on a scale never before seen in history.

Fund managers, financial planners, and others would be dazzled.

Especially for the likes of Cindywendy, a gold-digger, it was an investment he couldn't pass up.

Her mouth is watering and her eyes are glistening.

With a gleam in her eye, she pulled out the rest of the materials and thrust them in Vikir's direction.

“Do you think the barbarians will open up trade?”

“Of course.”

With the support of all the tribes, Vikir could pull off this megadeal of epic proportions.

It was the seed of a storm that could end the war and create countless other economic phenomena.

And right now, there are only two people who know about it, Vikir and Cindywendy, who has just heard about it.

Cindywendy picked herself up in a polite manner and sat down on her knees with her legs crossed in front of each other, showing Vikir the two documents.

“I guess I'll have to call you boss from now on.”

“As you wish.”

Vikir didn't seem to care about the title and went straight to the papers.

First came the first and most curious document.

It was about Pomeranian's identity.

<Pomeranian La Baskerville>

First granddaughter of Hugo Le Baskerville, head of the Baskervilles family.

Estimated age is 5 years old. It is a known fact that Hugo and his first wife, Roxana, are Penelope's children.

.

.

Vikir's interpretation was based on what he had heard from Butler Barrymore earlier.

Upon closer examination, the Pomeranian proved to be a direct descendant of Hugo.

Hugo had married a woman named Roxana when he was twenty years old.

She had given birth to Penelope La Baskerville while with Hugo and died in battle.

Later, Penelope La Baskerville died in an unexplained accident and was captured by hunters from the Rokoko tribe.

She gave birth to a daughter, Pomeranian, and died.

“There's something about this unexplained accident, too.”

Vikir thought as he looked at the bottom of the document.

Well, whatever.

Hugo's first daughter, Penelope, had disappeared about a year before Vikir was born.

Hugo was about forty-one at the time, so the timeline seemed to fit.

The fact that it was true was a relief. Vikir flipped to the next chapter of the book.

The next page detailed the official list of people scheduled to attend the dinner tomorrow.

<Hugo le Baskerville>

Rank: Patriarch

Title: Marquis

Title: Swordmaster

Other: Hugo Le Baskerville has a total of ... children, including direct descendants, illegitimate children, and adopted children outside of his lineage or bloodline. ...

(Omitted below)

.

.

It's no surprise that Hugo, the patriarch, is at the top of the list.

It was the next one that mattered.

<Boston Terrier Le Baskerville>.

Ranks: Knights of the Pit Bull – Knight Commander, Senator

Title: Count

Title: Graduator Supreme

Other: Half-brother of the Baskerville family patriarch, Hugo Le Baskerville.

Very belligerent and temperamental, hating to be tied down.

.

.

A Boston Terrier, a Knight Commander of the Knights of the Pitbull, is somehow present at the Great Banquet.

He is one of the elite of the elite, leading one of the seven Knights of the House of Baskerville, and is also one of the “Seven Counts,” representing the family's military might.

“For someone who normally dislikes formal and formal occasions like the Great Banquet,... why is he attending?”

Vikir scratched his head and flipped to the next page.

As expected, he sees an unexpected name.

<Great Dane Le Baskerville>.

Rank: Knights of the Mastiff – Knight Commander, Senator

Title: Count

Title: Graduator Supreme

Other: Half-brother of the Baskerville family patriarch, Hugo Le Baskerville.

He is reserved and reticent, unwilling to pretend to be anything but, and has a particularly bad relationship with the Count of Boston Terrier.

.

.

The Great Dane, leader of the Mastiff Knights, is also officially confirmed to attend the Great Banquet.

He is also a member of the Seventh Count, one of the pillars of Baskerville's military backbone.

They don't usually attend events within the family, so why are they attending the Great Banquet?

Especially when it's being hosted by their half-brother, who's a bit of a pain in the ass to look at.

When Vikir scratched his head, Cindywendy smirked.

“Are you even thinking about why they're coming?”

“Yes.”

“You really don't know, do you?”

Cindywendy pointed an index finger at Vikir in disbelief.

“It's because of you, I don't know why!”

“...?”

Vikir frowned, and Shindiwendi explained.

“Normally, the Senators, including the Seventh Count, don't interfere in the family's internal affairs, so why would they come to the Urrrr Great Banquet all at once? They're coming to see you, the young legend of the Baskerville family who returned alive!”

“Urrr? Are there others coming?”

“Don't be alarmed, all seven counts have requested to attend this great banquet.”

Vikir was a little surprised at that.

Seven counts.

Normally, they are rarely seen by the lesser hounds of Baskerville in their entire lives.

But the only two that had managed to make it onto the official list were a Boston Terrier and a Great Dane.

Cindywendy chuckled.

“I heard that all the other Knights Templar leaders were deployed far away, so it would take them a long time to return home. Only the Boston Terrier and the Great Dane, who were sent out on missions closer to home, were able to make it in time, and even then, they'll be arriving in a hurry.”

“Hmmm. I don't suppose they're just curious to see my face.”

“Of course not. They're here because they want to take you into their order, to set their sights on a future knight, and they've heard that other than Boston Terriers and Great Danes, all the other knights are stomping their feet because of the distance.”

The Great Banquet is a rare event that only direct blood relatives can attend, so they can't send a proxy.

So only two of the seven counts, who were relatively close by, rode through the night in good spirits to return home.

“We'll see tomorrow. I'll be bombarded with scouting offers for a while.”

Cindywendy giggled.

The pinnacle of two orders, the Pit Bull Knights and the Mastiff Knights, rumored to be at odds with each other.

And with a very tasty piece of meat between them.

Perhaps a Boston Terrier or a Great Dane, or both, will try to win Vikir over to their order.

“ But Vikir's response is short.”

“ ... I'm not interested in either of them.”

He just hopes it doesn't come to that.

Vikir read the following documents

At this point, important figures began to appear.

<Osiris Le Baskerville>.

Rank: Member of the House of Representatives

Title: Viscount

Title: Graduator Supreme

Other: The eldest son of Hugo Le Baskerville, the patriarch of House Baskerville. Currently first in line of succession.

.

.

The next generation of Baskervilles.

A cold, heartless genius. An ultra-elite who's growing up to be what Hugo once was.

He can already draw six teeth with the tip of his blade, and his swordsmanship is said to be on par with that of the Seven Counts.

Rumor has it that he will soon reach the rank of Swordmaster.

“...Osiris.”

Vikir was silent for a moment.

Before his regression, Vikir had seen Osiris a few times as a child, at a distance.

He was extremely reticent and cold.

He never said hello to anyone, not even his own siblings, let alone those of his direct lineage.

But it wasn't as if he had brothers who could speak to him before his overwhelming skill and charisma.

So he was always alone. A solitary, tortured genius.

Cindywendy looked at him and said.

“Aside from the Patriarch and the Seven Counts, he must be the strongest in the Baskerville Family, right?”

“....”

“No, maybe you're more...?”

Cindywendy sneakily tried to gauge Vikir's combat strength.

Vikir shrugged it off and turned the page.

<Seth Le Baskerville>

Rank: Underdog City Magistrate-Councilor

Title: Viscount

Rank: Intermediate Graduator

Other: Second son of Hugo Le Baskerville, the patriarch of House Baskerville. Currently second in line of succession.

.

.

The next presence was one that was still vivid in Vikir's memory.

Seth Le Baskerville.

His talent for swordsmanship was far inferior to his older brother's, and he had been particularly sickly from an early age.

So even when his brother Osiris was knighted for his prowess in battle against demons, he was only given the honorary title of Viscount.

His personality was unusually gentle and affectionate for a Baskerville, but this only made him appear weak and withdrawn to Hugo.

Hugo was especially cold and strict with his second son, Seth.

Seth, however, never lost his gentle nature.

He was the only one in the family to shed a tear for the hounds dying like garbage.

Vikir had seen Seth lay chrysanthemums at the memorial more than once.

“Hmph. I heard you were in training for the closing ceremony... but you must have stepped out to attend the great banquet.”

Vikir flipped through the information.

As he read slowly, his expression became more and more expressionless.

Then.

Vikir spotted a familiar name at the bottom of the document.

<Highbro Le Baskerville>

Rank: Academy Candidate

Title: Young Master (Shadow)

Rank: Sword Expert Advanced

Other: Direct descendant of Hugo Le Baskerville, patriarch of House Baskerville.

.

.

<Middlebro Le Baskerville>

Rank: Academy Candidate

Title: Young Master (Shadow)

Rank: Sword Expert Advanced

Other: Direct descendant of Hugo Le Baskerville, patriarch of House Baskerville.

.

.

<Lowbro Le Baskerville

Rank: Academy Candidate

Title: Young Master (Shadow)

Rank: Sword Expert Advanced

Other: Direct descendant of Hugo Le Baskerville, patriarch of House Baskerville.

.

.

“Another set of unexpected names.”

Vikir closed the file with a dry chuckle.

He was beginning to look forward to tomorrow's great banquet.

Chapter 112

The Great Banquet (4)

◆

“...?”

Vikir's mouth dropped open slightly in disbelief.

Hugo, the patriarch of the family and organizer of the Great Banquet, had been watching his siblings argue with an amused expression on his face.

The Boston Terrier and the Great Dane continued to argue.

Both dogs are normally more likely to bite than bark, but in Hugo's presence, they seem to be restrained.

Vikir studied Hugo's expression.

'...Why is he smiling like that? No way.'

It didn't take him long to come to a conclusion.

Every day in Baskerville, there are fierce battles.

Patriarch. Below him, under the umbrella of the Seventh Count, there are countless lines, each with its own independent factions.

Beyond the shadows, assassinations, framings, duels, mergers, acquisitions, and deals are made in a bloody game of nerves and politics.

It's not uncommon for one faction to keep another in check, and Hugo, the pinnacle of the Ironblade family, is no exception.

It's his job to keep an eye on his half-brothers and sisters who are rising in power within the family, as well as those from outside the family.

Ironically, the brother he should be closest to is the most feared enemy within the Baskervilles.

Hugo's greatest enemy, then, was the Seventh Count.

A fight between a Boston Terrier and a Great Dane would eventually lead to a split in the Count's ranks, which in turn would lead to more power for the Patriarch.

So Hugo probably wouldn't condemn this kind of power struggle among the counts.

In fact, he would likely encourage it.

“A cunning man, indeed.”

Vikir clicked his tongue.

Suddenly, Hugo's eyes shifted to Vikir.

When Vikir lowered his gaze to his plate, Hugo spoke in a low voice.

“It's good to see my son being recognized.”

What the hell is that supposed to mean?

Vikir looks up and sees Hugo's face, still wearing an extremely faint smile.

It's an extremely faint smile.

As Vikir stood there dumbfounded, Butler Barrymore sneaked up behind him and whispered in his ear.

“It is said that all seven of the Counts wished to attend the great banquet, all to see you, though the other five were too far away to come.”

“...Is that so?”

“The patriarch seems to be in a good mood, seeing his usually high-minded and dutiful siblings so restless. I wonder whose child you are.”

Vikir turned his head again.

...So that smile wasn't just him taking pleasure in seeing his siblings' division?

That he was actually happy to see his son recognized?

“It can't be.”

Vikir shook his head.

Not Hugo, who had no blood or tears.

Vikir shook his head and tried to focus on the meal.

Soon, the meal began to enter its main course.

One main dish after another.

It didn't take long before the table was set with an enormous feast.

“Thank God it's not haggis anymore.”

Vikir felt a little better knowing that he wouldn't have to eat the tasteless, filling haggis anymore.

Meanwhile.

“I see our Count Dane is trying to eat things raw again. Nature cannot be fooled.”

“How many glasses of wine have you had already? I think you're very drunk. Go to bed.”

The Boston Terrier and Great Dane were still fighting.

By now, they realized that growling at each other was a losing proposition.

And from then on, they both tried to get one more word out of Vikir.

“Yeah. Vikir, you've spent the last two years living in the depths of the Black Mountains with your enemies, so tell me about your experiences. This uncle is very curious. How many barbarians have you slain, and how many beasts have you torn apart? Ah! My blood boils just thinking about it! The blood of a pit bull, I mean, in my day, when I was eight years old, and had just been dropped by the enemy into the depths of the Black Mountains to take my practical examination, and had just competed with my brother Patriach in a hunt; but my nephew has done more than that, and I am very proud of him!”

“My brave and clever nephew, this uncle will not ask you such frivolous things. Of course, I am very curious to know how my dear nephew spent his time in the treacherous depht, but that is for you to read in your report later. But this uncle wants to ask you something else first. I know it's awkward coming home after two years, so if you need anything, just say so. This uncle will get you anything....”

Even the servants hiccupped in surprise at the normally reticent pair showing such a vulnerable side.

Vikir smiled weakly.

The Boston Terrier was openly curious about Vikir's life in the depths, and so was the Great Dane, though he pretended not to be.

But Hugo cut him off.

“Just let him eat, don't be too polite.”

He put his arm around Vikir.

The two counts grunted and stepped back while Vikir was still adjusting to this strange favor.

“Still, as a true uncle, I am curious to see how my nephew has grown over the past two years....”

“That's right. I can't help but wonder how much my nephew, who was so amazing two years ago, has accomplished in the meantime, so I rode my horse all those miles....”

The two counts still couldn't let go of their regrets. Hugo's brow furrowed slightly.

“So. Are you saying you're going to torture my son right here at the table?”

“Well, not that.”

“...Ck.”

Even the Seventh Count doesn't cower in the face of Hugo's momentum.

The Boston Terrier and Great Dane look away, unable to find the main event.

Then.

A voice saves them both.

“Proof of accomplishment is not difficult.”

It was Vikir.

Vikir's words brought color to the faces of the Boston Terrier and the Great Dane.

Hugo sounded unusually concerned.

“Hmm. Still, my son, it would be tiring to talk about such things over a meal when you need to go out on the stage to prove your accomplishments, and you've come a long way.”

“It's okay, father, and....”

Vikir set his fork down on the table.

Then he spoke.

“I can show you my skills anytime, anywhere. Life is all about practice, isn't it?”

At that, the faces of Hugo, the Boston Terrier, and the Great Dane brightened with satisfaction.

“Brother. You sure did a good job raising your son.”

“That's right, and if I had a son like that, I'd really wish for nothing.”

“Hmph. Enough of that. What's this....”

Hugo turns away, tugging at his mustache.

Butler Barrymore watched him with an amused expression.

“By the way, how do you prove your skills?”

The Boston Terrier asks.

The Great Dane stares at Vikir inquisitively, too.

Vikir doesn't answer.

He simply raised his hand and placed it still on the table.

“....”

There was a slight pause.

Then, after a long moment of silence, Vikir's mouth opened.

“I think Uncle Dane's steak is slightly undercooked.”

At the same time, Vikir turned his head to look at the Boston Terrier.

“Uncle Terrier has too much wine in his glass.”

With that, the Boston Terrier and the Great Dane looked at each other's steaks and wine.

Then.

Something amazing happened.

Tsk, tsk, tsk...

Vikir's hand twitched, and the utensils on the table rattled slightly.

The Boston Terrier and the Great Dane immediately took their hands off the table.

The mana from Vikir's body was flowing onto the table.

And then.

A strange phenomenon occurred before the two counts' eyes.

Chiiiiig...

The Great Dane's steak began to sizzle and cook.

Nothing changed around them, but only one side of the steak was being cooked by the intense heat.

The blood dried and steam rose.

The steak had gone from rare to well-done.

“...Hurr.”

The Great Dane picked up his fork.

The fork was right next to the plate of steak, but it wasn't hot at all.

He dug in, and the meat was firm, with just the slightest hint of charring.

Meanwhile.

“Kahahahaha!”

The Boston terrier was also laughing, looking at the glass of wine in front of him.

Bubbling, bubbling, bubbling...

The wine in the silver goblet boils purple.

In the blink of an eye, the wine turned to vapor and disappeared, sending a sweet smell throughout the banquet hall.

The bubbling wine reached the waist of the goblet and stopped boiling.

Exactly half of it had vaporized and disappeared.

Just by placing his palm on the table, he cooked meat and brewed wine.

He could touch things and channel mana into them, causing them to explode exactly where he wanted them to.

What would happen if that was applied to swordsmanship?

You would be able to channel mana into your sword and produce an aura of the desired strength and viscosity at the desired point.

And that's what the world calls it.

“Graduator.”

Before Swordmaster. The most mature stage a great swordsman can reach. They symbolize the power of the Empire.

Vikir was an intermediate Graduator, a level that even the geniuses of Baskerville could only reach around the age of thirty-five.

A seventeen year old Intermediate Graduator. The youngest ever.

It was enough to shatter all official records of the Baskervilles up to this point.

Chapter 114

The Great Banquet (6)

◆

Seth Le Baskerville. He had been speaking to Vikir in a gentle, friendly manner since earlier.

“How is it to be home after a long time? Is it hard to adjust? Does your brother help you?”

“My father and brother are a bit cold, aren't they, but they're being incredibly gentle with you, because you're young and talented, and for someone like me who has no talent, they're like icy....”

“Try this, too. It's specially prepared by my favorite chef. It's delicious, isn't it? Sturgeon roe baked with cream~”

“I'll come to your room later, so tell me about your experience in the depht. I'm weak, so I'm always in the medical or pulmonary training hall. Oh, my training hall is also very close to Underdog City, where you were the deputy chief!”

“Come to think of it, thanks to you, the city of Underdog became much more peaceful, right? It's a good thing. Originally, I should have been there as an deputy...... I have a weak body and little talent, so it is a burden to sit in an important seat.”

“It would be nice to have a brother as capable as you to help me run things, haha-”

Seth talks to Vikir constantly for the sake of not making him feel awkward.

He even greets the servants who bring him food one by one.

A normal half-breed hound would be overwhelmed by this kindness and friendliness from Seth.

So would Vikir before the regression.

But.

The post-Regression Vikir is different.

“....”

Vikir stared into Seth's face as he spoke softly to him.

For a long time, Seth had been unusually good-hearted and caring for the people around him.

Because of this, he was not well-liked by Hugo or Osiris, and because of this, he was always sad and sullen.

The younger Vikir, before his regression, had a liking for him.

...But.

Now, as a seasoned veteran of the Age of Destruction and an iron-blooded hound, Vikir saw Seth in a different light.

'Seth Le Baskerville' was presumably not human.

Vikir recalled the information Cindywendy had sent him last night.

In truth, he didn't need to recall it.

The stench from Seth's mouth had been making him sick to his stomach.

The kind of odor that would make even the most squeamish Vikir struggle to keep a straight face.

But no one else in the vicinity could smell the stench emanating from Seth.

Vikir knew exactly what it was.

“It's the smell of a demon.”

This intense stench, a mixture of soaking intestines and rotting corpses, could only be smelled by hounds from the Age of Destruction.

Before my return, I was numb to the smell of the world because it was so omnipresent, but when I smelled it in the peaceful world after my return, I knew it at once.

Fahrr...

It was an unholy scent, so foul that even Beelzebub, who lurked in the veins of his arteries, and even the wraith of Madame, who was imprisoned in Beelzebub's orb, were frightened.

'Why does Seth's body emit such a foul odor?'

Vikir quickly regained his composure.

Next, Vikir sipped from his goblet.

The red glistening surface reflected the images of Hugo, Osiris, and Seth.

But.

To Vikir's surprise, there were only two reflections in the glass.

Hugo and Osiris. There was no reflection of Seth in the glass.

'See?'

Vikir wondered to himself.

Demons. Beings of the demonic realm.

They are generally divided into demons and beasts.

The difference between the two is that demons refer to higher demons with spirituality, while demonic beasts refer to monsters.

This is similar to the distinction between humans and animals.

While a typical demonic beast can be seen in a mirror and reflected in water..., this was not the case with demons.

They cannot be seen in mirrors or water unless they use special magic to deliberately conceal their appearance.

It's something that everyone will learn (and pay for expensive lessons) in the Age of Destruction, but for now, no one knows.

...Except for Vikir, that is.

'You let your guard down, Seth.'

Vikir thought as he drained his glass.

Seth had become too arrogant to even bother watching his glass.

He might be wearing the shell of the second son, but underneath, he was likely a completely different person.

Vikir recalled the testimonies of those around him about Seth.

'Master Seth, he's a good man. When he was younger, he was blunt and cold, like most of the other Baskervillians, but since... 'that unfortunate incident,' he's changed a lot. I'd say he's become softer.'

'What? The unfortunate incident? Oh, by the way, I'm only telling you this for Master Vikir's sake... In fact, Master Seth once attempted suicide, the night he was severely scolded by his master for his lack of talent....'

'Luckily, we caught him early enough to save his life, but he was so traumatized by it that he's been completely gentle and affectionate ever since, probably because of that near-death experience....'

Once upon a time, Vikir had started a small fire in Baskerville's great library.

He had covered it up for the servants when they became restless, and they had been friendly to him ever since.

Based on the information he'd gotten from the servants, Vikir reasoned.

'The real Seth probably died that day, and the ... demon took over the empty shell.'

Suddenly, another thought occurred to him.

Generally speaking, for demons, the blood of human children is treated as a medicine.

As Cindywendy's investigation revealed, the large-scale abduction in Underdog was not just focused on abduction.

Orphans have disappeared from numerous orphanages and childcare foundations.

They were adopted here and there through formal or informal channels, and then all were lost.

They only existed on paper.

Cindywendy used money and informants to track down the missing children.

The last place they had in common was the training center where Seth Le Baskerville was practicing.

It's a neighborhood not far from the city of Underdog.

“After I took over a childcare foundation, I investigated the adoption route of the children in the name of donations, and I finally found out about this illegally.”

I can see Cindywendy's face in my head.

Vikir listened very carefully, for this was also the reason why he had been executed before his regression.

Demons suck the blood of children.

Vikir, who was serving Seth at the time, was accused of being in league with the demons because a large number of bones with the blood of young children were found in the cellar near his room.

And executed. He regressed.

'Maybe... really maybe, Hugo is not guilty.'

It was unlikely, but not impossible.

Hugo, who knew nothing, might have executed Vikir out of sheer selfishness.

He might have been fooled by the conspiracy of his second son, Seth.

Vikir thought grimly.

“The question is, how far has Seth's soul eroded?”

A stench this strong means it's almost 100% consumed.

Seth must have harbored a lot of resentment, hatred, inferiority complexes, lack of affection, and self-destructive feelings towards his father and brother before he died, and that's how you open the door to your soul and invite demons in.

Vikir stroked his chin once.

The realization that the only master he had ever followed before his regression was actually the mastermind of the Dead Dog Cooking does not shake him.

Instead, I felt my blood run cold.

But Seth, unaware of Vikir's secret, continued to speak to him in a friendly manner.

“So, little brother, which of the Knights do you like best? I like the Wolfhounds the best. Well, pit bulls and mastiffs are good, too. Oh, and personally, I used to like the Doberman Knights best when I was a kid, they have the coolest uniforms!”

“....”

“So, now that you're back home, what are you going to do, get into the academy after all? Well, that's what your brother Osiris did. Or are you going to stay on at Underdog as a Deputy Magistrate, I heard your favorite citizens were protesting for a permanent position? Maybe we can work together when I return to the Magistrate's office!”

Seth rambled on while Vikir stabbed a piece of meat with his fork.

Vikir was just about to frown at the foul odor from Seth's mouth.

“Moderation.”

Osiris interrupted Seth.

When Seth shut up, Osiris spoke in a cold tone.

“How chatty you are, even though you haven't finished your meal.”

“....”

“Finish your meal and don't interrupt your brother's meal with your chatter.”

With that, Seth shut up and bowed his head.

Vikir was finally freed from the stench of demons on Seth's breath.

'It's different seeing you like this.'

Vikir pulled back slightly and watched the relationship between Osiris and Seth.

The younger Vikir, before the regression, would have understood what had just happened as Osiris persecuting Seth.

What had just happened would have been seen as the cold and arrogant firstborn driving a wedge between the other middle children.

In fact, the servants around him were making eye contact, indicating that Osiris had gone too far.

They pitied Seth, who shook his head in disbelief.

But only then did Vikir see the relationship between Osiris and Seth.

Osiris felt an indescribable discomfort and distance from Seth, which was why he was trying to keep his other siblings away from him.

This is why he frowned at Seth whenever he opened his mouth, as if he smelled a bad odor.

In other words, Osiris's genius instincts and senses are subconsciously disliking Seth's demonic nature.

It was the same with Hugo.

'...So perhaps I, who served under Seth before my regression, had a chin to look good on.'

Vikir turned and looked at Osiris.

Though cold and distant, there was a glimmer of humanity beneath.

So much more human than Hugo.

Besides, Osiris had been looking out for Vikir, a newcomer to the Great Banquet, in his own way.

Even if it was in his own way.

“Vikir. Knife #3 should not be held in your hand.”

“Tilt the plate to the other side. Don't make a scraping sound with your utensils.”

“You need to brush up on your aristocratic dining etiquette. Napkins are not folded in that direction.”

It may seem like a high-pressure lecture, but it's really just a way to keep an eye on your younger brother to make sure he doesn't make a mistake in front of your father or other adults in the house.

And there was no reason to be offended because he was only pointing out the things that were wrong, and he only chose the right words.

If there's something wrong, you just fix it, and Osiris doesn't say much about the improvement.

Of course, if it were a normal child, they would have been scared and cowered.

'He's a bit of a jerk, but... doesn't seem as bad as I thought he was.'

Not so with Vikir.

After three scoldings, Vikir demonstrated such good table manners that he didn't need to be scolded anymore.

Only then did Osiris' lips curl into a slight smile of satisfaction.

“I see. Now there's a bit of nobility.”

The clumsy warmth grows a little stronger.

◆

With that, the long meal came to an end.

The Baskerville family's Great Banquet takes two hours for the appetizers alone and about five hours for the entire meal.

By the time it was over, it was nearly midnight.

Vikir was about to leave the banquet hall.

“...Wait.”

Hugo stopped him.

“There's something I need to talk to you about, son.”

“Yes, Father.”

Vikir stood upright in front of Hugo.

Hugo stared at him for a moment, then spoke.

“No, no. It's late today, so come back tomorrow morning.”

“Do you have any further engagements after midnight?”

“No, I don't. I just thought you might be tired.”

Vikir was surprised again.

Even though he had no plans afterward, Hugo was willing to wait until tomorrow morning because he was afraid he'd be tired?

This Hugo who only knew his own time?

He was the kind of man who would turn on the lights of the entire castle and rouse all the humans from their slumber at midnight or dawn if he had to.

He would put off speaking to his son until the morning for dread of his tiredness.

The servants drew the curtains of the western windows early, instead of the eastern ones, for the sun might rise in the west tomorrow.

Vikir's tongue was still in his cheek.

“....”

Vikir bowed his head, his expression nonchalant.

Then, as Hugo left the banquet hall, Vikir and Butler Barrymore were alone.

Butler Barrymore turned to Vikir with a smirk on his face.

“Perhaps the Lord is calling to discuss your admission to the Academy. Congratulations in advance, Master.”

“How do you know that?”

Vikir asked, and Butler Barrymore spoke in a tone of certainty, as if he had known it would happen.

“Because I received a letter from the Academy last night announcing the new class.”

Chapter 115

The Great Banquet (7)

◆

Vikir left the main hall where the Great Banquet was being held.

He had just stepped out of the main gate and turned into the path between the training grounds and the castle.

“....”

Vikir had to stop in his tracks at the mouth of the training grounds.

There was life beyond the bushes, a blatant hallucination.

Then a black stalk snaked toward him.

An aura as sticky as honey and as red as blood, a sword strike that only a Top Graduator could unleash.

Six teeth sliced through the air, aiming for Vikir.

'Should I fight back?'

Vikir thought for a moment.

An attack of that caliber could be blocked and countered.

But Vikir was only an Intermediate Graduator, and there were only so many ways he could react in a situation like this.

Vikir draws his longsword from his belt, deflects the blow, and rolls to the side to correct his stance.

The number of teeth Vikir drew in that brief moment was four. Six teeth that flew out.

Four of the teeth bumped into each other and canceled each other out, leaving only two teeth aimed at Vikir.

Vikir decided to just take them with his body.

With the protection of the Styx River, Vikir's body instantly turned to black iron.

Kkaang! Ttang!

Unsurprisingly, the sword, which contained an intermediate Graduator aura broke into two, and a handful of the hem of the cloak was torn off.

Quack, quack, quack!

The strike flew off in a deflected trajectory, leaving a large scar on the ground.

The two teeth that made contact with his body scattered on their own before he could fight off Styx's protection.

“...!”

Vikir realized that the attack hadn't flown to harm him in the first place.

Instead, he heard laughter coming from beyond the bushes.

“My nephew, you're grown up.”

The Earl of Boston Terrier. One of the Seven Counts, he smiled wryly at Vikir.

Vikir straightened his stance in front of the Boston Terrier. He stood in front of the Boston Terrier and straightened his stance.

The Boston Terrier's eyes sparkled as he realized that Vikir was even more precious.

Then.

“Who goes on a rampage with a knife in the house?”

Someone stood between the Boston Terrier and Vikir.

A hulking man, his black hair whipping around him. It was the Earl of Great Dane.

He glared at the Boston Terrier.

“Attempted murder,” he said, “and if your brother knows about it, you'll be on probation for at least a few months.”

“Do not discredit your uncle's affection for his niece.”

“Affection? Hiding and letting go of the sword is affection?”

“Kids grow up fighting.”

“You're a f*cking kid, are you?”

At the Great Dane's words, the Boston Terrier bared his teeth under his sunglasses.

“Stay out of the next pit bull's business and go on your way.”

“The next pit bull? Maybe the next mastiff. I can't believe we're sending our darling niece to such a ragtag bunch of misfits.”

“A bunch of big mutt bastards, begging for their lives with their guts spilling out at the slightest crack in their stomachs.”

“Hoo hoo hoo. You're so big, there's no skin to tear.”

The Boston Terrier leading the pit bulls and the Great Dane leading the mastiffs were snarling at each other tensely, neither giving an inch.

Now that there was no Hugo, they could go at it with impunity.

“Good! Whoever wins here gets Vikir!”

“Anything for the future of my beloved nephew!”

The two counts drew their swords and faced each other.

“....”

Vikir had long since walked away.

'Troublesome people.'

He'd expected the brash Count Boston Terrier to be pestering him to show him exactly what he was capable of.

It was a good thing he had an opponent, the Count of Great Danes, who was a bit of a handful.

Meanwhile, Vikir recalled the force of the earlier blow.

'That was more than I expected.'

Before the regression, the Seventh Counts were the highest level of Graduators, and the current Seventh Counts were equally accomplished.

Vikir was also a top Graduator, but the difference between them was in the level of swordsmanship they used.

Now, however, Vikir had mastered the seventh form of Baskerville and was more accomplished than the seventy counts who had mastered the sixth form of Baskerville.

And with the protection of the River Styx and the power of the magic sword Beelzebub?

'I can take on one seventh count, but not two.'

Who would believe that this was an accomplishment at only seventeen?

Vikir closed his eyes, planning his next move.

“Brother!”

He hears another voice calling out to him from behind.

He turns to see what it is, and a sickening stench hits his nostrils.

Seth Le Baskerville. Hugo's second son.

He's looking at Vikir with a big smile on his face.

“Where are you sleeping tonight?”

“....”

“If you don't have plans, why don't you sleep at my castle, it's not far from here.”

Vikir watched Seth's mouth twitch with excitement.

What in the world lurked beneath that shell that made him reek so badly?

Perhaps it is evil, but it is not ordinary evil.

We already have some evidence that Seth is responsible for numerous kidnappings and the disappearance of adopted children, thanks to the testimony of Cindywendy and Chihuahua.

This was also the most damning and conclusive of the accusations against Vikir before his regression.

“...And there was more.”

Some of the additional information that Cindywendy brought to the table were things that Vikir hadn't even guessed about.

For example, it was Seth's mother who sent two venomous snakes to Vikir's cradle when he was an infant, and it was Seth who kidnapped Hugo's oldest daughter, Penelope, from the Rokoko tribe.

Cindywendy uncovered how Seth's men had purchased two bloody mambas from the natives of Depht seventeen years earlier, and further uncovered how Penelope's walking route and itinerary had been leaked to the Rokoko.

Both were uncovered while preparing to trade with the tribes of Depht on Vikir's behalf.

'How fitting, then, that it was Ah'Heman of Ballak who sold the Bloody Mamba ....'

Vikir smiled dryly. He had unintentionally paid off a debt from his infancy.

Well, whatever.

The reason Seth hadn't been taken as a suspect was because he'd been playing his usual good-natured, soft-spoken self.

He wouldn't have been a suspect at all if he hadn't been wearing a child's body at the time.

So Vikir could only stare at the set, or rather, the shell of a set, in front of him now, and stare at this strange thing that had been pressed against Baskerville Street for decades.

“So, little brother, what are you going to do now, come back as the Underdog's Deputy Commissar or enter the Academy?”

Seth remained at Vikir's side, trying to be friendly.

Then. A voice interrupted him.

“I said moderation, Seth.”

Osiris. He rode in on his horse, separating Seth and Vikir once again.

He turned to Vikir and Seth with a stern look.

“Do not speak loudly in the presence of nature, and since it is late at night, we will save this conversation for another time.”

A stranger would have thought he was a jerk.

Vikir, before his regression, had thought similarly.

But having read Osiris's true intentions, Vikir simply bowed his head.

“I'll see you next time and say hello, brothers.”

Osiris' expression softens slightly at Vikir's words, while Seth's face hardened.

But it's hard to tell if it's praise or resentment.

Vikir's demeanor was very formal, and as such, not exactly flawless.

The eldest son spoke, and with good reason. It was the elder son's word against the younger son's.

Even Osiris could not help but admire Vikir's skillful way of looking out for his own interests in the most neutral and objective way possible.

◆

There are many castles in Baskerville that have been around for a long time.

As a result, there are many remote and hidden corners.

Vikir had come to Yuasa Castle today in search of a temporary place to stay.

His room, where he had spent many hours as a child.

He crossed the entrance to a flooded cellar and climbed a spiral staircase through abandoned food storage and unrepaired cracks.

Vikir walked through these dank corridors, recalling memories from decades ago.

A moment.

A strange sense of déjà vu hits him.

Vikir stopped in his tracks and turned his head.

There was a scene that reminded him of ten years ago.

The triplets of House Baskerville, aka the Trident of Baskerville.

Highbro Le Baskerville, Middlebro Le Baskerville, and Lowbro Le Baskerville.

The half-brothers, who hadn't spoken a word to each other since meeting at the Great Banquet, stood.

Now eighteen years old, they had grown to full height, and their jawlines had thickened.

“....”

“....”

“....”

They still had the same stiff demeanor whenever they were in Vikir's presence.

Vikir, meanwhile, wore a dry smile.

It's pretty obvious what he's waiting for in this dingy, remote place at sword-point.

“What?”

I asked, ready to draw my sword at a moment's notice.

And then.

Thud.

The triplets wordlessly drew the swords from their waists.

They didn't emit any auras, but the energy emanating from their bodies seemed to have some sort of hard resolve.

'I must kill them.'

Vikir made a decision. A hound that can't cover its shit and sinks its teeth in like this is no answer.

A killing blow.

This was a good time to bury what happened in the depht two years ago.

...?

The triplets then began to react in a way that even Vikir hadn't anticipated.

...Shaking.

All three knelt on their right knees in front of Vikir, heads bowed.

The tips of their drawn swords rested on the insteps of their right feet, the tips of their handles pointed at Vikir.

“...?”

Vikir's face contorted in bewilderment.

This was the oath of the knights of the Empire when they met their destined masters.

Chapter 117

Falling in Love (2)

◆

Vikir felt goosebumps creep over his entire body.

Goosebumps rose on his forearms.

'...What did I just hear?

LOVE. LOVE.

It was a word so unexpected that even a seasoned warrior, a man who had seen it all and had survived the Age of Destruction, would doubt the ears that had protected his life for so long.

Hugo is the last person in the world you would expect to hear the word love.

I never thought I'd hear it from his lips.

Vikir felt his entire strategy crumble in the first chapter.

And then, as if on cue, Hugo said, with distaste and disgust.

“Yes. She was the love of my life, and I hate to say it, but we fell in love at first sight.”

Hugo's answer was almost a monologue. Hearing it, Vikir thought to himself.

'I never asked.'

He doesn't need to hear the full answer. Vikir is just about to say the next thing.

“I was a retarded high marquis, and Roxana was a commoner with nothing, but the moment we looked into each other's eyes, we knew that neither our backgrounds nor our origins could separate us.”

Vikir thought for a moment after hearing that.

'I didn't ask.'

But Hugo kept muttering.

“Yes, indeed. Certainly, our love was turbulent. From the first moment I laid eyes on her, I felt a passion that shook me to my very soul, but she didn't. She tried to get away from me because her lowly origins were a nuisance to me, and I followed her, forsaking everything I had. Yes, for her sake, I would have given up everything-not just my body, but my soul.”

“Mmm. Yes. Father. Thank you for your answer. Now, I must ask you to....”

“But! Our love has been put to the test once more. The Baskervilles set up a chaser.”

“....”

Vikir wasn't particularly curious, but he decided to listen anyway.

Hugo continued to speak through gritted teeth.

The love affair that ensued between Hugo and Roxana was a rough one.

A typical romance-fantasy cliché. But the sentiment is timeless.

Hugo Le Baskerville is a cold-hearted flower child and a genius at everything.

And Roxana, a poor, spirited, and cheerful girl.

Their love defied all odds and eventually found a happy ending.

Quarreling over minor misunderstandings, crying and laughing at the supporting characters who tried to steal their love, and sometimes crying out at the harshness of fate, they finally overcame the opposition of their two parents and brought their love to fruition.

Vikir nodded thoughtfully.

“...Was that Penelope?”

Penelope la Baskerville.

At the mention of the name, Hugo's pupils fluttered once more.

His reaction was even more intense than when I mentioned Roxana.

“What the hell kind of answer do you want to hear!”

“....”

Hugo sighed in disbelief as Vikir remained completely nonchalant.

“Oh, yeah. That's right. My first child, Penelope She was.”

Hugo shuddered for a moment as he said the name, Penelope.

Vikir stared at him blankly.

He'd never seen an absolute powerhouse with a foot in the realm of the Supreme so shaken.

Perhaps not even Butler Barrymore, who had served him his entire life, had ever seen him so shaken.

Hugo opened his mouth.

“Roxana was a weak woman. She died of illness not long after giving birth to Penelope, and I raised her alone.”

Penelope was a bright and cheerful child.

She inherited a strong spirit from Hugo and a kind heart from Roxana, and she grew to be the favorite of all the Baskervilles.

And then one day. “The accident” happened.

Out for a walk, Penelope was captured by the Rokoko tribe, who were out hunting humans.

No one knows how the invaders learned of Penelope's route.

Known as a cannibalistic tribe, the Rokoko kidnapped Penelope and disappeared into the depths of the Black Mountain with their enemies from that day forward.

And from that day forward, Hugo went mad.

The swordmaster with the heart of a furnace and the blood of iron abandoned all his assets and power in the ecliptic and moved his entire family to the margins.

His reasoning was to expand the empire's territory by exterminating the demons and barbarians of the depth.

Hugo then abandoned all of his wealth and threw himself into his work like a madman.

His cold-blooded grasp of the weapon has left countless enemy generals lying on the ground.

But he could only do so much alone.

In his quest to slay every last one of the barbarians on the continent, Hugo multiplied his wives through a series of arranged marriages and produced children who shared his martial prowess.

The emperor gave the marquis, who had withdrawn from the center of power and asked to be sent to the remote regions, every support.

There were no restrictions on the number of soldiers and no surveillance.

Taxes were waived, and countless grants were handed out in various guises.

Hugo threw everything he had at the task and continued to rebuild the empire.

For decades.

A great family on the margins, yet untouchable by anyone in the Imperial ecliptic.

Baskerville, House of Ironblood, was born.

Vikir nodded at the words.

'...I see. Somehow, even when I joined hands with that hated Morgue, I knew something was wrong.'

Vikir remembered what Butler Barrymore had hinted at at the time.

Hugo had agreed to join the Morgue at Red Salt Castle because he had heard that a girl of Morgue descent had been taken by the Rokoko tribe.

Did he recognize his first daughter, Penelope?

Vikir remembered that Camus had cried when he heard that his flesh-and-blood sister had been taken and eaten by the cannibalistic Rokoko tribe.

Butler Barrymore reflected on the incident.

'It was after that incident that my Lord became the cold person he is today. If only his eldest daughter Penelope had been alive, he would not have been so....'

From Vikir's perspective, there's no way to know what Hugo was like before. It was before he was born.

However, Vikir was familiar with Hugo's personality from his two lives.

An iron-blooded warrior without blood or tears. A cold-blooded man who cared only for the glory of the empire and the revival of his family.

But to see him in front of me now, tormented by the story of an old love, was an overwhelming sense of strangeness.

“...Yes. I did.”

Hugo's voice was shaking as he spoke. His eyes are red and moist at the corners.

Vikir was so surprised by his appearance that he almost had hiccups.

But don't let the look fool you.

His opponent is a heartless man who, in the aftermath of the loss of his first daughter, has sent each of his sons into battle with the barbarians.

He would even go on a rampage if he knew his granddaughter had barbarian blood in her veins.

Vikir awakened Beelzebub the Magic Sword, ready to draw his blade if necessary.

He spoke in a voice of extreme caution.

“First, thank you for answering.”

“....”

Hugo dried the moisture from his eyes in an instant and raised his bloodshot eyes to glare at Vikir.

“Why did you ask me this, if not to satisfy your insatiable curiosity....”

But Vikir held up a palm, cutting Hugo off.

He asked his question.

“What would you do if you had the blood of your first wife's daughter, Penelope la Baskerville?”

“...What?”

Hugo's brow furrowed at Vikir's words.

He looked like he'd heard every stupid thing in the world.

But Vikir had never said a single thing that wasn't true.

Just as Hugo was slowly realizing that fact.

...Thud!

Vikir stretched out his left hand and slammed an object from his pocket onto Hugo's desk.

Hugo's eyes widen at the sight of it.

“...This, this!”

It's a pendant, an artifact salvaged from a Rokoko village that was nearly wiped out by the Red Death.

Inside are portraits of the past of Hugo and Roxana as young men, and Penelope as a child.

“My, I made it! The pendant I gave to Roxana, the one I made in my workshop, and the one I gave to her, and the one I wore around Penelope's neck at the end, for sure...!”

Hugo pointed to the pendant on the table with a hand that trembled so much that it almost seemed to shake.

A moment.

A ding!

Hugo's hand shook so violently that he dropped the pendant on the table.

As Vikir snatched it up, Hugo screamed like he was having a seizure.

“Do it, give it back, give it back to me!”

“Calm down. Father.”

Hugo flailed in the air, disoriented.

Vikir obediently handed the pendant back to Hugo, who seemed to be half out of his mind.

“....”

The faded portrait inside the pendant handprints where the lid's hard metal plate had been worn away.

Penelope, their lost first child.

Where is she? Is she alive? If she is dead, where are her remains? What were her circumstances and thoughts before she died? How lonely, confused, and scared must she have been? Did he resent his father for not coming to his rescue? Did he despair, thinking that his father had forgotten him?

Hugo was always scared.

He wondered if she would blame herself to the end if she would blame her father, who had never said a kind word, who had always been so strict, who had never come to visit or heard from her.

More and more, Hugo flogged himself. He hadn't given any of his children any love. He didn't care if they didn't feel the same way about him. It was easier that way.

When he thought of Penelope, he couldn't imagine her suffering somewhere.

And when he looked at his sons, who had the same faces and personalities as he did, he could only feel a terrible feeling of self-hatred.

...But.

Looking at the pendant, which had been so stroked that the lid had worn off, Hugo felt as if an ice cap had melted in his heart.

Thinking of his daughter clutching this pendant until her last breath, Hugo couldn't help but shake his head.

A single, thick tear finally hit the cold stone floor.

And then.

There was one word from Vikir that brought Hugo's eyes back to life.

“There is a daughter of my sister, Penelope.”

“?”

Was it Vikir's voice, so dry and emotionless?

“??”

Hugo's face was blank, as if he hadn't understood what Vikir had said.

“????”

So, as if on cue, Vikir spoke to Hugo again.

“I'm saying that you have a granddaughter.”

And then.

“!”

Hugo's eyes widened until they couldn't get any bigger.

Chapter 118

Falling in Love (3)

◆

A man's tears.

It's a rare thing to see. The older you get, the more so.

Men are socially conditioned not to shed tears.

It's a rare thing to see in a normal family home, but not in Baskerville, where the iron-blooded sword is a thing of the past.

Iron blood boiling in the heart of a furnace. A Swordmaster without human emotion.

Hugo Le Baskerville, the iron-blooded swordsman of Baskerville.

Tears are not the word to describe him.

A needle in his eye would make him bleed, but not tears.

So Vikir was surprised this morning when he saw Hugo crying.

...So surprised, indeed.

In an age of destruction, through a devastating decade of war, he could think of few times when he had been so surprised.

And so Vikir thought.

'There will be no more surprises.'

I've seen Hugo cry, what more surprises can there be?

Vikir thought.

...But.

Vikir had to be surprised once more, even more so than when Hugo cried earlier.

“Alas, peek-a-boo!”

In front of him now was a Pomeranian sitting awkwardly.

And the Pomeranian is sitting on someone's lap, and the one who is trying to make the Pomeranian laugh with this stupid joke...... as soon as.......

'I hate to admit it, but that's Hugo Le Baskerville.'

Vikir put a hand to his forehead.

'It is indeed Hugo the Ironblade, Lord of Baskerville, who now has Pomeranian in his lap and is making a ridiculous face with his hands, tongue, and eyes.'

Character Breakdown. It's as if all the common sense Vikir has ever possessed has come crashing down.

He's shocked, and so is everyone else in Baskerville when they hear the conversation between Hugo and Pomeranian.

“???”

“????”

Just as Butler Barrymore and Osiris Le Baskerville, now standing beside Vikir, are open-mouthed.

Vikir even thought to himself.

'Has he been brainwashed by demons?'

But no matter, Hugo is still his usual self.

“Uh heh heh, do you find this grandfather's mustache strange? Is it fun to pull? Now, there is this one too.”

“Moustache... dirty....”

“Hmm? Heh heh heh – dirty! This old man always shampoos and rinses his mustache. Today, I did a special essence because you were coming.”

“Installment... mustache... pick it off....”

“Hmmm? The installment? Ohhh! Yes, yes, yes, it's Grandpa! Do you want to call me that again? Hehe, I'm your grandfather.”

It was a roundabout way of saying it. Hugo's reaction was not at all what Vikir had expected.

“Where did this come from?”

Vikir recalled a moment in time.

Hugo looked at the Pomeranian with that same trembling look in his eyes.

'This, this, this child, is this really Penelope's child?'

'It is. The dark hair and red eyes are characteristic of Baskerville; and, judging by the portrait, she bears a striking resemblance to Roxana the First Lady, and also to Penelope's sister....'

'Not so much as a resemblance, I, I thought Penelope was alive and well, no way!'

Pomeranian's whole body proved that she was Penelope's child.

The tiny mole on the nape of his neck and the blue stain on his calf were physical features that Hugo also had.

What's more, the Pomeranian was found among the Rokoko tribe that had taken Penelope, and he even had a pendant that Hugo had made himself.

She also remembered her mother, Penelope, quite clearly.

“Mommy... was always happy... laughed well....”

Hugo laughed and cried at the same time.

From what he heard, Penelope must have had a wonderful life.

“Yes, Mama... is always behind on her installments... and she's sick of seeing them, but she's tried to go back so many times, she can't... Madame Depht... won't let us enter her territory.”

Hugo scratched his head.

The Pomeranian spoke well for a five-year-old, but he still didn't fully understand.

That's when Vikir, who had spent two years in the depht, helped translate.

“Sister Penelope says she's always missed you, and that she's tried to return to the clan several times, but has been unsuccessful because a powerful demon's territory blocks the center of her path.”

“What! Are you saying that it was a demon that separated me from my daughter?”

“Yes, it was a dangerous creature called the Depht Nightmare, and now I have killed it.”

Hugo admired Vikir's words.

“Well done. You have avenged me where I could not. Well done, well done.”

You get what you deserve. Hugo hadn't lost his Baskerville colors.

Finally, Hugo turned his head toward Vikir.

His eyes were red with moisture.

“I'm glad to hear of my daughter's last days, and that they were happy in their own way. I don't know if I'll ever have a better day in the rest of my life, especially now that I have the granddaughter she left behind.”

Praise. This expression of extreme joy from Hugo's mouth stunned both Barrymore and Osiris.

Even Osiris, who, like Hugo, rarely shows emotion, was stunned to see his mouth open and his eyes wide.

Then. Hugo strode over, cradling the Pomeranian in his arms, and stood in front of Vikir.

Vikir instinctively cowered, ready to fight back.

But contrary to Vikir's instincts, Hugo stopped in his tracks.

And then.

“Thank you, son.”

Hugo bowed his head to Vikir. His back bent ninety degrees.

Barrymore and Osiris' mouths dropped open again at the unprecedented sight.

After a few moments of silence, Osiris stammered.

“It's a short life, but...... Of all the moments of my life, today will be the most amazing.”

“I have lived quite a long time, but... I think so too, Lord.”

Barrymore replied, barely able to move his mouth.

Then, Osiris's gaze fell upon Hugo.

Parents are mirrors of their children, and children are mirrors of their parents.

Up until this point, Osiris had always tried to mirror Hugo's stoic and cold demeanor.

He'd killed his emotions and suppressed his ego as much as possible.

From the smallest desire to eat something tasty to painstakingly turning away from the woman he was attracted to, it was a quest that bordered on self-abuse.

But. Today, Osiris's feelings about Hugo have changed slightly.

“I wonder if my father was like that.”

That means he has a side like that too.

And Osiris had learned a lesson today.

He didn't have to suppress the clumsy warmth within him so much.

'Can't I be a little bit of what I want to be?'

You don't have to try to be perfect.

The humanity that comes from a little flaw, a little imperfection, is enough to make even my cold father smile.

“....”

Osiris mirrored his father's face as he smiled broadly at the Pomeranian.

Barrymore, who was standing next to him, was stunned to see Osiris' face.

'My God, he's smiling! He's smiling!'

Even Barrymore, the butler, had never seen Osiris laugh so easily in his life.

Naturally, the butler's face lights up when he sees his master and little master laughing.

There was a breeze in Baskerville that hadn't been felt in a long time.

...Just then.

A voice wiped the smiles from Hugo's, Osiris', and Barrymore's faces.

“I have a word with you, Father.”

It was Vikir.

Vikir. Suddenly, the atmosphere cleared.

As Vikir opened his mouth, both Hugo and Osiris turned to look at him with serious expressions.

The one who had brought them this great happiness.

Their gazes toward the belly of the family were grave, but they were also filled with undeniable favor and gratitude.

Hugo quickly understood Vikir's purpose.

“Oh, yes. The reward.”

The reward should be clear. That was Hugo's theory.

You've found Penelope, you've avenged her by killing a demonic creature, and you've rescued a granddaughter you didn't even know existed.

These deeds are unspeakable.

Hugo nodded, ready to listen to anything Vikir had to say.

Beside him, Osiris did the same.

“Tell me what you want, son.”

“Anything I can do to help, brother.”

Vikir nodded.

Now that things had gone so well, it was time to set his sights on the end goal.

Before heading to the Academy, there was something he needed to take care of within the family.

It is revenge for the miserable end before the return. And it was the first step to prevent the age of destruction that was about to unfold.

“There's a demon I'd like to hunt.”

“...?”

“A very dangerous one.”

“...!”

Hugo and Osiris' faces hardened as they heard Vikir's words.

They were the iron-blooded swords of Baskerville, the Master and Young Master, the swords of the Empire, fighting demons.

Hugo asked.

“What kind of demons?”

“If you're asking what kind of demons, I don't know exactly. But....”

“Just?”

Osiris asked, this time.

Vikir answered tersely.

“I only know the location of where they are hiding.”

At that, Hugo and Osiris nodded in unison.

“Yes. And what is that location?”

Vikir answered as if he had been waiting.

“Inside the family estate.”

“...!”

The two men's eyes widened.

At this point, Vikir told them what he really wanted.

“Half a day. I want to borrow the Seven Knights of Baskerville for half a day.”

Half the power of the Baskervilles.

A single weak nation could be wiped off the map in a day.

Chapter 119

The Hunt for the Second Son (1)

◆

In a darkened cave.

A man sits alone in a training hall on the outskirts of the Baskerville estate.

Seth les Baskervilles. Hugo's second son.

He is reading a letter delivered by a three-eyed raven.

“...Hmm. So, Vikir, he left for the Academy, huh?”

Seth closed the letter.

Tsutsutsutsutsuts...

Then the parchment on which the words were written burned away.

The flames were black and vivid.

Seth opened his closed eyes.

For a moment, each eyeball seemed to turn in a different direction, and then only a stark blackness filled her orbit.

“But. I'd rather not have it. There was a lot of room to get in the way when the family was swallowed up.”

Seth smirked and leaned his head against the wall.

As he did, a dark, giant shadow fell across the rock face.

“It was bad enough having to deal with Hugo, Osiris, and the Seventh Count, but now you've got that little bastard. I should have killed him in the depth. Alas, I should have done it when I let the viper loose in the cradle in the first place, because of that stupid mother and nanny bitch.”

Seth mulled this over, and then, in a fit of nervousness, reached out to the side.

There was a frightened-looking child.

“Huh, Patroness, where am I?”

“Umm. Don't worry. This is the house you're going to live in.”

“Eh? Ha, but the nursery director said I would be adopted by a good home... but this is a scary cave!”

The cave was dark as far as the eye could see, and filled with a foul stench that made it hard to stand for more than a moment.

Seth tugged on the child's arm and chuckled.

“A cave? Alas, you mean here. There must be some misunderstanding, but of course this is not your home.”

At Seth's words, the child's expression relaxed, if only briefly.

But.

“This is where you will go.”

At the same time, Seth's mouth dropped open as he looked into the child's face.

A row of razor-sharp teeth sprouted from its gaping mouth.

A single large eyeball in its hood flashed across the child's face with a horrifying crackle.

Before the child had time to scream, Seth swallowed its head in one gulp.

...Woodchuck! Woodchuck!

The child's shadow twists miserably against the cave's rocky walls.

The blood splattered on the walls quickly lost its color, and the last warm breath sank into the depths of the abyss.

Seth wiped his mouth a few times before stripping the bones off and tossing them to the floor.

“Human fluids are the most delicious, I can't get enough of them. Maybe we should start a collective and breed them.”

Seth looked at the bones on the floor and smirked.

In the darkness, a mountain of bones had already piled up on the pitch-black floor, emitting a foul stench.

The smell of decaying flesh, Seth wrinkled his nose and made a happy face.

“Mmm. The scent of home. Home sweet home.”

Seth flopped down on a pile of bones.

Just then.

A three-eyed raven opened its mouth.

[Hey, Ten, how's things going?]

“Ugh, what a surprise.”

Seth spat out the bones he had been gurgling in anger.

The raven shines its three eyeballs and says.

[We must open the 'gate' to open a new era. The dawn of a new era is just around the corner. You haven't forgotten, have you?]

“I see. Keep an eye on the others, I'm not the only one, what are you doing?”

[I can't be bothered with you for the time being, I have one more human to pay attention to].

“Another human to pay attention to, Eight, yourself?”

[More like you].

Seth frowned at the raven's words.

“By human I'm paying attention to, do you mean Vikir? It's in Morgue where the Eight are infiltrating. ...If so?”

When asked who the newest up-and-comers in Morgue were, Seth quickly found the answer.

“You mean the newest member of the Dark Faction? What's his name, Camus? Why?”

[....]

The crow didn't answer. Instead, he gave Seth a pincushion.

[I won't answer unnecessary questions. Also, have you guys been eating too many human fluids lately? There have been too many kidnappings and missing infants around town. The dogs of Baskerville have good noses, so be careful not to give them away].

“Don't worry, I'm doing a good job of staying undetected. I've never been disturbed.”

[I'm a little concerned about all the bones in the cave. What if someone breaks in?]

“Don't worry. The cave is wired so that only demons and human fluids under the age of eight can enter. No one will find it.”

The raven nodded, finally relieved. And he ended the conversation at will.

[For the destruction of humans. For the Ten Commandments.]

With that, the magic emanating from the raven's eyeballs faded. The raven fell to the ground and died.

“Still talking out of your ass, you asshole.”

Seth crushed the crow's corpse with his foot as if it was a nuisance.

“Damn it. I'm still a long way from building up enough magicpower to open the gate. I wonder how much human blood I'll have to suck before I can. At this rate, I'll be waiting at least another decade.”

Seth grumbled, flashing his demonic glare.

His cunning brain calculated the amount of mana needed for the plan and the time it would take to gather it.

Twelve and a half years, to be exact.

That's at least as long as he needs to hide in the human realm.

Only then could he create a giant gate between the demonic and human realms, setting the stage for the Great War.

“We must open the Age of Destruction as soon as possible. ... Alas, it's a thrill to think about.”

Seth squeals with delight at the thought of the inferno and the devastation of the human world to come.

The thrill seemed to last for quite some time.

“Open what?”

...If it weren't for the unwelcome intruder who suddenly burst into the cave.

In an instant, Seth jumped to his feet.

“!”

He didn't even feel the intruder.

No flow of mana, no concentration of magic, not even a sound.

Seth was horrified to see the face of the man who had entered the cave.

Vikir. Vikir Van Baskerville. It was his brother, the one Seth had been watching so closely.

“Uh, what happened to you? Weren't you going to the Academy?”

“I'm going, but not before I see your face.”

Vikir replied in a nonchalant tone and stood in front of Seth.

Seth squinted and stared at the man before him.

He could smell the extremely faint but unmistakable scent of magic on Vikir, especially around the wrist of his right hand.

“So you were able to break through the crystal?”

Seth stretched out his mind to see the crystals.

There were marks on the grid where a drumstick had been torn with something like an awl.

There was a distinct crack, small enough for only a Vikir to fit through.

Meanwhile, Vikir looked into Seth's eyes.

The irises were eyeless, filled with blackness, and the demon's signature magic radiated from their sockets.

“You don't even bother to hide your identity anymore.”

“Not since you've discovered the scene.”

Seth shrugged at Vikir's question.

Then, seeing the remains of the children on the ground, Vikir swallowed hard.

In a previous life, he had been framed and executed for this horrific crime. It was a futile end, even after the Age of Destruction had ended.

And now, the man who had framed him was laughing in his face.

Because of him, Vikir had been deceived countless times, had come close to death many times, and had actually died.

Pomeranian also lost his family and had a difficult childhood.

Hugo and Baskerville's misfortunes were also caused by this creature.

Seth Le Baskerville. No, something under his skin.

Vikir gave a short warning to the enemy in front of him.

“Don't laugh.”

But Seth let out an even louder mockery.

“Pufu-fufufuhehehe...... little brother I don't know how you came to know about this place, but I can't believe that you have the confidence of an intermediate graduator. You are too arrogant.”

Seth snatched his flamberg from his waistband.

Suddenly, the aura of an advanced Graduator began to envelope the sword.

With a dark smile, Seth swung the sword at Vikir.

At that moment.

...Puff!

A short blood-curdling sound resounded.

Seth could only stare in horror as he realized what had just happened.

Then.

Thud!

There was the sound of something falling to the ground.

It was the left arm that wasn't holding the sword.

Blood was gushing out of the neatly cut off left arm.

“...?”

Seth looked up, dazed, and saw Vikir's sword coming at him.

The magic sword Beelzebub. And the seven teeth it depicts.

The Seven Deadly Sins of Baskerville.

But it was something else that stunned the set before them.

An aura as sticky as nectar and as red as blood.

A step up from a Graduator to peer into the realm of a Master.

The aura of a peak Graduator was exploding!

“Don't laugh.”

That was the last thing Vikir said before he tore the skin from both sides of Seth's mouth.

Chapter 121

The Hunt for the Second Son (3)

◆

<'Tenth Corpse' Andromalius>

Danger Rating : S

Size : ?

Found in: In the depths of the Gate of Destruction, 'The Serpent's Womb'

-Nicknamed 'Tenth Corpse'.

One of the Ten Calamities, natural enemies of mankind, inscrutable and unkillable.

“They shall swarm like flies.”

– The Ten Commandments 10: Top –

'The top ten corpses'.

Refers to the ten Demon Kings who opened the gates to the Demon Realm and ushered in the Age of Destruction, or the ten corpses that became their bodies.

Before his regression, Vikir had a vague idea of their existence, but he hadn't realized they were actually Seth.

'It's a good thing we met relatively soon.'

Vikir thought as he stepped back.

More innocent children would have been sacrificed if he had been allowed to live longer in the Baskervilles.

Someone else would have been falsely accused, too.

Like himself before the regression.

Vikir calmed his mind and eyed the enemy before him.

Sure enough, Andromalius, the Tenth Corpse, rose like a mist behind Seth's body, and then began to take shape.

Red eyes, black flesh, horns curved like a ram's.

From his severed left arm sprouted a long, massive snake, writhing and slithering.

The powerful demon that had taken over Seth's body growled into his mouth.

[I never thought I'd show my true form to a human].

“You should have hidden better.”

Andromalius's expression went blank for a moment as he heard Vikir's short rebuke.

Why is it that the humans in front of him are never surprised to see him for who he is?

Of course, Vikir had no intention of answering Andromalius' question.

He simply compares his pre-regression knowledge with the information from his current life to make the best possible plan.

'...I wondered where the culprits who would bring about the Age of Destruction in the coming decades were hiding.'

I never thought it would be this close.

Vikir cut off any and all feelings he had for Seth.

He was no longer the kindly half-brother he remembered.

Not even a monster, not even a fiend, but a demon, a true blooded evil.

A demon of the highest order, a demon whose family name is somehow tied to the Abyssal Lineage.

“Even so. There's no business in swords.”

Vikir was unfazed.

He drew out as long as he could, and the tip of his Beelzebub was imbued with an aura of power.

Pooh-pooh-pooh-pooh!

In the short time it took for Andromalius to descend and reshape Seth's body, Vikir laid down over thirty stabs.

A trajectory so clear in its intent, aimed at killing, not dueling or contesting.

The malice displayed by Beelzebub the Magic Sword was unmistakable, following an extremely efficient route, selecting only Andromalius' vital organs to stab.

[Ugh! Why, why is it painful, why does the pain of a mere body reach to the soul!]

Andromalius then turned his attention to the awl-like sword that Vikir was wielding.

Sensing the magic emanating from Beelzebub, Andromalius cries out in horror.

[What, no! Beelzebub, the Sword of Gluttony? The remains of the ancient Demonic Constellation, Lord of the Flies!]

Long ago, when Andromalius was not yet born.

A relic of one of the seven great and long-dead kings who once ruled the demon world.

Only then did Andromalius understand the source of Vikir's confidence.

A normal sword can harm the body of the corpse possessed by Andromalius, but it cannot damage the spiritual body behind it.

Unless it was an aura sword, which was a concentration of pure mana.

However, it's a different story with demonic or holy swords.

They are the only non-standard objects that can physically interfere with a spiritual body.

And a magic sword or holy sword with an aura?

It becomes a powerful weapon that even a Demon of the highest order cannot ignore.

Moreover, Vikir is a seasoned warrior who has accumulated karma from killing countless demons in his past lives.

Andromalius, who hasn't yet gained his full strength, is confused as to where this monster came from.

“Die.”

Vikir wanted to end the battle as quickly as possible while Andromalius was still in the dark.

Before Andromalius had taken his body, Seth had been an intermediate Graduator, and now that Andromalius was in complete control of Seth's body, he could easily be a Sword Master or higher.

But Vikir was confident, too.

His body was strengthened by the River Styx, his battle experience gained over two lifetimes, and the power of Baskerville family swordsmanship and the magic sword Beelzebub.

Even a Swordmaster could be killed by surprise or assassination.

Vikir sank his teeth into Andromalius' flesh with conviction.

However.

[...Yes, that was a bit of a surprise, I'll admit, but that's it].

Andromalius is essentially an endgame boss, an Archdemon so terrifying that he plotted the destruction of the human world with only ten others.

Andromalius, who had somewhat adapted to Vikir's onslaught since breaking through the barrier, immediately took action.

Shiriririk!

The snake that had replaced Andromalius' left arm swooped down, open-mouthed.

Vikir swung the hilt of his Blood Wind to strike the snake down, but the snake's teeth left a long trail of blood on his forearm.

Then a dark smile appeared on Andromalius' possessed Seth's face.

[That's it, you're done].

With that, Andromalius stretched out his right hand.

Vikir's forearm turned white for a moment, and then blood began to gush from the wound.

...Gurgle! ...gurgle! ...gurgle! ...gurgle! ...gurgle!

Andromalius drained the blood from Vikir's body and absorbed it into his own.

Waaaah!

Vikir suddenly heard the unpleasant flapping of wings.

Flies.

The ugly insect, plump and fat, was sucking blood from Vikir's wound.

“...Is a bloodsucker.”

Vikir crushed the fly, killing it, and quickly pressed his arm against the wound to stop it from bleeding, but it was no use.

Weeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee.

Flies were everywhere.

The flies that had been frantically licking the children's bones now clung to Vikir.

...Buzz! ...buzz! ...buzz! ...buzz! ...buzz! ...buzz!

Andromalius sucked the blood from Vikir's body, no matter how far away they were.

The streams of blood gushing out of Vikir's body were being coiled like snakes by the flies and being absorbed by Andromalius' right hand.

[Hmph- my strength is returning].

Seth's tattered body began to recover.

Infinite bloodsucking using a swarm of flies.

This power that Andromalius possessed was semi-immortal.

As long as there are wounded and exhausted things around him, his life force is limitless.

The art of digging into the wounds of others and draining the life force from them is common among demons.

And one of the best at it is this Andromalius right in front of you.

'Seth, too, has long since become his sacrifice.'

The need to be accepted by his father, the inferiority complex of his brother.

With these two emotional wounds, Seth would have been easy prey for Andromalius.

In the end, Seth was left empty-handed, with everything sucked out of him, and this is the result.

Vikir remembered Seth's usual monologue before his regression.

'I want to be accepted by my father, I want him to look back and see that I'm here.'

'You're so amazing, I wanted to be like you, I wanted to walk beside you, side by side with you.'

We don't know if it was a faint remnant of Seth's subconscious, or if Andromalius memorized and mimicked Seth's last words.

But at the very least, it's clear that Seth had those feelings when he was alive, and it's equally clear that Andromalius used them to take over Seth's mind.

“....”

That made Vikir feel terribly uncomfortable.

Even though he didn't know Seth, he empathized with him on some level.

Quadruple!

Vikir swatted away the snakes and flies that were biting at his chest.

Thanks to the protection of the River Styx, he was not mortally wounded, but several chunks of flesh fell off his breastplate.

Andromalius looked at it and mocked.

[Yeah, that's how you die, with all those wounds. Now, let's suck blood again...... ?]

But the sneer didn't last long.

Ping-.

Was it an illusion? For a moment, my vision burns black.

And for the briefest of moments, my head pings as I realize it's not an illusion.

Stagger.

The moment I regained my senses and came to my senses, this time, the strength in my legs was released.

[Cough!?]

Andromalius felt a foreign sensation that took his breath away.

It wasn't just his nose and throat, it was his entire body, and it was happening simultaneously.

He checks himself to see what's going on and realizes that his entire limbs are numb and shaking.

The blood vessels were clogged with sticky masses, blocking blood flow.

Searching for something, I looked inside my body, and soon realized that I was surrounded by black, clotted blood that was clinging tightly to my veins.

A combination of stroke and other conditions assaulted Andromalius' soul at once.

As the blood stopped flowing, so did the mana.

For a moment, Andromalius lost control of Seth's body.

[What the fuck! What the fuck!]

Andromalius raised his head, watching the body scatter as it lost its host and turned into mana with nowhere to go.

Whack- whack- whack- whack-

Dead flies fell from the sky.

And there stood Vikir, regenerating the scars on his arms and chest with terrifying speed.

...Dip! ...dip!

Vikir raised his forearm with a nonchalant expression.

The red blood from the wound in his forearm drips to the floor and turns into a dark dot like tar.

Chiiiit-boiling...

Vikir's blood made an unpleasant sound as it touched the bones of the floor, and began to boil black.

Andromalius looked dazed.

Finally, he understood. Why his body had changed like this.

[Yes, you... your blood state changed to...!?]

Normally, an ordinary drop of blood.

But the moment its owner harbors malice, it becomes a deadly poisonous liquid.

A venomous poison that can make even the most powerful in the world cower.

Madam Eight-Legs, the nightmare of the depth, her ghostly toxicity has wrapped itself around Andromalius' entire body!

Chapter 122

The Hunt for the Second Son (4)

◆

“The poison is listening a little late.”

Vikir pieced back together the torn flesh of his chest and forearms.

He could feel the wraiths sealed in the slots of his magic sword, Beelzebub, rampaging madly.

<Binge Fly 'Beelzebub'>/ Awl

-1 slot: Venomous -Madam Eight-Legs (S)

Slot -2: Silent Hill – Mushuhushu (A+)

Slot -3: Super Regeneration -Bog Salamander(A+)

With his body restored by the regenerative powers of the Swamp Salamander, Vikir inspects the slots on Beelzebub.

Crackle-crackle-crackle-dahlgraak!

The red beads beneath the blade clattered against each other, churning violently.

The wraith raging most furiously within Beelzebub right now was Madam Eight-Legs.

She seemed to be very proud of the fact that Andromalius, who had been poisoned by her own poison, moved normally for a while.

But Vikir was surprised enough by the effect for now.

The Madame's poison was so powerful that it made even the world's tens of thousands stumble, and it was so terrifying that even a life that had already died could be endangered again.

Being able to inflict debuffs like slow, numb, and blind against such a high ranking demon was a huge win.

Andromalius, meanwhile, watched in horror as his own body faded to black.

[A poison that even the dead can't escape? Where in the world is this poison... a mere mortal!]

Andromalius thought as he struggled to control his spinning vision.

How many demonic creatures in the world possessed such a vile poison?

The cunning spiders of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, the nine-headed snakes of the Giant Country, the great jellyfish under the Black Sea....

There are several other candidates that should come to mind that live in the depths of the Outer Demon Realm, but how their venom is being used by mere mortals is beyond me.

'It's so virulent that even the greatest demons are reluctant to deal with it, and it's impossible to even contain or store it somewhere, so how could a mere mortal....'

But there was no time to think about it now.

Andromalius gritted his teeth and stepped back.

The bloodsuckers followed suit and backed away.

He looks around to see if there are any other bloodsuckers around, but there aren't.

The only bloodsucker is the Vikir in front of you.

But his blood is already tainted with a terrible poison, and sucking on it will only poison you, as it is now.

“Not good for you.”

The Vikir bites down on his index finger, drawing blood and spraying it into the air.

Cha-cha-cha-cha.

The bubbling droplets of venom flew like bullets.

The blood could turn from mundane to venomous at any moment, depending on Vikir's will.

Not only is it hemorrhagic and neurotoxic, but it is also deadly acidic, burning Andromalius' body and soul at the same time.

[Off-aaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!]

As a demonic sword, Beelzebub deals direct damage to a demon's spiritual body.

Andromalius had no choice but to attach meaning to each and every one of Vikir's attacks.

What's more, Vikir's own brute strength was more than enough to draw out the power of a sword of the highest Graduator class.

Baskerville Seventh Form. Six teeth, followed by a seventh, small but distinct.

Once again, the tip of the sword oviposited Andromalius' entire body.

[Ugh! What the hell!]

Andromalius gnashed his teeth at the absurdity of it all.

He hadn't expected to be attacked by a mere mortal, much less on his home turf.

Ehhhhh...

Andromalius swatted at the remaining swarm of flies, forming a black mist, and quickly ducked behind it.

He stepped back, intending to close the distance.

“That's what I was hoping for.”

Vikir didn't bother to follow Andromalius as he fled deeper into the cave.

Only.

Kararak-

pulled two black sticks from his back and assembled them into one.

It was the black bow wielded by Adonai, the legendary archer who had led Anubis and Ballak in their prime.

...Boom!

An arrow from Anubis flew out and pierced Andromalius' body.

Boom!

Andromalius hit the cave wall and looked down at the hole in his chest with a horrified expression.

The arrowhead was dyed red and, of course, coated with Madam Eight-Legs's venom.

[Ugh, a bow!?]

This is unbelievable.

Why would a Baskerville swordsman use a bow?

He looks up and sees Vikir walking toward him.

........................

His stride as smooth as a snake's, his killing intent eerie.

The ghostly figure made no sound as it walked, and Andromalius felt goosebumps creep up his spine.

“No.”

Andromalius decided that he could not face Vikir in the cave.

We-Eng-

At Andromalius' call, all the flies gathered in one place.

“They shall swarm like flies.”

These were the flies that had been licking the flesh off the bones of the children and swarming over them.

These myriads of grave-dwelling flies loyally rallied at their master's call.

But.

“Flies are the spider's food.”

Vikir intermittently slashed his wrist, black blood pouring from it.

The fog of blood, laced with venomous spider venom, was killing the flies like nothing else.

Buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz.

The stiffly moving flies melted like ice cream dumped into a flame as soon as they touched Vikir's blood mist.

That wasn't all.

Vikir had also contaminated the groundwater flowing along the walls and ramps with his blood, so the flies were constantly draining their health without a place to stick.

Vikir was in control of the situation, including the terrain around him.

Waaaahhhh...

His breathing is getting tighter.

He didn't know why he was being pushed.

Andromalius' expression crumpled.

“...For God's sake, spare a few children.”

He'd never regretted eating all the children he'd kept in the cave for blood bags as much as he did now.

...But.

[Yeah. I'll give you credit for pushing this body this far as a mere mortal].

Andromalius was still not relaxing.

Outside the cave, outside the circle, there was a river and a sandy bank that cut a wide swath through the training grounds.

If he could burst the bank and divert all of the river's overflow into this cave, he still had a chance.

'The regenerative powers of the flesh will not be able to keep up with a demon.'

He would lose some magic power, but that would also delay the summoning of the gate that would open the Age of Destruction by quite a bit, but it was unavoidable.

[Ku-k-k-k-k...... Yeah, that was fine for a human. It was for a moment, but it was embarrassing. But that's it. You crossed the line.]

Andromalius raised his blood-red eyes and glared at Vikir.

Then, he took the first step toward leaving the cave.

He broke the bonds.

Tsutsutsutsutsuts...

The binding that had enveloped the entire training hall disappeared.

Only demons and children under the age of eight could enter the Demon Binding Realm, and it required an enormous amount of magic power to maintain.

It's no wonder it's so secretive that even an archmage can't detect it, and it's so powerful that it can't be broken by anything less than demonic strength.

Breaking the bond restored Andromalius's magic to a great extent.

With that, Andromalius suppressed the poison that was eating away at his body and leapt up through the hole in the ceiling in the center of the cave.

[Hold on, I'll show you hell in a moment].

Andromalius slammed into the rock with a sickening laugh.

On the other hand, he was glad to see the dangerous bastard now.

In a few more years, he'd be truly unbearable.

'If Hugo, Osiris, and the Seventh Count had been the only ones prepared, it would have made a big difference.'

Better to make sure they're dead now, so they'll be ready for the next time they want to devour Baskerville.

Then.

Andromalius reached the end of the hollow, where he could see the night sky, and suddenly stopped.

Down below, he could see Vikir standing still.

[...?]

Andromalius furrowed his brow and bowed his head.

Somehow, Vikir hadn't given chase.

He just looks up and stares at Andromalius with his usual expressionless face.

...With a strange looking whistle in his hand.

With that, Vikir raised the tooth-like whistle in his hand to his mouth and blew.

A high, piercing note echoes through the hollow.

Andromalius felt a chill run down his spine as he heard it.

[...!]

It is impossible not to know that he also has the experience of living for decades wearing the skin of the second son of the Baskervilles.

What is that whistle in Vikir's hand, and what does it mean?

And then.

The night has grown even darker.

Dark clouds blocked out the moonlight and a veil of inky darkness fell.

Long shadows began to cast countless shadows from outside the hole in the ceiling Andromalius had climbed.

Flutter.

A black, blood-colored wisp fluttered in the night breeze.

Andromalius raised his bloodshot eyes to the sky outside the hole.

The ceiling after the Demon Binding had disappeared.

There, the tips of countless shadows pointed at Andromalius.

“What are you doing there, ... son?”

Hugo Le Baskerville standing waving a black robe.

Beside him, his eldest son, Osiris Le Baskerville.

And the seven hounds standing behind their father. Seven counts.

Pit Bull.

Mastiff.

Doberman.

Shepherd.

Rottweiler.

Wolfhound, and so on.

A total of one hundred hounds under each knightly order, seven hundred in total.

The full force of the iron-blooded military power.

All the dogs of Baskerville were assembled.

Chapter 123

The Hunt for the Second Son (5)

◆

Hugo Le Baskerville asked.

“..., Son, what are you doing there?”

An expressionless face. The tone so casual.

It's like a father coming out of a bar and seeing his son on the side of the road.

Hugo's casual tone was calm enough to make Andromalius continue his mimicry of the set.

[Ah, father, you're here on business...!?]

Andromalius' face lit up, and then he realized what was happening.

He was now in demonic form.

A demon that had taken over Seth's body.

He's been seen. He had been caught.

There's no point in trying to mimic it anymore, since he's been caught right there on the spot.

But the way Hugo looked down at Andromalius was as consistent as ever.

Trash.

It didn't matter if it was Seth or Andromalius, Andromalius with Seth's body, or Andromalius with Seth's soul.

At some point, the unpleasant object becomes invisible.

Hugo was looking down at Andromalius with such a gaze now.

“You look terrible, my son.”

Hugo said, still with the same horrible indifference.

For a moment, Andromalius gritted his teeth.

[“Son, son, don't do it. How dare you mock me on a human subject!”]

Andromalius' anger exploded at Hugo for daring to call him son when he knew better.

...That moment.

[...!?]

Andromalius felt the snake on his left arm stiffen as he reached for Hugo.

“What?”

Andromalius started to surge out of the cavity, but stopped.

His feet were tingling like rats.

With Hugo in front of him, he was frozen in place.

'Why is my body stiffening? Why?'

Andromalius is the king of the demons. Ten demons who crossed over to the human realm to bring about an age of destruction.

But why does he freeze at the sight of a mere mortal?

'Fear? That's impossible. Even if you're a Sword Master, you're just a human in the end!'

Nevertheless, Andromalius found himself unable to move.

As much as he hated to admit it, it was obvious that this uncontrollable emotion surging within him was fear.

Andromalius finally understood the phenomenon.

I'm not afraid, but I'm afraid? It sounds strange, but it's possible.

Andromalius was clearly not afraid of Hugo.

The problem was the body.

Seth Le Baskerville.

His body is afraid of Hugo.

Andromalius's mouth is half open in disbelief.

A dog is an animal that cannot move before its master.

It is their destiny to go when their master calls them, even if they know they will die.

'But he died a long time ago.'

Andromalius thought.

But the fear that Seth felt for Hugo was beyond his imagination.

A fear that was imprinted in his bones. A fear he would never forget, even in death.

And it was affecting the next user of the body, Andromalius.

'Oh, no, no, no, no, this is off the table! I have to move fast...!'

Andromalius's face showed his impatience.

He turns his head and sees the river in the distance.

All I have to do is burst the dam in front of me and draw the water into this cave, and it will be over.

But the corpse's feet, already frozen, don't move at all.

They're even shaking, making it difficult to stand on the ramp.

Andromalius is just rolling his eyes.

“...I'm sorry.”

An unfamiliar voice rang out.

Andromalius looked up, and there was Osiris.

He was shaking his head with an expression he had never seen before.

“I'm sorry, brother. I didn't expect you to be so crowded.”

Hearing this, Andromalius was filled with joy.

So he turned his face to Seth's and cried out mournfully.

[It's all because of you that I'm like this! If only you'd acknowledge me! If only you'd guided me to the right path, I wouldn't be like this! I wouldn't have sold my soul to the devil!]

“....”

With those words, Osiris shakes his head, his expression even more somber.

Andromalius was about to move when he realized that the direction Osiris was standing was the only way out.

...Pfft!

A dagger pierces his back, protruding from his breastplate.

[What the hell, this asshole is doing it again...!]

Andromalius cried out, spewing black blood from his mouth.

Before he knew it, Vikir, who had approached from behind, had driven his sword through Andromalius' spine.

“I'm used to rock climbing.”

He'd spent days and days climbing on the way to raid Madame's nest, so he was good at it.

Vikir lifted his head and looked up at Osiris above.

He had once thought Osiris cold-blooded, without blood or tears, but now that he had grown older, he could see his true colors.

Vikir said.

“Don't pay any attention to what he says, brother.”

“...!”

Osiris looked up.

Vikir spoke briefly.

“Brother Seth has already died in childhood, and this demon has only been acting, hiding in his skin.”

It was half a lie, but there was no way to prove it, so what the hell.

Given the circumstances, I can't say much more.

As Vikir comforted Osiris, he placed three or four more stabs into Andromalius' body.

Only when Andromalius stretched out the snake on his left arm to counterattack did Vikir fall backwards, kicking off the rock wall and onto the ceiling.

Then, Vikir and Hugo's gazes met.

Nod.

Hugo nodded.

He was the Lord of Baskerville, but he was not authorized to call upon the dogs of Baskerville at this time.

Half a day.

For half a day, Vikir is their master.

That was what Hugo had promised when he brought the Pomeranian to him.

Vikir glanced up.

The moon in the dark clouds was slowly falling.

Until its light faded and the dawn's first rays rose, all of the Ironbloods belonged to Vikir.

Then the master gave the hounds their first command.

“Bite and kill.”

The target is self-explanatory.

“Heh heh heh...... You're cutting through all the demons like that in my life.”

“A demon of the highest rank. This will be a good experience.”

Count Boston Terrier and Count Great Dane sheathed their swords.

All the seven counts, who were just gathering at the family to see Vikir, draw their swords at once, and terrifying killing intent burst forth.

Thud.

Osiris Le Baskerville, a young master of the Iron Blood Sword Family, also drew his sword.

A brotherly love that has never been shown because it is clumsy in expressing emotions.

When Osiris touches his sword, it spreads to a pale bloody color.

It fluttered.

And then. The black robes fluttered in the wind.

Seven hundred Graduators, led by the Seventh Count, raised their swords.

Puff-puff-puff-puff-puff!

Andromalius's entire body began to explode.

Slash, slash, slash. Stab, stab, stab.

Countless fierce teeth oviposited Andromalius' entire body.

Andromalius was immobilized by Madame's poison and the fear of his body's original owner.

[Aaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhh!]

Andromalius unleashed his demon power with all his might.

Countless bloodsucking flies were unleashed.

A family of grave-dwellers. The great insects that once ruled this world soared high into the air.

But they could not rise too high, pickled in the water that ran down the cave walls, the groundwater tainted with spider venom.

Thud.

Even more so after Osiris' sword split Andromalius' spirit body and Seth's body in half at the same time.

[...Urgh!?]

As Seth's head flew into the air, Andromalius' head was also severed.

It was a fitting end for a man who had brought the continent to the brink of destruction before his regression.

And now. The situation was settled.

Each Knight made their way into the training hall where Seth had been staying.

With Seth gone, it was easy for anyone to enter the training hall.

The foul smell of magic and poison, the corpses of flies, and the bones of children strewn about were enough to make anyone cringe.

“You've done it again.”

“He's my nephew, and he's amazing. I'm so proud of him.”

Boston Terriers and Great Danes come up to pet Vikir's head, showing off their inner faces.

The other Seven Counts also sneak up on Vikir, pretending to know him, and showering him with praise and compliments.

“....”

Meanwhile, Hugo and Osiris are silent as they look into the depths of the training hall.

Countless strewn bones, strewn miasma, the rotten and twisted interior of the cave.

“...Is this the inside of Baskerville.”

Hugo's voice rose from the depths of his lungs.

He didn't show it, but he, himself, seemed shocked.

Is it because of the corruption and death of the second son, or is it about a mighty demon hiding nearby, or both?

I don't know what else is in his mind. No, maybe even himself.

Osiris's mind, on the other hand, was a little easier to read than Hugo's.

“...Seth.”

Osiris stared into the deep pool where Seth supposedly resided.

A cold, narrow, lonely den. Was this where Seth had spent all those years sharpening his sword and harboring his poison?

Osiris thought back to the long years of Seth's training.

Where had it all gone so wrong.

Then.

Vikir stepped forward.

“You have nothing to blame yourself for, brother. This is all the work of demons.”

But Osiris shook his head.

“No. I'm just as guilty of giving the demon a chance. I am to blame. Seth has been a great admirer of mine since he was a child.”

The confession was somewhat surprising coming from his mouth. Vikir's eyes widened a little, but he didn't show it.

Osiris spoke, a hint of sadness radiating from his expressionless face.

“It is the second thing to feel sorry for the corruption and death of flesh and blood. Prior to that, the people of Baskerville, the children who would become the future of the family, had been sacrificed so many times...... And I regret that I have been neglecting it until now.”

“....”

On that point, Vikir could only nod.

But this happened even before the regression. It wasn't something that could be stopped.

...Just then.

“What!”

A member of the Pit Bull Knights shouted in the distance.

Staffordshire Baskerville. The knight who assisted Vikir in the past stretched out his sword and shouted.

“Enemy, the enemy is alive, fleeing!”

At those words, more than seven hundred eyes turned in unison to one place.

It was the mask that underestimated the amazing vitality unique to demons.

[Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha, you stupid hounds! Die!]

Andromalius was fleeing with only his head.

He stretched his winged serpent tail down the cut side of his neck and flew away at tremendous speed. Toward the river in the distance.

[The time to open the gate will be delayed, but it can't be helped! That's what the other brothers will do! Hahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha-]

Andromalius cursed at the Baskervilles and charged toward the dam.

....

...No, he was not going to run.

Thwack-

He would have if Hugo hadn't drawn his longsword from his belt.

...Flash!

A sound like explosives, a strike faster than lightning.

In that brief moment, every knight in Baskerville saw it.

Seven crimson thunderbolts, powerful enough to split the sky into seven pieces.

It evaporated a thick layer of dark clouds in an instant and aimed for Andromalius beyond.

[Hahahaha... ha?]

Andromalius didn't even finish laughing.

Digig-

He disintegrated in midair without leaving a single scrap of meat behind.

Even his soul was shredded to pieces.

“....”

All the swordsmen of Baskerville were humbled by Hugo's incredible strength.

Even the Seventh Count and Osiris the young master, stared at Hugo's back with trembling pupils.

Meanwhile. Hugo muttered as he looked up at the sky split into seven pieces.

“...Mustache. I'll shave it.”

It seemed that he was remembering the only traces of Roxana and Penelope, who had parted a long time ago, and the only traces of their reunion.

Chapter 126

Admission to the Academy (2)

◆

“So, this is where I'll be going to school from today!”

A boy enters the academy.

The boy walks to the Academy's main gate, full of ambition.

He is surrounded by a huge crowd of people in the same situation as him, the new students of the 20th class.

They are like carp swimming backward towards the gate.

Suddenly, I hear a middle-aged woman's voice behind me.

“Oh my God, look at him, he forgot his backpack!”

It was the mother of a freshman boy, and she ran toward the academy's main entrance in a panic, calling her son's name.

“Hey, Vikir, don't forget your backpack!”

Suddenly, a few heads turned among the crowd of people climbing the main entrance.

“Huh?”

“Me?”

“Me?”

A dozen or so boys scattered about turned their heads.

This was because they all had the common name of Vikir.

“Oh, mom, don't call me that loud!”

Vikir, who had forgotten his backpack, scurried down the hill, red-faced, grabbed his backpack, and started back up the hill.

The other nine Vikirs turned their heads again, realizing that their mother hadn't called them.

...But.

There was one Vikir who never looked back in the first place.

A freshman with stuffy bangs hiding his face, horn-rimmed glasses completely obscuring his eyes, and a shabby shirt and pants, carrying a modest backpack.

Vikir. Vikir Van Baskerville.

A boy who shed his Baskerville surname to take the Academy exams as a commoner.

Inwardly, Vikir thought it was a good thing he'd left the Baskerville name behind.

However, the name of Vikir Van Baskerville, which had been recognized by the imperial court, had become so famous that it had become a nuisance in his daily life.

“ ... It defeats the fundamental purpose of coming to the Academy.”

Vikir had a clear idea of what he wanted to do when he joined the Academy.

To capture and kill the demons lurking in the ecliptic, the traitors and traffickers of humanity.

To do so would prevent an age of destruction in the near future.

Vikir remembered a time before his regression.

Ten high-ranking demons descended upon the mortal realm.

Together, they erected ten giant pillars and formed a gate to the demonic realm.

One of those ten demons was Andromalius, the demon who wore the skin of Seth Le Baskerville.

Luckily, we were able to kill him before he could accumulate too much power, or we would have been in trouble.

If it hadn't been for Vikir in the first place, no one would have noticed Andromalius' presence.

And now, it's clear that the other nine Demon are also hiding in the human realm, wearing human skin.

“According to Cindywendy's research, several high-ranking individuals who were in contact with Seth have gathered here on the Imperial City.”

The more people there are, the more likely it is that demons are lurking.

That's why Vikir has come to the Academy here, and why he's assumed a suitable identity to avoid suspicion.

An academy freshman from a commoner's background.

He often has to travel outside the academy to attend classes and go on assassination missions, but becoming too famous and drawing attention to himself can cause many problems.

So Vikir purposely entered the academy as a commoner.

Just to focus on the written exams.

“I'm confident in ... theory.”

It was a bit too much to get first place, but in reality, written grades are not treated well anyway.

Maybe it was because he hadn't been able to take the academy's theory class properly in his previous life.

<The Holes and Gaps in Modern Swordsmanship Theory...>

<Anthropological Perspectives on the Ecology of the New Species Mushuhushu...>

<Examination of the habits and strategies of yetis living in the snowy mountains of the northern continent...>

<Discussion on the possibility of the existence of undead-type demons that do not have divine power and their strategies...>

The field experience of a seasoned veteran who had survived through an age of destruction was a great help in verbalizing and describing theories.

Thus, Vikir was able to write the answer sheet with ease, and that alone earned him first place honors.

Meanwhile.

At the dormitory where Vikir went to unpack his belongings for the rest of his life, he was greeted by many of his fellow students.

“Do you know the Dao, and would you like to explore it with our Domino club?”

“Hey, you look so lucky! Why don't you join our pufferfish cooking study group!”

“Hey, I'm trying to be nice, but come over here! Our meditation study group is....”

“It'll only take a minute, but can you fill out a survey and put your fingerprints and seal stamp on the sign-up sheet for your favorite club?”

Clubs, research groups, clubs, societies, organizations, etc.

Many current students are working hard to appeal to new students.

Among them, the clubs that most freshmen are interested in are major-level clubs that help them with their specs, or clubs that sound interesting just by hearing about them.

Student council, various sports, band, dance, theater, economic research, and culinary clubs are the main ones that attract freshmen.

On the other hand, newspaper clubs, horticulture clubs, art clubs, reading clubs, and long-lived beetle research clubs are relatively unpopular.

Meanwhile. The seniors who were inviting students to join the clubs were also looking for some freshmen with a light in their eyes.

First of all, 'Tudor' from the Donquixote family, famous for his spear skills, and 'Bianca' from the Usher family, famous for her archery skills, were the first targets of the seniors.

The same goes for “Sinclaire,” who, despite her unknown affiliation, scored a staggering 1st in practical and 2nd in written.

...But none of this matters to Vikir.

All he can think about is getting back to his dorm, unpacking, and getting some rest.

Because he has to go on a killing expedition starting tonight.

“How many pages are there in the book of killings alone?”

The blacklist.

There were many things that deserved to die, even among humans, not demons.

Traitors who sided with the demons and sold out humanity.

'...That's a lot of people to kill.'

Vikir thought to himself as he walked through the crowd of new students.

Just then.

“Newspaper department, newspaper department, keep up with what's going on in the school.”

A familiar voice called out from somewhere.

Vikir turned to see a familiar face hawking flyers and enrollment forms.

St. Dolores L. Quovadis.

The youngest early admit student.

Current third-year senior.

The academy's student council president.

And the head of the newspaper club.

The school's number one idol who hasn't missed a beat in the past three years.

She was handing out application forms by hand.

“Senpai, please take a look at this, kaaaak!”

“Senpai! I'm a fan! I love you!”

“I joined the academy just to see you!”

“Wow, you're so beautiful, so pious, so holy!”

The freshmen are jostling to get the flyers handed out by this legendary senior, hoping to catch her eye for once.

“....”

But as they pass in front of her, Vikir only presses her face-hiding bangs and thick horn-rimmed glasses even tighter.

He has already met St. Dolores.

“ ... I met her once when I was a hound of the night.”

The holy water she brewed for us helped to quell the water plague.

But the holy woman doesn't know Vikir's true face now because he wore a mask.

So Vikir had to turn away from her and return to his dormitory without giving away his identity.

There was no point in being recognized.

◆

The atmosphere in the dormitory building was quite relaxed.

The building was large and grand, but from an individual's point of view, there was no need to wander all over the place.

It was very well designed so that you didn't have to wander too much beyond the limited area of your floor, hallways, and stairs.

The boys' and girls' dormitories were attached to the two main buildings in an A-shape, but were strictly separated, with different floors for different grades.

4th grade is on the 1st floor, 3rd grade is on the 2nd floor, 2nd grade is on the 3rd floor, and 1st grade is on the 4th floor.

I think this is because the older you get, the harder it is to climb the stairs.

The rooms are neither large nor small, and the standard option is a simple setup with a large bunk bed, an equally large desk, and two chairs.

It had the feel of a standard youth hostel, except that the restroom with shower was a bit dated.

...Tuck!

After arriving at the room, Vikir dropped his simple luggage, consisting of a few clothes, on the desk.

Then.

“...Uh, hey, are you in this room too?”

The voice came from the side of the bathroom.

Vikir turned his head to see a short boy standing there.

Blond hair. His cheeks were less chiseled and he had a few false teeth, and his androgynous appearance quite cute.

A nametag was pinned to his chest, written in crude handwriting.

'Pigi.'

This was his roommate for the next year.

And Vikir already knew this guy.

'Pigi. Here we go again.'

Before the regression. He remembers him as a nice guy.

He was the first to reach out to Vikir, who had come to babysit the Baskervilles' triplets, even when he was doing odd jobs.

In this life, Pigi was nice, too.

“Uh, so your name's Vikir, so you'll be good to me in the future, and you'll have to forgive me if I'm a little clumsy and slow. Oh, and I heard there are two bunk beds, so you can pick your own first!”

Vikir sighed briefly at Pigi's cheerful suggestion.

The students at the Academy are young, but they're smart.

They've been around the block and heard the elite talk, so they're no strangers to civility, betrayal, politics, and bullying.

A nice, innocent guy like Pigi gets lost in the jungle of freshmen, where there is a lot of first-mover advantage.

'...In a previous life, that's exactly what happened.'

Pigi was a longtime victim of bullying.

His cute looks, small size, and timid personality made him stand out from the crowd of big, muscular, and outspoken boys.

His hobbies of reading and analyzing information in solitude didn't fit in with the academic culture of power.

Vikir knows this, and it's why he can't help but look at him with compassion.

'Before the regression, Pigi's roommate was Highbro Le Baskerville, I believe, so I have an idea of what his academic life was like back then.'

Whether he realized it or not, Pigi breathed a sigh of relief at the thought of having a roommate whose first impression, while a bit reticent, was still friendly.

He must have worried a lot about meeting a scary roommate.

Then.

Pigi spoke to Vikir first.

“Hey, Vikir, you're going to O.T. later tonight, right?”

Freshman orientation.

I read it as a time to educate the newly admitted freshmen about the basics of the academy ... and a time for the seniors to meet the freshmen and get to know them over drinks.

It's not really required, but it's still something that every freshman should attend.

The idea is to get to know the people you'll be spending the next four years with and to network with the seniors.

The connections you make here will be the foundation of your future career, aka your “line,” and you've fought through a “bloodbath” to get here.

...But.

“No.”

Vikir was not interested in any of that.

The Assassination Act.

Because from now on, the real bloodshed was to come.

Chapter 127

Admission to the Academy (3)

◆

“...?”

Pigi looked at Vikir with a blank expression.

Then, in a tone of deep embarrassment, he asked.

“Oh, you're not going to OT?”

“No. I'm not going.”

Vikir was still adamant.

Pigi gestured frantically toward Vikir, who was unpacking his few remaining belongings.

“Oh, no! We have to go! If we don't go to OT, we'll be labeled an asshole by our seniors, and we'll be a pariah among our peers, which will make it very difficult for us to get information and connections....”

Aah. Outsider is a word that refers to a person who does not belong to a group and stands out.

Not only do they face difficulties in situations that require group strength, such as unexpected lectures, class schedule changes, and group assignments, but they are also at a disadvantage in networking and information gathering.

Therefore, Pigi's point about attending OTs is well taken.

.......That is, in the case of a normal freshman.

However, in Vikir's case, it was much easier to be active without being seen by everyone, as he rather wanted to become an assassin.

Meanwhile, Vikir stared down at Pigi, who was looking sullen.

Pigi's gaze was genuinely concerned about Vikir's academy life.

He's still a nice guy, almost to a fault.

“It's going to be hard for him to fit in at the academy with this personality.”

Pigi is timid but cautious and good at collecting and analyzing information.

If Cindywendy saw him, she'd scout him out in a second.

However, among the new students at the Academy, Pigi is the easiest person to take advantage of and bully.

The academy's culture favored practice and actual work over notes and theory.

It's a belief that has been passed down through the generations, not only in the Colosseo, but in other top institutions such as the Magic Academy, the Magic Tower, and the Varangian Academy of Martial Arts.

In other words, within the academy, power is always above all else.

It's not about childish brawls or fistfights, it's about performance in practical assessments.

Without that, it's hard to get noticed.

In reality, Pigi was good at gathering and analyzing information because he had a good head on his shoulders, but that's it, he wasn't very good at anything in Cold Class or Hot Classes, so he always got stuck in practical exams.

His caring nature, at best, and timidity, at worst, led to subtle ridicule, scorn, and bullying.

'And to add insult to injury, he had the misfortune of meeting the vicious Highbro of Baskerville as his roommate for the first semester.'

From then on, Pigi was always on the sidelines.

Because of Highbro's personality, Pigi was barely treated as a human being, and other classes, and even upperclassmen, were always bullying and taking advantage of him.

But despite this, Pigi was a good boy who always had a smile on his face.

Whenever he saw someone who was weaker than him, he would always lend a hand and help them as best he could.

“....”

Vikir glanced at Pigi and then looked away.

Pigi, meanwhile, had no idea what Vikir was thinking, and was still trying to convince him of the necessity of the OT.

“There's a lot of powerful seniors coming to this OT! St. Dolores, the student council president, is coming! And we have a great class! You've heard of Tudor, the eldest son of Donquixote, and Bianca, the eldest daughter of Usher! That's not all! The Baskervilles have triplets, and they're all amazing! There's a kid named Sancho from the Mercenary Guild of the North, who passed up a chance to be a top student at Varangian to come here! And then there's Sinclaire, who's a top in the Hot Class, and this person came to the Colosseo after being accepted as a top in the Magic Tower! Isn't it amazing that he's a top in the Colosseo's Hot Class? These guys are already considered the next generation of heroes, so you should definitely go see them! I can't believe I'm in the same class as these guys.....................”

Actually, it's great that Pigi already has this information.

If the seniors of the current students had heard of it, they would make a scouting offer to their club or family just with their ability to collect and analyze information.

“How's that? You're feeling a little more motivated now, huh?”

Pigi looks up at Vikir with a twinkle in his eye, like he's looking for a compliment.

But Vikir still shakes his head.

“But I'm not going.”

“What? Why? What the hell-”

Pigi, who had hoped to go to OT with his roommate so that they could have each other's backs, was faced with an unexpected challenge.

In fact, it was rare, even impossible, for a freshman to skip OT.

To this reasonable question, Vikir had a short answer.

“I just don't want to go.”

That was it.

Vikir gathered his things and quickly left the room.

He quickly disappeared down the hallway, which was bustling with freshmen.

Pigi watched, dumbfounded, and muttered.

“...Cool. My roommate is a cool guy! I should learn from that kind of determination!”

Always the positive Pigi.

◆

Gloomy evening. The afterglow burning over the high walls of the academy.

The streets leading down to the lecture hall were already crowded with new students.

Girls dressed up brightly, boys dressed smartly.

But somehow, the atmosphere was sloppy and green.

Sloppy makeup and overdone hairstyles are still on display, and the girls are standing a bit stiffly.

Boys and girls are exploring each other's groups, looking like they're about to be blown away.

And the seniors were gently leading the newcomers to the meeting place.

“Okay, Cold Class A, please gather this way.”

“'Hot Class C', we'll meet under the red flag over here~”

“Student council executives, please lead the new students to the venue!”

In the lecture hall where the evening play is over, students and newcomers enter every empty classroom because the beginning of the semester has not yet arrived.

In the corridors of the lecture hall, which quickly became crowded, rumors and gossip about the new students were spreading.

“These freshmen are really tough. They're all killing it on their practical assessments~”

“Of course Tudor, Bianca, and Sinclaire are the ones you're most excited about, right?”

“ Well, individually, I suppose, but then there's the Baskerville triplets, and I'm more excited about their synergy together.”

“But didn't that... crap say that 'he' was getting in from Baskerville this year?”

The chatter among the freshmen heats up even more at this last statement.

“Oh, you mean Vikir? I thought that was a rumor.”

“There's no way he could have accomplished such a feat in his late teens, isn't he a fictional character?”

“Yeah, well, aristocratic families tend to spread rumors to boost their family's stock price, and Baskerville is a pretty closed community....”

“There are more than a dozen kids named Vikir in this freshman class, and they're all commoners.”

“But there's one kid who stood out, and he's the one who took the first written exam.”

“A written exam? Ah, what's so great about a guy who only knows theory? I don't find studying worms like that attractive – jocks are cool!”

Soon, the chatter in the hallway became more and more frequent.

New students have entered every classroom in the lecture hall.

Boys, girls, boys and girls.

After a few moments of small talk and eye contact, the classmates quickly bonded.

Although the friendships were hastily made, they have already sprouted between them.

“ Is everyone here? Let's take a roll call of the new students in class 20.”

The seniors of the student council call out the names on the list and proceed to check the attendance of the class.

And then a name is called out.

“Vikir.”

“Yes.”

“Vikir.”

“Yes.”

“Vikir.”

“Yes.”

“Vikir.”

“....”

“Vikir?”

The one absentee who had been called a few too many times by common names.

Vikir van Baskerville. No, just “Vikir” now.

He did indeed not attend the OT.

It's just that he wore a black cloak and mask as the Hound of the Night instead of the student Vikir.

...Boom!

Vikir stepped on the roof of the academy's spire wearing a black cloak and a gas mask shaped like a stork's beak used by medieval plague doctors.

Over a wall almost as high as the city walls, he stepped into the beautiful city center of the Imperial City, with its countless waterways and bridges.

Vikir melted soundlessly into the pitch-black city.

It's a night when classmates of the 20th class are drinking and strengthening their friendships with their seniors and classmates.

In the meantime, Vikir will visit the mansions of those on the kill list, one by one.

The demons. And traitors.

It is here, in the Imperial City, that the traitors of mankind gather!

'...My comrades, be patient. I will avenge you in a moment.'

Vikir remembered the faces of his fellow hounds who had been betrayed and died, recalling the bad ties of his previous life.

And then.

He followed the faint scent of demons across the city.

The Night Hounds have finally begun their hunt.

Chapter 129

The Freshman Talent Show (1)

◆

Vikir walked into the lecture hall in search of class B of the Cold Class.

A large group of people were gathered in a circle, drinking, and in the center of the room, one by one, the new students came forward to perform a talent show.

As Vikir walked into the classroom, he heard a welcoming voice right by the door.

“Vikir, you're back! Why are you so late?”

It was his roommate, Pigi.

Pigi was so happy to see him that he rummaged through a box on the table and pulled out a nametag that read, “'Vikir, class 20′”.

“It's my job to hand out name tags to everyone who comes in. Here's yours!”

“...Why are you doing this job?”

Handing out nametags to newcomers is usually the job of the second-year seniors.

Since Pigi is also a newcomer, why is he doing the chore of handing out name tags to his classmates?

Vikir wondered.

Then Pigi smiled wryly.

“Oh, the seniors said it's a hassle to keep track of all the name tags, so they asked me to help out a little.”

Vikir's head snapped up at that.

Sure enough, several of the sophomores who had deferred to Pigi had mingled with the crowd, watching the newcomers' talent show.

“Whoa! Tudor is awesome! Encore!”

“Swoon! Cold Class! Go Tudors!”

“You're the best, Tudor! My sister's already a fan, eek!”

A pretty tough bunch, even for sophomores.

To get to know the newcomers who seemed to be doing well, they had already assigned chores to Pigi, who didn't seem to have any ability or backbone, so I thought they were definitely quick to understand.

Meanwhile.

In the center of the stage, the newcomers who have completed the talent show are seated in rows on one side of a long table.

On the other side of the table are a few professors, teaching assistants, and seniors.

The seniors are few and far between, as they are preparing to enter the workforce.

St. Dolores, the student council president, was making the rounds to each class, stopping to check on the remaining juniors.

“The president is here!”

“Saint, I would be honored if you would accept my cup!”

“Sister, you're here to write an article for the Cold Clas's senior and junior reunion, right? Please take care of the article!”

“I love you president! Kyaaak!”

Dolores was a hit with everyone; she was the center of attention.

At this point, the sophomore emcee grabs the mana-filled megaphone and makes a comment.

“Yes, it's time for the next talent show, and the one everyone's been waiting for, the Super Rookie of Class 20, Ms. Usher Bianca, please join us!”

Thunderous applause erupted.

Then, with all eyes on her, Bianca stepped forward.

Her complexion was calm, as if she had just received a rooftop confession.

However, her breathing was slightly uneven, as if she had rushed down from the rooftop.

She then bowed her head in front of the seniors.

“I, a junior who is lacking in many ways, dare to raise a drink to you seniors.”

Bianca nonchalantly picked up the bottle and popped the cap.

And then.

Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow!

She grabbed the bottle and gave it a quick shake, sending the liquor flying through the narrow neck.

In the space of a single sip, it flew a long way, over the heads of the people in front of her, and landed precisely in the glasses on the table behind her.

Clink, clink, clink, clink!

The seniors let out a collective exclamation of admiration at this strange trick of throwing liquor from several meters away and filling the glasses.

Bianca kept the mood high for a short but intense moment, then bowed her head.

Then she turned back to the crowd and thought to herself.

“Whoever this is, they're going to have a hard time with the next one.”

Bianca's stunt, while entertaining, didn't really deserve the cheers it received.

The outpouring of support was probably due to her background, abilities, and appearance.

So unless a newcomer comes along and does something amazing to match Bianca's background, abilities, and appearance, it's going to be hard to keep the momentum going.

In other words, having set the tone, the next newcomer is going to be under a lot of pressure.

'Well, it's none of my business.'

Bianca returned to her seat, deciding that there was no reason to be considerate of the motives of those behind her.

And then, in a cruel twist of nature. The host called for the next act in the talent show.

“Okay, we've got our highly anticipated super-rookie, Ms. Bianca, and we've seen her pouring skills! What are we going to do about this heated atmosphere? We need our next performer before it cools down!”

The host immediately called out the next name.

“Next! New student from class 20! Mr. Pigi, the cutest little guy!”

Pigi's name was called.

Then Pigi, who was handing out nametags at the back of the crowd, stiffened.

“Uh, uh, uh, I thought you said you'd let me out of the talent show if I volunteered to hand out these name tags...?”

As Pigi turned his head in embarrassment, the sophomores who had been handing out name tags to Pigi giggled and turned their heads away.

Turning away.

Pigi looked up in disbelief.

The host continues to gesture toward Pigi, who remains oblivious.

“What are you going to do about this atmosphere, we can't let it cool down like this, hurry up!”

Pigi felt his head go blank.

His vision goes white and his hands and feet shake.

A cold sweat broke out at the crown of his head as he felt all eyes on him.

“Pigi? Pigi, what are you doing? Come on out!”

The host kept calling for Pigi.

Then, one by one, the seniors who were applauding also shook their heads, their smiles disappearing.

“Aah....”

Pigi despaired.

His timid and introverted personality made it difficult for him to talk to others eye-to-eye, and he couldn't imagine performing in front of such a large crowd.

Pigi's hobbies and interests include reading, listening to music, drawing, and having pets.

These are not the kinds of things that will help you get up in front of a crowd.

It would have been one thing if I'd been prepared from the start, but the fact that I was caught off guard by the promise of exclusion made it all the more confusing.

'Uh, what do I do? What do I do....'

I'm breaking out in a cold sweat and my legs are shaking. I want to run away right now, but my legs are stiff and I can't get off.

“....”

The room was getting quieter and quieter.

Even the hosts who were making comments looked awkward and stiff.

The seniors around me also looked confused.

Just then.

...Jaw!

A hand gripped Pigi's shoulder.

“We'll do the talent show together, we're roommates.”

A low, gravelly voice from behind.

A boy with bushy bangs and thick horn-rimmed glasses covering his face stepped forward.

It was Vikir.

“Oooh, who's who, Vikir from class 20? Alas, you were late for roll call earlier!”

The host broke the awkward silence and greeted Vikir with a smile.

“Yeah, yeah, yeah, I usually don't do that, but I'll make a special exception this time! You're roommates, and you're going to have to live with Miu and Kouga for a year, so why don't you be nice and show us your talent!”

Many eyes now turned to Pigi and Vikir.

“Vikir....”

Pigi looks up at Vikir with a questioning gaze.

Vikir simply blurted out in a nonchalant tone.

“I'll sing.”

“...?”

“You shall dance.”

Then Pigi threw another tantrum.

“Me, are you serious? Well, of course I'm tone-deaf, but.......”

“It's okay. Anyone can do it.”

Vikir shook his fist at Pigi, first from top to bottom, then from bottom to top.

It was a simple dance, really, requiring only that he repeat the motion and stomp his right foot each time his fist came down.

“Uh, uh, uh... can you make this work?”

“That's enough. Just make it hard, and make sure you bow.”

Vikir grabbed Pigi by the shoulders and led him to the center of the crowd.

Then, as everyone watched, Vikir's song and Pigi's dance began.

...?

The gazes of the hosts and seniors became slightly subtle.

Surprised, yes, but not with admiration....

“What is this?”

They all looked confused, unable to grasp the situation.

He was right, the song Vikir was singing was a completely different kind of song from what the newcomers had been singing.

“High mountains, deep valleys, deserted mountains, snowy fronts, here we come.”

A military song.

The kind of songs they used to sing on the front lines.

Vikir didn't have any particular talent to get the crowd going.

He'd spent his entire life wandering the battlefields of the Nine Rivers without the luxury of hearing a single popular song.

...But only one thing.

He knew one song that could move anyone, that could make anyone shudder, that anyone could relate to.

In those days, when the bodies piled up into mountains and the blood flowed into rivers.

'The Age of Destruction.'

A song that could be sung by anyone who had ever held a sword and fought a demon.

It was a war song that was shared and enjoyed by all.

“The spot where a young soul died. The wounded old pine forgot his words.”

A monotonous shaking of fists and stomping of feet.

But the thrill, the emotion, the heart and soul of those days when thousands, tens of thousands, hundreds of millions of people rolled and cried and sang together.

Vikir scanned the faces of his seniors and classmates gathered in the academy.

Brothers who had died in long wars, old comrades who had stood shoulder to shoulder guarding the borders, brothers who had shed tears of blood for him, even to the point of being falsely accused and executed, still sat there, green and young and frail.

Vikir looked at them and swallowed back the bitterness and longing.

“Do you hear, comrade, that angry voice?”

A hound from an age of destruction, understood by none.

Can you see it, comrade, the tearful eyes.

And with that, Vikir finished the last verse of the song.

When he was finished, Vikir gave a respectful salute.

He turned around, gave a quick bow, and disappeared into the crowd.

....

There was a strange feeling in the air that was hard to describe.

The excitement was definitely dampened, but not in a bad way.

One way or another, Vikir's song had left a mark on everyone's hearts.

“What, what's with this creeping vibe?”

“Are you an old man? What are you doing all of a sudden?”

“What's with this atmosphere~”

Most of the people complaining about the dampened excitement were younger students.

However.

The atmosphere in the hall slowly began to change.

“...Oh.”

The old professors sitting in the front row suddenly burst into tears.

Chapter 133

Test Your Skills (2)

◆

“Judging by that pathetic sight.”

Professor Banshee is a man who takes unusually strong pride in his class.

The cold anger in his voice, and the blatant disparagement in his intentions, had all the students in both Hot and Cold Classes on edge.

“There was a reason why the Hot Class seniors gave out 'ice that doesn't melt well' made with magic. I keep putting it on the nape of my neck so I don't feel sleepy.”

“Wow, I'm jealous. They used to hand out little metal sticks, and when you get sleepy, you poke your thigh with it.”

“By the way, that Vikir guy is in trouble. He's going to get his ass handed to him by Professor Banshee on his first day.”

“Ugh, he's screwed. I heard that professor gives you a group grade whether you do well or not.”

“He just gave Ms. Sinclaire 10 points for her attitude and 1 point for the entire Hot Class.”

“It would be nice to have a top student, Hot Class.”

“On the other hand, you're doomed from the start, Cold Class. All because of one stupid troll.”

“How could you fall asleep at the beginning of class? Even the most nervous idiot can't....”

The students look at Prof. Banshee and give a small bow amongst themselves.

...Not a single person stiffened.

Except for Vikir.

“....”

The controversial Vikir is deep in thought, unaware of the attention being focused on him.

'Come to think of it, there was something off about all the guys I killed yesterday.'

He recalled the twenty-nine faces he'd snuck outside the Academy to assassinate before attending the OT last night.

Every single one of them had a distinctly demonic stench, and their 'faces' had melted away upon death.

It was the trait he most associated with the ninth of the Ten Corpses, the Nine Top Corpses, whom he was now pursuing.

'It's most likely that 'he' is involved, I'll have Cindywendy focus her investigation on him....'

Vikir was making plans for the next demon hunt.

“...Vii, Vikir. Vikir!”

I feel Pigi poking me in the side, making me groggy.

The first thing I see when I open my eyes is Pigi's sullen expression and the fierce glares of my fellow Cold Class.

The first thing I saw was Professor Banshee's angry face beyond the giggles of the Hot Class students.

Then, with a crooked smile tugging at the corners of his mouth, Professor Banshee turned to Vikir.

“Vikir of Class B of the Cold Class, I see from your detention record that you already have a bad attitude. How in the world did you ever get into the academy if you've been dozing off since the first day of class?”

Professor Banshee's words brought sighs from the cold students and scoffs from the hot students.

It's clear that a single Vikir will result in a deduction in the attitude score of the entire cold section, which will lead to a relative advantage for the hot students.

Then.

Something happened that shocked the entire class.

“I wasn't asleep.”

Vikir blurted out.

“...?”

For a moment, Professor Banshee doubted his ears.

He hadn't seen a freshman talk back to him in the twenty years since he'd been on the faculty.

He'd seen plenty of students who cried or fussed over a point.

No freshman had ever dared to argue with Professor Banshee's waxen, pale expression and the grim aura of a warlock from Morgue's Dark Faction.

Not even fourth-year undergraduates, not even graduate students, not even professors like him.

So Professor Banshee checked his own ears to make sure they were functioning properly and asked Vikir once more.

“You're not asleep?”

“No.”

“That's a lame excuse, even though everyone saw you with your eyes closed?”

“My eyes were closed, but I wasn't asleep.”

Then Professor Banshee's expression turned harder and harder.

At the same time, the faces of all the students were getting whiter and whiter.

Professor Banshee's smile grew even more crooked.

Then he spoke again in a sarcastic voice.

“I see, I must have misunderstood you, for you have branded a student who merely had his eyes closed as a lazy slacker.”

“It's okay. You may have misunderstood.”

“....”

Vikir's nonchalant response left his classmates, and even Professor Banshee, speechless for a moment.

For a moment, I thought, 'Did I really misunderstand?

...Poof!

Professor Banshee closed his mouth, and a terrifying sound emanated from it.

The sound of gnashing teeth made the students in the front of the room shrink their shoulders in unison.

Anything that comes out of a warlock's mouth should be taken with a grain of salt, but that was before the problem.

As if the temperature in the room had dropped a degree or so, Professor Banshee turned to Vikir and asked him his earlier question in a sharp tone.

“Alright, if you weren't dozing off, you'd be able to answer my question. I will do you a favor and remind you of the problem from earlier.”

Professor Banshee glared at Vikir as if to say, “I'm going to repeat the problem from earlier.”

“If you have memorized and understood my lecture so far, this should be easy for you to answer: name the places where the hunters of the barbarian tribe of Ballak have engaged the armies of the Empire, and based on their locations, guess where their home base is.”

When he had finished, he glanced from Sinclaire, who was fidgeting in the front seat, to Tudor and Bianca, who were seated side by side behind him.

Professor Banshee glared at Vikir.

“Your classmates gave me some not-so-bad answers earlier, and you don't tell me that even those capable of coming up with their own answers have been taking my class with their eyes wide open, and you, who aren't even close to that level, have been taking my class with your eyes closed? Now, I expect an answer.”

Professor Banshee left the lectern as if he had made up his mind and walked up to Vikir's desk.

It was his intention to take this opportunity to give the entire class a steamer clearance by frantically gnashing his teeth on one of the dullards.

But.

'Oh, so this is the kind of problem the youngsters at the Academy solve.'

Naturally, Vikir was not the least bit fazed, only amused.

For Vikir, a war veteran with decades of battlefield wear and tear under his belt, these problems are easier than tying his shoelaces.

The answers were imprinted in his flesh and bone, especially since his life depended on it.

Naturally, the depth of the theory is much different than just a fountain pen on paper.

However, Vikir was so familiar with the answers to these kinds of questions that he hadn't realized that Professor Banshee had deliberately given them to the students as a stunt.

So he made the mistake of answering the question over and over again.

“The places where the Ballak and the Empire fought were the 1st, 4th, 5th, 7th, 8th, 14th, 27th, 30th, 75th, 207th, and 306th heights of the Western Front, many of which are incorrectly characterized as basin and peak terrain, but in fact most of the battles were fought in the winter, when the ice and snow accumulated and melted. The warriors of the Ballak are characterized as ultra-long-range snipers and guerrilla warriors, easily traveling great distances and high terrain, while taming wolves for mobility on the plains, so their settlements are expected to follow the general characteristics of nomadic peoples, and based on their movements, it's clear that they are located on high ground, deep within the jungle. Based on that map, I'd say the most likely location is the salt river to the west, between points A and B, and the waterfall area that borders the west coast.”

Even military secrets, things that hadn't yet been reported to the academic community.

“It doesn't matter anyway, the natives of Ballak have moved elsewhere since the Ah'Heman incident.”

Even if they did, no one could get there.

Wild beasts, poisonous insects, dangerous plants, harsh terrain, and endemic diseases keep the Imperials out.

So Vikir came up with an answer that would not offend the natives of Ballak.

...But.

Even as Vikir answered Professor Banshee's question, the silence in the room remained unchanged.

“?”

Vikir finally turned his head.

He looked up and saw a puzzling scene.

....

Pigi next to him, Tudor and Bianca across from him, Sinclaire beyond him, and finally Professor Banshee Morgue.

Everyone in the classroom, hot and cold, student and professor, was staring at Vikir with their mouths agape.

Chapter 134

Test Your Skills (3)

◆

Wide-open eyes. Half-open mouth.

“....”

Professor Banshee Morgue wore an expression he hadn't worn in years.

If you didn't know him, you might think he was a little surprised, but if you did, you'd have a different opinion.

For Professor Banshee, who was so expressionless that he was often nicknamed “the wax figure,” to be wearing this expression was an expression of sheer astonishment.

Everyone in the room was stunned and speechless.

Professor Banshee was the first to break the silence.

“...Hmm. Correct.”

But then he added

“However, your answer seems to contain a number of controversial and unreported points that have not yet been vetted by the academic community.”

To be sure, there were some things in Vikir's answer that even Professor Banshee hadn't heard before.

But Professor Banshee didn't think he could dismiss Vikir's answers out of hand, because they were eerily accurate.

How does he know about the 14th and 27th battles, battles that no graduate student, let alone a professor, should have to learn and study in the first place?

And the Battle of the 306th Parallel is a historical fact that has only recently been discovered by academics and is just beginning to be studied.

'...Isn't this the kind of information that only senior officers in the active Imperial Army, or even a member of the House of Baskerville, would know?'

Professor Banshee swiped a hand across his forehead, finding it difficult to control his expression.

In truth, the question was far beyond the ability of the freshmen to answer.

Tudor and Bianca of the Cold Class could be called outstanding freshmen if they knew only the first, seventh, eighth, seventy-fifth, and twenty-seventh battles.

Here, Sinclaire of the Hot Class was memorizing the battles of the 4th, 5th, and 30th heights, which was beyond the level of an undergraduate student.

However, how was he supposed to explain this freshman in front of him?

That's where Professor Banshee's confusion comes in.

“How do you know something that hasn't been reported in the literature and why are you answering as if it's true?”

Prof. Banshee asked Vikir.

Meanwhile, Vikir remained nonchalant.

'I can't say I've lived it. It's too much trouble.'

When it comes to enemies and the Ballak of the Black Mountains, Vikir knows more than anyone. Perhaps no one in the Empire knows more about the Ballak than Vikir.

Vikir sidestepped Professor Banshee's question with a good reason.

“Recently, trade between barbarians on the Western Front and the Empire has begun. Many merchants are vying for trade. In the meantime, Do is just a common stock market slob. Sorry if I sounded assertive.”

Vikir took a step back, and even as Professor Banshee, it was hard to press him further.

After all, he'd gotten more answers than he'd asked anyway.

But the way Professor Banshee looked at Vikir was a little more intense.

“....”

The difference was that the intent in his gaze shifted from disdain to curiosity.

“You're quite interested in economics, aren't you?”

“It's not that big of a deal, I'm just a little guy with a sensitive side.”

“How modest.”

Professor Banshee narrowed his eyes and studied Vikir's face.

He opened the attendance book and flipped through the pages, taking in the student's personal details.

After a moment, Professor Banshee salivated.

“....I see. Perfect score on the handwriting.”

Professor Banshee muttered under her breath, and the entire classroom fell silent.

“Oh, so that's the one with the perfect handwriting?”

“But he got a perfect score in handwriting, is that possible?”

“The handwriting difficulty in the academy is really terrible.”

“It's crazy, I was fourth overall in this handwriting, and I flunked it.”

Everyone looked at Vikir like they were looking at a monster.

But there was one person who was most surprised.

“......A perfect score?”

The girl stares at Vikir with rabbit eyes.

She was Sinclaire, the runner-up on the handwriting test.

An honors student with a score of 931 out of 990.

It was a long way from the 700s in third place and the 500s in fourth.

But just when she thought it was weird to be in second place, Sinclaire got a little dazed when she heard the difference between her score and the first place score.

His opponent's perfect score meant that he could have scored much more.

He only scored 990 because the limit was 990, but no one knows where his skill lies.

That's what a perfect score is.

Meanwhile. Professor Banshee looked away from Vikir.

“Vikir. I'm going to give you 10 points for your excellent answer, but I can't condone the fact that you had your eyes closed in my class, so I'm going to deduct 10 points from your attitude again, and I'm also going to add one point to the attitude score of the entire Cold Class.”

Prof. Banshee then went back to teaching as usual.

Vikir was able to move on quietly, with neither extra credit nor a penalty.

The faces of the Cold Class students brightened.

But that didn't mean that their reaction to Vikir was particularly favorable.

“What an arrogant bastard. You're sleeping in class just because you ace the written exam?”

“You could have flunked the whole class.”

“I was afraid I was going to get a failing grade for attitude. I'm glad I got extra credit in the end.”

“When I see sandals like that studying, I want to punch them for nothing.”

All the students, hot and cold, gossiped.

Many students didn't recognize Vikir, as the academy's academic style emphasizes practical skills over written work.

This was especially true for the cold-class students.

This is because students in the Hot Class, represented by “mages” tend to put a lot of emphasis on handwriting, while students in the Cold Class, represented by “warriors” put less emphasis on handwriting.

Next. Several of the cold students began to discuss their devious plans amongst themselves.

“He seems like a study bug, so let's see if he can be as cocky in his afternoon class.”

“Maybe there's a physical education lab in the afternoon liberal arts requirement?”

“Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, 'Naphtali' is a real physical education class. It's even an anti-war concept.”

“It's a great way to break the snout of an arrogant asshole.”

“Everybody hold still, I got him.”

And so began a fierce battle of nerves between the freshmen.

◆

Tudor Donquixote.

The head of the Cold Warrior A class, he was currently in the center of the academy for physical education.

“...This class is for me!”

This afternoon's lesson was practical 'Naphtali'.

Naphtali is a type of sport that is categorized as a ball game.

A total of forty people, divided into two sides, try to score points by throwing the ball into the opponent's goal.

There are goals at each end of a large field, 50 meters long and 100 meters wide, and players from both teams have to carry the ball in any way they can to get it into the other team's goal.

It can be kicked, thrown, or picked up and thrown.

In the middle of the game, you can try to body slam your opponent or attack them with your fists and feet.

Either way.

Whether you dodge, fight, or pass the ball into the other team's goal is entirely up to you.

Only two things are prohibited: using mana and using weapons.

“Hahaha, Naphtali is what I do best. Let's go somewhere!”

Tudor stepped forward to represent Class A. Despite having no mana and no weapons, he was confident.

And there were three members of Class B standing in his way.

“What are you talking about, I'll kill you.”

“I'll kill you.”

“Kill him.”

They were the Baskerville triplets.

And so began the back-and-forth between the A and B teams.

“Pass! My ball!”

Tudor waved enthusiastically at his classmates from the start of the game.

Soon, a leather oval-shaped ball flew out and landed in Tudor's hands.

Tudor picked it up and started sprinting forward.

'That's it. This is the real deal!'

What's the point of memorizing theories for a written exam?

A true dragon, a true knight, must be able to run like the wind to blow past his enemies and reach his target.

Tudor was in the Runner position, and he was running fast.

And then.

There were three linesmen in his way.

“Cocky bastard. How dare you try to break through.”

“How dare you.”

“Dare.”

Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro stand in Tudor's way.

No mana, no weapons, just pure physical combat.

The iron-blooded Baskerville and the spear-wielding Donquixote were about to go head-to-head.

...But.

“I beg your pardon, sir, but I have no intention of going toe-to-toe with the monsters of the Iron-Blooded.”

Tudor whirled in place.

In the blink of an eye, he sliced through Middlebro and Lowbro and slipped through the gap between them.

It was a ghostly dodge and an all-out charge.

The rest of the class cheered at Tudor's super play.

“Wow, that's Tudor? That's amazing!”

“I can't believe he has no mana and no weapons.”

“I heard Donquixote had a genius in his family.”

“That's what you get for being the head of the Cold Warriors Class!”

The cheers didn't last long, though.

“I'm going somewhere.”

A shadowy figure followed Tudor as he ran.

Highbro Le Baskerville.

The strongest of Baskerville's tridents, he blocked Tudor again.

“The ball. Give it to me.”

And with that, Highbro hand and Tudor's hand met, and the result was....

Poof!

Surprisingly, Highbro lost.

Tudor dodged a flying Highbro's hand and left a deep palm print on his chest arm.

“Boom!”

Highbro stumbled back half a step, and Tudor spun him around at the same speed he'd been running.

“Hahaha, block him if you can!”

There was no stopping Tudor once he had outrun even Baskerville's Trident, the ace of the B class.

Pow! Boom, boom, boom, boom!

No one is taller, no one is heavier, and no one is bigger than Tudor.

With the waist of a leopard and the back of a bear, Tudor ran fast and stamped on everyone in his path.

Speed to speed, strength to strength.

Tudor Donquixote is the most powerful runner and lineman in the world.

After smashing through or past every obstacle in his path, Tudor finds himself in front of the B Class goal.

The goal is a large Y-shaped iron hoop, and if you throw the ball through it, you'll score a point.

Tudor pulls his arm back, ready to score, when something catches his eye.

“...!”

It was Vikir, standing off to the side near the goal.

Apparently, he hadn't been assigned a particularly important position and was playing a modest backup defender.

For a moment, Tudor's grim smile widened.

'Isn't that the boy from Professor Banshee's lecture this morning?'

He remembers Vikir rambling on and on about the theory.

It made his first response sound like a dumb answer.

'Let me give you a little poke.'

Tudor stopped throwing the ball and lunged forward a bit more.

He was going to bump into Vikir's shoulder and send him sprawling to the ground.

'Hey, buddy, I hope this inspires you to work out and not just study!'

And then.

...Puck!

That was Tudor's last thought.

Chapter 135

Test Your Skills (4)

◆

“What's ...?”

Tudor jerked awake.

Had he dozed off?

No, that couldn't be it. How could he doze off in the middle of a match when he was sweating it out in the first place?

As time seemed to pass slowly, Tudor recalled the situation just before his memory was momentarily interrupted.

'I'm pretty sure I got the ball, I dodged the Baskerville triplets, I broke Highbro's pursuit, I ran forward, I took a shot at the defenders in my way, and....'

And?

I don't remember what happened next.

I'm pretty sure I spotted the goal and was about to throw the ball in, but... why did I stop?

Thought after thought led to another.

...!

And with that momentary lapse in thought, Tudor came to his senses.

'What am I doing?'

Only then will his vision return to normal.

After a moment of blackness, his vision returned to normal.

The green grass of the training field, the blue sky, the towering goalposts, and the surprised faces of his enemies and allies.

So far, it's the same scene I saw just before my memory faded.

The only thing different is... that they're all upside down?

“Huh?”

Only then was Tudor able to come to his senses.

He was now stuck in the corner of the field, also upside down and in a ridiculous position.

“Ugh!?”

Tudor scrambled to his feet, looking down at the dirt and grass that covered him.

He looked down at the dirt and grass on his body, and in front of him stood Vikir with a nonchalant expression.

Tudor suddenly remembered everything.

'That's him. Just before scoring a goal, I gave him a sneaky shoulder-bump....'

A guy who was only good at studying and seemed very corrupt.

For a moment, I had the nasty thought of giving him a hard time.

But the moment I reached him and slapped him on the shoulder, Tudor was impacted as if he had been hit by a giant mountain.

He bounced off and rolled on the floor, leaving him stretched out in a ridiculous position and momentarily stunned.

Somehow, the guy who'd actually gotten the shoulder block was just standing there, dazed.

Tudor scrambled to his feet and was about to say something to Vikir when he heard a voice.

“Class A goal!”

Tudor heard the referee shout.

Tudor looks up, startled, and sees the ball rolling under the B team's goal.

As Tudor spun out of the way of Vikir, the ball floated upward and somehow went in.

It was a lucky, lucky goal, like catching a mouse in the back of a cow.

But there wasn't much of a roar from the crowd.

Even Tudor's head, after scoring the goal, was marked with a '?'

'What did I do? Why did I fall?'

Tudor continued to look bewildered.

“Even though I scored a goal, I didn't feel any sense of accomplishment.”

It was just a silly goal that went from bad to worse.

The question is, why did Tudor fall?

Tudor had never encountered a situation like this before in his career.

Even at the age of 17, he was able to overwhelm the knights in his family with his physical strength, and his talent was especially evident in the sport of Naphtali.

A jack-of-all-trades who could jump, run, dash, pass, and wrestle.

Holder, kicker, punter, returner, running back, fullback, quarterback, receiver, tackler, guard, center, linebacker, sapper, all-arounder who could play any position.

Donquixote's unrivaled ability to outwork his peers.

That was Tudor Donquixote.

But he was beaten to the punch by that study bug in front of him, the sandy-haired Vikir?

'No, that's not possible! Even if I hadn't spent any mana, that's impossible!'

Tudor shook his head in disbelief.

If Vikir had been a good lineman and blocked his charge, he wouldn't have allowed the goal to go in in the first place.

'There was something wrong there, let's do it right again!'

Tudor corrected his stance and ran back to his side of the field.

Next thing you know, the B team's keeper has kicked the ball out of play.

Tudor, being the genius that he is, snatched the ball up.

It was a phenomenal display of ball possession.

“Block it!”

Tudor hugged the ball and ran at full speed.

What?

For some reason, he couldn't see the Baskerville triplets who had been blocking him with their eyes lit up.

“...?”

I looked up, hoping to see something, and saw the back of the stadium.

The Baskervilles' triplets were blocking Vikir's path.

It looked like they were escorting him.

'What are they doing? Why aren't they staying on the line?'

Was it because they didn't feel confident enough to confront him?

No, I don't think so.

Tudor, the eldest son of Donquixote, had heard rumors about the Baskerville triplets.

Strong, cunning, and rascals their own age.

They are not the kind of people who would give up just because they were pushed out once.

Tudor ran straight for them.

Papapapap!

Tudor, a near-professional when it comes to lead dribbling, once again flipped off the Baskerville triplets and drove deep into the B team's goal.

“Someone like a loach.”

Highbro Le Baskerville closes in on Tudor.

...Puff!

Highbro's muscles and bones, hardened by the protection of the Styx River, clashed with Tudor's.

However, in hand-to-hand combat, Tudor was definitely outmatched.

“This isn't martial arts, my friend.”

With a flowing motion, Tudor slipped through the hollow under Highbro's flank and ran straight for the back.

Suddenly, the goal was in sight.

Except.

This time, it wasn't the goal, but Vikir, standing far behind him.

Even without mana, Tudor was confident.

The power of his grueling training had been summoned from his lower and upper body, from the soles of his feet, through his hips and waist, and exploded in his palms.

Tudor's arms flew out like a single giant spear, smashing through the targets in front of him.

'There will be no coincidence this time, try it!'

And then.

...Puck!

Once again, that was Tudor's last thought.

◆

Meanwhile. Vikir clicked his tongue as he watched Tudor crash into him and fall away.

'Why does he keep coming this way?'

Since the other party is getting upset, the atmosphere makes it impossible for you to get upset too.

Vikir gave him a cursory glance in the direction of his position with a look of annoyance.

But.

This time, I hit him pretty hard, and Tudor is worse for wear, completely unmoving.

Looks like he'll be stunned a little longer than last time.

Dorrrr...

The ball rolled and landed at Vikir's feet.

Mmmmmmmm.

Vikir stared at the ball rolling on the floor.

But to his surprise, no one came to pick it up.

Tudor's unrivaled performance had kept everyone, friend and foe alike, away.

Then. A tremendous amount of cheering came from the stands of the B team.

“Who is he! You're in class B, right!?”

“Tudor's in the grass! Now's your chance!”

“But why did Tudor fall?”

“I don't know! Does it matter now! We're going to lose to the A class if we keep doing this!”

“Run! It's almost game time!”

“But who is he?”

“I don't know! He's in our class, so cheer for him!”

Everyone in Class B, who was about to lose 1:0, started cheering for Vikir.

Vikir sighed softly to himself.

He didn't want to stand out, but in such a high-profile crisis, doing nothing would only make him stand out more.

Unable to help himself, Vikir reached out and grabbed the ball.

'Oh well.'

But the situation was pretty hopeless.

All of his allies were either on the ground or far away, having been pierced by Tudor.

There were only A's running toward them.

Vikir was faced with a dilemma: Is he going to lose the ball like this? If he did that, He'd get the risk of being branded as a traitor and receiving more attention throughout the new semester.

But he also didn't want to charge with the ball, score a goal, and become a star.

In the end, Vikir made his own compromise.

Swoosh.

Vikir picked up the ball and pulled his arm back.

The game was seconds away from ending. The cheering Class B students muttered to themselves in disbelief.

“Alas, 5 seconds before the end of the match, it's over.”

“Can't believe we've been losing to Class A since the beginning of the semester.”

“...? Look at him. What's the kid with the ball trying to do right now?”

“What are you doing? There's three seconds left.”

Everyone was frustrated.

Even the Team A linemen were slowing down, realizing that the game was over.

And then.

Boom.

Vikir's arm moved.

A throw.

The ball flew. Straight up into the sky.

But with one second left in the game, what's the point of a ball flying?

One by one, the students who were watching the sporting event packed up their things and left the stands, as if they had nothing to look forward to.

Only a few students, who are unusually attached to the victory, follow the ball's trajectory with regret.

...But?

The ball flies a little far.

A little too far.

Zoom, zoom, zoom.

The ball continues to rise, even though it has passed the distance where common sense would tell it to stop.

Shhhhhhh.

And now it began to fall in a gentle curve.

“...?”

“Huh!?”

Everyone's eyes widen, A and B teams alike.

Time had run out and the game was over.

But the ball, still hovering in midair, continues to move forward, not caring that the game is over.

And then.

BANG

The ball hits one of the posts of the iron Y-shaped goal and slides into it.

And.

....

The center of the field is immersed in silence.

All the students in the stands and on the field were at a loss for words.

The professor who officiated the game dutifully dropped the whistle in his mouth and muttered in a daze.

“...Buzzer Beater.”

Chapter 136

Test Your Skills (5)

◆

The buzzer beater is one of the more unusual rules of the game.

It allows a goal to be scored at the same time as the buzzer sounds, or even slightly later, as long as the ball has left the player's body and is still in the air when the end of the match is announced.

Vikir's ball hit the post almost simultaneously with the signal to end the game.

The score was tied at 1:1 between the two teams, and the game went into overtime.

By then, Tudor, sprawled out on the field, had come to his senses.

“What the hell is going on?”

Tudor still hadn't quite gotten his composure back.

It was inexplicable, unless he had slipped, but the mighty Tudor would never make such a rudimentary mistake.

??

In the midst of all the questions, a large hand rested on Tudor's shoulder.

“Let me deal with him.”

Sancho, who has been Tudor's best friend since enrollment, steps forward.

Sancho Barataria, was a scholarship student selected for integration by numerous mercenary guilds in the North.

He's given up his keeper's position and moved to the front of the field to pay back Tudor for recognizing him as a friend and someone he can trust with his back.

Sancho stared across the field at Vikir with a serious expression on his face.

Unlike Tudor, he hadn't let his guard down.

“In the frozen north, where even the frost itself groans, everyone fights their own battles, from the newborn to the dying. Everyone is a warrior.”

Warriors are tempered by the harsh climate and terrain.

Sancho was well aware that even the most insignificant of men could take the life of a great man.

Tudor said to Sancho.

“I thought you were only a keeper?”

“How can I stand idly by when my friend has been struck down twice?”

Sancho said as he stood next to Tudor.

He had promised himself he wouldn't play in his age group's league because he was too physically overpowered.

Tudor was touched by Sancho's words and patted him on the arm.

And then, the game was on.

Overtime.

The first team to score a “golden goal” in either A or B would win.

This is a performance evaluation that is also reflected in the midterm evaluation, so everyone was on the line.

“Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! It's the last one! Let's win!”

“It's a B-side shootout! All defenders, come out and attack!”

“Linemen, get together! Block it!”

“Smash it!”

All the students began to shout back and forth.

Then.

“Anyone get it!”

Highbro, who was holding the ball, found a gap in the siege of Class A linemen and passed it.

He threw it to the guy who thought he was on the same side based on his uniform.

“...?”

It was Vikir.

He had been half-dragged out by the B team's strategy of using every defender as an attacker.

...Jaw!

Unintentionally, Vikir caught the ball.

“....”

As soon as Vikir caught the ball, he looked at Highbro.

Not wanting to be the center of attention, Vikir's unspoken message to Highbro was simple.

“Do you want to play?”

“...Sorry.”

Highbro met Vikir's gaze, even in that urgent moment, and lowered his eyes.

It was the same with Middlebro and Lowbro.

When the Baskerville triplets suddenly became sullen for an unknown reason, the morale of the Class A linemen skyrocketed.

Tudor and Sancho also seized the opportunity to hit.

“What's going on? Why are they suddenly so intimidated?”

“I think it's our guts. Here we go!”

Sancho stepped forward.

Doo-doo-doo-doo-doo.

Sancho charged like a buffalo toward Vikir, who was standing in the distance with the ball.

Then, his muscled, log-like forearms and palms slammed ferociously into Vikir's chest.

Just then.

“...!”

Sancho's eyes flashed open to an unreal scene.

It was a memory from a long time ago. It was a memory from his childhood, when he used to push and roll huge boulders for training.

Does his small body have the ability to roll over a much larger rock?

But the young Sancho kept pushing and pushing and pushing that rock.

And now.

...Bam!

The same frustration he'd felt then was being felt in the tips of his palms.

'What kind of power....'

Sancho felt a huge boulder in Vikir's slender body.

He pushed with all his might and it didn't budge.

In fact, it felt so heavy and counter-elastic that it pushed him back.

But.

Sancho gritted his teeth.

He had never been pushed by another person before, not with mana, but with pure strength.

Not by people his own age, not by older warriors like his father and mentor.

'I've never been defeated by strength in my hometown, so how can I lose here at the Academy!'

Even in the frozen northern continent of the warriors, he was unbeatable.

Even Sancho as a child had been forced to push a seemingly insurmountable boulder.

'It will happen again!'

Sancho snorted and used his arms to push Vikir away.

...Kuguguk!

The giant boulder finally moved.

'Look at that! How about that!'

Sancho smiled curiously and looked down at Vikir.

At that moment.

“...!”

Sancho had to face it.

Vikir's gaze, unmoved, just staring back at him with an expressionless face.

A rock, what he thought was just a giant rock.

The moment he's knocked backward by Sancho's force, and the moment he stretches one leg out behind him, heels on the ground behind him.

A thud!

A different kind of gravity, a different kind of weight, stood in Sancho's way.

It was overwhelming (壓倒的).

He pushed against what he thought was a large boulder, only to find Mount Tai standing behind him.

'No way! How can this little guy...!'

Sancho was amazed.

When Vikir kept his feet horizontal, he could push back a little, but now that he had one leg stretched out behind him, he couldn't push back even a millimeter.

Kuguguk...

Vikir was bearing Sancho's strength and weight and still not losing the ball.

He was just thinking.

'Should I let him fall?'

Vikir wasn't using any mana.

His bones and muscles had been strengthened beyond their limits by the protection of the Styx River that permeated his body.

Before his regeneration, this would have been impossible, but for Vikir in this life, who had tapped into the power of the Styx River from a young age, it was quite possible.

It is also said that a healthy body is a healthy mind.

The karma, experience, and the smell of blood imprinted on his soul from slaying countless demons had pushed his physical strength to the limit.

The Baskervilles' superior physical strength, coupled with their hardy souls that had seen it all, allowed them to surpass the natural limits of their weight class.

...But that doesn't mean you have to use mana to win here.

Eventually, Vikir backed off.

“Oh no. I can't take this.”

Vikir collapses in a heap.

The ball was thrown far enough away that Vikir was no longer a target for the Class A linemen.

As the ball flies away, all eyes turn back to him.

“Oooh, Sancho got the ball!”

“...Yaah, but that guy who got tackled by Sancho isn't dead, is he?”

“Who cares, shut up and get the ball back!”

All the students rush after the ball again.

...But only one. Sancho's gaze was still on Vikir.

'What was that?'

He collapsed into a heap at the end, but the gravitas he'd displayed just moments before was still making Sancho's palms and wrists tingle.

He'd managed to push him off eventually, but his vision had gone black with frustration during the clash.

Tudor, seeing the look on his friend's face, realized what was happening.

“That guy's got a really tight body.”

“Guess he wasn't a studying worm-like ....”

“His basic physique is pretty good, maybe even better than yours or mine.”

“It would be a different story if he used mana.”

“Yeah. That's too bad. If you'd been born into a noble family and gotten some organized training, you'd be an Expert by now.”

Tudor and Sancho looked at Vikir, who had fallen behind them as they ran for the ball.

There was pity, envy, and a bit of recognition in their eyes.

◆

Then, with a dramatic golden goal from Highbro Le Baskerville, and great assists from Middlebro Le Baskerville and Lowbro Le Baskerville, Class B won.

It was the Baskerville triplets who got the cheers.

Chuak-

The B students are laughing and splashing soda on their heads.

Meanwhile, Vikir was a little farther away from everyone's hugging and jumping around.

Then.

Clang!

Something spilled over Vikir's head.

It turned out to be a soda.

“...?”

Vikir looked up to see Tudor and Sancho standing there, equally covered in soda, laughing.

“You're the one who won Class B, and you're not going to get away with it.”

“You should be more excited. Your buzzer-beating goal is the reason they won.”

Tudor, covered in soda, smirked and shouldered Vikir.

“Honestly, I was a little jealous that you were so good at answering questions on your own in that last lecture. I wanted to give you a hard time in gym class.”

“....”

“But I was the one who got humiliated, and I knew it when I saw it. I realized how sleepy I was. Ugh, I'm sorry.”

Tudor apologized honestly.

Vikir simply nodded in agreement.

Tudor Donquixote, hero of the spear family.

He would later go on to hunt countless demons in the endless wars of destruction that followed the dawn of the Age of Destruction.

The hero who saved countless human beings, closed the gate, and died a spectacular death. He was Tudor.

Vikir nodded, remembering Tudor's heroic traits from his previous life.

Just then, Sancho, the man next to him, asked Vikir.

“By the way, what kind of exercise have you been doing? You're so out of shape, I thought you were using mana.”

Sancho reached out and rubbed Vikir's chest, shoulders, and back.

Vikir smiled weakly.

“If I had used mana, I wouldn't have been able to defeat you.” “I have a terrible amount of mana.”

“It's a shame, you blessed with a great skeleton. With an early education, you would surely have become an exponent like me. It's not too late for you to start taking lessons in mana breathing at the Academy.”

Tudor sounded genuinely sorry.

But Vikir only smiled.

Tudor felt the tip of his nose twitch once more at her nonchalance.

Meanwhile, Sancho chuckled as if he liked Vikir's hard body.

“By the way, what size are you in the 3rd generation? Without mana. Would you like to go to the weight room later and work on ironing together?”

“Dude, what are you talking about working out again, drink this, I don't have any alcohol, it's soda!”

“Ugh! Yuck! Don't feed me this stuff, I'll lose muscle!”

Tudor and Sancho playfully splash their drinks at each other.

Vikir laughed softly and turned away.

Soon, students from other classes who were watching passed bottles of water to the lead runners from Class A and Class B.

“Tudor, here, drink this water!”

“Wash your sweat off with this ....”

“And here's a towel!”

The idea was to wash the sweat and drink from their bodies.

A crowd of girls crowded around Tudor, offering him water and towels.

“Haha, thanks girls, it's only classmates after all~”

Tudor smiled warmly and accepted the water and towels.

The Sancho and Baskerville triplets also grabbed bottles of water to wash their hair and faces.

...And Vikir did the same.

You have to take off your glasses to wash your face, which is sticky with sweat, dirt, and drink.

Vikir took off his glasses and slicked back his bangs. Then he rinsed his face with clear water.

Beneath the hair that covered his face, his bare face is revealed.

Vikir looked up, dried his face, and walked back to the stand, dripping with water.

And a moment.

....

The gymnasium is suddenly silent.

Chapter 137

Test your skills (6)

◆

The next day.

A curious crowd gathered in front of Class B of the Cold Warrior Class.

It was a mix of first, second, and third years, and even a few fourth years who don't show up for public events due to graduation and employment.

The common thread was that almost all of them were girls.

“Hey, who's that kid who was dripping water off the end of his chin after the game yesterday?”

“Is that him? Is that him from yesterday?”

“Wow, that face is crazy. How did he get that look?”

“Oh my god, he's so cute... I want him....”

The girls hadn't gotten over the shock of yesterday's game.

Everyone who watched yesterday's class-level lead Naphtali competition between the Cold Class, whether in person or on the magical video or photos, all noticed one thing: the Naphtali was amazing.

'Holy shit. Who is that?'

'I, I stopped breathing...... 'It takes my breath away.'

'Wow, he's so ridiculously handsome.'

That's the face of a schoolboy walking back to the stands after the game, swiping at his damp bangs.

That sweaty, water-soaked face belonged to Vikir.

Yesterday, Vikir had taken off his glasses for a few moments and put on his bangs.

And it struck unexpectedly at the defenseless hearts of countless female students sitting in the stands.

As Vikir returned, water dripping from the tip of his chin, countless water bottles and towels were thrust in front of him.

'Here, use this handkerchief, do you want some water too?'

'Big brother, my water is cooler, take this!

'Funny, why brother, we're in the same class?'

'Who cares? If he's handsome, he's my brother!'

Vikir was quickly recognized as the star of the game.

The moment he returned to the stands, the brief movement of brushing his bangs was embedded in the mana screen as a “snapshot,” which was played over and over again on the sports page of the magically created school newspaper.

[Exclusive] The Identity of the 'Face Genius' Who Appeared in the Cold Warrior Class's 1st Year Naphtali Game!? / Views: 29,872

-Last night in afternoon physical education class, an unidentified freshman was returning to the bench sweating after the game. This mysterious male student is known to have contributed greatly to the class' victory by showing excellent skills in the game and scoring one point, making it a hot topic...

<Comments: 13,021>

?(Cold Class 1st year student): Isn't that synthetic?! What kind of person has a face like that?

??(Hot Class 2nd year student): ???I'm the first to hear that there's such a visual in the Cold Class~.

??(Hot Class 1st year student): I don't think any of our classmates had that kind of look?

??(Hot Class 1st year student): I didn't see him in OT?? If he had a face like that, I'd definitely ask him out~.

??(Hot Class 2nd year student): Why are you flirting with a 1st grade topic, CC is only from 2nd grade?

??(Cold Class 1st year student): Wow but he's really good looking;;; Who is he? I'm a guy and I'm still in love with him.

??(Cold Class 1st year student): He's the guy who played Naphtali with me yesterday... He really looks like that... I was surprised and just stared for a while...

??(Hot Class 3rd year student): Look at his jawline...his disheveled hair...his face...he's so cute! ????????????

??(Cold Class 3rd year student): Water droplets flow along the jawline and cut...My sister's heart breaks ??

??(Hot Class 4th year student):???? I'll go see you right away tomorrow...I'll find you even if my sister searches all the Cold Classrooms!!!

??(Hot Class 3rd year student): ?Oh my... calm down... I have to graduate...

.

.

It was truly unknown when a passing student from the newspaper club took the picture using Mana Screen.

“Who's Vikir, where is he!”

“Tudor was nice, but... I came to see Vikir!”

“Vikir, where are you? I love you so much!”

“My sister bought 10,000 handkerchiefs to wipe the water off our Vikir's face!”

After hearing the rumors about Vikir, a lot of girls and some boys(?), regardless of classmates and seniors, came to the party, especially the seniors.

Then.

“...What's going on?”

There was a voice that froze the crowd gathered in front of class B of the Cold Warrior Class.

Professor Banshee Morgue.

His entrance caused the mass of students in front of the lecture hall to scramble to make way for him.

Professor Banshee sternly warned everyone, especially the older students.

“I don't know what all the fuss is about, but don't you dare come into the underclassmen's classrooms. It's against school rules.”

The students turned away with sullen faces.

...And there was one person who was relieved to see Professor Banshee.

It was Vikir, sitting in a window seat in the corner of the classroom.

Vikir had taken Pigi's advice and was listening to the lecture with a hood and glasses covering most of his face.

'Professor Banshee saved my life. I didn't expect to be in the papers.'

Even Vikir, a man of the world, hadn't expected this to happen.

Before his regression, Vikir's face was a mess of burns, stab wounds, and poisoned scars from his childhood.

This was the first time he realized that his appearance could attract such attention.

'Hagiya, I haven't really had any scars on my face since I returned.'

Even if he had, he'd regenerated it all with the monstrous regenerative powers he'd stolen from the monsters, so there was no way he'd have any scars left.

'In my previous life, I never spoke to a woman. Ah, no. Saint Dolores, she was not frightened by the sight of my face. She was merciful and fair to all.'

While Vikir was thinking this over.

“Now, ..., let's go over the homework assigned last time.”

Professor Banshee began his lecture.

He had asked the students to do their own research and write a report on a few specific types of monsters.

They were the following monsters

<Venompion>

Danger Rating: A

Size: 3 meters

Found in: Sand Falls, Harsh Desert, Eastern Continent

-Named the Reaper of the Sands.

A scorpion armed with heavy armor and powerful venom.

Its exoskeleton is harder than steel, and it swings its powerful pincers to crush or strike its prey to death.

The venom that oozes from the tip of its tail is said to be capable of killing 44 humans with a single drop.

A large scorpion is stretched out on a test tube.

Venompion. A rare creature from the deserts of the distant Eastern Continent, it had been preserved and stuffed as soon as it died, and was now Professor Banshee's favorite prized possession.

Professor Banshee's eyes lit up.

“This scorpion hides itself under the sand and burrows quickly to find its prey. It sticks its tail out of the sand like a shark with its dorsal fin above the surface.”

At this point, the students caught in Professor Banshee's gaze shake their heads and avert their eyes as if they were being stung by a scorpion.

This is because Professor Banshee's questions are always tricky to answer.

Moreover, the Venompion is still so little known to the scientific community that it is not even listed in most of the magical encyclopedias.

Professor Banshee smirked as he looked around at the new students, who were already avoiding his gaze.

“Okay, let's see who's brave and wise enough to explain this monster to us, but let's give the cold students a chance first, and the hot students shouldn't feel too bad.”

The hot students burst out laughing and the cold students sulk.

When no one volunteered, Professor Banshee clicked her tongue.

“Are you really not proud of your research results? So what do you plan on doing after graduation? What about graduate school? What about employment? You guys are pathetic.”

But still, there is nothing he isn't confident about.

Professor Banshee scanned the faces of the cold-warrior students and said in a stern tone,

“If there's no one else, I'll name one.”

With that, he stretched out a long, slender finger and pointed at someone.

“Heh!”

It was Pigi.

Pigi, who ranked third on the written exam, was a brilliant mind in his own right.

But even the information he'd worked so hard to gather and analyze wasn't up to Professor Banshee's standards.

“E... Venompions have a black, thick exoskeleton that is harder than steel. Their large right claw acts more like a hammer than a pair of scissors, and they kill their prey with the venom contained in the poisonous stinger at the tip of their tail. Official records state that they grow up to three meters long, but some natives say that during times of great drought, individuals over five meters long are often seen....”

“That's enough. You're to be commended for finding and gathering such rare material, but that's it. You have no new arguments, so what's your original research, just a bunch of rehashed discussions? What's the difference between that and a parrot's mindless chatter?”

Pigi's face contorted into a scowl at Professor Banshee's point.

“I'm deducting one point from your entire Cold Class score. Now, let's see your Hot Class score.”

As it turns out, Professor Banshee's notoriety was not a myth.

This time, the Hot students began to squirm and stare like lab rats waiting for the syringe.

Then.

A small, white hand rose high above the crowd of students.

It was Sinclaire.

Professor Banshee narrowed her eyes.

“First in the Hot Class. I take it you'll be taking notes this term.”

“Yes, Professor.”

“Try.”

Professor Banshee said grimly.

Sinclaire, on the other hand, stood up with a glint of enthusiasm in his eyes, and began to read his report with a flourish.

“Yes, I'm Sinclaire, class A, first year, Hot Class, and I'm going to start my presentation now!”

Sinclaire pulled out four sheets of paper, each one crammed with scribbled notes.

“I've categorized the Venompion's attacks, or hunting patterns, into three different categories and drawn different conclusions.”

“Hmm?”

After hearing Sinclaire's argument, Professor Banshee looked mildly intrigued.

Sinclaire then proceeded to explain in a serious tone.

“Venompions have a reputation for being one of the hardest monsters to defeat in the desert. Aside from a few large worm-like monsters like the Sandworm, it has no natural enemies.”

“That's a story everyone already knows.”

“Yes. As I said, I've compiled a list of cases where Venompions have attacked humans, or where they've been seen hunting their prey, and I've categorized their personalities into three types.”

Sinclaire held out the report.

In it, along with numerous graphs, Sinclaire categorized the creature into three types, each with a different strategy for dealing with it.

“Simply ignorant”: Exceeds others in dashing speed, strength, and endurance, but has significantly lower intelligence, such as an inability to flee when in danger or escape when trapped.

When defeating them, it is better to surround them, ambush them, or set traps than to fight them head-on.

'Wimpy': Has a small skeleton and inferior physical abilities compared to other individuals, but exhibits unpredictable attack patterns, such as popping out from unexpected places or using its middle or last leg to make ineffective attacks.

When fighting them, it is best to kill them before they can get close with a powerful single shot or ranged attack.

'Cunning': Not only physically strong, but also intelligent. Combines the best qualities of 'Simply Ignorant' and 'Wimpy' into a drunken state.

※Siege and annihilation by high ranking knights or mages is the only answer.

Sinclaire's argument was so new that even the demanding Professor Banshee nodded.

“There have been too few sightings of Venompions to fully categorize them, but you have a point, and I will make a formal report to the academy and let you know the results.”

The words of recognition from Professor Banshee's mouth were enough to stun all the students.

Sinclaire snorted with pride and sat back in his seat.

She seemed to be aware of someone else, as she glanced at the window seat outside the classroom with a furtive look.

Then Professor Banshee looked back at the Cold Class.

“That's an excellent idea, Hot Class. It's still just a possibility, but it's an idea that could contribute to academia in its own way. What do you guys have?”

None of the students from the cold side stepped forward to answer.

“Vikir from class B, then.”

Professor Banshee called out to Vikir specifically.

Ever since the last incident, he'd been questioning Vikir from time to time.

It was clear he didn't like it.

When Vikir raised his eyes from behind his bangs and gave him an annoyed glance, Professor Banshee crossed his arms with a wicked grin.

“I'm sure you know a lot about these evil scorpions, so let's see some of your reports, see what you've been working on for the past hour.”

“There's a report here: ...It's just the basics.”

Vikir felt the pressure of Professor Banshee's gaze.

He didn't want to be the center of attention among the students anymore, and his nightly assassination runs outside the academy had left him with an absolute lack of time to work on his assignments.

So Vikir had only scribbled down a few lines of the most basic, common sense stuff for this preliminary report.

...It reads.

“Venomphion is a B+ ranked monster that is not difficult to catch as long as you pay attention to the first stinger on its tail and the second stinger on its belly.”

It's so generic and common sense that I was just writing down what I thought everyone knew.

...But.

As Vikir talks about his research topic and conclusions, every head in the room turns from left to right.

Finally, Professor Banshee asks with a furrowed brow, as if he's never heard of it before.

“...'Second sting'? What is that?”

Chapter 139

Men are Power (2)

◆

...Flash!

Black and red strikes crossed each other.

Vikir felt a crackling pain in his wrist as he landed on the ground.

'That's a lot of weight, even for a rotten Graduator.'

Turning his head, he saw the creature crashing through the outer wall of the building beyond.

[Grunt...]

He's carrying a large hammer, and the sticky aura that symbolizes the Graduator is completely coating the large surface area of the hammer.

Bubbling...

His aura is like boiling tar, or liquid asphalt.

I'd estimate it to be an advanced Graduator.

Vikir squinted at it.

“That's clearly a blunt technique of the Faithful Saint. Why would a demon use this technique?”

The holy power of the Rune Religion was clearly the antithesis of the demons, and it was a great irony that the martial technique to draw out that holy power was unleashed by the hands of a demon.

'Does that mean the Quovadis have some sort of connection to the demons after all, because I'm sure they have their own rotten parts....'

Maybe, just maybe, he'd pick up a clue about the Face Hunters, the stealthy men in the Imperial City.

The traitors, renegades, and insiders he's hunted so far have all been dealing with the same demon, and they all have one thing in common: they lose their faces upon death.

And the creature in front of him seems to be a similar case, as he wears a black sack over his head.

Vikir loaded his sword with mana in earnest.

“First, I'll cut off your limbs. Now for the interrogation. All you need is a mouth.”

An aura stretched out from Beelzebub.

Superior Graduator, solid and dense, the aura stretched out and drew a half-moon trajectory.

Thud.

A solid marble pillar was sliced diagonally.

The monster hastily raised his hammer to block the blow, but he was unable to avoid the crumbling debris behind him.

...Crunch!

With that, the creature burst through the rubble and dirt.

His black suit was torn to shreds, revealing muscular flesh, the words jaggedly etched into his chest like a knife.

'Ephebo'

“Ephebo, is that your name?”

Vikir asked, and the creature did not answer. Just.

...Whoosh!

It only emitted an even more intense aura from its body.

But even then, it was only an Advanced Graduator, the level Vikir had been at when he first arrived in Ballak's village and was settling in.

“That's good, I've been having a hard time picking up trash.”

Vikir smiled, though only briefly.

He was a little sore from all the time he'd spent hunting down weaklings.

An opponent of advanced Graduator level should still be able to exert some strength, so it was time to stretch a bit.

...Flash!

Vikir also raised his aura.

The Seven Forms of Baskerville now manifested their terrifying trajectory.

First tooth transposition.

Second tooth central incisor.

Third tooth Lateral incisor.

Fourth tooth molars.

Fifth tooth wisdom tooth.

Sixth tooth premolar.

Seventh tooth molars.

Four in the upper jaw and three in the lower jaw. A total of seven teeth fell towards Ephebo, the demon with a black sack.

...Thud!

The first tooth bit into Ephebo's body.

The second tooth ripped open the wound the first had inflicted, pulling it apart and severing it.

The third tooth helps the second strike continue strong, connecting it to the fourth.

The fourth tooth crushed Ephebo's entire body, leaving it tattered beyond regeneration or repair.

The fifth tooth funneled all the recoil damage from the previous four strikes into one place and slammed into Ephebo's body again.

The sixth tooth was assisting the seventh, completely sealing off even the tiniest crack that Ephebo could have gotten through.

The seventh tooth was still so small and weak that it looked like a gap, but with the sixth tooth supporting it, it didn't matter.

On the contrary, if the trajectory in which the seventh tooth was located appeared to be empty, and it tried to escape through this gap, it would be oviposited by the sixth tooth cleverly hidden behind it and quickly become a rag.

Such was the case with Ephebo.

Quack, quack, quack, quack!

The trajectory of Vikir's sword, the sequence of teeth, and the fact that he had managed to find a gap in it, made Ephebo immediately realize that it was a trap.

The seventh tooth, relatively small and seemingly less intimidating, was actually optimized for killing more than any of the others.

“They don't call it the seventh for nothing.”

Vikir said as he stamped on Ephebo, which quickly turned into a rag.

It may be small, but it is a seventh tooth.

No one had ever seen it before, except for Vikir and Hugo Le Baskerville, the patriarch of the Baskerville family.

In the future, when this seventh tooth grows and reaches its full size, it will be the moment when Vikir becomes a Swordmaster.

'And when he does, he will not be afraid of Hugo.'

Vikir's feelings for Hugo had softened considerably since he realized that his death in his previous life had more to do with Seth than Hugo.

But despite this, Vikir still didn't feel good about Hugo.

After all, it was he who had struck his own throat in his final moments before regressing, and it was he who had tossed so many of his brothers aside like they were expendable.

“So, shall we begin our interrogation?”

Vikir kicked the tattered Ephebo and impaled him on a steel beam jutting out of one of the stone pillars.

Gurgling...

Vikir's small and delicate hands bent the thick steel frame like a taffy stick and shaped it into a hook.

Ephebo struggled, but with his body pierced by the bent steel like a fishing hook, he could not escape.

The kind of overwhelming power that can subdue and nail a top-ranked Graduator in an instant.

If the students of the academy who had just played with Vikir had seen this, they would have fainted a few times.

Vikir asked in a cold tone.

“Now, who is your master, who made you like this?”

[Grrrr...]

Instead of answering, Ephebo growled low. It was clear he wasn't going to admit anything.

(Though it was questionable if he even spoke the language in the first place).

But Vikir didn't mind.

“Interrogation is not always verbal.”

A lot of information can be gleaned from the body of an interrogate, the condition of their internal organs, the placement of their bones, their wounds, the freshness of their blood or the concentration of mana in their veins, and the social status of their life.

From now on, Vikir planned to dismantle Ephebo's entire body into pieces and dispose of them.

Then.

“Heehee... heehee....”

He heard the sound of wind behind him.

Turning his head, he saw the fat man from earlier, Nursery Director Doxeller, smiling with drool dripping from the corner of his mouth.

“It's him... he's coming... hee hee... face... to get my face back... don't make a mistake.”

I could tell at a glance that he was out of his mind.

No wonder, it was understandable for a commoner to go insane after witnessing a battle between Superior Graduator and monsters at the highest level of mana explosion from a very close distance.

Waves of mana, shockwaves, and collapsing debris would have been disastrous enough for the average person.

With that, the Doxeller began to stagger away.

“I have to hide... I have to hide....”

He rummaged through the rubble until his fingers were bloody.

Eventually, he pulled out a fairly sizable vault.

“Hmph.”

Vikir watched the scene with interest.

Something was coming out of his subconscious that he hadn't admitted to during his torture earlier, something that perhaps he wasn't even aware of.

If anything, it was a good thing that he had gone mad.

Then.

BEEP-BEEP-BEEP

As he turned the dials on the vault, Doxeller suddenly stopped.

And then.

“Boom, boom, boom, boom!”

Something happened.

The doxeller's entire body suddenly began to expand.

As soon as Vikir felt the rushing torrent of mana, he threw himself backwards.

And then.

Boom!

Dokseller's body suddenly exploded with a loud bang.

Apparently, the demon had placed a restriction on him to self-destruct after certain actions.

“...Yikes.”

Vikir was out of the blast's radius, but he still took quite a bit of damage.

The wounds were minor and he could regenerate them all with his bog salamander powers, but his clothing could not.

His cloak, shirt, and mask were half burned away.

Vikir pulled off the plague doctor's mask that covered his face and tossed it to the ground.

“....”

I turned to see Ephebo, nailed to a stone pillar, had disappeared.

Judging by the bits of flesh and guts stuck to the gritty surface of the steel, it must have been forced out with quite a bit of effort.

It was a difficult escape for a living human to pull off.

“Well, at least you got a harvest.”

Vikir peered into the vault that had been shattered by the self-destruct.

Much of the vault's contents had been preserved, thanks to the fact that Doxeller had fired the blast just before he detonated, minimizing the aftermath.

The vault contained a significant amount of gold bars, real estate documents, and jewelry.

Probably the proceeds of selling children with nowhere else to go as food for demons.

But Vikir didn't care about wealth.

What really caught his attention were the stacks of papers beyond.

A ledger.

They detailed the deposits of money, where children were taken from, and where they were sent.

“This will need to be analyzed.”

Vikir crumpled the papers into his arms.

He would mail them to Cindywendy immediately and have her investigate.

“Ugh! Stop working, please!”

I could already hear her singing.

◆

After Vikir's departure.

The guards were called to the midnight disturbance.

They looked at the ruined nursery and stuck out their tongues.

“Looks like some giant beasts have come and stirred things up.”

“Wasn't this nursery under the control of the Quovadis family?”

“What kind of madman trespassed on the territory of the Faithful?”

The guards scoured the ruins.

But they found nothing.

What they did find was a large amount of wealth of unknown origin in abandoned vaults.

Why all this money was here, and where it came from, was a mystery.

And why would the supposedly frugal branch of the Quovadis have all this black money?

The investigation was inevitably prolonged, and the guards soon made a shocking discovery in the basement of the nursery.

The bodies of children aged between 10 and 13 years old.

Dozens of bones and skeletons lay in the ground beneath the former nursery building.

The guards were all horrified.

And then. Some were more surprised than others.

“...!”

Saintess Dolores.

A direct descendant of the Quovadis family, student council president and newspaper editor of the Academy Colosseo.

She had rushed over at the news that an organization affiliated with her family had been attacked.

Students from the Academy's newspaper department were also there to cover the event.

Originally, the Academy's newspaper had rules.

First-year students only cover events inside the academy.

Second and third year students can cover events outside the academy.

First-year students are still too immature to go outside the academy, and they need time to adjust to the school, so their coverage is limited to the academy.

However, in the second and third year, they were allowed to go outside the academy.

Just like Dolores is doing now with other student journalists.

“...What in the world.”

Dolores is speechless at the sight before her.

A ruined nursery school, with the remains of many children.

Who could have committed such a senseless act?

The guards were eager to be interviewed by student journalists.

“By the time we arrived, it had already happened....”

“Judging by the blood and flesh splattered everywhere, whoever attacked this place was strong and evil....”

“It appears to have been a one-man raid....”

“There is a terrifying villain in the city, and similar incidents are popping up all over the place....”

The students at the academy took the guards' statements seriously.

It was an outline of tomorrow's newspaper articles that would be distributed to the academy the next morning.

Then.

“...?”

Saintess Dolores, looking around in a panic, spotted something.

Avoiding everyone's gaze, she went back under the pile of rubble and picked up what had fallen to the ground.

“This is ....”

What Dolores picked up was a half-burnt mask.

It was a plague doctor's mask with a stork's beak attached.

Chapter 140

Identity of the Villain (1)

◆

Back at the Academy, Vikir thought back to last night's events.

'That guy with the black sack. He must have used the blunt technique of the Quovadis, right?

He had the word 'Ephebo' tattooed on his chest.

He had the skills of an advanced Graduator, so it took some effort to deal with him.

That didn't stop him from running away halfway through, which was a shame.

'Tomorrow night, I'll have to go around even more intensely. I'll have to hit every place that smells like a demon, and I'm sure I'll see him again.'

If you don't want to come out, you won't be able to.

I'm going to wipe out all the businesses the demons have set up in the human world.

'Demons love human blood, especially the blood of children, so we'll focus on the most vulnerable orphanages, hospitals, and monasteries.... I need to become a Sword Master as soon as possible to make the hunt a little smoother.'

Vikir is currently a Superior Graduator, having fully regained the strength of his former life.

Combined with the protection of the River Styx, the magic sword Beelzebub, the Baskerville 10-style swordsmanship, and the experience gained from slaying countless demons, he can now truly compete with a Sword Master.

Considering he's only 18 years old, there's a lot of room for improvement.

“First, the seventh tooth. I need to master the Baskerville seven tooth technique first....”

Vikir was mulling over his thoughts.

“Okay, everyone!”

A voice snapped Vikir out of his thoughts.

A second-year girl stood in front of the first-year students and focused their attention.

Her nametag reads something like this.

<Newspaper Club (Media Society Participation Club): Ryukeion (Λ?κειον)>.

Club.

A student organization is also known as a circle, society, club, etc.

This club, called Ryukeion, is a small newspaper club run by about 30 students.

However, despite their small size, their influence was enormous.

The daily newspaper, which was a mix of news from inside and outside the academy, always sold like hotcakes and was in great demand outside the academy.

Students wanted to know what was going on inside the academy, no matter how small, as soon as possible, while parents and stakeholders outside the academy wanted to know more.

It's no wonder that the world's eyes were on this group of young people, who would later become world changers.

And Vikir was one of the most desperate for information.

By day, he lives as a normal student inside the academy, hiding his identity, and by night, he's a hunter who goes out and hunts demons.

To do so, he must utilize the information inside the academy to the fullest.

The only way to know what happened at night faster than the morning newspaper, and what happened during the day faster than the evening newspaper, is to join the organization that produces the morning and evening newspapers.

A newspaper inside an academy like Ryukeion.

'By the way, they don't have many members, surprisingly.'

Vikir turned his head to look around at the scene inside the newspaper department.

The room was filled with magical printing presses that printed mana screens onto paper, and various photographic materials.

However, the number of people in the room was small.

A few sophomores led the freshmen in the club. The rest were freshmen like Vikir.

The current first-year entries for the newspaper were as follows.

Tudor Donquixote (Class A, Cold).

Sinclaire (Class A, Hot).

Sancho Barataria (Class A, Cold).

Usher Bianca (Class B, Cold).

Pigi (Class B, Cold).

Vikir (Class B, Cold).

In the beginning, there were more newcomers.

But Ryukeion is a very demanding club, and the workload is too much for a hobby club to handle.

Furthermore, at the academy, where exams are so rigorous that even the slightest neglect of personal study can result in a detention, it was impossible to combine schoolwork with the club unless you were extremely talented.

Moreover, the head of the newspaper department, Saint Dolores Rune Quovadis, is known to be a workaholic, so it's no wonder the freshmen are falling apart at the seams.

Worse, it's rumored that being a staff journalist for Dolores' newspaper is harder than midterms and finals.

The remaining freshmen were a tough bunch.

One of the sophomores gathered the freshmen together and asked.

“How did you guys end up in the newspaper? We're known for our discipline here at Ryukeion.”

Tudor was the first to answer.

“Hahaha, I'm an alpha male, so it's no problem, academics, clubs, I can do it all!”

It was the confidence of a top student in the Cold Class and a member of a seventh-generation family.

Sancho was the next to speak.

“Hmm. I stayed because I don't want people to think I'm just a strong-minded fool. The newspaper club sounds like something intelligent, and I want to be an intelligent man.”

Everyone was a little surprised by the unexpectedly serious answer.

Pigi was next.

“Well, I originally like collecting and analyzing information...... I think it's my calling!”

He stuttered a lot, but it was still a pretty bold ambition.

This time, it was Sinclaire, a good student, who spoke up.

“Isn't money, information, and power inseparable in the first place? Of those, I think information is the most dominant.”

It was an answer that accurately understood the inseparable dynamics that move the world.

Finally, Bianca spoke up.

“Ugh. I was tricked into joining by Dolores.”

“Tricked?” Everyone looked at her in disbelief.

Bianca hesitated for a moment before answering truthfully.

“He told me this was a 'sniping' club....”

She wasn't wrong. Every once in a while, there's an article in the newspaper about sniping someone.

When Bianca finished, we all laughed heartily.

One of the sophomore captains giggled and patted Bianca on the shoulder.

“Well, by that measure, we are a sniper club. Look at this article!”

She showed them a sports article on page two of the last issue of the morning paper.

The magically animated photo displayed views and comments.

[Exclusive] The identity of the 'face genius' who appeared in the first year's Naphthali game!? / Views: 48,999

-Last night in afternoon gym class, a mysterious freshman was seen in a......

<Discussions: 31,021

?(1st year student Cold Class): Every time this guy frowns, I also frown a can of beer... I'm upset... ???

??(2nd year student Hot Class): A girl like me... I was a woman like Simon*'s bed who could not be shaken even by idols from Imperial Capitals the size of an empire... Today, I received a serious heart attack... As a retaliatory assault, I got hit on the lips and made to pay for it once. Ask me?

??(1st year student Hot Class): I'll watch this video even when I'm a granny.

??(1st year student Hot Class): My oppa whose name I don't know... I want to make a promise to my oppa that I will live and die just for today while smoking cigarettes on the veranda of the 10th floor of my private villa in the Imperial Capital...★

??(2nd year student Hot Class): I heard that this person's MBTI test result is SEXY...? ????? Take me away...

??(1st year student Cold Class): A person who wants to be crushed by this mysterious newbie's brow wrinkles

??(1st year student Cold Class): 2 ppl.

??(3rd year student Hot Class): 3 persons

??(2nd year student Cold Class): I thought his name was Vikir.

??(1st year student Cold Class): ...Let me stain your life with my name...

??(4th year student Hot Class): Mmmm... What's a beauty class? What a joke...

??(3rd year student Hot Class): Don't like Vikir/What is that?/Don't like Vikir/How do you do that?

??(4th year student Cold Class): Oppa... Oppa Vikir... Even though you are younger than me, you are my eternal oppa... I keep crying because of you, so a new big lake was built in our territory...

.

.

Crazy results with almost 50,000 views and 30,000 comments.

Upon seeing the article, Tudor and Sancho burst out laughing.

“Wahahahahaha! Hey, Vikir, this is the day, right? Our Naphtali day!”

“....”

Vikir put his hand to his forehead and sighed lightly.

Meanwhile, Bianca's head is turned away with a pathetic expression on her face, and Sinclaire is staring at the newspaper article with Vikir's picture on it.

Pigi was staring enviously at Vikir, who seemed to have made friends with Tudor and Sancho.

Just then.

The door to the club burst open, and Ryukeion from the newspaper department walked in.

“Hey, guys!”

St. Dolores, the head of Ryukeion, called the meeting to order with her usual enthusiasm.

She gathered the first, second, and third year students together and began to discuss what would be published in today's evening paper.

“Last night, the second and third year reporters went outside the academy to do some reporting. They got good stories, we just need to decide on a headline.”

Dolores placed the finished articles on the table.

The articles covered the following topics.

[Unpublished article] / Views: 0

-Late last night, October 0, at dawn. A mysterious assailant appeared and ransacked a nursery school in 00...

Unusually, the attacker didn't touch the riches in the vault...

The conclusion was that it was not the actions of a person with whom he had a grudge. ...

Nothing is known about his identity, what his objectives are, or what his fighting strength is...

The damage done to the nursery in this incident is untold...

The number of girls between the ages of 10 and 13 who died unjustly is only confirmed...

Meanwhile, no official comment has been made by the imperial family and the Quovadis of the Faithful on the matter...

<Comments: 0>.

Last night, an unknown assailant broke into an orphanage on the outskirts of the Imperial City, killing the director and a number of poor, parentless children and leaving the neighborhood in shambles.

He didn't touch any of the gold or jewelry in the vault, and his intentions were purely murderous.

...Well, it goes something like this.

Vikir looked at it and thought.

'There's a lot of misunderstanding here.'

The demons had killed the girls, not Vikir.

However, the imperial guards who arrived late seemed to have judged that Vikir was responsible for the demons' actions.

'It doesn't matter, we're not going to get caught, but we need to run the data on this nursery raid through Cindywendy to see if it's connected to Viscount Gambino's slave auction, which I robbed earlier.'

While the rest of the newspaper staff was trying to figure out what to call the story, Vikir was thinking about something else entirely.

Meanwhile, serious discussions continue around the table.

Everyone was eager to put their own headline on the front page of a newspaper that would be seen by the entire nation.

“Fearsome Villain Born!?”

“Outside the academy, a monster stirs up the Imperial Capital!”

“What is the Imperial Guard up to!”

“An Unprecedented Villain Challenges the Quovadis!?”

“Girls, mysteriously going to their deaths. Who's Behind It?”

The titles are tantalizing.

But none of them hit the spot, and the debate stalled.

The smart newspaper staffers quickly realized what was holding them back.

“Oh, we don't have a name for the villain yet!”

“That's right, it's not as if we can call him a villain or a villainous criminal!”

“Let's give him a nickname first!”

Often, heinous criminals are given ominous nicknames such as “King of the Cave,” “Son of the Fountain,” “Murder King,” “Human Snow White,” “Bluebeard,” and so on.

So we needed a catchy nickname for this villain, too.

Someone who suddenly and unexpectedly appeared one day and terrorized the night of the Imperial City.

A villain of epic proportions who brutally murders prominent dignitaries of society, or mercenaries whose names are widely known, and then disappears like a ghost, leaving no clues behind.

What should we call this unprecedented villain?

The students of the newspaper department were excited and participated in a nickname contest.

“Since the incident took place in District, how about 'The Wolf of District'?”

“Well, the raids and murders didn't just happen in the district. How about 'Nightcrawler of Misfortune'?”

“Too long. How about 'orphaned predator'? It's more impactful.”

“'Orphan' is too discriminatory and demeaning. If we're going to go with that, let's go with 'nursery raider'.”

“But orphanages aren't the only facilities that have been attacked. There's been monasteries, hospitals, places of worship, and even district offices. How about 'Mr. Terrorist'!”

“Hmmm, this is a little tricky.”

There was a lot of discussion, but nothing really stuck.

“....”

“....”

“....”

Just when everyone's opinions were lulled into silence.

Saintess Dolores murmured softly, unconsciously.

“...The Night Hound.”

Chapter 141

Identity of the Villain (2)

◆

Dolores was deep in thought about last night's events.

'...That mask I picked up yesterday, I'm sure I've seen it before.'

That's right.

Dolores had gotten the call yesterday that the Imperial Guard was on its way, and in her capacity as Saintess of the Quovadis and head of the Academy's newspaper department, she had quickly responded.

She saw with her own eyes the devastation she had witnessed, the deaths of so many people and the destruction of so many buildings.

Buildings were lying in ruins as if a large amount of explosives had been set off, and the remains of mummified boys and girls were found beneath the ruins of the nursery school, their blood drained from their bodies.

The second- and third-year student journalists with me, and even the imperial guards, had never seen anything quite like it.

...And there was a half-burnt mask lying nearby.

Dolores moved stealthily and picked it up, hiding it in her arms from the sound of the footsteps behind her.

'It must have belonged to Mr. Night Hound, why would he be there....'

She thought back to the first time she met the Night Hound.

He had come to recover from a vacation at the academy.

A man who stood out amongst the visits of greedy, lowly nobles.

'He's ...just a lost lamb.'

I remember the first time I saw him, he bowed his head in humility, not boasting of his prestige or wealth.

Later, the Night Hound worked tirelessly to treat slum dwellers affected by the plague, the Red Death.

Though his appearance, identity, and behavior were questionable, his love and dedication to the less fortunate was genuine.

As proof, he even tapped into the divine power of the runes in a small way.

“The mask I picked up yesterday must have been his, because it had all the marks and bloodstains of a Red Death victim's struggle.”

Dolores was certain that the half-burnt mask she had hidden in her arms was the one worn by the Night Hound.

But why was he at the scene of yesterday's tragedy?

Had he really killed the director of the orphanage and harmed the boys and girls in it?

'...But why the good man?'

I do not believe that the image of the Night Hound treating the poor of St Mecca, the noble and holy image of treating people despite being covered in all kinds of filth, was just acting.

She has always believed that the Night Hound, who stole the Saint's tears at the end, must have been doing so for a cause.

“Could it really be him, the Night Hound? No, it can't be, my eyes are accurate, he's not a wicked man, and if he is the culprit... surely, surely there must be something going on.”

Dolores felt her head begin to ache.

The mask in her arms must be evidence of last night's murder, and by hiding it from the guards, she was guilty of destroying evidence.

She had no excuse, no accomplice, for letting her personal feelings interfere with the investigation.

So Dolores had been suffering since last night for the trust she had placed in the Night Hound, and for the guilt of hindering the Guard's investigation by hiding him.

'Did I really do the right thing by hiding that mask? Was I doing the right thing?'

She thought about it when she woke up, when she bathed, when she ate, when she was in class, and even now, here, at the club meeting.

Even.

'By the way... I don't know if Mr. Night Hound will be okay. It seems like he was caught in a huge explosion that burned half of his mask off, and even though he's a very strong man, if he wasn't able to defend himself properly, I wonder where he is now... and what he's doing? I wonder if he's seriously injured and suffering somewhere....'

I'm even worried about that.

Dolores didn't know why she was worried about him now, not even the underlying reason.

Then.

“'Night Hound'... sounds good!”

A voice next to her broke Dolores out of her reverie.

“Huh?”

Dolores looked up to see a group of second- and third-year students already busily working.

Whirring, whirring, whirring.

The newspapers that will be distributed today were already being torn out.

??

Dolores turned her head with a dazed expression, and Pigi beside her gave a thumbs up.

“I think I like the nickname 'Night Hound', it's a bit barbaric, but that's what makes it all the more violent, isn't it?”

“Mmmm. I think so, too. There's something sinister about it.”

“I'm afraid I agree. It's always happened at night.”

Tudor and Sancho nodded in agreement with Pigi.

Sinclaire and Bianca nod as well.

“I agree with you, boss!”

“Me too.”

Dolores turned her head in confusion.

“What did I just mutter to myself, ...?”

And then he saw the stacks of finished newspapers.

[The Night Hound, the villain who terrorized the Imperial City, who is he!?] / Views: 0

-In the early hours of the night on October 0. A mysterious assailant appeared and ravaged the nursery school of 00...

Unusually, the attacker did not touch the riches in the vault...

<Comments: 0>

Dolores exclaimed in anger.

“What, what is this!”

Pigi replied with a cheerful expression.

“You nicknamed him the 'Night Hound,' and we all thought it was a good idea, so we went right ahead!”

“Oh, no, when did I say that, really?”

Dolores asked in disbelief, and everyone nodded in agreement.

In a matter of minutes, things had come together.

Dolores looked at the stacks of newspapers and sighed heavily.

“Guys, we still don't have any confirmation that he's the killer, and with a headline like that, it just looks like a story written for views.”

Then Tudor, Sancho, Sinclaire, Bianca, and others questioned.

“Oh, there's testimony from the guards, but whatever. They said they were pretty sure that the Night Hound smashed up the building and killed the orphanage director, and there's some physical evidence, too.”

“Well, the boys and girls looked like they'd been dead for a long time... but I don't think that would happen in a nursery under the direct control of the Quovadis family. I think it's much more believable that the Night Hound did it.”

“You're trying to remain neutral, since you're from the Quovadis family. I'm impressed, but with this much certainty, I think we can go with it for now.”

“'Night Hound' or whatever, as soon as you're in my sights, I'll take you down with an arrow!”

The first years chatter excitedly.

Dolores sighed heavily.

He felt guilty that his mistake had brought the honor of the Night Hound into disrepute.

But the others had a point.

Whether the Night Hound is indeed a villain or not, and if he is, what happened to his formerly clear-eyed, flesh-and-blood charity, and if he is not, what happened to the bodies of the boys and girls found in the orphanage controlled by the Quovadis, and the vast riches of unknown origin.

Everything is jumbled.

Only Dolores knows the true nature of the phenomenon behind the phenomenon, and she is confused.

Finally, she made a judgment call.

“I need to make some changes to the article. Make it as objective and unbiased as possible. Take out any unsubstantiated speculative statements from the Imperial Guard's interviews.”

“Yes, but then I won't have anything to write about?”

“If you're not sure, don't bet on it. It's not too late to run a scathing article when it's clear what the Night Hounds are up to, and then we'll be able to criticize them with real vigor.”

Dolores said, and the others nodded.

Bianca nodded in agreement.

“If the director says so, then so be it.”

“...I agree.”

Sinclaire nodded as well.

Sancho and Pigi quickly shut down the tuning fork and began to modify the articles.

But the heroic Tudor was still a little unhappy.

Tudor turned to Vikir, whom he had gotten to know over the course of the Naphtali Games, and asked in a low voice.

“Hey, buddy, what do you think?”

“...What do you mean?”

“The Night Hound. He looks like a villain to me. What do you think?”

“I don't think so.”

“Oh, come on. How can you not think about it? Is he a villain or does he have something going on?”

Vikir thought for a moment before answering.

'Am I a villain?'

Countless faces flashed through his mind.

The world of destruction, the hell that would unfold within the next decade, the faces of so many he had failed to protect.

The end of colleagues, comrades-in-arms, friends, older brothers, younger sisters, and all the people you miss and love.

How could he be anything but a sinner, carrying their lives and sacrifices on his shoulders and coming back alive alone.

So Vikir was able to say firmly.

“He's a villain for sure.”

Because he was never a good man.

...?

The Tudor who asked the question is unusually quiet.

“?”

Vikir looked up.

He saw the confused looks on Tudor's face and the shaky gazes of the other new students.

They were all staring at Vikir's back.

Vikir turned his head to see Dolores's face staring down at him with a cold gaze.

“What have you been listening to all this time, that the Night Hound is a villain?”

How did they get this far?

Dolores, who just happened to be walking by, asks you coldly if you heard the entire conversation between Tudor and Vikir.

“....”

When Vikir doesn't answer, she repeats herself.

“You may miss ten thieves, but don't make one innocent citizen. No matter how circumstantial the evidence, find the last hard evidence you can, and then report it.”

“....”

“If the 'pen is mightier than the sword', then the pen should be heavier than the sword. You should take responsibility as a journalist from now on. Don't just blurt out things you're not sure about without thinking.”

Dolores's words, which are directed at Vikir, cause the entire freshman class to tense up.

But Vikir just sits there with a nonchalant expression on his face.

Dolores, who was even more displeased with his attitude, added a sarcastic remark.

“I thought your name was Vikir. Are you even tardy anymore?”

Vikir had been photographed by Dolores since the beginning of the semester and had received several detentions.

But when Vikir remained silent, Dolores took a deep breath as if to say something more.

“Anyway, new students these days are the best...... When I was.......”

Then. A sophomore member burst into the club room, looking for Dolores.

“Boss!” “The Club advisor Professor Banshee wants to see you for a moment!”

“What? Why?”

“Because of this article! He wants me to revise the article to say that Night Hound is definitely evil!”

“Haha... he's a conservative and likes to make enemies on the outside. Okay, I'll talk to him.”

Dolores wrapped up the conversation.

He followed the sophomore out of the clubhouse to meet with Professor Banshee.

Only then did the stale air in the room release.

Tudor breathed a sigh of relief and patted Vikir on the shoulder.

“I'm talking about you and the director. You seem like a bit of an old man.”

“......It was like that in the old days.”

“A long ago? When?”

“There was a time when it was just like that.”

Vikir only smiles faintly.

'Why don't you push the paladin line tighter? They're so irreligious these days!'

'The younger ones are slipping away, and I want them to slay at least one more demon in their spare time!'

'Back in my day, if a demon came out, I'd just run straight to it and bang!'

'You're stronger! Charge!'

'Heroes don't die!'

Before he regressed, Dolores was in her 30s, leading the Paladins on the front lines of the Battlefield of Destruction.

Chapter 142

Identity of the Villain (3)

◆

Another new day has begun.

At 6 a.m., the students wake up to the sound of the wake-up call and head to the field in front of the dormitory building.

The field is divided in half, one side for women and one side for men. All wearing gray sweats.

They follow the gymnastic movements of the instructor standing at the front, shaking off the last of their sleep into the cold early morning air.

Afterward, when the exercise is over, the students disperse.

Some go back to sleep to catch up on their sleep, some head straight to the bathhouse, and some head straight to the dining hall.

For the girls, some head straight for the long process of applying makeup.

The academy's baths are quite large and well-equipped, with cold, hot, and even a sauna.

After passing through the locker rooms smelling of pungent foot odor, a dip in the hot water and the early morning chill in the air would not only help you sleep, but also revive your appetite.

As roommates, Vikir and Pigi headed straight for the bath after gymnastics.

“Ugh, the air is so cold at this time of day. Please don't make me do early morning gymnastics, I think my brain could use a little more sleep at that hour....”

Pigi, a morning person, grunts like his entire body is falling apart during every gymnastics session.

Vikir comforts him as he heads to the bathhouse.

Two people see them and wave to them.

They were Tudor and Sancho, who were also sharing a room.

“Hey, Vikir and Pigi. You came straight to the bathhouse again today.”

“Yeah. I come right after gymnastics so the showers are free. We have to wait in line for the showers after breakfast.”

Tudor and Sancho follow Vikir to the showers and get into the hot water.

“What are you guys going to do after your bath, eat right away?”

“I don't have an appetite today, so I'm skipping it. I'm going straight to the lecture hall to catch up on my assignments.”

“I'm going to sleep a little longer and eat just before the cafeteria closes. That way I can eat a lot of leftovers. What's the side dish today, anyway?”

Pigi, Tudor, and Sancho are deep in discussion about what to do with their morning.

That's when Vikir chimes in.

“I'm going straight for the food.”

It's always the same pattern for Vikir.

He doesn't change his plans based on other people's schedules and always walks his own way.

Pigi, Tudor, and Sancho thought for a moment before nodding.

“I guess I'll go eat, then.”

“Hmm. Now that I think about it, I'll be hungry until lunch if I skip it. I should eat too!”

“Right. You're going to eat right away, and I'll join you. Rice tastes better together.”

Vikir's consistent lifestyle was quickly becoming a standard for his friends.

Whether consciously or unconsciously.

At exactly ten minutes, Vikir got out of the tub, showered, and left the bathhouse.

Pigi, Tudor, and Sancho did the same.

Tudor shook his head as they left the bath.

“That's weird.”

“What?”

Sancho asked, and Tudor smirked.

“That Vikir guy. When you're with him, you naturally stand next to him.”

“Is that so?”

“It is. It's like you're looking at a big brother, or an older brother. Is it because I don't have an older brother in the house?”

“Yeah. He's always moving like a machine. I think it's good that we move together because it keeps me on track. It's something to emulate.”

“I'd like to get to know him a little better, but he's a bit stiff. He doesn't let go easily.”

“Time will tell, we'll be seeing each other for the next four years.”

It was the same for Pigi, who was listening to Tudor and Sancho's conversation.

'Vikir is amazing.'

Tudor, a highly retarded member of the Donquixote family, and Sancho, a scholarship student from the Northern Mercenary Guild, both want to get to know him first.

He even studies well and is popular with the girls.

He's even kind enough to help someone who was struggling in a talent show.

Pigi thought he was lucky to be roommates with someone like that.

'I should be a good roommate to make Vikir feel lucky to have me.'

Just as Pigi was saying to himself.

“Hey. Pigi.”

Vikir, walking at a steady pace in front of him, suddenly stops and looks over.

Tudor and Sancho, who were walking next to him, also stopped and looked back.

“Ugh, huh?”

Pigi asked, a little confused, and Vikir gestured toward him.

“Why are you coming from behind like that. Walk a little faster, we're supposed to be working on our morning class assignment together.”

Vikir said, glancing to his side.

Suddenly, Pigi's face lit up.

“Yeah! I'll go! My leg hurt for a second....”

“Your leg? Did you hurt it?”

“No! It doesn't hurt now!”

Pigi rushed over and stood next to Vikir with a look of pride on his face.

Then Tudor and Sancho say something to Pigi, too.

“Did you hurt your leg in gymnastics? Where does it hurt?”

“Small injuries should not be taken lightly. I'll give you some of the herbal juice I brought from the north. It's a salve that even works on broken bones.”

Pigi smiled brightly at his two new friends' concern.

Something sprouted in Pigi's chest, an unfounded confidence that he could make it through the next four years.

◆

Later, after bathing, they went to the dining hall for breakfast.

Bread and cereal, grilled corn and pineapple, and some blanched vegetables.

There are also sausages, chicken, fried eggs, and grilled octopus legs, but few people eat a full breakfast.

There wasn't as much separation between boys and girls as there was in the cafeteria, but first-year boys and girls generally sat far apart.

After breakfast, Vikir headed straight for the lecture hall.

Pigi, Tudor, and Sancho walked beside him, side by side.

Then.

Tudor suddenly stopped walking and called out to Vikir.

“Huh? Wait a minute. Hey, Vikir, this is the way to the main staircase, and we can't go there because it's only for professors and fourth years!”

“....”

That was something Vikir already knew.

Except.

'I'll have to find the least traveled way out of the academy at night so we can use it to get back in.'

As a matter of strategy, Vikir had checked out every single passageway in every single building in the academy.

As a result, even though it was early in the semester, he had a pretty good idea of the layout of the Academy's buildings.

Of course.

“Beep, freshman, why are you taking the central staircase?”

It also put him at a huge disadvantage in terms of his lifestyle score.

Then, the face of the person who had warned Vikir drew closer.

Dolores Rune Quovadis. The student council president had spotted Vikir and given him a detention.

When Dolores recognized Vikir's bushy bangs, horn-rimmed glasses, and face, she placed her hands on her hips in wonder.

“Vikir. Is it you again?”

“I'm sorry, ma'am. I'm a stray.”

“This central staircase is where the professors and seniors do their research. How many times have I told you that it's off-limits to freshmen, not only because it's supposed to be quiet, but because there are many experimental areas that are classified or downright dangerous?”

“I'm sorry.”

“There's no such thing as a junior in the club, it's a demerit.”

Dolores wrote down Vikir's demerits and the reasons for them in her magic journal.

<Vikir-Life Attitude Points (Demerit Factors)

-1 point for using the emergency exit on the third floor of the dormitory building.

-1 point for entering the 4th grade private area of the performance hall

-1 point for using the central staircase on the 1st floor of the blind reading lab building

-1 point for entering the smoking area of the Experimental Monster Breeding Center

-1 point for using the central staircase on the 6th floor of the Faculty Research Center

-1 point for using the central staircase on the 3rd floor of the Hot Class.

-1 point for entering the physical training room after hours.

-Entering the restricted area next to the cafeteria food warehouse -1 point.

.

.

The demerits were already piling up.

Dolores looked at it and opened her mouth in disbelief.

“...You're a very poorly behaved child, aren't you?”

A stunned Pigi, Tudor, and Sancho stepped forward and apologized to Dolores.

“S-sorry! We should have told you!”

“Oh, well, he's such a stray.”

“We'll take better care of him next time. Hey, when did you get so many demerits....”

They all looked back at Vikir and gestured for him to keep his head down.

But Dolores wasn't about to be deterred by their pleas.

“No, no. Your demerits are out of line, Vikir, and you have to do mandatory community service this weekend.”

I had already done community service several times over the weekend.

I don't know why, but it was because Professor Banshee Morgue had a thing for me.

Dolores' punishment was a little off the mark for Vikir.

“If your demerits were at a certain level, I would end it with community service, but... you deserve more than that. A lazy kid with a bad attitude like you won't be able to get away with community service.”

“...If that's the case.”

“Then what, you're off-campus service!”

Hearing Dolores' words, Pigi, Tudor, and Sancho covered their faces with their hands.

Vikir had crossed the river of no return.

Everyone looked back at Vikir with pity.

Off-campus service.

This is not the kind of service that involves cleaning toilets on the weekends or working a few shifts in the cafeteria.

You have to go to a facility outside the academy, like a hospital, monastery, or orphanage, and do odd jobs throughout the holidays.

This weekend happened to be a ten-day long golden holiday with a long weekend, the school's anniversary, and Easter celebrations.

Unfortunately for Vikir, he was sentenced to forced labor during this time.

“You have over a week to reflect on your volunteer work. If you're lucky, your demerits will be reset on the last day, depending on what the heads of the institutions think.”

Dolores looked Vikir up and down with a cold gaze, then turned and walked away.

Tudor and Sancho looked back at Vikir and offered words of comfort.

“Looks like you've got some ugly hairs on your back from that club thing. Cheer up, boy.”

“You mean your opinion that the Night Hound is a villain? I personally support your opinion, Vikir. I do not understand the saintess's reaction.”

Pigi, meanwhile, spoke in a pitying tone.

“Vikir. I'm going to tell you where you're going to do your community service this time. You need to know where you're going so you can prepare yourself.”

Pigi was a wealth of information.

He knew where the academy's troublemakers and flunkies were sent for community service.

“This time, you'll be going to the Indulgentia Children's Home.”

“Indulgentia Home?”

Vikir, Tudor, and Sancho repeated, and Pigi nodded.

“It's a orphanage run by the Indulgentia family, a branch of the Quodavis family, and its director is the founder of the Orphanage Foundation, as well as an outside instructor at the Academy.”

“The director? Who is that?”

Vikir asked in a serious tone, and Pigi tilted his head once before answering.

“Quilt L Indulgentia, head of the House of Indulgentia, an outer relation of House Quovadis.”

Vikir's eyes narrowed at those words.

Quilt. Householder of House Indulgentia.

A man whose name he had recognized many times before, even in the reports sent by Cindywendy.

He was Vikir's next assassination target.

Chapter 143

Volunteering for the Golden Week (1)

◆

The ten-day-long holiday has begun.

A weekend, the school's anniversary, and the Rune Church's Easter celebration. Combine that with the class schedule, and it was a golden holiday that could last for more than a week straight.

From the beginning of the semester, everyone was happy to have such a long holiday.

First-year students enjoy traveling around the Imperial City to get to know their classmates better and invite them to their homes.

Sophomores and seniors traveled to secluded places to catch up on assignments, study for exams, or just to rest their tired bodies.

Fourth-year students study hard on weekdays and holidays, as they are close to graduation and employment.

...And here, despite being a freshman, there was one person who was forced to work hard.

Vikir. He was the hound of the Ironbloods.

Clap-clap- Clap-clap-

Day one of community service. Vikir was washing a mop.

At Indulgentia, a large orphanage on the outskirts of the Imperial City, with a large number of children, there is a never-ending stream of tasks.

Cleaning, laundry, cooking, feeding, washing dishes, carrying equipment, repairing facilities, playing with children, etc. ....

While on-campus volunteering can be supported by professional staff, off-campus volunteering has no such support.

You have to do everything yourself.

During the holidays, when the students at the academy are resting or playing, Vikir finds herself living here, doing all the dirty work.

And of course.

“Hey, Vikir, you should be grateful, we're here for the holidays too!”

“Well, I have to fulfill my volunteer hours anyway due to the Academy's noblesse oblige policy, so I might as well do it now.”

“Me, I'm fine with it, I always liked to do community service!”

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi. These loyal friends followed Vikir.

Vikir nodded silently.

“Thank you.”

Everyone was surprised to hear a thank you from the usually reserved and blunt Vikir.

“Uhhhhhhh.”

“Hmmmmmmmm.”

“Hehehehe.”

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi giggled and started sucking on the mop together.

Vikir looked at them and smiled weakly.

No matter how much they tried to act grown-up, they were still kids who had just turned 18, cheerful kids who could make a friend's day with a simple thank you.

But not so with Vikir himself.

His tattered soul, the weight of life he carries, doesn't allow him to smile easily.

As Vikir mopped the corridor where the orphanage children played, he kept thinking, thinking, thinking.

'Yesterday, I ended up in the newspaper.'

Vikir recalled the newspaper that had been created at the Academy, and then the articles that had begun to appear in newspapers across the Imperium.

[The Night Hound, the villain who terrorized the Imperial Capital, who is he?]

-Last night, on the 0th day of the month, at dawn. A mysterious assailant appeared and ransacked a orphanage in 00...

Unusually, the attacker did not touch the riches in the vault...

[Faithful Saint in Peril Is everything okay as it is!?]

-The orphanage, monastery, and hospital managed by the Faithful Saint Quovadis family are in a series of crises...

Meanwhile, within the Quovadis family, the Old Order and New Order factions are currently at odds...

Meanwhile, some have criticized the government for being slow to respond to the terrorist attacks due to the family's internal politics...

[Old Order vs New Order, Quovadis family quarrel brings terrorists!?]

-The civil war within the Quovadis family is intensifying. This long-running confrontation began with the controversy between Cardinal Humbert of the Old Order and Cardinal Martin Luther of the New Order...

The conflict between the Old Order faction and the New Order faction is truly old, and these two factions are concerned about whether or not it is legitimate for the denomination to sell 'indulgences' and 'indulgences.' ...

As a result, citizens are becoming increasingly concerned about the delay in the investigation to catch the terrorists...

[Is the 'Night's Hound' a real villain?]

-Citizens of the city are on edge over the appearance of a monster that has been stalking the streets of the Imperial City...

However, some have continued to question whether this villain really exists...

Why is it that only welfare organizations under the jurisdiction of the Quovadis family are being attacked? Could this be the result of a power struggle within the Quovadis family...

It's no secret that there is a long-standing feud between the Old Order and New Order factions within the Quovadis family...

It remains to be seen if this is the result of a conflict between the Old and New Order, or whether a truly rare demon has appeared......

.

.

Vikir pored over the newspaper articles.

Thanks to Pigi, it was easy to gather newspapers from all over the Imperial City.

Vikir pieced together the information he'd gathered from Pigi and the information Cindywendy had sent him.

The conclusion.

The places Vikir had raided in disguise as the Night Hound had all coincidentally been linked to the Faithful Quovadis.

“If we're just following the scent of the demon, and only certain groups get caught, then we have a problem.”

Vikir remembers the commonalities of the men he's killed so far.

Unidentified money, the bodies of young boys and girls, and beasts whose faces melted after they died.

They wore the masks of religious organizations, but it was clear that the demons lurked underneath.

Like in Seth Le Baskerville.

'...And the most suspicious one is in this orphanage.'

Vikir glanced up from his mopping.

A portrait of the director hung at the top of the hallway wall.

A gentle, middle-aged face.

A sculpted, handsome man who, in his younger days, must have struck a chord with the ladies. He even bore a striking resemblance to a famous theater actor who had recently retired.

House Indulgentia, a branch of House Quovadis and a clerical family of the same rune religion.

In addition to being the patriarch of House Indulgentia, Quilt is also the director of the Indulgentia Orphanage .

It's probably the largest orphanage in the Imperial Capital.

But what's the point in all that?

'...Only one thing matters.'

He's the target of Vikir's assassination.

It's the Golden Week, so the window is wide open.

Now that he's managed to sneak into his target's lair, all that's left is to get to work.

Vikir used the excuse of cleaning to move from room to room, carefully studying the layout of the building.

'For an orphanage, this building is incredibly strong.'

Vikir mopped, estimating the number of rebars in the stone columns.

The orphanage was sturdy enough to be used as a military facility.

The orphanage's recruitment process was also a bit unusual: instead of taking in children from small local orphanages, the orphanage put out notices so that children would come to them from far away.

Because the facilities were so good and the welfare was so good, many children came to the center voluntarily, so it was difficult to keep track of how many children came and how many left.

At the end of the day, no one could tell if the numbers on the books were off by a zero or two.

'The more orphans you have, the more money you get, so no one would think you'd under-report the number of kids.'

A typical orphanage would exaggerate the number of children they have in order to inflate their funding.

So most audits are focused on whether there are fewer children than there are on paper.

The demons are the opposite.

It's in their interest to falsely claim to have fewer orphans and receive more.

That way, they can drain the blood without turning around.

Vikir notes the number of children in the Indulgentia orphanage, which appears to be much higher than the paperwork indicates.

While some praise Quilt for lending a helping hand to as many children as possible without seeking funding..., Vikir has a different opinion.

'Boys and girls under the age of 13, runaways, unrelated, unregistered births... all of whom are difficult to trace.'

In just one day, Vikir had noticed a number of suspicious things about the place.

And the intense smell of the demon wafting through the entire orphanage only solidified his conviction.

'I'm going to start seeing blood tonight.'

As Vikir was formulating his murderous plan in his mind.

“Hey, hey, hey....”

A voice interrupted Vikir's reverie.

“?”

Vikir turned his head to see an unexpected figure standing there.

A short, gray-haired woman, her hair fluffy like a puppy's.

A female student, neatly dressed in the academy's uniform despite it being a holiday, was looking at him.

Vikir knew her name.

No, no first-year student at the Academy could possibly not know her.

Sinclaire. Head of the Hot Class.

For some reason, she is here doing volunteer work.

Chapter 146

Volunteering for the Golden Week (4)

◆

The next morning arrived.

The volunteer students managed to sleep an extra two hours and woke up at 8:00.

Unlike the academy's schedule, where students wake up at 6:00 a.m. and start their day at 8:00 a.m., the orphanage wakes up at 8:00 a.m. and starts its day at 10:00 a.m.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Vikir, who were sharing a room, woke up early, washed up, and headed out the door.

As Vikir was just putting on his shoes and heading out the door, Pigi called out to him.

“Hey, Vikir. Where did you go last night?”

“...?”

Vikir looked up, and Pigi rubbed his sleepy eyes.

“No, I had to pee in the wee hours of the morning last night and got up to go to the bathroom, but you weren't in bed.”

“I was in the stall at the time.”

“Oh yeah? Ugh, I don't go big for at least a week when I'm in a new place. I guess you've already adjusted.”

It's a lie, of course.

Vikir had spent the entire night investigating the nursery buildings.

Though he'd turned on a false alarm last night when he'd lost Quilt's trail halfway through the chase.

'He's more suspicious than I thought. He's changing his routine to disrupt the chase.'

Hounds follow scent to track their prey, but they can't pick up where the scent leaves off.

But Vikir is human. Humans know how to use tools.

A complete map of the nursery and a building register.

Vikir was able to get a copy of the architectural plans for Indulgentia Orphanage from when it was first built, which allowed him to locate Quilt, the director of the orphanage.

'His lair was hidden deep in the center of the nursery. This gave me a clear target.'

Quilt's quarters were hidden in the center of a circle of buildings housing the children.

The volunteers' quarters were outside of the children's buildings, so to kill Quilt, you would have to go through the four children's buildings.

Therefore, in order to pass through the children's living quarters at night, we had to volunteer in as many locations as possible during the day.

This way, he could learn the layout of the buildings and plan the best route.

That's what Vikir does today.

“Work hard, with sincerity.”

He planned to serve children.

But Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi, who didn't know it, were impressed by Vikir's spirit of service.

“Vikir. Honestly, I saw you again this time. I'm ashamed of myself for working so hard for the kids, for trying to fill in the hours so I could get points. I should take a cue from you and work harder to be a true hero.”

“I thought you were crazy when you stood up to your professors and seniors, but it turns out you're strong for the strong and weak for the weak. I admire you even though you're my classmate.”

“Vikir, I'll try harder too!”

Of course, Vikir didn't listen to his sentimental friends.

The important thing was not to be recognized and praised by others, but to capture and kill the demon lurking in this orphanage.

Then.

“Good morning!”

A voice called out to Vikir as he made his way to the children's area.

Sinclaire could be seen waving her hand in this direction.

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi looked at each other's faces.

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi stared at each other's faces, because none of them were close to Sinclaire.

“?”

“?”

“?”

A “Hey, you too?” vibe formed between the three.

Then.

Sinclaire walked over with a big smile on his face and tapped someone on the shoulder.

It was Vikir.

“Brother, why don't you pretend to know me!”

“I didn't realize it was a greeting for me, and....”

My brother?

Vikir's brow furrowed.

There was something uncomfortable about being called brother by a young girl.

'I'd rather be called mister.'

So Vikir corrected Sinclaire's title.

“We're classmates, so don't call me brother.”

“Why? I'm a year younger than you, and you're still my brother, no matter how you say it.”

“Because it's uncomfortable to hear....”

But Vikir didn't finish his sentence.

Tuk-tuk-tuk-tuk-tuk-tuk-

Six hands clamped over Vikir's mouth.

“Ooh, we love being called big brothers!”

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi said to Sinclaire as they clamped their hands over Vikir's mouth.

“...?”

Sinclaire tilted his head with rabbit-like eyes, then grinned.

“Yeah? I'll call you something else if you don't like it. I'll think about it until lunch.”

“Ouch!”

“Well then, Mr. Tudor, Mr. Sancho, and Mr. Pigi, good luck today!”

Sinclaire waved both fists at everyone, then turned and ran.

In the distance, she headed in the direction of where the kids were doing the lead run.

“Guys, she's back! Yay!”

“Whoa- Sis Sinclaire, here's the pass!”

Sinclaire quickly blended in and started playing with the kids.

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi's jaws dropped at her innocence.

“Sinclaire seems like such a good kid.”

“He's good at school, good at magic, and good with kids.”

“And most of all....”

The three spoke up at the same time.

“She's the prettiest of all the new students!”

Just then.

“What a bunch of boys.”

A sneer came from behind them.

All heads turned to see Bianca standing there with her arms crossed.

Bianca said.

“If you're here to serve, serve, not to judge others behind their backs.”

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi all flinch at her chilling words.

...Except for Vikir.

Bianca looked at Vikir, who stood still, expressionless.

“At least you're a little better. You don't flirt with idiots.”

Then Tudor, who was standing next to Vikir, spoke up.

“Who's an idiot!”

“You.”

“Don't you realize that you and I have similar writing scores?”

“Where does that come from? You had months of rigorous, expensive tutoring before you came to the Academy, and I got that grade just by playing around. I heard your father spent almost a castle to tutor you, and you got that grade after all that work? You're so subpar. Will you please save your nobleman's face?”

“What's so noble about a first year getting caught applying makeup, getting called out by the second year sisters and scolded, and berating them by bringing up the family's prestige, and then being caught by the instructor and being forced to serve?”

Tudor and Bianca had been enemies since before they entered the Academy, so there was nothing they didn't know about each other.

“You bastard, what's the point of being proud of a commoner girl's face behind her back?”

“I called her pretty because I thought she was pretty, and don't you realize that discrimination between commoners and nobles is forbidden in the academy? You're disqualified from being a hero because you're so full of selfishness!”

“Don't you ever get tired of your heroism? You're just like Donquixote!”

“It's the Usher family's trademark to be gloomy and sarcastic!”

“You're talking out of your ass. Pfft!”

“You might as well be screaming at a rock. I'm in!”

Tudor and Bianca had always argued about who was the true head of the cold warrior class, and this argument was no different.

Sancho, fed up, interrupted them.

Meanwhile, Vikir quickly left.

He didn't want to waste any more time getting caught up in the children's fight.

Pigi followed Vikir and said.

“Oh, by the way. Vikir. I have a piece of information to tell you.”

“Information? What is it?”

“Nothing big. It's about Sinclaire.”

...?

Vikir cocked his head.

Pigi scratched her head.

“It's really nothing. I saw Sinclaire go to the outreach coordinator the other day and ask for something.”

“Like what?”

“About where you're going to volunteer. She asked me where you were going and wanted me to assign her to it. She seemed so desperate.”

Pigi chuckled and gave Vikir a swat on the side of the head.

“See what I mean? Good luck with that.”

Vikir got a serious look on his face when he heard that.

He knew exactly what Pigi was talking about.

'She actually changed her volunteer location to follow me, at this time of year? That's suspicious.'

Something smelled of conspiracy.

At the same time, Vikir remembered what Sinclaire had said yesterday.

'It's a coincidence that we're both assigned to the same place.'

'It is.'

'Actually, I saw your volunteer application last week, but I didn't think we'd be going to the same place.'

'I see.'

Sure, yesterday was a coincidence. But it was a deliberate and thoroughly planned move.

Vikir looked at Sinclaire in the distance with a distant glance.

'Come to think of it, when you said that yesterday, you had a strange increase in heart rate and unsteady breathing. It is the hallmark of those who have something to hide.'

An uninhabited world in an age of destruction is understandably wary.

The demons are so vicious that they can slip through the cracks and stab you with their deadly sting.

Recalling the faces of his comrades-in-arms, sad and futile, makes me even more alert.

I couldn't feel anything other than clear energy in her soul, but I still don't know.

'There's no harm in being wary,' he thought, 'but I'll have to keep my distance. Far, far away.'

Pigi's meaningful warning was also troubling.

Perhaps he sensed something ominous and was trying to warn me about it.

'...Well, if you can get rid of it without rats or birds noticing, that's all you need.'

The dead are silent, for the dead have no words.

Vikir walked away, grateful to Pigi for the warning.

From now on, he would keep a close eye on Sinclaire's every move, but he would also keep his distance.

Chapter 149

Not Brother, But Uncle (1)

◆

The volunteer work of the Golden Week has come to an end.

Everyone will return to the Academy tomorrow morning.

On their last night at the orphanage, the volunteer students gathered in the great hall to hear a speech from the orphanage's director, Quilt.

Resembling an old-time theater actor known for his eloquence, Quilt addressed the audience.

“ ... So, our parents are working hard for you even at this very hour... but unlike you, the children in this orphanage have no parents... and so you, the wonderful people of the Academy, who should be an example to all, have become the guardians of these children... and these children will remember for the rest of their lives the grace you have shown them over the past ten days... and you are no different than the parents who have given birth to these children in your hearts....”

The tongue. It is only truly effective when it is attached to the demon's lips.

The demonic tongue is indeed the tongue of the demon, and it brought tears to the eyes of many students throughout the auditorium.

Quilt's speech reminded the volunteer students of the grace of their parents and made them feel, if only temporarily, a strong sense of compassion for the children of the orphanage.

It's not even funny.'

Except for Vikir.

In fact, Vikir knew that Quilt's speech was nothing more than a clever tapping into the feelings of respect and indebtedness that the Academy's students naturally have for their parents.

Proof of this was the giant donation box that appeared immediately after Quilt's speech.

“Now, show the children of our nursery the love you've felt for them these past ten days. As much as you've received from your parents, give to the children here!”

At Quilt's words, the students rushed to open their wallets.

Clink, clink, clink!

The sound of gold coins clinking together.

As much as the students of the Academy respect and love their parents, the coins are stacked on top of each other, forming a small mountain of gold.

...Of course, Vikir didn't pay a cent, because he didn't have any respect or love for Hugo.

Nor did he have any intention of donating anything to the demon.

Then.

Vikir was approached by someone.

It was Sinclaire.

She tugged on Vikir's collar and said.

“Hyung. Aren't you paying?”

“...No money.”

“Money? Why don't you have money? You're an Academy student.”

Admission to the Academy required an enormous amount of tuition each year.

Sinclaire looked a little angry and poked Vikir in the side.

“Don't you think you're being too harsh? The poor kids here have no parents, and we should help them.”

That was the general reaction of the volunteer students.

Everyone except Vikir. I mean, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi... and even Bianca were all sobbing and dropping all their money in the donation box.

But Vikir shook his head resolutely.

“I don't need parents.”

“Oh?”

Sinclaire's eyes widened in disbelief.

Vikir added briefly.

“You have to navigate the world on your own anyway. Parents are only functional in childhood, when they are essential, but otherwise they are unnecessary.”

In fact, Vikir didn't think the children in the orphanage were pitiful or needy in the first place.

Just as he had been born and raised as a hound in Baskerville, he didn't think the children in the orphanage needed a parent to help them through their childhood.

The “world” is full of pain, something to be fought and overcome, and “parents” are merely the initial guides to help with the first tutorials of that long battle.

It's a functional view, not an emotional one, but it's the way of parenting in Baskerville, where Vikir has lived his entire life, and in the Age of Destruction, where he's lived half his life.

And naturally, that perspective is somewhat unfamiliar to the average person in this day and age who hasn't lived through the Age of Destruction.

It's been said that those who have lived through war and those who have not will never understand each other, even in death.

Sinclaire's gaze shifted slightly as he looked at Vikir.

From a curious, playful look to a sad, wistful one.

“Type ....”

Finally, Sinclaire spoke up.

“You should come to my house sometime. For the holidays or something.”

“...?”

“We can eat together.”

Sinclaire stood on tiptoe and stretched out his hand to stroke Vikir's head.

“...What are you doing?”

Vikir asked in disbelief, and Sinclaire pulled his hand back with a snap.

The look of genuine embarrassment on her face told me that she hadn't even realized she was doing it.

“Uh...... Well, then I'm done! I'm going to go see the kids! Hyung! Really, let's have a meal later! Because I will buy it! Just make sure you're free when you get back from volunteering!”

She backed away in a huff, waved, and disappeared into the crowd.

“...What a weird girl.”

Vikir frowned.

Memories of who Sinclaire had been before the regression flashed through his mind.

A girl who didn't talk much, but smiled a lot. A girl who was reasonably friendly with everyone, but never really connected with anyone. A super genius who never missed the top spot in any of her written or practical exams during her four years at the academy. And the mysterious one who disappeared upon graduation, never to be seen again.

She was said to be of commoner descent, but strangely enough, nothing was known of her origins or background.

Vikir frowned.

'Come to think of it, one of the pieces of crap Cindywendy sent me said, There's a royalty in the mix among this year's 20th batch of Academy newcomers... You mean...?'

Given Sinclaire's good looks, talent, and strangely hidden background, it's not out of the question.

As Vikir was thinking about this.

The voice of the Mean Quilt comes back.

“Now, from now on, the children of our orphanage will be thanking their parents for giving birth to them with their hearts!”

Just then, a spotlight shines on the far side of the stage.

There, lined up in a row, are the children of the nursery, all dressed up and looking awkward and embarrassed.

Each and every one of them holds a crudely crafted wreath in their hands.

Quilt grinned from ear to ear.

“Now, children – let's thank them for being your parents for ten days, shall we?”

It's obvious that Quilt's plan is to use the kids as bait to scrape more donations out of the academy's inexperienced students.

But the heart and connection between the children who made the wreaths and the volunteers who were happy to wear them around their necks was genuine.

The children were excited to share their handmade bouquets and flower necklaces with their sisters, brothers, and older siblings, hoping that they would like them, and their sisters, brothers, and older siblings were overjoyed to receive their gifts.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca hugged them tightly.

“Awww! I'm Tudor, I swear! I will come to you every week until the day I become a great hero, and of course after that!”

“In the North, we cherish our children most. The future of the empire depends on you. Do your best.”

“Awww! I'll be back! Next time I come, I'll bring lots of goodies!”

“Well... ten days is a short time if it's short, and a long time if it's long. You've gotten yourself into a lot of trouble.”

The children tied garlands around the students' necks and kissed them on the cheeks.

But.

“....”

Noticeably, the children were not coming closer to Vikir.

This was partly due to Vikir's blunt and cold demeanor, but the main reason was that he hadn't been in front of the children for the past ten days.

Cleaning the sewers, repairing the plumbing, tiling the cafeteria, maintaining the playground, etc.... Vikir always took care of the dirty work behind the scenes, so his activities went unnoticed.

Is that why? Vikir's community service scores, ratings, and image were quite low.

Then.

A little kid walked up to Vikir's side.

It was Nymphet.

“....”

“....”

Nymphet stared at Vikir.

Vikir stared at Nymphet, too.

Unusually, Vikir broke the silence first.

“...What do you see?”

Nymphet, somewhat hesitantly, held out what he'd been hiding behind his back.

It was a small, crudely made wreath.

“Mmm. Thank you.”

Vikir took the wreath from Nymphet's hand.

Normally, he would bend down to the child's eye level and let the child tie the wreath around his neck, but Vikir had no such consideration.

Then, Nymphet grabbed Vikir's hand.

She moved her tiny fingers and wrote on Vikir's palm.

'Thanks for the ball, oppa.'

For your work in the sewers.

Vikir nodded once.

“You're welcome.”

Vikir was unimpressed; he'd only done it to save Madam Eight-Legs's eggs.

Unexpectedly, the Nymphet was willing to continue the conversation.

“Will you come again?”

For a moment, Vikir's pupils fluttered.

Next time. Would there be a next time?

Hounds prepare for death every moment.

They could be killed by their prey or boiled by their master.

So Vikir, like the other volunteers, didn't find the word “next” easy to say.

And Nymphet was no stranger to disappointment, especially with the increasingly less frequent volunteer visits.

After a moment's hesitation, Vikir finally nodded.

“As long as there is a 'tomorrow' for me and for you.”

That was the most Vikir could promise.

Nymphet's eyes went wide for a moment.

Then Nymphet smiled wryly and nodded.

“I'll wait.”

In Vikir's parched palm, Nymphet's moist fingers plant a message of promise.

And then. It's kissing time.

All the other children kiss the cheeks of the other volunteers.

But neither Nymphet nor Vikir stood still, not particularly trying to bring their mouths and cheeks close to each other.

Finally, Vikir turned away.

“It's okay if we don't kiss. I don't like it either.”

“....”

Nymphet was visibly flustered.

For some reason, Nymphet hesitates, fidgeting with its hands.

To Nymphet, Vikir had one last word.

“......And.” “It's not 'oppa,' it's 'uncle.'”

For a thirteen-year-old girl, it was somewhat unfamiliar to hear her brother called Vikir.

Leaving a visibly disappointed Nymphet behind, Vikir turned to leave the auditorium on foot.

“Now, wait!”

Vikir would have done so, had it not been for Saint Dolores standing in his way.

Chapter 150

Not Brother, But Uncle (2)

◆

“Now, wait!”

Saint Dolores stopped Vikir in his tracks.

“Aren't you being too hard on her? Did she get a kiss?”

“No.”

“It's not 'no', it's 'not'! She wants to kiss you like that, so give her a kiss!”

“I'm embarrassed.”

Dolores opens her mouth in disbelief.

I've never seen anyone say “embarrassed” so openly before.

She pushes past Vikir and picks up Nymphet.

“Uh-oh,” she says, “that cold-hearted oppa doesn't like kisses. Can I do it to my sister instead?”

“....”

“Oh, you hate big sister...?”

But Dolores was a very determined Nymphet.

Dolores watched in disbelief as Nymphet walked away and Vikir walked away.

'She never seems to open up to anyone, does she....?

She knew why Nymphet had opened up to Vikir.

Nymphet had dropped her ball in the sewer while running, and Vikir had jumped into the sewer to retrieve it for her without hesitation.

How could anyone not be moved by the sight of him returning the ball to her, even with filth dripping from his body?

Dolores, who must have been watching the scene from a distance, was moved to tears by the sight of Nymphet herself, who dropped the ball into the sewer.

'...Vikir. What an unknown.'

Dolores thought to herself as she watched Vikir's back shrink in the distance.

He wanted to know more about the junior.

◆

The day drew to a close.

Vikir left the great hall and headed for his dormitory.

The four-man dormitory was shared by Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Vikir.

The daycare workers on duty in front of the dorms waved to the students.

“Okay, volunteers, come on in.”

“If you're late, you know, all the doors to the building will be closed, and we won't be able to open them for you.”

“You are not allowed outside the dormitory after 10:00!”

The curfew here at Indulgentia Orphanage is strangely strict.

At night, the doors and windows of all the buildings are locked, and traffic is strictly prohibited.

The dormitory supervisors are always roaming the halls, listening to the volunteers' complaints, but Vikir realizes that it's not for protection, but for monitoring.

'...Especially in the dormitories where the children stay.'

Even Vikir had never visited the children's quarters at night before.

Guards roamed the exterior of the building, and the four shadows of Quilt stood guard inside.

Geronto, Hebe, Pedo, and Ephebo.

I had never seen them, but I could smell their presence by the faint stench they emitted.

As long as these four troublesome obstacles stood in his way, he could not move forward.

So Vikir stood still and waited for the right time, when their scent would fade even further.

And today, on the night the dark clouds swallowed the moon. It was time to hunt.

Vikir made his way to the public shower room, stepped out of the shower, and wrapped a towel around himself.

Dinner would be served in a few minutes, and then it would be time for bed.

He dries off and heads to bed with a nonchalant attitude.

“Hey, Vikir!”

As planned, Tudor shoulders into Vikir.

When Vikir turned his head, Tudor grinned evilly and whispered.

“You, man. Look at those fucking abs. Who did you get ripped like this to kill?”

Tudor chuckles and rubs Vikir's stomach.

Then he narrows his eyes and coaxes Vikir in a low voice.

“That's right. Are you just going to take this fine body of yours to bed tonight?”

“Then what and where are we going?”

“Come on, Vikir. When you die, your body rots and turns to dust. We need to use this young, limber body a little more efficiently. It's for the greater good, isn't it?”

Tudor chuckled as he looked at Vikir's public good(?) body.

Sancho, who was next to him, looked down at Tudor in a pathetic way.

“So, you're talking at length about sneaking off to the girls' dormitory at night. Is this coming from a guy who claims to be a wannabe hero?”

“There is a saying that a hero has his true colors.” “Heroes naturally like colors.”

At Tudor's words, Pigi, who was beside him, timidly asked.

“Isn't this a heroic lecher?”

“Hahaha! Anyway, it's a knight's romance to find a lady who will give him her all, and who can blame me?”

Tudor began to persuade Sancho and Pigi with a glint in his eye.

“Isn't it delightful to imagine,” he said, “to cross the pitch-black night, and the mighty boundary, and climb up the east wing of the castle wall, and meet her! If only there were no dragons in the way, it would be chivalrous literature! As you know, even the dormitories at our academy are strictly separated for men and women, and if it weren't for this opportunity, I wouldn't be able to spend a night in the same room with a woman for four years!”

“Uh, what are you going to do with them?”

“Yes, Pigi! That's a good question! What do we do... just drink and hang out! We play drinking games and talk about more serious things, huh?”

“Hmmm. Drinking games? You mean, like, drinking until one of us collapses and dies?”

“That's a very Sancho opinion, why would you play that kind of game with girls, not that stupid northern drinking game, but a random game or a truth game or something!”

Sancho, a native of the North, was intrigued by Tudor's comments, as his only experience with nightly drinking was with a group of sweaty men.

Pigi, too, had never really talked to a girl her own age before, and looked at Tudor with half concern and half anticipation.

“Hmmm. I'm all for it, but the question is whether the girls will like me, ... or think I'm a lust-blind muscular pig.”

“Whoa, hey, Sancho. Girls think the same way as boys, and I've already kissed with one lady during the day. We've arranged that if we go to the right place at the right time, she'll sneak out the back door to greet us.”

“Hey, can I come too? I hope I won't be too much of an annoyance....”

“Haha! The more people the better, so we can share the punishment if we get caught, and Pigi! Be confident! You're chubby and cute, so you're secretly in high demand!”

The conversation goes well(?).

Having succeeded in getting Sancho and Pigi on board, Tudor nervously turns his head.

Vikir stood there, expressionless.

Tudor looked at him and opened his mouth.

“Uhm. Vikir. As much as I'll try to keep you out of harm's way as much as I can... since we're sharing a room for four, I think it's best if you have one last night of excitement for your memories.....”

“Let's go.”

“Aww, don't be so cut and dry about it... eh?”

Tudor rolled his eyes.

And so did Sancho and Pigi.

Vikir made it clear again.

“Let's go. I like girls.”

“....”

It was the most mismatched look and line in the world.

Tudor stuttered and opened his mouth.

“You do realize we're not going to duel with girls, right? It's socializing, you know.”

“I know.”

Vikir nodded, and Sancho and Pigi widened their eyes.

“Vikir. You're not sick, are you? Tell us if you are. My salve, made from herbs that grow in the north, heals even the mind....”

“Vi, Vikir. What's wrong with you? You usually had no interest in women...... ?”

Of course, as his friends had feared, Vikir had never been interested in women.

But Vikir had something else in mind.

'Tonight is the best time to kill the demon ....'

It was a moonless night, and the nocturnal world was the perfect hunting ground for the Night Hound.

Vikir will sneak out of the dormitory under the guise of a group of men and women, and he'll look for any loopholes in the rigorous guard.

If he's caught early on an assassination mission, he can use the other boys as an excuse.

Boys of his age do that, girls of his age do that, and adults who see the innocent love of youth often smile tolerantly.

Tudor is from the high nobility, and Sancho and Pigi are students at a young academy, so their identities are pretty much guaranteed.

If Vikir is caught wandering the halls, he can probably get away with the excuse that he got lost looking for the girls' quarters.

Meanwhile, Tudor excitedly outlined the day's plan.

“Great, Vikir's on board, so all the boys in our room are going. When we hear the clock tower bell ringing at midnight, we're going to pretend to go to the bathroom, then we're going to go out into the hallway... and follow the exhaust vent in the ceiling... and climb up the water pipes... to where the latch on the first floor bathroom window in the girls' dormitory is broken... and then we're going to go up to the emergency exit, where the girls will write down the room number of today's rendezvous point on a note and put it under the flower pot.....”

It was a fairly specific and thorough plan for a kid's rendezvous.

Vikir's rarely serious expression matched the innocence of the plan.

The larger the number of boys and girls involved in the plan, the more room there was for distractions.

“ ... This way. Tonight, there's a gap when the wardens on duty change. We'll gather at the end of the emergency exit and leave when the midnight bell rings.”

The fluffy one-day puppies groan with excitement at the deviation they are experiencing for the first time in their lives.

And then.

Mixed among these little balls of fur was an experienced hunting dog hiding its sharp teeth.

Chapter 152

The Drinking Game (2)

◆

○◎○○◎

○◎○●○

◎○●◎●

A white, pure and spotless fortress.

This spotless and virtuous white citadel has been invaded by hordes of dark evil for some time now.

Vikir. And the black cavalry, led by Vikir, split into several lines to attack the White Citadel.

The Paladins of Dolores were helpless in front of this mysterious movement, which was like a black cavalry unit, digging through the smallest of cracks, destroying the entire inside, and then breaking through the gap on the other side.

'This isn't a level 2, did he trick me!

Dolores rallied her remaining troops and reinforced the walls.

The strongholds and outposts were made a little tighter, and the fortresses on the four corners of the city also had thicker walls.

But once again, the black cavalry broke through the snow-white walls and trampled on them.

◎○○○◎

○◎●●○

○●●◎●

○●◎●◎

●◎●◎●

What used to be white is now empty, and black is taking its place.

“Oh, no! If we let any more in, we're going to...!”

Dolores rallied her best troops, reinforced the walls of the citadel, and secured the passage.

The last bastion. The last line. A land like Althoran that guarantees unconditional victory if it can be defended.

...However, the premise is 'as long as you can keep it'.

Once again, Vikir's black soldiers bared their fangs.

Black auras, shaped like awls, pierce through white walls and ravaged the interior.

The white land inside that Dolores had defended so steadfastly was eventually covered in the black marks of Vikir.

◎◎◎◎●

●●●●◎

◎◎◎○●

○○○●◎

●●●●◎

It all ended with the black hound inside the protective box with its mouth wide open.

“Adari.”

Vikir took the saint's arm in his mouth.

Now, if he bit down hard enough, her right arm would snap off.

The same fate would eventually befall her left arm, then her right leg, then her left leg, then her torso, and finally her neck.

Sweat began to trickle down Dolores's forehead as she realized that the entire group was about to be annihilated.

'What can I do? What can I do....'

No matter how hard he tried, he couldn't see a way out of the black monster's jaws.

The feeling of defeat is already setting in.

And Dolores couldn't bring herself to admit it.

After all, all go players are competitive.

She had been through heaven and hell many times in the short time she had been in the game.

And today, Dolores had met the right man.

“It's like a handshake at the end of the move.”

The attack on Vikir's mind continued.

Meanwhile, Vikir was a little surprised.

'...In today's world, this is probably a level 5.'

It wasn't that Dolores was a bad player, but rather that she was a better player than he expected.

Vikir had played against quite a few people on the battlefield in boring confrontations before his regression.

One of the sergeants, who was a good player, said to him, “How's your level?”

'What's your level of skill? I'm about a level one. Of course, I was rated before the war.'

He said that at Vikir level, he would be at level 2 or 3.

He's a first-rate, and Vikir's skills are only slightly below his own.

'Hahaha, after the War of Destruction against the Demon World, there were no organizations or tournaments to certify one's strength.'

Is that why? Vikir thought that he would be around the level 2 range, but it seemed that with proper verification, he would be much higher than that.

And eventually.

...Just like that!

The last stone hit the board, and Dolores's head dropped.

“...Lost.”

Regardless of defeat. It doesn't even make sense to calculate the house.

Then, exclamations followed from around the area.

“Wow! This is the first time I've seen a saint give instructions in Go!”

“Ms. President, didn't you appear in the newspapers in your youth? As a Go prodigy.”

“Even when there was a Go club in Colosseo, our president was the one who single-handedly massacred the magic tower's Go club and the Varangian's Go club...... How can this happen?”

Since the other person is Dolores, everyone is cautious about what they say.

It was a result that would not have been strange even if there had been harsh evaluations such as 'it was torn apart' and 'it was ripped apart'.

Vikir was just about to clean up the board.

“Now, wait! One more game, one more game, this time in shorthand!”

Dolores stretched out her hands and clung to Vikir's.

By nature, all Go players are competitive, especially those who are called geniuses.

If nothing else, Dolores had a competitive streak in this area.

In the end, Vikir accepted Dolores' offer.

The game is called Shogi (快棋). The rules are simple. You have three seconds to decide on your next move.

This would dramatically reduce the time it takes to play a game.

Vikir and Dolores had moved to the front of Dolores's bed so as not to disturb the other students' drinking.

The students, however, followed closely behind them with their drinks in hand, sitting in a circle around the board where the game was being played.

Apparently it was fun to watch.

“This is surprisingly fun. Go.”

“Yeah, I used to get bored watching my dad play.”

“I don't know, did you just put the boss and Vikir in a tense situation?”

“I don't know, but... I do know that it wasn't a close game.”

On the battlefield, where everyone's eyes are on the saintess's white and Vikir's black, they clash ferociously.

...Bam!

...Click!

...Click!

...Click!

...Click!

...Click!

...Click!

...Click!

Black and white flashed across the board at breakneck speed.

Then a dry voice escaped from Vikir's mouth.

●◎●◎●●◎●◎●

◎●○●◎◎●○●◎

●○◎○●●○◎○●

◎●○●◎◎●○●◎

●◎●◎●●◎●◎●

●○●○●●○●○●

◎●○●◎◎●○●◎

●○●○●●○●○●

●◎●◎●●◎●◎●

◎●◎●◎◎●◎●◎

“All clear.”

The moment Dolores heard those words, she thought seriously.

“ ... Should I turn it upside down?”

It was a violent thought that I had never had in the past dozen years.

But as she felt the stares around her, she couldn't help but say the words in a stifled voice.

“...I lost.”

The students around them, who had been watching the fight without breathing, let out a collective gasp.

Sinclaire broke out in a cold sweat.

“I thought I was pretty good at Go, but... can't read my hyung's moves.”

Pigi nodded in agreement.

“In the first place, Vikir's style isn't the style nowadays. None of the current knights play like this, and it's obviously not a good move, so how can he play like this?”

Dolores, on the other hand, could not hide her bewilderment.

Go is all about building a house.

But Vikir was acting like he didn't care about the house.

It was a mess, a dog fight.

Instead of building his own house, Vikir was all-in on destroying his opponent's house.

Vikir bites and bites and bites like a madman with no backbone, and Dolores ends up with both hands and feet.

“....”

Vikir smiled bitterly at Dolores, who shook her head in disbelief.

As I have said before, those who have not lived through war will never understand those who have.

When the age of destruction came, there was no point in building a house or raising a family.

You never knew when the demons would attack and wipe out your family.

The only way to live was to roam the battlefield and destroy the enemy's strongholds first.

It was this atmosphere, momentum, and values that created Vikir's play style, but Dolores and the other students didn't realize it.

“Ugh, I don't know much about Go, but I can tell he's a mad dog.”

“It's a mad dog style... Well, it has its own charm.”

Tudor and Bianca nodded in agreement.

But to Dolores, none of this chatter fell on her ears.

Who am I, where am I, and where am I going?

After all, everyone has a board game to be proud of.

We all have a board game we're proud of. ...until we get robbed by the wrong person.

And once that happens, your whole world is turned upside down.

No matter how undefeated you've been, you can lose all your confidence in a single defeat.

In the end, Dolores was forced to swallow her punishment once again.

“...Gulp.”

A burp comes from drinking too much soda.

Dolores tried desperately to hide her bulging belly and burp.

Then.

A hiccup!

She started to hiccup.

“...What the hell?”

Dolores turned her head to look at the students around her.

All of them were smiling from ear to ear.

Dolores quickly checked the label on the glass bottle of soda.

Sure enough, it contained too much alcohol to be called a drink.

“You guys tricked me... hiccup!”

Dolores's face began to grow redder and redder.

She feels hot and sweaty.

In a room stacked high with empty liquor bottles, the air was getting hotter and hotter, with red-faced boys and girls mingling with each other.

...Just then.

Thud, thud, thud, thud.

Footsteps began to pound outside the door.

Dolores felt the drunkenness that had been creeping up on her a moment ago begin to fade.

“Here comes the supervisor!”

Everyone in the room jolted awake at the sound of Dolores' words.

It was as if they had been splashed with cold water.

“Bottles! Hide the bottles first!”

“Ouch! The ceiling panel suddenly won't open, and the window is too narrow to get out!”

“Where do we hide the boys?”

“In the bed, under the covers, everyone!”

“Ha, but what about the men and women?”

“Don't be ridiculous! He's a man after all.......”

“Shut up and turn off the lights! Turn off the lights first!”

Everyone was in a panic.

And in that atmosphere.

...Bang!

I heard the sound of a key opening the door.

Click.

The supervisor entered the room.

Chapter 153

The Drinking Game (3)

◆

...Bam!

The female supervisor in charge of the girls' dormitory opens the door and peers into the room.

“Isn't it strange, I thought I heard something?”

It's a quiet room, with only the window faintly illuminating the darkness, and a dark cloud slowly gathering outside.

Saegsaeg-

If you listen closely, you can hear small gasps of breath.

The supervisor looks around the room, careful not to wake the students.

....

Everyone is sleeping quietly on their beds. With the covers pulled over their heads.

Not seeing anything out of the ordinary, she scratched her head.

“Did I hear something wrong?”

But she wouldn't know. That she always heard.

In fact, there was something quite bizarre going on inside the lump of blankets that now lay on the bed.

'Hey, get off me-it's too close.'

“How am I supposed to get out of here, am I going to get expelled?”

Bianca is lying in bed, covered head to toe in blankets.

Beneath her is Tudor, now sprawled out in a stiff position.

The two of them are always at loggerheads, and even in this situation, they were fighting.

'Oh shit, why did you have to get into my bed!'

“I had no choice, I was in an emergency!”

“It's dirty, don't whisper in my ear, you're breathing on me!”

'Shhh! We're going to get caught!'

Tudor and Bianca pressed their pounding hearts against each other's chests.

When both of them slightly raise their heads, the supervisor's shadow, bathed in moonlight, can be seen faintly penetrating across the white blanket.

'.....Hic!'

Both Tudor and Bianca were startled by the shadow of the supervisor who had come so close that they clung to each other even closer.

Forgetting their usual grudges, they hugged each other tightly.

It did lower the height of the oddly shaped lump of futon a bit.

And it was a common occurrence in all the other beds.

Meanwhile.

'....'

Dolores, lying on the bed, covered with a blanket, was recalling the events of a few moments ago.

...Let's see, how did this happen?

Seconds before the door opened, she blew out the candles and quickly jumped into bed.

It all happened in a split second.

The girls, the original occupants of the room, jumped into their beds, and the boys who were closest to them followed suit.

A blanket was pulled over them and the lights went out.

Dolores was a genius with extraordinary powers of observation and memory, and she was able to recall exactly which boys went into which girls' beds just before the lights went out.

“I'm pretty sure Tudor went to Bianca's bed, Pigi went to Sinclaire's bed, and Sancho went to....”

The faces of the boys and girls alternated in my mind.

Luckily, the sex ratio was just right, with one girl hiding one boy.

And that means... Dolores also has to hide one boy in her bed.

'And in my bed?'

Dolores remembered the face of the boy closest to her.

Vikir.

Dolores's face instantly brightened at the memory of his nonchalant expression.

Soon he will come into her own blanket.

Her heart thumped wildly at the thought.

'Ugh, what should I do! Oh my god!'

I've never seen anything like this before, and I don't know what to do.

Dolores closed her eyes tightly as she felt her hands gripping the corners of the blanket becoming damp.

....

...But?

Time passed, but Vikir didn't crawl under the blankets.

At this point, it was Dolores who was burning up.

What in the world was he doing in this desperate situation, when the supervisor could be coming in any moment?

“...?”

Dolores pushed the blankets down slightly and looked out of bed.

By this time, Vikir was standing still, staring silently at the corner of the ceiling.

'It's about time.'

The boys were moderately drunk and moderately entertained.

They should all be in bed now, sleeping or heading back to their dorms.

Vikir had planned to take advantage of this to escape through a hole in the ceiling and assassinate Quilt.

He had enough alibis by now.

'If I disappeared like this anyway, you would think I would have been scared and gone back to the men's dormitory.'

So Vikir chose this moment to disappear out of sight.

Just as he was about to launch himself toward the ceiling.

'What do you think you're doing!'

A hand grabbed the hem of Vikir's robe.

It was St. Dolores, pulling Vikir to her feet with her whirling eyes.

“...?”

Dolores was so flustered that even Vikir was flustered with her.

With a face covered in cold sweat and rolling eyes, she grabbed Vikir by the hem of his clothes and pulled him into her blanket.

“Wait, wait....”

There was no time for Vikir to make excuses.

The blanket was pulled over him, and he found himself on top of Dolores.

And at that point.

Kkiiig...

The door opened and the supervisor walked in.

◆

“Did I hear wrong?”

The voice came from outside the futon, from the bedside.

Dolores felt her eyes roll back in her head and shouted.

'No! You heard me right! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!'

Vikir is lying flat on top of her.

They were now so close that the tips of their noses touched and crumpled slightly.

'...Ha.'

Vikir sighed lowly.

If he missed this opportunity, he might never get another chance to slay a demon, and he shouldn't be wasting his time here.

But Vikir's sigh seemed to mean something else to Dolores.

'Hot, hot!'

Her ears burned as if they were on fire from another's breath.

The saint flinched involuntarily as she felt her entire body tickle.

At the same time, a great trial came upon Dolores.

Yao Yi.

I've been drinking too much soda, or rather, too much alcohol, since I lost the game of Go earlier, and I'm starting to belch and my stomach is bloated.

Vikir's body was pressing heavily on my lower abdomen, making me feel even more sick.

Dolores cried out desperately inwardly, not to God, but to the supervisor, who stood outside the futon.

'Please, please go back!'

But whether or not she realized the wishes of everyone in the room, she continued to look around the room.

“Hmm, a little dry. I don't want the Academy's volunteers to get sore throats. Shall I sprinkle some water on the floor?”

“The windows are rattling in the breeze, in case you're a light sleeper.”

“Is the room at the right temperature? I hope it's not too cold, seeing as how you're all sleeping with your blankets over your heads?”

Ironically, the supervisor's compassion was making everyone suffer even more.

Especially Dolores, who was holding her urine inside the blanket.

'A restroom! I'd do anything for a restroom!'

Dolores gritted her teeth and pushed with all her might.

And Vikir had to be embarrassed by Dolores' inappropriate grip(?).

“...?”

Dolores was squeezing Vikir's waist with both thighs.

It was a necessary action, but one that Vikir didn't know enough about to understand.

Vikir was just about to pull himself away from Dolores.

...Thud!

Dolores raised her hands and grabbed Vikir's back.

Dori-dori-

She pleaded desperately.

'Please don't fall off!'

She said with her eyes, something like that.

If Vikir, who was now pressing down on her lower abdomen, were to move, the slightest shift in weight would cause drastic changes in her body.

But Vikir doesn't understand Dolores' desperate gaze.

Boosh.

Vikir removes himself from Dolores' belly.

'...It leaked.'

Dolores felt her body relax slightly.

She wondered if Vikir, on top of her, had noticed. And what if he did?

'Oh, no, I don't think he noticed.'

At most, the lower half of my body is very slightly, minimally wet.

I've got clothes, I've got a blanket, I'm sweating, and the situation is so urgent, I don't think he'd notice.

Just as Dolores is slipping into a trance with her spinning eyes and blurred vision.

...Kwang!

Above Dolores' head, a palm slammed into the bed near the bedpost.

Oops. She was standing right in front of Dolores' bed.

Everyone in the room froze at the unexpectedly loud sound.

Especially Dolores, who heard it right in front of her.

The moonlight shadow of the supervisor loomed very close over the white sheets.

Did we get caught? Did we finally get caught?

A second stretched into a year of silence in the room.

....

Finally, the supervisor muttered to herself.

“...Wow, it's hot and there are mosquitoes in this weather.”

She held up her palm and winced.

“Oh, no. Look at me. Oops, that was loud. I'm sorry about the volunteers-”

She bowed to the already sleeping girls a few times before stepping back and then hurried out of the room.

Chirp- Thud!

The door slams shut and his footsteps echo down the hall.

After a few moments of silence, the blankets on the bed began to be pulled back one by one.

“Whoa- I thought I was going to get caught.”

“I was so freaked out, I cried a little.”

“That was a thrill, man. Haha!”

The boys and girls said as they pushed themselves up onto the bed one by one.

“....”

“....”

Some, like Tudor and Bianca, were blushing as they glared at each other like they were going to kill each other, but most seemed to think it was just a pleasant affair.

...But.

Only one person here. There was one person who was not pleased about this.

“...! ...! ...! ...! ...! ...!”

St. Dolores. The academy's student council president.

Even though the supervisor returned, she was still unable to take off the blanket and come out.

'What should I do, what should I do, what should I do, what should I do, what should I do, what should I do, what should I do, what should I do, what should I do...'

Cold sweat pours out like rain, my eyes are spinning and my vision is blurry.

...I did it. I did it.

A warm and wet feeling was already rising from the lower part of my body.

I've lost a Go game and had too much to drink. The amount was no joke. This is an overwhelming wetness that cannot even be called sweat or moisture.

I don't even know if the liquor had many vitamins and even the color......

It wouldn't be a problem if I just threw away my bed, blanket, and clothes, but I can't even hide the fact that Vikir's pants, which were close to me, were completely soaked, there was no way I could hide it.

And what about the smell?

What would happen if the world found out?

The image of the noble and compassionate student council president that I've been building up will be destroyed.

With about two years to go until graduation, it was obvious what kind of nickname would follow.

'Pisser.'

Not bad. Dolores would probably suffer from this nickname for years.

It would tarnish the reputation of the Quovadis family, and it would provide a good excuse for enemies within the family.

Dolores cringed at the prospect of such a negative future.

Is that why? She was still sobbing in her blanket, even though all the students had thrown off their covers and gotten out of bed.

She didn't even know how to look at Vikir's face, which was now on top of her.

...Just then.

Grasp!

The blanket was pulled back relentlessly.

Vikir had pushed Dolores out of the way.

There was no hesitation, no mercy.

'Ah!'

Dolores was dumbfounded, realizing that this was it.

Now Vikir would express his displeasure at having something dirty on him, and the mood in the room would quickly turn awkward.

The mood will be completely ruined, the drinks will be spilled, and there will be plenty of gossip to go around.

My head was spinning.

A cold sweat had already drenched my entire body.

My body is hot and my tongue refuses to listen.

'...Should I just jump out?'

Dolores is staring out the window, thinking the most extreme thoughts.

One word brought her back to her senses.

“No more drinking.”

Vikir's raspy bass voice drew everyone's attention.

Tudor looked puzzled as he pulled the remaining bottle from under the bed.

“What do you mean, the night is just beginning, the drinking game is just beginning!”

“No. It ends here.”

“...?”

Neither Tudor nor Sancho nor Pigi shake their heads, as it's the first time they've ever heard Vikir be so assertive.

Then.

Vikir threw off the blanket completely and stepped into everyone's view.

His pants were soaked, yellow and wet.

Everyone's eyes widened at the sight of them.

Naturally, the gaze that lingered on Vikir's lower half turned to Dolores' lower half on the bed.

The bed and the blankets, equally wet and yellowed.

The expressions on the faces of every man and woman in the room were one of horror.

Dolores covers her face with her hands as the stares fall like arrows.

Frustration, despair, shame, self-destruction, anguish, wailing, screaming, feeling her own self plummeting into the abyss of it all.

....

...But at that very moment.

There was a saving grace that pulled Dolores back from her downward spiral.

“I've been drinking and pissing myself.”

It was Vikir's touch.

Chapter 154

How to keep your night shift employees safe (1)

◆

“That's what happened. I'm sorry.”

Vikir turned around and apologized.

Dolores, blank-faced, was unable to respond.

And the others surrounding them couldn't help but misunderstand his blank expression.

“Vikir! Are you crazy! Why are you so bold!”

“The saint is in shock!”

“Aaaah! Sister, quickly go to the shower room! I will help you!”

Who in the world would pee on a saint's belly?

It was hard to believe what was happening.

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi were stunned by this unprecedented disaster.

Sinclaire and Bianca are also at a loss for words, their mouths gaping like koi fish.

Only one. Only Vikir remained calm and rational.

“A person can drink and make mistakes.”

That's what Vikir said to Dolores, trying to comfort her.

He was trying to tell her not to worry too much.

But for the other students watching, it was just too much.

“Saint. Let's declare a crusade.”

“Vikir! Get down on your knees and pray, or you're expelled!”

“A crusade! There's going to be a Crusade of the Quovadis!”

Meanwhile.

“....”

Dolores's mouth dropped open, but she couldn't say anything.

His vision was spinning.

'...What the hell is going on here? Why is everyone yelling at Vikir? I'm the one who peed.'

Thoughts raced through her mind, paralyzing her.

Panic. For the first time, she lost her cool.

Normally, she would have accepted being called a pisser, but she wouldn't have put her stigma on others.

But Dolores was in such a state of shock that she couldn't tell if this was really real or a nightmare.

That's why she's sitting on the bed with her mouth half-open, unable to speak.

She is even showing signs of temporary aphasia.

Sinclaire and Bianca are on either side of Dolores, who looks like a lost soul.

“Ms. President. Let's get you to the bathroom first.”

“Don't you guys look away! I'm going to stab you with an arrow!”

Sinclaire and Bianca scooped up the half-fainted Dolores and ran to the bathroom.

The rest of the girls looked on and began to clean up Dolores' bed.

The boys look on, unable to move.

Next. Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and the other boys surrounded Vikir and asked in disbelief.

“Vi, Vikir. Did you really pee yourself, didn't you? Please tell us you didn't.”

“You must have just sweat... explosively on your lower body, right, buddy?”

“Please, Vikir, at this rate you're not just going to be called a pisser; you pissed on a saint's belly, that's blasphemy!”

But Vikir was not listening to his friends.

He had taken on Dolores' shame for two reasons.

The first was as a small repayment for the blessing he had received from St. Dolores before his return.

Dolores, then known as the Saintess of the Battlefield, had brought countless wounded soldiers back from the brink of death, and Vikir was one of them.

Though Dolores had no memory of Vikir's name or face at the time, Vikir had not forgotten her grace in his second life.

And the second is assassination.

Quilt. I must kill him before this night is over.

In truth, I didn't have much time for such childish games.

I must finish my drink quickly.

But then the saint gave me a good excuse.

“I'm sorry, friends. When I drink, I turn into a dog.”

A dog is a dog. A hunting dog.

Vikir apologized, and his friends were surprisingly forgiving.

“Ugh, you've ruined the party. Oh well.”

“Well, it's definitely a memorable night, though.”

“ Vikir... I'll find you a good transfer school. I'll always remember it. Hik... hik hik....”

Tudor and Sancho laughed hysterically, while Pigi cried for Vikir's future.

Pigi could see how hard it would be for Vikir to do well in school now that he had been spotted by the saint, and by all the girls in this room.

...Of course.

“Then let's go back now. Sorry about the cleaning. Tell the saint to charge me for the laundry later.”

Although Vikir himself didn't seem to mind at all.

◆

Late at night.

The boys who had infiltrated the girls' dormitory had returned to the boys' dormitory under the cover of night.

Just before returning to their respective rooms, Vikir purposely lagged, alone.

“I'm going to stop by the laundry room for a while.”

He had a good excuse – he needed to wash his pee pants – so he didn't arouse suspicion.

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi patted Vikir on the back as he headed for the laundry room.

“Come on, Vikir. I am your friend, even if you turn the faith religion into an enemy. Our Spear will be your strength.”

“If you are expelled, don't worry about finding a job. I will recommend you to the Mercenary Guild of the North. With my recommendation, you should be able to get an office position.”

“Come on, guys, let's leave Vikir alone. I'm on your side, of course! I'm a commoner, but I'm sure that my family can help you if you need it!”

With that, everyone hurried into the room, as if to give Vikir some time alone.

Until the door closed behind them, they were still talking about Vikir.

What... 'Even a saint wouldn't expel him,' 'If we're going to make this a public issue, we'll have to reveal that we've been sneaking drinks at night, and that's going to hurt everyone,' 'I hope this incident stays quiet,' and so on.

Meanwhile.

“....”

Vikir returned to the laundry room, stripped off his wet clothes, and quickly changed into the outfit he had hidden away.

The Night Hound.

Wrapped in black cloth and a plague doctor's mask over his face, he looked like an unstoppable monster.

The hound is now on the hunt.

'The timing was not bad.'

Tudor and Bianca had organized the boys' and girls' meetings so well that they already knew the supervisor's shifts and patrol routes.

They had also memorized the layout and shape of each building from their volunteer work.

Vikir quickly scaled the laundry room's window ledge and scaled the opposite building's exterior wall.

He was able to find his way around with his eyes closed because he had worked so hard in the past.

Vikir scaled an old drainage pipe he had drilled, crossed the roof of a building he had repaired, and moved from building to building through a window he had installed.

The drainpipe was welded together at various joints for him to grab and climb, and the building roof was carved with recesses for him to crawl under and hide.

Even the bare walls, which originally had no windows, had red bricks cut into them for easy access.

The chimneys on the roof, the laundry room, the shower, the toilet, the hallway windows, etc.

Then.

Vikir faced a circular group of buildings that surrounded Quilt's quarters in four layers.

The first was the building 4, which housed children aged 17-19.

The second is the building 3, which housed children aged 13-16.

The third is the building 2, which housed children aged 8-12.

The fourth was Building 1, which housed the newborns.

Only after passing through these four buildings and going deeper and deeper inside did Vikir find the room where Quilt was sleeping.

Vikir slid across the roof and landed at the back door of Building 4.

When he shakes the glass window at the end of the hallway he had previously loosened, the latch comes off, and the window opens.

...Rattle, rattle, rattle-

With a ghostly movement, Vikir climbed through the window and was immediately confronted with the dark, silent corridor of Building 4.

And then.

“...!”

Vikir found a notice posted on the other side of a hallway as quiet as a tomb.

It was grim and meaningful enough to hold Vikir's gaze for a moment as he walked deeper into the hallway.

-This orphanage provides the following rules of conduct for the safety of night shift staff.

※The information below must never be disclosed to the outside world, and this Orphanage will not provide any compensation for accidents that violate these items.

Chapter 158

Familiar Faces (2)

◆

Tsutsutsutsutsuts...

Efebo's face melted away at a tremendous rate, and he dissolved into the water.

Sticky oil floats on top of the murky water, and the smell of rotting meat fills the air.

Meanwhile, Vikir and Dolores had already seen Ephebo's face before it melted.

It was a face that looked familiar to both of them.

“...Mozgus?”

Vikir muttered as he picked up a black sack floating in the water.

A bald head without eyebrows, bulging eyes, a bulbous nose, and tightly clenched lips.

The face I had seen a moment ago was unmistakably Mozgus's.

A paladin of the Quovadis, a pious priest who carried a thick Bible and led the charge against heresy.

If fate holds true, when the era of destruction arrives, the person who will have to go to the front lines and fight against demons, why are there corpses lying around here?

Vikir's brow furrowed in unresolved mystery.

'Mozgus was a human before he was turned, surely, and he was a hero who was cohabited with a thousand demons during the Age of Destruction, so how can...'

Vikir's question was answered by Dolores.

“This is not Mr. Mozgus.”

Dolores looked at what was left of Ephebo's body and shook her head.

“Mr. Mozgus had a twin brother, who, unlike us, belonged to the Old Order.”

Mozgus's older brother.

He, too, was a paladin, with a body like an iron wall and powerful divine powers.

However, he had long ago retreated to the depths of an Old Order monastery for retirement training and has not been seen by anyone since.

...As far as the world is concerned, the story goes.

“So you didn't disappear because of your hermit training, but because your body was taken over by a demon.”

Vikir swallowed hard, and Dolores furrowed her brow in concern.

“There are quite a few people in the Quovadis who are currently in the Closed Training, but... it can't be true, can it?”

“I can't guarantee anything.”

That wasn't the only problem now.

Vikir remembered that the Baskervilles' second son, Seth, was also in the closed training.

If the Baskervilles and the Quovadis were already in such a state, then any of the world's most recognizable powerhouses who were in closed training, or who had been missing for long periods of time, were also in danger.

Vikir turned and looked down at the headless body of Ephebo.

My ninth of ten.

He must have the power to turn others into demons and control them, while at the same time stealing their faces.

Most likely, Quilt's face had been stolen from someone else, too.

'By the way, how come Quilt's face resembles an actor who retired a long time ago?'

It's not hard to see why the actor retired and why we haven't heard much about him.

Vikir also knew of a powerful man who had recently disappeared from the scene, claiming to be retiring.

'When will you enter the academy? Let's match it with me. I think I'll probably enroll 1-2 years early. It would be so fun if we went to first grade together.......'

It's a tough relationship that started when they were 8 years old. If it were up to me, we would have entered the academy together.

Camus Morgue.

Seeing that face in her mind made Vikir feel uncomfortable for some reason.

She had been searching for Vikir ever since he disappeared in the depths of the Black Mountains with the Enemy.

All the while Vikir had been training in Ballak's village for the past two years.

But one day, Camus suddenly left the academy and transferred to a dark hall, and since then, she has disappeared from the world, claiming to be practicing in the closet.

Even Vikir was not entirely sure why.

“ ...We'll worry about that later. For now, it's time to stick to the hunt.”

Vikir clicked his tongue behind his mask.

Most of his troubles and worries would be solved once he succeeded in killing the demon.

Yuck.

Vikir took the black leather sack that Ephebo was wearing over his face and stuffed it into his pocket.

It was an artifact that emitted a similar kind of magic to Beelzebub's, but its concentration was relatively weak compared to Beelzebub's, about 25%.

'But if we can get the skins of Hebe, Pedo, and Geronto, that's a different story.'

Vikir was thinking to himself.

“Uh, excuse me, Night Hound.”

Dolores hesitantly called out to Vikir.

When Vikir turned her head, she opened her mouth with a look of sadness, confusion, doubt, and trust.

“If this is what's going on inside the Faithful Quovadis,... what am I supposed to believe from now on?”

Quovadis had always believed in absolute goodness.

Even though the Old and New Orders were at odds, it was believed that it was only a temporary quarrel over the sale of indulgences, and that they would eventually be united under the Rune religion.

But the destruction within the family now leads me to believe that is not the fundamental problem.

The demons are behind the Old Order.

Having seen and heard this with her own eyes and ears, Dolores felt that everything she had ever believed in was being denied.

The Quovadis is no longer an absolute.

They are easily corrupted and easily manipulated, no different from any other household.

What does it mean, moreover, for a demon to appear so directly among humans?

“...War! Demon War!”

The intelligent Dolores could sense just how much of a storm she was in the middle of.

And how long and hard a battle this mysterious creature, the Night Hound, was fighting.

“I don't know, I don't know what to believe anymore. Maybe there's more than what the eye can see...”

Dolores bowed her head, her voice lacking confidence.

She was beautiful and vulnerable in a way that would have made any man's heart flutter.

But Vikir offered no words of comfort.

“You decide what you believe.”

He just walked on, bluntly, straight ahead, as he had always done.

Just as he had always done.

◆

Vikir left the fourth building and entered the third.

Dolores was following closely behind him, though she didn't seem to notice.

The third building, which housed children aged 13 to 16, and the second building, which housed children aged 8 to 12, were connected in an H-shape like twins.

-The orphanage provides the following rules of conduct for the safety of staff working at night.

The following must never be disclosed to the outside world, and the orphanage will not provide any compensation for accidents caused by violating these items.

The same sign was posted here. The only difference is that the letters are slightly more faded.

And the deeper we went into the building, the thicker the demonic aura became.

A damp, foul odor indicated that something meaty was rotting in large quantities deep within the corridors.

A claustrophobic feeling, like digging down into a narrow, deep hole, a damp, earthen grave, weighed on my lungs along with the stench.

'There's something else in ....'

The Night Hound pushed forward with his keen sense of smell.

Dolores, meanwhile, seemed to have fully understood that the Night Hound hadn't blindly attacked the branches of the Quovadis, but had been acting with reason and principle.

And she had been actively trying to help him ever since.

“First of all, I'll let the higher-ups in the family know about this. I'm sure they'll believe me if they're New Order, not Old Order, especially some of the groups I'm involved with.”

“...Do as you please.”

With Vikir's permission, Dolores diligently composed the letter.

It was mostly about the existence of Ephebo, the fall of Mozgus, and a request for gratitude to House Indulgentia.

Dolores took a small pigeon from her bosom and tied the letter to her leg.

The addressee was Cardinal Martin Luther, head of the New Order.

If it was an Old Order figure, even his father, Cardinal Humbert, could not be trusted.

“Please hurry up, little one. I apologize for making you work at night.”

Hearing the saint's plea, the white pigeon flapped its wings and soared into the sky.

Pow!

A few white feathers fluttered in the darkness.

The pigeon, carrying Dolores' letter, soared into the sky with great speed.

...But.

Puff!

A piercing jab swooped down and split the pigeon's body in two.

Dolores' letter, too, was caught in the aura and crumbled to ash.

“....”

Vikir narrowed his eyes behind his mask. This is because the speed at which the slash flew was unusual.

Sssssss...

The smell of rotting meat mingled with the odor of moss.

Soon, two dark shadows appear in the center of the hallway connecting Buildings 2 and 3.

“Who are you!”

Dolores's expression was alert.

Suddenly, two men appeared in front of Vikir and Dolores.

Tall, lanky men, dressed in sharp suits, with black sacks over their faces.

'Pedo&Hebe'

Pedo&Hebe.

Like Ephebo, these two are Quilt's hounds.

At first glance, they appear to be high-level undead, as they both exude an unusual amount of energy.

...But there was something even more worrying than the powerful auras and odors they were emitting.

“Could those undead be people we knew in life?”

Dolores asked with concern in her voice.

Humans corrupted by the demon himself could not possibly have been ordinary beings in life.

They must have been known to the world in some way.

Vikir replied in a nonchalant tone, his eyes fixed on Pedo, Hebe, and beyond.

“Let's hope it's not ....”

Chapter 160

Familiar Face (4)

◆

Geronto.

A thin female mage.

Her long red hair tumbles out from under the black sack she wears on her face.

Dolores spoke with a stern expression.

“She's a relatively recent recruit to the Quilt, and judging by her body type, she looks quite young....”

“....”

Vikir swallowed hard instead of answering.

Then, Geronto stepped forward.

A storm of dark mana began to engulf her entire body.

...Hiss, hiss, hiss!

Complex magic circles were drawn in the air, followed by crackling flames and tiny black spikes.

The spikes pierce the floor and shoot upward, red-hot from the flames.

Anyone who touched them would be burned and cut at the same time.

Dolores was stunned by the sheer amount of mana Geronto unleashed.

“This, a magic of this class should be at least 5th... or 6th class, he must have been an incredibly talented mage in his lifetime!”

Flaming iron spikes flew everywhere.

Vikir drew his Beelzebub long enough to deflect the flying spikes.

Crackle!

The wall of fire swirled around, impeding Vikir's movement.

Every time Vikir hesitated, more spikes shot out from the floor, walls, and ceiling.

Red and black. It was a familiar sight.

Sizzle, sizzle, sizzle...

Vikir backed away from the flames that clung to his shoulders, across his back, down his sides, and to his toes.

In the meantime, the central lobby of Building 1 had been turned into a furnace.

A cauldron of melting molten iron, red-hot spikes of flame like teeth.

Crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle... Boom!

Geronto continued to summon fire and spikes from the other side of the furnace.

The flames continued to engulf the mass.

Each of the sharp iron spikes flying out of it was extremely threatening.

The air is so hot it burns your lungs if you breathe it in, and your vision is limited by the thick smoke and overly bright flames.

Pushed to the edge of the gate, Dolores called out to Vikir, who was directly in front of her.

“Night Hound, we can't even approach it at this rate!”

“....”

But Vikir didn't answer.

Instead, he stared out through the goggles attached to his mask at his enemies, the black landscape, and the red-haired mage standing beyond.

Then, with the growl of a Night Hound, he said.

“ ...I need to see your face.”

“What?”

“I need to see your face.”

Leaving Dolores with a questioning look, Vikir took a step forward.

The floor had already been transformed into a furnace of sharp metal spikes and blazing flames.

Vikir sprinted toward it.

Screech! Crunch!

Every time Vikir stepped on the ground, a metal spike shot up.

It pierced his instep or heel and came up to his knees.

Those protruding from the walls and ceiling were scorched by the flames, and gradually melted away, turning to boiling lava.

...POP! ...POP! ...POP! ...POP! POP!

The metal spikes that had sprouted from the ceiling melted away, and drop after drop of molten metal began to drip down the hallway.

Below, new spikes continue to sprout, and the flames grow stronger, raining fire and molten metal from the ceiling.

“....”

Vikir pushed forward on the thorny path, drenched in molten metal and spikes.

Puff-puff-puck!

Dozens of spikes flew at him, piercing every inch of his body, but Vikir was unfazed.

“Face.”

Rage boiled up from the bottom of his throat, hotter than the bubbling mud.

“Let me see your face.”

The smell of burning flesh, cooking blood.

Dolores was horrified to see Vikir endure this torture alone.

Why would he go to such lengths? Did he know the mage woman? And if so, what is their relationship?

The unanswered questions made her dry mouth and throat ache even more.

“...Ugh!”

Dolores squeezed her eyes shut and followed Vikir's lead.

Divine light is not very effective against elements other than darkness.

But even so, Dolores followed the path the Night Hound had blazed, plunging into a furnace of blazing fire, molten metal, and spikes.

Despite the stabbing, slicing, and burning pain in every part of her body, she pressed on, undeterred.

'Night Hound has a harder road ahead of him, and I can't whine about merely following him!'

Dolores gritted her teeth and followed Vikir, her body beginning to be covered in burns and cuts.

By this time, Vikir had reached the end of the furnace.

Meanwhile. Geronto had run out of mana, and was stumbling backwards, unable to produce any more fire and spikes.

And in front of him stood Vikir, standing tall.

Iron spikes piercing through his body, flames burning through his veins.

But Vikir didn't care about any of that, his hand reaching out.

“Take off your mask.”

Geronto's throat was clamped shut, and Vikir used his other hand to remove the black sack that covered her face.

Boom.

The very moment the black sack was removed from Geronto's head.

[Gurgle!]

Geronto spat out a bloodcurdling sound as he struggled.

The mana in his body turbulent like crazy.

Vikir realized what it was and quickly pulled his hand away and stepped back.

“W-what!”

Dolores exclaimed, barely able to hold her breath.

Quack, quack, quack!

The mana in Geronto's body that had run amok instantly turned into a giant bomb, destroying everything in its path.

...Boom!

Geronto's body, burned from the neck up, fell backwards.

Flutter.

Only a single black sack remained untorn and unburned by the explosion, lying on the ground.

“...It looks like they planted a bomb in her head.”

Dolores said, frowning.

Meanwhile.

“....”

Vikir stands, speechless.

He was staring at Geronto's body, now sprawled on the floor in front of him.

A woman's body, shrouded in black robes.

After a moment of silence, Vikir moved.

Dolores's eyes widened slightly.

“Night Hound, what are you doing....?”

She had every reason to panic.

Vikir was now undressing Geronto.

Thud, thud, thud!

The tough robes were torn to shreds by the strong grip.

The white-skinned woman was now naked.

But there was nothing obscene about it. Her head had been ripped off, and she was a corpse.

Her body was covered in patchwork marks of iron, leather, and other materials that had been pieced or sewn together.

The lack of intact flesh and bones suggests that the pieces of her body were not fully assembled when she was resurrected as an undead.

...This means that before she became undead, she died without leaving her body intact at the time of her death.

In other words, she died a very painful and gruesome death.

“....”

Vikir stared at Geronto's corpse for a moment.

Then.

“No.”

He added briefly.

Dolores asked, puzzled.

“Did you know her?”

“...I thought I did, but I guess not.”

Vikir thought of Camus Morgue in his mind.

In fact, Vikir was thinking that Geronto might be Camus.

They were the same age, the same height and build, and even the magic they used was similar.

Even the color and length of his hair was the same as the last time he had seen her.

Furthermore, Camus had not only left the prestigious academy for no reason, but also joined a dark hall known for its black magic, and had even recently entered the closed-door training.

However, after checking it himself, Geronto was not Camus.

Geronto was slightly shorter than the last Camus he saw.

There was also a slight difference in secondary sexual characteristics, with Geronto being slightly less developed.

This suggests a difference in age.

Crucially, Vikir had seen Camus naked as a child. He was eight years old when Camus burned off her clothes during a combined training exercise.

'She definitely had moles on his chest and under his collarbone.'

But there are no such marks on Geronto's body.

Her red hair, strong magic, and skill with iron and fire make her look like one of Morgue's women, but she's very different from Camus in many ways.

'...The question is, why is she here, as an undead?'

Morgue is not alone. The Baskervilles, Donquixote, and the young men of the Quovadis were also turned undead.

How far do the roots of demons reach?

Vikir realized he needed to step up his demon hunting.

Then.

“I've heard that the tombs of some of the great houses have been robbed a lot lately.”

Dolores said with a hint of concern.

At that, Vikir stroked his chin with his hand.

“Grave robbing.”

Normally, grave robbers were after the gold and silver treasures buried with the bodies.

But this case was different. The body itself was the object of the grave robbing.

“...Demonic bastards.”

Vikir picked up the fourth leather sack that had been covered over Geronto's face.

Once again, this black sack held powerful magic.

Together, the four were almost as powerful as the magic sword Beelzebub.

'What kind of artifacts are these, anyway? I'll have to investigate them later.'

Vikir clutched the four black sacks in his arms.

With that, the troublesome gateways were over.

Ephebo, Hebe, Pedo, and Geronto.

With all four hounds gone, there was truly only Quilt, the Lord of Indulgentia.

Vikir thought back to the steps he had taken to get to this point.

He'd earned his demerits within the Academy, spent the entirety of the Golden Holiday volunteering and serving as a scout.

And now, all that remained was the final goal of this assassination.

Vikir composed himself and was about to take the final step.

Clap-Clap-Clap.

From beyond the pitch darkness came the sound of applause.

“...!”

Vikir and Dolores looked up to see a familiar face.

Quilt L. Indulgentia.

He was sitting on the railing and looking down with a smile on his face.

Chapter 164

Sin and Punishment (4)

◆

A dark red sky. A flock of crows circling. A neck hanging high on a pole.

Dolores's mouth was half open at the horrific scene before her.

'Where the hell am I?'

No other battlefield in the world, no other conflict zone, to her knowledge, is this harsh and barren.

What's more, the head hanging above her is....

'Who is it?'

Dolores squinted, trying to focus.

Perhaps that neck belongs to someone very closely associated with the Night Hound.

So Dolores decided to take a closer look at the decapitated man's face.

It might help him guess the identity of the Night Hound.

But.

Cackle.

A crow swoops down and begins pecking at the severed head.

Cluck, cluck, cluck, cluck, cluck.

More crows swoop down, pecking at his throat.

Dolores swallows hard at the sight of the neck through the black feathers.

It was impossible to tell from the shape of his neck what his face had once been.

It was already so badly decomposed and pecked at by so many crows that it was all but a skeleton.

'Is this the shameful memory of the Night Hound?'

Dolores turned her head slightly to look at the Night Hound beside her.

“....”

He stood still, unmoving.

There was no way to tell if he was wearing a mask of shame or not.

Only.

“Reminds me of old times.”

The short word was still dry, and the only emotion it contained was a pungent, ashy regret.

<Name: ...ir ......Kerrville

The room, which is almost completely torn, flutters softly.

In the end, Dolores was unable to glean any information about his identity from the Night Hound's memories.

It only made her more curious and more pitiful about what he had been through.

'...What kind of life has this man led, and what kind of burden is he carrying alone?'

Just like in the past when treating plague patients together, the grave look of the Night Hound aroused even more faint and sorrowful feelings in her.

It was more than maternal love, more than just compassion for a neighbor in need, more than a saintly compassion.

Meanwhile, Vikir was looking at a scene he hadn't seen in a long time.

The old homeland.

The old world he had left behind.

He missed it a little, but he never wanted to go back.

The world line where he was executed after being falsely accused of being a traitor. The owner abandoned him even though he worked hard as a hunting dog.

'I've gotten my revenge, and there's nothing left for me to do.'

Hugo Le Baskerville, the man who cut off his own head and hung it on a pole, but it turned out to be the handiwork of Andromalius, disguised as Seth Le Baskerville.

Since he was eliminated and all the people involved in the family were hunted down and executed, the fundamental revenge is already over.

Of course, there was still revenge for Hugo Le Baskerville, but that would come later.

Ugh.

Vikir raised his sword in a casual manner and sliced through the landscape in front of him.

The blow flew, shattering its neck and sending the crows circling it away.

Black feathers fluttered in a mess.

Screech!

Caw caw

Caw caw caw

Cackle cackle cackle cackle

Cackle, cackle, cackle... cackle cackle

Ak Ak Ak Ak Ak

Cac cac cac cac

Ak Ak Ak Ak

cac cac

caw caw

The crows circled and disappeared into the sky.

The world was soon torn to shreds.

Then, from beyond the black fog, came Dantalian's snarl.

[What are you? Who are you? Why are the landscapes of my homeland in your memories?]

The laughter was gone from his voice, replaced by confusion and bewilderment.

Vikir did not answer Dantalian's question.

[...Yes. It doesn't matter if you don't answer, I'll just have to see for myself].

Dantalian opened the next sack.

The sack pulsed as if it were alive, and he pulled the next one out of its mouth.

It was 'Fear', rummaging through Vikir's memories to find the most terrifying.

Tsutsutsutsuts...

Soon, an old man walked out of the night fog.

Vikir recognized him at a glance.

“Hugo, Hugo Le Baskerville!”

A gray-haired old man. His face covered with age spots and wrinkles, countless burn marks and scars.

“Who, who is that?”

Dolores didn't recognize Hugo at all.

Of course, she did recognize him.

As a high ranking member of the Quovadis, she often exchanged pleasantries with Hugo, the iron-blooded swordman lord of Baskerville, at great events in the Empire.

But the last Hugo in Vikir's memory was a world away from the one she knew today.

The long years of war had completely changed a man's appearance.

Hugo's face, which seemed stubborn but solemn and dignified, aged rapidly within a few years after the war began.

Not only are there wrinkles and age spots, but the face itself has become more severe and harsh.

Moreover, the numerous slash marks and makeup marks on his face make old Hugo look even more murderous.

Normally, a hound should be paralyzed by the majesty of its “master,” imprinted in its bones.

But for some reason, Vikir didn't feel so scared of Hugo in front of him.

'Maybe it's because I saw you holding the Pomeranian and smiling like an idiot.......'

Hugo had even recently shaved off his mustache to suit the Pomeranian's tastes!

When the master loses his dignity, the hound stops listening.

Thus, Vikir, too, was able to let go of his instinctive fear of Hugo to some extent.

What's more, Dantalian hasn't yet accumulated enough magic to fully recreate the power of the figure in his memory.

Tsk-tsk.

Vikir pushed the aura contained in the magic sword Beelzebub to its limit and thrust it forward.

Seven teeth bite down on Hugo.

Yes, this time it was the hound biting his master.

'Not long from now.'

Vikir tore the fake Hugo's entire body to shreds before his eyes, vowing that one day he would bite him in real life.

Dolores, seeing the illusion shattered, asked Vikir cautiously.

“Excuse me..., if you don't mind me asking, who was that old man just a moment ago?”

“My father.”

“...Ah.”

Dolores remained silent.

She had seen her father in the sack of fear.

And the Night Hound had seen him in the sack of fear, too.

Dolores saw herself in the Night Hound.

Could the Night Hound see himself in her?

Dolores thought to herself, '...... I thought, 'I hope so.' If only it could be of the slightest comfort to him.

Just as he had been comforted by the Night Hound.

Meanwhile.

[Off!]

The blow that Vikir had unleashed in killing Hugo was returned to Dantalian.

[Yelp! How, how do you overcome shame and fear so easily, you inhuman thing!]

Dantalian exclaims in a blood-curdling voice.

[But! Even for you, who are so emotionless, it won't be as easy this time, ho ho ho ho!]

The last sack began to move.

'Love'. The most primal element that drives humans.

An essential, indispensable emotion that is necessary for a person to live.

This time, it was the turn of Vikir's most beloved thing to emerge from the sack.

“....”

Dolores felt herself tense up for some reason.

Although it was really immature and pathetic to feel this way in the middle of a fight against a demon of Demon King rank.

'...I'm still curious!'

Dolores cursed herself for letting her eyes wander, but she remained alert.

He would keep an eye on whatever came up.

Whether it was in preparation for a fight with a demon, or out of curiosity about the Night Hound's past, she couldn't tell.

And now.

Tsutsutsutsuts...

The sack Dantalian had left behind as a last resort opened wide.

[Hohohohoho! A guy like you is bound to break down miserably in the face of love! No matter how hard you are, you can't help but lose your composure and become embarrassed in front of the face of your loved one! It's not for nothing that romance sells well regardless of the era! Love is something that transcends everything...... uh!?]

But Dantalian's cheerful voice didn't last long.

“...!”

Even Dolores felt the same way as Dantalian for now.

Flutter.

Her eyes widened, and the sack of love opened wide in front of her.

The face of the Night Hound's beloved had emerged from the dense night fog.

Chapter 165

Sin and Punishment (5)

◆

The sack opened wide.

What came out of it was a face, the face of Vikir's beloved.

“...!”

And the moment she saw the face.

Dolores could only stare blankly.

'Isn't anyone here?'

Yes, it was.

The sack was empty.

Nothing. Nothing at all.

This only perplexed Dantalian even more.

[Nonsense! I've heard that man is an animal that lives for love! No, not just humans, but all animals have the emotion of love! But what the hell are you...!]

But Dantalian's words were cut short.

...Thud!

Vikir's sword, which had appeared while throwing away the black sack, had ferociously dug into his chest.

[Thud!?]

Dantalian stumbled backwards, spewing black blood.

All thirty-six faces contorted in disbelief.

Could it be that the magic hadn't been activated?

Maybe that's why no faces emerged from the sack?

Unfortunately, Dantalian's hopes were dashed.

The spell had been activated as normal, and the massive mana cost of the spell, as well as the massive recoil damage from the shattering of the spell, were still a burden to Dantalian's body.

Furthermore, as Vikir burrowed into Dantalian's defenseless embrace, he continued to thrust his deadly sword at him, stabbing him repeatedly.

...Puff, puff, puff, puff!

An aura so dense that it felt like a solid rushed in.

It pierced through flesh like the teeth of a beast, shattering bones and slicing through entrails.

A boiling aura slithers out from its teeth, gnawing at the very soul.

Even in the body of a demon, there is no business.

[Aghhh...!]

Dantalian backed away in a huff, clutching his ragged stomach.

Blood, flesh, and guts dripped down, covering the floor like asphalt.

[No way! How is it possible that a human has never loved anyone in his entire life! There is no such thing as a human!]

“You know, here.”

Vikir answered, short and dry.

Having been taught from a young age to always kill her emotions, Vikir grew up straight, not crooked.

In a way, that straightness may have been a form of crookedness, but he didn't know it at the time.

A killing machine, stripped of all emotion and driven strictly by command. A hound of death.

That was Vikir van Baskerville in his previous life.

A time when all things were fleeting.

Was there any room for love in a hound whose emotions had been worn and dried over five hundred crossfires, great and small? Was there anyone to teach him to love?

“....”

And Dolores, watching behind him, could vaguely imagine Vikir's reasoning.

It was the smell of life, the resonance of souls, that Vikir felt the more he opened his aura.

In the process of praying, healing, and buffing for others, priests empathize deeply with their souls.

They are affected and sometimes even assimilated by those feelings.

Dolores remembered a phrase she once heard from the Night Hound.

'Theology is the study of understanding people.'

At the time, she didn't fully understand the true meaning of this statement, but now she understands why.

At this moment, Dolores was empathizing more deeply than anyone else with the feelings and condition of the Night Hound.

'What kind of life has he led? How heavy a burden has he been carrying alone? How long has he been fighting this lonely, solitary struggle?'

Right now, she knew the Night Hound as a terrorist not long ago.

The newspaper club she belonged to had even given him a 'villain name'.

...But no.

He was a fighter, fighting the evils of this world before anyone else.

A prophet who was persecuted by the world, understood by anyone, and loved by no one throughout his life.

How far does he stand and how far does he look ahead?

How lonely, how hard, how sick, how wounded must he be?

Suddenly, a warm tear dampens the corner of her eye.

Dolores wanted to stand behind him, or beside him, as a human being.

To walk with him, to be his strength, not just along his path.

Like the legend of a priest who went on a long journey along with a warrior to subdue the Demon King a long time ago.

I wanted to stand beside him, hold him close, and comfort his scarred soul.

I wanted to wrap my arms around his thorny feet and hold him close.

I wanted to hold his slashed hands.

I wanted to let you know that you are never alone.

...But Dolores also knew.

The Night Hound was never one to lean on others.

He would never give his side to another.

He will not lean on or depend on others.

He will always stand tall, alone, and forge ahead.

Even if it is a thorny ascetic path, a path of blood and gore.

Dolores, whose soul's temporary and partial assimilation had allowed her to know it so well, felt all the more sorry for him.

Deep down, she knows that the person she hopes will come to her will never come to her.

But what a painful, agonizing, and maddening feeling it is to be a woman who knows but can't help but wait.

...But she was not the only one who was sick and tired of waiting.

[Aaaahhhhhhh!?]

Dantalian.

He really is sick and tortured.

The demon, who until now had been sitting in an arrogant posture and laughing at humans, contorted his 36 faces and screamed.

Vikir grabbed Dantalian by the hair and wouldn't let go, stabbing him here and there with his sword.

Hounds don't let go once they bite. That's how they're trained.

Vikir was trying to stay in the close combat, even as his body was being torn apart by Dantalian's waves of mana.

[Aaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!]

Dantalian picked up a random shard from Vikir's memory.

Vikir's memories are filled with cold, sharp shards.

Dangerous enough that even the demon Dantalian could cut his hand if he made a mistake.

It was like sifting through a sack full of shards of sword and glass.

'...Fuck. What kind of human has lived this kind of life!'

Dantalian's hands turned to rags, and he picked up the one fragment of memory that still had some warmth in it.

He turned it into a face that he hoped would stir Vikir's familial feelings.

[Behold, the face of one who once cared for you; can you stab me like this?]

...It happened to belong to Seth Le Baskerville.

Seth had in closed training for so long that even those within his family had forgotten his face, and Dolores could only shake her head when she saw it.

'...Who is that?'

A handsome man with white skin, dark eyebrows, and a rather aloof appearance.

His face was strikingly handsome, but his skin was bloodless, giving him an eerie appearance.

'Could he be related to the Night Hound?'

But there was no time for Dolores to study Seth's face and remember.

“Thank you, for encouraging me.”

Vikir's reaction was much quicker.

Seeing the look on Seth's face made him even more excited than he was before the regression.

So what was supposed to be one poke became two.

Puff! Puff-puff-puff! Pooh-pooh-pooh-pooh!

Seth's face explodes from the frenzied barrage of blows.

At the same time, the entirety of Dantalian's body began to be shredded into smaller and smaller pieces.

[Aaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!]

A terrifying baptism of fire as even the demon's soul is shredded.

Then.

[...Aahhhh! Don't bully me!]

One of Dantalian's many faces changed.

An age that appeared to be early teens. Beautiful blonde hair. Fair skin. Slightly sunken eyes that looked somewhat sad.

An old, crude gold necklace around her neck with the word 'Nymphet' written on it.

Suddenly.

“...!”

Vikir froze.

Dantalian didn't know what made Vikir pause, but he figured this was his chance.

[Fuck you!]

Countless faces shouted, purple tongues lolling out.

Dantalian sticks out his blade-like tongue, indeed a demon of discourse.

But.

Kurrrrr!

Dantalian's attack fails again.

Dolores, enraged by the look on Nymphet's face, intervened with another burst of white flames.

“I told you you had the wrong person.”

Dolores scorched the tip of Dantalian's tongue and immediately leapt to the Night Hound's side.

In a moment of crisis, she became even more poised and calm.

“?”

Vikir scratched his head, not sure why Dolores had suddenly become so brave.

Then, Dolores looked back at Vikir and said with a determined air.

“If it gets hard, lean on me.”

“??”

“I'll always wait for you.”

“????”

Vikir tilted his head in confusion once more.

...Pow!

The white light that Dolores had just emitted instantly enveloped Vikir's entire body.

“...!”

“...!”

At that moment, both Vikir and Dolores felt it.

Soul resonance.

It's the kind of feeling you get when you're walking down the same path together.

It was literally the kind of connection that can only happen between 'soul resonance'.

And the moment it happened.

...A flash!

The light emanating from Dolores's body exploded tenfold.

The Awakened Saint's buff.

And the one that had the greatest impact on a saint's soul.

The only being that can cause a Saint to awaken.

Those who possess a soul of the same magnitude.

The Night Hound.

He is what St. Dolores recognized as a “soul resonance”.

Whether consciously or unconsciously.

“...Aah?”

Dolores felt all the strength drain from her body.

Divine power exerted with all her might to the point where she could not even stand.

The enormous buff of power that had been unleashed was instantly absorbed into Vikir's body.

Dolores, who was naturally gifted, had an enormous amount of divine power.

Now that it had exploded tenfold, the resulting buff was no ordinary buff.

The moment Dolores' buff entered his body.

Boom!

Vikir felt the wall that had been standing over his head had been breached with a single blow.

The high, solid wall that had seemed impenetrable for so long had been torn down, and he could see beyond it.

Swordmaster.

The realm of the supreme.

The realm of the superhuman.

Chapter 166

Sin and Punishment (6)

◆

The moment Dolores saw the face of Dantalian's created Nymphet, she felt something snap inside her head.

The string of reason she had always held so tightly in her calm attitude.

The moment it snapped, she was plunged into an incredibly irrational and emotional state, and the intensity of her emotions unleashed a power she didn't know she had.

And that emotion and power is directed toward one person.

Vikir. The Night Hound!

Buffed by Dolores' spirit, Vikir saw a new world open up to him, a world beyond his own.

Swordmaster.

The amplified aura within him radiates from the hilt of his magic sword, Beelzebub.

Quack, quack, quack!

Gas to liquid, and liquid to solid.

Boiled to the limit and hardened, the aura gradually becomes a solid mass, like a lump of blood coagulated by heat.

And then it began to spin in a circle, following the laws of mana.

Kiyiyiying-

The solid aura coated on the sword rotated at an invisible speed, hovering around the edge of the sword.

It looked like countless logging saws gathered together and rotating.

Weing- Kagagagagak!

Vikir flicked the sword lightly, and the rocks, rebar, and other debris in front of him burst into flames.

Just a flick of the sword was enough to do this. It was an insane cutting power.

'...This is insane.'

Even the normally dull Vikir was deeply surprised.

Had Hugo always felt like this?

When you're at the level of a master, you can't see what's below you.

He could see why Hugo had been treating people below him like flies.

'Hugo, in his previous life, had even risen two levels from Swordmaster.'

It would soon be revealed that there were lower, middle, and higher levels of Swordmaster.

Vikir had temporarily become a lower Swordmaster with the help of a saint from the peak level of Graduator, and he would take this sensation to heart from now on.

Later, he'd have to make it this far on his own, without buffs.

Meanwhile.

[Aaaahhh!]

Dantalian was being torn apart from the inside out.

Vikir was slashing at Dantalian's body with shards of aura spinning at lightning speeds, slicing here and there.

The awl-like magic sword Beelzebub had been used primarily for stabbing, but not anymore.

Rather, the rotating form of its aura specialized more in slashing, but that didn't mean its stabbing power was weakened.

'Aside from my increased combat power, this feeling of exaltation makes me feel like I can do ... anything.'

Vikir was in a rare state of elation.

The resonance of the soul, the arrangement of the buff as if it were made by knowing the size and location of the internal organs and blood vessels of the entire body.

It was an excitement that felt like an extension of the feeling of wearing new clothes that fit and looked good on you.

The holy power of Dolores spread warmly throughout Vikir's body, accelerating the flow of mana.

Blood vessels expand and blood and mana flow more quickly.

The aura trembled, and the amplitude it produced expanded.

This was the result of the 'soul resonance' effect.

And Vikir had some knowledge of this phenomenon.

'Yes, before the regression, Dolores, Saint of Steel, only granted this buff to a few heroes in her vicinity.'

At the time of the annihilation war, there were only a handful of beings who could receive Dolores' buffs.

Dolores healed everyone without discrimination, but she was careful with her buffs.

Only a handful of Heroes had the power to maximize the effectiveness of her buffs.

Heroes like Hugo Le Baskerville, patriarch of the House of Ironblood Swordman, and Camus Morgue, patriarch of the House of Morgue and known for his nickname, The Empress Dowager.

But what about now?

Vikir has Dolores' buffs all to himself.

It meant that Dolores recognized and understood him deep down, but unfortunately, Vikir didn't know this.

He just assumed he was lucky.

Meanwhile.

Dolores was feeling her body and the Night Hound's body completely envelope and merge into one.

It wasn't just their bodies, but their souls as well.

She found great comfort and empathy in this process, even if it was only temporary.

She had never heard the Night Hound say anything particularly comforting, but somehow she felt as if he had embraced her fatigue and feelings of inferiority.

She had often wondered this.

'Everyone in the world confesses their sins and pours out their troubles to me, but... then to whom do I confess my sins and pour out my struggles?'

Sometimes it's not enough to talk to God.

You need to talk to a fellow human being.

But for years, Dolores hadn't been able to talk to anyone about her mental health.

As Dantalian said, she had to always appear dignified and resolute as someone's president, someone's manager, someone's saint, and someone's daughter.

But for once, she let go of all that and her loneliness.

She pushed all of her emotions onto the broad back of the Night Hound in front of her.

To her partner for the night, her 'soul resonance'!

Thump, thump, thump, thump!

Vikir pushed against Dantalian with a strength far beyond his usual.

Dantalian, who had been burned by the Saint's holy fire net, was unable to withstand the sudden rush of Vikir's aura.

Vikir stretched out his sword and attempted to decapitate Dantalian.

Dantalian's head, with its many faces clustered together like grape vines, and the slender neck that connected it to his body!

It was then that Dantalian made his final move.

[Brother! Help!]

Nymphet. Her face turns to Vikir.

The faces of all the children in the nursery turned to Vikir and cried out.

[Brother! I can still live!]

[If this demon dies, we die too!]

[Brother! Please! Please don't kill this demon!]

[You murderer! What do you care what happens to us!?]

And Dantalian's plan seemed to work.

Vikir's sword had slowed, ever so subtly.

Taking advantage of it, Dantalian summoned all his magic and unleashed Soul Strike.

Boom!

Dozens of Dantalian's tongues converged to form a single spear, which struck Vikir directly in the heart.

“...!”

Vikir couldn't even scream, he was bounced off the spot and sent flying, smashing two stone pillars and burying himself in a pile of debris.

“No!”

Dolores cried out in horror, but it was too late.

Dantalian pushed his bloodied body to his feet and laughed grimly.

[Ho ho ho! In a fight between the original masters, a single move is all that is needed to produce such a futile result].

Then, he strode towards Dolores, who stood there with a dazed expression.

Smirksmirksmirksmirks...

The face in front of him changed back to that of a man.

A stern-looking, middle-aged man, Cardinal Humbert, the head of the Old Order.

[Daughter, this father is a disappointment].

“...!”

[I sent you to the academy to raise the prestige of the family, and now you're doing this? Do you think it's a good idea to tell the world about the family's affairs?]

Humbert's face contorts into an expression of contempt for the pathetic.

[I thought you were a better human being, Dolores].

“...!”

Dolores' small, slender body began to shake again.

'...Night Hound.'

She had overcome Humbert's form before, when it had leapt out of the sack of fear, because the Night Hound had been by her side.

But there was no hound to save her now.

She cowered, losing her earlier confidence.

She crouches down, losing her confidence.

Tsk-tsk.

Then, Humbert's face opens wide.

His mouth, which lacks a jaw joint in the lower jaw, gapes wide open, resembling the gills of a giant snake.

Dolores in her shell, and the snake about to devour the eggs.

Dantalian smiled a sickening smile as he sought to devour Dolores.

[Now, give your face to me...rr!?]

But Dantalian's voice was cut off mid-sentence.

Pfft!

Hot blood splashed black.

Without a sound or a movement, the sword sliced through Dantalian's throat.

Vikir was now standing behind Dantalian's back with a cold gaze.

[Uh, how? I'm pretty sure it's the heart...]

Dantalian, with the face of a Nymphet, stammered.

Instead of answering, Vikir opened the inside of his black cloak to show him.

Tsk-.

There was a black sphere with an incontinence.

The egg of Madam Eight-Legs. It had protected Vikir's heart from Dantalian's spear!

Though the shell is slightly cracked, the egg is still strong.

Vikir cradled it in his arms again and looked at Dantalian.

“I don't know what else to say, but....”

With that, Vikir snapped Dantalian's neck completely.

“Go to a bad place.”

That was the last of Dantalian.

...Thud! ...Thud! Degurr!

The faces of the Dantalian fell to the ground and rolled across the floor.

However.

[Brother... Brother... I'm in so much pain...]

Dantalian's remains were still there.

Arms and limbs regenerated from beneath Nymphet's face.

It crawled across the floor, trying to get away.

But Vikir stood in its way. With an unwavering gaze.

...Boom!

The final strike pierced through the center of the nymph's body.

Only then did the Nymphet cease to move.

[....]

She raised her eyes that looked like they might close at any moment and said in a voice that looked like it might break at any moment.

[Thank you... uncle].

And then... Vikir's gaze faltered.

“....”

Vikir carefully bent down and cradled Nymphet's face in his hands.

Then Nymphet lifted her collapsing body with difficulty and wrapped her arms around Vikir's neck.

Jjog-

Nymphet then kissed Vikir lightly on the cheek.

Tsutsutsutsuts...

And then, it was all gone.

All the darkness vanished, leaving only the rubble of the ruins.

Dolores' palm came closer and wrapped around the back of Vikir's hand, who was sitting still.

“Night Hound... are you all right?”

Despite being overwhelmed by Humbert's visions only moments ago, her first concern was for Vikir's well-being.

Just then.

...Ttang-geulang!

The metallic sound of something falling through the crumbling stone pillars rang out.

Vikir and Dolores turned their heads at the same time.

Sparkle!

A golden necklace was shining brightly.

'Nymphet.'

The words stood out like a beacon in the snow.

Chapter 168

Adorable Pet (1)

◆

[Exclusive]

“I must see him again”

On the morning of January 0, Saint Dolores of Quovadis Family revealed a strong hostility towards the Night Hound.

As she bit her lip and muttered, her grave expression was suffocatingly foreboding.

Whether the Night Hounds are worthless or the Quovadis are worthless, the results will tell.

In the meantime, some have suggested that Dolores, who is usually mild-mannered and euphemistic in her language, is using such stubborn and strong language that a “holy war” could be declared. ...

Various newspapers began to circulate.

When the volunteers returned to Colosseo Academy, they were surprised to read the article in the academy's weekly newspaper.

“Wow, an article already appeared? We were at the scene of this history.”

“Hmmm. The head of the department has declared a holy war.”

“I didn't feel like I was in the mood for that. I think the article went too far.”

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi turned to the newspaper, each saying something.

Next to them, Bianca and Sinclaire nodded.

“That's what journalists do. They have to be sensationalized to get views.”

“Hey, Vikir, what do you think?”

Sinclaire asks, and everyone's eyes turn in the same direction as hers.

In the back, a few feet away from the group, stood Vikir.

“....”

Vikir walks quietly, reading a newspaper article.

His mood is somehow lonely and despondent.

“Why is he in such a mood, dude, aren't you going to come, then I'll go first....”

As Bianca opened her mouth to speak in a sarcastic manner, Tudor, who was next to her, slapped her on the side.

“Hey. Don't you have any sense of consideration?”

“What? Considerate of what?”

“How do you think Vikir feels right now?”

“...How do I know what's on his mind?”

“Tsk, tsk, you inhumane bastard. You're the same as always.”

Tudor turned his head slightly to look at Vikir behind him.

Then he turned back to look at Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire.

“Vikir, that guy, he peed in front of everyone yesterday.”

“Yeah, and on the head of the department's body.”

“...There was a lot of it.”

“Ew, that's dirty.”

“Your brother must be feeling really bad right now.”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire each chimed in with a comment.

Finally, Tudor nodded.

“Vikir, he probably wants to be alone right now.”

“I know. I would have done the same.”

“I'm afraid that hasty comfort can be poison.”

“Maybe he needs to take a piss, man, timidly. You don't think we're going to gossip or anything.”

“...No, I'd be nervous, to say the least, about that.”

Sinclaire glanced back at Vikir behind him and muttered something wistful.

“...I don't mind my hyung peeing on me.”

“? Of course you wouldn't mind. You're not fucking cheap.”

Tudor said to everyone, clapping Sinclaire on the shoulder.

“Okay. Okay, so let's leave Vikir alone for a while. Pigi, why don't you sleep in our room tonight so he can be alone.”

“Huh? Can we do that?”

“Why not? We'll go do some work together later.”

“Okay, thanks, Sancho.”

It seemed that Pigi had gotten to know a lot of the other kids through this volunteer work.

They naturally drifted away to give Vikir some alone time.

Meanwhile.

'They're going first, thank goodness.'

Vikir sneaked off to the side, watching his classmates swarm in front of him.

Thud.

Back in his dorm room, alone, Vikir sat down at his desk.

A small wreath and a stick of incense were placed on the desk.

As the incense burned, Vikir held the wreath in silence.

It was a mourning for Nymphet.

'Are you being too hard on her? Did she get a kiss?'

'No.'

'It's not 'no', it's 'don't'! She wants to give you a kiss like that!'

The conversation I had with the saint at the farewell replayed in my mind.

'If I had known it would be like this, I should have waited until then to get a kiss.'

Vikir's brow furrowed slightly.

“ ...I'll have to hunt harder.”

When the Age of Destruction arrives, innocent children like Nymphet will die in countless numbers.

It was necessary to hunt demons more diligently to prevent that.

Demons would be slain, as well as the traitors who had joined their ranks.

“To do that, we'll need to check the... harvest, right?”

Vikir pulled something out of his bosom.

It was a black leather sack, taken from Ephebo, Hebe, Pedo, and Geronto, one from each of them.

Each one of these sacks seemed to be alive, with pulsing threads beneath the black leather.

I put them together.

“This is ....”

Vikir's eyes widened slightly.

It was a single, large mask.

An oversized mask that looked like a bandana and a hood combined.

The ears had two pointy protrusions that looked like the scalp of a Doberman with its ears cut off.

And Vikir already knew what it was.

“So, this is what I get for my money.”

The mask radiated an ominous aura.

It was an artifact comparable to the Magic Sword Beelzebub.

/ Mask

-Fratricide (同族相殘) +0

-Human Face – Beast Form(人面獸心) -Off

Vikir closed his eyes and recalled the information about the artifact.

Long ago, he had seen it in a book of all things in the East.

'It was a mask that grew stronger the more you killed your own kind.'

The mask was a demonic mask that, if worn by a human being, would give them the power to kill their own kind.

I've also heard that the mask has mystical powers, granting the wearer incredible recovery and mana accumulation.

'...Although I've heard it has some side effects.'

Vikir decided to try on the mask.

Flutter.

He flicked the mask off and placed it on his head.

“...!”

Vikir felt his body change.

His tattered body and stamina from the last fight with Dantalian began to recover rapidly.

It was a level of regeneration far beyond that of a Bog Salamander.

'This is amazing!'

Although the Bog Salamander's regeneration power was excellent for repairing its tattered body, it couldn't replenish its physical or mental strength.

But this mask can do that. With this mask, he could always recharge his fatigue.

...But there was one problem.

“...?”

Vikir gasped as he realized how much smaller he had become.

“Haeg-haeg-haeg-”

He quickly turned to the mirror and saw a black dog, a black ball of fur, panicking in the room.

'This, this is me?'

Vikir gasped as he looked at his reflection.

There's a saying that 'alcohol makes you a dog', but it's only used as a metaphor.

There are other words like 'less than a dog', 'worse than a dog', 'like a dog', etc.... All of them are just metaphors.

But Vikir himself is now a real dog.

Shiny black fur, sharp teeth, cute little eyes, and pink jelly on his paws.

He looks like a puppy.

'Wait, this is a side effect of the mask? Oh, no!'

I exclaimed to myself.

“Grrrr-”

The only sound that comes out of my throat is the sound a puppy makes when it has to poop.

/ Mask

-Fratricide (同族相殘) +0

-Human Face – Beast Form (人面獸心) -On

The artifact's status is a little strange. Vikir felt the artifact turn from off to on.

Vikir quickly touched his neck with his forepaw.

Fortunately, there were still traces of the mask.

When Vikir showed his will to take off the mask, it fell from the flesh and skin and slithered away as if it had a will.

/ Mask

-Fratricide +0

-Human Face – Beast Form -Off

Off again.

Soon enough, Vikir regained his human form and stood naked in front of the mirror once again.

Vikir chuckled as he looked at the clothes on the floor.

“It would be nice to take off all my clothes at once before washing.”

He pulls himself together and puts on the mask again, and this time he doesn't turn into a dog.

There's a clear line between on and off, so perhaps the mask can change when the wearer wants it to and not when they don't.

Vikir took off the mask and kept it.

'The ability to turn into a dog at will. More of a sub-ability than a side effect, I suppose.'

The ability to turn into a dog would be useful in many ways in my future career as a Night Hound.

Not only would it make me much more resilient, but it would also help me escape from prying eyes.

'...Let's see, was it possible to have a pet inside the academy?'

Luckily, there is no rule that says you can't have animals inside the academy's dormitories.

Many students have owls, pigeons, turtles, hamsters, etc.

However, they were not allowed to have large animals that could cause damage to their surroundings, which meant bears, elephants, etc.

Just as Vikir was looking through the book of dorm rules.

Pozak-

A sound caught Vikir's attention.

“...?”

The sound of something small and insignificant breaking.

Vikir turned his head to see what it was.

It was coming from his coat hanging in the corner of the room.

He dug into his pockets and found something amazing.

A Madam Eight-Legs Egg.

The black sphere was getting incontinent.

“Ah, so this is the one that blocked Dantalian's spear at the end.”

I knew it was unexpectedly hard and bouncy, but I didn't think it would be able to withstand a demon spear.

But now that I look at it, it wasn't even damaged.

Crack, crack, crack!

The shell was cracking.

'Even the mother, Madam Eight-Legs, dissolved her eggs in her acidic saliva, so they were resistant to the shock....'

Vikir stared at the egg in disbelief.

And then.

Bam!

The shell cracked completely.

The thing inside opened its eyes for the first time and looked at Vikir.

“...?”

Vikir shook his head.

Inside the cracked shell, he could see something burnt, like a piece of bread.

It was a creature he'd never seen before.

And the creature, upon waking, saw Vikir for the first time.

Vikir shakes his head, and the creature shakes his head back, mimicking Vikir's behavior.

Vikir was a little nervous.

Though small and insignificant, this was clearly the young of Madam Eight-Legs, the reigning 'depth nightmare'.

Vikir had nearly died many times trying to hunt the giant spider.

But.

Amazingly, the dust-like thing leapt right into Vikir's arms.

He rubbed his face in Vikir's arms and started making the most unexpected noises.

[Woof- haeg haeg- kkingkking-]

It was like a newborn wolf pup.

Chapter 170

The Anti-Columnist (1)

◆

Vikir took the article from Pigi.

[Exclusive] 'The Night Hound', the birth of an unprecedented villain who roams the Imperial Capital!

-The Night Hound has shown up again. The nature of the threat has remained unclear until recently, when a terror like no other has swept across the Imperial Capital. Nothing is known about the Night Hound, whether it is an individual or an organization, or what its purpose is, and no family, not even the Imperial House, has been able to uncover it. All eyes are now on who will be the first to uncover the identity of this vicious villain and bring him to justice.

The seven great houses of the Empire – Baskerville the Ironblooded, Morgue the Mage, Donquixote the Spearman, Usher the Archer, Leviathan the Poisonous, Bourgeois the Tycoon, and Quovadis the Faithful – have organized a hunt to capture the terrorist, and the Imperial Capital has placed a bounty of 1,000,000,000 gold on the head of the Night Hound. ...

And underneath the newspaper, you can see a few pictures stuck to it, animated by magic.

The newspaper was published by a large newspaper outside of the capital, and the pictures showed the locations where the Night Hound had raided, selecting only the branches of the House of Quovadis, most notably the Old Order.

Naturally, the orphanage at the bottom, run by the Indulgentia family, was also in the picture, and Vikir could be seen in it.

Of course, Vikir is just a tiny figure in the corner of the photo, flanked by Tudor and Sancho. Pigi, Bianca, Sinclaire, and others were also in the picture, so there wasn't much room for error.

“Look, Vikir, we're in the papers! I'm having one of those media days!”

Pigi was thrilled to be featured as a passerby in this tiny photo.

But it's only for a moment, and Pigi soon grows sullen.

“Ugh. Come to think of it, this is a picture of the scene of the worst disaster ever, and I can't believe you like it. I'm the devil....”

“Calm down. The guy who caused the disaster is the bad guy, not you.”

Vikir patted Pigi on the shoulder and went back to reading the paper.

“ ...Hmm. No mention of a saint declaring a holy war.”

“Uh-huh. Strange, that didn't make the paper. It's also missing the part about the attack on the Quovadis Old Order faction, and all the sins she's been granting indulgences to society's leaders, and the sins they've pardoned. Why isn't that in there?”

Vikir smiled dryly at Pigi's question.

That's what the press is for.

A trumpeter for the powerful.

A dog barking for a more appetizing piece of meat.

It is the law of the wild that you bite off more than you can chew.

'Cardinal Humbert's breath must be that strong. Or maybe it was 'above him'.'

No matter where you look in the newspapers, you won't find anything about the Old Order's scandalous behavior.

However, in order to cover up this situation, they have made one 'Night Hound' a public enemy, and they're biting hard to cover it up.

Pigi's next words made Vikir nod.

“Oh, by the way. Did you hear about this week's club assignment? Our advisor wants us to each write a column condemning the Night Hounds' acts of terrorism. It's supposed to be a simple current events piece. If it's good, he'll publish it in the Academy's newspaper, even if it's from a first-year. ....”

It seems that the Academy has decided to join the hunt for the Night Hound.

'I suppose it's best to go with the flow for now, to avoid suspicion.'

Vikir could accuse the Night Hound better than anyone else.

He knew his misdeeds better than anyone.

“Is this a column... where I can write down the most outrageous things I hear?”

Vikir took out a pen.

And then he began an arduous (?) battle with himself.

◆

An angry voice rang through the Academy's newspaper department.

“Why was my column killed?”

Dolores. Student Council President of Academy Colosseo and head of the newspaper department.

She was now calmly protesting to Professor Banshee Morgue, the newspaper's advisor.

“Do you not know ...?”

Professor Banshee's eerie eyes shine through his dark hair.

A pair of one-eyed glasses hangs precariously from the tip of his hawkish nose.

Professor Banshee tossed Dolores's column onto his desk.

What is the true antithesis of The Night Hound?

-There were more than half a dozen branches of the Quovadis family that the Night Hounds raided.

Prof. Banshee said in a blunt tone.

“The Academy is politically neutral. We can't publish such biased current affairs commentary.”

“I didn't say it was biased, I wrote the facts!”

“Facts? Didn't Cardinal Humbert of the Old Order deny all of this, and the leaders of society on the 'indulgence list' have said it's not true.”

“That's a lie!”

“It could be the truth. Missing one thief shouldn't make ten wronged people. I thought that was your usual belief?”

“....”

Dolores clenched her teeth so hard that blood stood in her throat.

Professor Banshee continued.

“It's also no secret that you're the Academy's student council president and head of the newspaper department, and that you're a saint of the Quovadis, the religious saint at the center of this controversy, and that the Quovadis saints are, for the most part, members of the New Order.”

“....”

“So, do you think it's okay for you to make your own arrangements and write such a biased article, or not?”

Then a line of blood stood on Dolores's forehead.

She turned to face Professor Banshee.

“The Academy's rules state that 'all students admitted to the Academy are equal' and 'are not influenced by their status outside the Academy'.”

“....”

“Although I am a member of the Quovadis family, and am affiliated with the New Order, that is only a status outside of the Academy. While I am a student at the Academy, I am simply Dolores, a normal human being, and a student of the Academy. I am also free to express my opinions about the Quovadis.”

This time, Professor Banshee was silent.

“....”

“....”

Dolores and Professor Banshee's gazes locked together.

Finally, Professor Banshee sighs.

“I see. I admit it.”

“...?”

Dolores tilted her head, and Professor Banshee's brow furrowed.

“There's a letter from the Quovadis sent to the Academy.”

“A letter?”

“Yes. It's a press release for this story.”

“...!”

A press release. That's a way of predetermining the direction of a story.

Professor Banshee shook his head.

“They want us to focus mostly on the horrific acts of terrorism committed by the Night Hounds and interviews with their victims, and to keep keywords like 'Quovadis,' 'Old Order,' and 'New Order' to a minimum, or not at all.”

“That's ridiculous! That's trying to control the neutrality of the Academy!”

“Well, it is. The dean is quite troubled by it.”

“Is Cardinal Humbert that powerful? So much so that even the Dean of the Academy is in trouble?”

“If it were only Cardinal Humbert, you wouldn't have listened to me in the first place, would you?”

Dolores' expression hardened at those words.

Above Cardinal Humbert. There is only one such being in the Quovadis.

The Pope. The oldest and most exalted of the classical saints.

'...How can he?'

He is the one who will not lose his integrity, even if everyone else has fallen.

How is this happening?

'There's been a lot of talk lately about how the Pope's judgment has been a bit blurred lately due to his old age... Could Cardinal Humbert be taking advantage of that and blurring the Pope's eyes and ears?'

Dolores had a new cause for concern.

When she was silent, Professor Banshee tapped his finger on the article on his desk.

“And what... all this aside, your column doesn't belong in the paper in the first place. It's too politically biased, and I can't help but get the impression that you're secretly favoring the Night Hound.”

“So what do you think you're going to put in that empty space? The theater club's new release, the sports club's lead-in to the big game, the breathtaking backside of the Academy's cover girl?”

“Don't be sarcastic, Dolores. I'm the professor, you're the student.”

With that, Professor Banshee opened a drawer and pulled out a piece of paper.

It was a column.

“....”

Dolores's eyes narrowed.

“The Night Hound,” a viciousness beyond measure.

-The Night Hound has crossed the line. Your sins against the imperial family and the Seven Houses have reached the skies...If you listen to the cries of countless people who have been unfairly harmed...... Soon the fearsome spears, swords, arrows, and magic will become the maces of justice and bring you to the judgment seat......Having seen the Night Hound in full force on the night of the tragedy at Indulgentia Orphanage, I can say with confidence that... turning yourself in now and waiting to be hanged may be your last chance for a peaceful end!

Professor Banshee said.

“I'm going to put this column in the newspaper instead of yours.”

“It's a shoddy piece of writing, with no evidence, no objectivity, no reasoning, just an appeal to emotion. ...It's vague in wording and overly emotional.”

Dolores said in a rare use of strong language.

These were probably the worst words she could muster.

But Professor Banshee shook his head, a wry smile tugging at one corner of his mouth.

“I don't think it was very well written, either. But it's properly condemning, properly appealing, and properly agitating, so it's the most appropriate thing to say at this time. And it's an eye-witness report, so it has some credibility.”

“....”

“Anyway, with that out of the way, the midterm practical is coming up soon, so do your best, and remember, you're supposed to be studying, right?”

Professor Banshee rose from his seat and strode past Dolores, out of the room.

Dolores bit her lip.

The disaster at House Indulgentia the other day was enough to make her furious, especially after spending the night with the Night Hound.

'The Night Hound isn't bad, it's the Quovadis, and the demon that lurked within!'

How many such demons are there in the world?

How hard a fight has the Night Hound had to fight so far, and how much more will it have to fight?

'You can't help it, but you try to hinder and suppress it....'

But there is no way to expose the demon, its collaborators, and those who are unknowingly being used all at once.

Even if there were, it would take too long.

The Night Hound I met once told me that time was running out.

The frustrating conversation I had with Professor Banshee today made sense all at once.

Why he'd become a vigilante, why he'd risked his life to kill demons one by one.

“I can't do this, I have to help him.”

No matter how much you write in favor of the Night Hound, it doesn't really help.

It was time to take up the sword, not the pen, to help him now that he had come down from the top to the bottom.

“I'd rather find the Night Hound on my own. I must see his face and know his name, so I can help him.”

Saint Dolores was determined. She would go to meet the Night Hound herself.

To do so, she needed to gather as much information as she could.

As much information as possible about the Night Hound's identity.

“....”

Dolores' gaze fell to the paper on the desk.

It was the column that Professor Banshee had chosen in place of hers.

An article full of criticism that harshly condemns the Night Hounds.

Dolores' brow furrowed as she read it.

It was an ugly, low-class article, but one phrase caught her eye.

'The Night Hounds, a viciousness beyond measure.'

-The Night Hound has crossed the line. Your sins against the imperial family and the Seven Houses have reached the skies... If you listen to the cries of countless people who have been unfairly harmed...... Soon the fearsome spears, swords, arrows, and magic will become the maces of justice and bring you to the judgment seat....... Having witnessed with my own eyes the full force of the Hounds of the Night on the night of the tragedy at the Indulgentia Orphanage, I can say with confidence... that turning yourself in now and waiting to be hanged may be your last chance for a peaceful end!

“You mean you saw it with your own eyes?”

For context, when the writer of this column saw the Night Hound, it was clearly right after all the disaster had ended.

That means he saw the Night Hound more recently than Dolores.

'Perhaps I have seen the face behind the mask of the Night Hound.'

Dolores's mind raced.

If this column were to be published in the newspaper, there would probably be a flood of reporters trying to interview the author.

Luckily, Professor Banshee had anonymized the column's authors to prevent this, and Dolores was able to identify the contributors to the column, which had not yet been published in the newspaper.

'It's an abuse of power, but it's necessary!'

It was necessary for the sake of justice.

Dolores turned the column over and found the name of the person who wrote it.

Suddenly, she recognized a familiar name.

Chapter 172

The Anti-Columnist (3)

◆

“Who is this, a bunch of fools from Cold Class?”

Granola de Leviathan.

He is a skinny, tall, and somewhat hate male student of the Cold Class.

He comes from the extremely powerful House Leviathan, one of the Seven Great Houses of the Empire, and was also the runner-up student at this year's Hot Class.

He looked at Tudor and sneered.

“What are you so afraid of? You're so shaky, I can feel the vibrations all the way up here.”

“You're crazy.”

Tudor cut through Granola's sarcasm with familiarity.

But Granola didn't stop.

“Hoo-hoo-hoo. I overheard you discussing the Night Hound. If you're so cowardly, how can you claim to belong to the prestigious Colosseo Academy? You're pathetic.”

“Well, he's seen the Night Hound himself.”

Tudor said, pointing to Vikir.

Granola smiled wryly.

“His name is Vikir, and he's seen the Night Hound with his own eyes?”

“His name is Vikir.”

“Are you showing off your memory by remembering the name of a lowly commoner?”

Granola looked at Vikir with a mixture of interest and disdain.

Then she shrugged and said.

“Whatever. Don't tremble too much at the Night Hound, my weak and pitiful comrades. It's said that the incompetent are cowardly, but it's still ugly to look at. If the Night Hound were to appear at the Academy, I will personally come to your aid and protect you, even you insignificant brats.”

“What a fucking concept. Dude, we were saying the same thing until we saw the tragedy with our own eyes, but according to the newspaper reports, the Night Hound is at least an advanced Graduator. What makes you think you can handle a Graduator?”

“Whoa, whoa, whoa – you believe those articles straight out of the paper, you naive bastards. Rumors are inflated. I don't think a coward who hides behind a mask would be in such lofty heights. ...And!”

Having finished speaking, Granola stirred his palm and slapped his companions behind him.

At that moment.

...Push!

A pale black mist began to envelop Granola's body.

It was the paralyzing poison.

The poison mixed with mana and sprayed out like a mist of water, causing Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi to jump back in fright.

“Granola, you lunatic! Are you trying to show off your skills in school?”

“It's just a little tease, just a little demonstration of my mighty skills.”

In reality, Granola's poison, and the amount of it, was nothing to sneeze at.

A paralyzing poison that would leave you tingling and stiff for a few minutes if it touched you.

But the image of the Leviathan, an ultra-poisonous cancerous creature with a mastery of all kinds of poisons, makes everyone shrink back in horror.

...Only one. Except Vikir.

“...?”

At first, Vikir takes a step back, too.

What?

[Whoops-]

There was a being that sucked in the black mist spraying at Vikir.

The cub dangling like a watch from his left wrist saw the poisonous mist that Granola had sprayed and immediately began to breathe it in.

...Horrorock!

The poisonous fog disappeared in the blink of an eye, with no sense of being sucked in.

It was like a food fighter inhaling a chopstickful of ramen.

[Kkeoeog – haeg – haeg -]

The cub devoured the weak paralyzing poison, letting out a small burp.

Then it sticks its tongue out again and hacks like it always does.

Thank goodness, Vikir thought, that he'd gotten some food for the cub this time.

'Granola? That means he's from House Leviathan, so he must have a lot of poison.'

Vikir began to watch Granola carefully.

Meanwhile.

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi just stared, unable to comprehend what had just happened.

“What happened? Where's the poison Granola just sprayed?”

“It just suddenly disappeared.”

“Ew, I'm so scared. Was it a fake?”

Even Granola was looking around a bit surprised.

“Huh? What happened, where did my poison go?”

“You sprinkled it, why are you surprised, aren't you a fool?”

Tudor sarcastically asks, and Granola gulps, then comes to his senses.

Granola retorted, stumbling slightly.

“You have just done this body a favor deeper than the abyss. I didn't want to waste my poison on a bunch of heartless fools with muscles up to your brains.”

Then, Granola's cold, dark gaze turned to Vikir and Pigi.

“Apparently, you're a bunch of ragtag commoners who don't look like they're even in the lower ranks of Expert. I can see the level of Cold Class you're working for, and it's so boring it makes me want to die.”

Currently, the Academy's freshman class averages between an Expert Lower Intermediate and an Expert Upper Intermediate, and the graduating class averages an Expert Upper Intermediate.

Despite being only 18 years old, two years younger than their classmates, Tudor, who was already at the advanced level of Expert, and Sancho, who was at the Intermediate level of Expert, were exceptional geniuses.

Pigi was in the Lower Expert class, and while he was quite talented outside of the academy, he was below average inside of it.

Then Tudor, the leader of the pack, stepped forward.

“Don't insult my friends, Granola.”

“Hoo-hoo, you can tell a man's level by the friends he keeps. I can tell your level by the friends you hang out with.”

Granola didn't back off despite Tudor's threats.

Behind him, Granola could hear his colleagues, the elite of the Hot Class, giggling.

“Don't you insult my academy with your lowly, inferior skills. Well, this midterm examination will prove it all.”

“The midterm practical is just the first test you'll face, it's not meant to prove anything. It's just a record of how you're doing so that you can improve.”

“Shut up, midterms are like murder to me. Take it seriously, so I can have the satisfaction of crushing you as you flounder with your shoddy, shallow talent.”

Then.

“Hyung- what are you doing there?”

A voice called out to Vikir as he approached.

Sinclaire.

A commoner, but the head of the Hot Class, she was coming this way.

As soon as she reached Vikir, Sinclaire smiled and asked.

“Did you finish that book you borrowed from the library the other day?”

“You mean Raising Spiders?”

“Yeah. I've been reading some books about it. Want to discuss it later?”

“No thanks.”

“Why? Weren't you studying them to use later in the practical monster strategy class?”

“No.”

“Then why are you studying ahead of time? Let me know so I can ace the written exam.”

Sinclaire's eyes were filled with sincere eagerness and curiosity as she looked at Vikir.

Seeing this, Granola's expression twisted into a complex.

“Tsk, the only option for these insignificant commoner bastards is 'solidarity'. These pathetic people, whose only way to survive is to tangle with each other in crude grassroots.......”

He stopped talking and called out to Sinclaire.

“Hey! Sin, sin, sin...... Claire! You're disgraceful about Hot Class and doing it all by yourself! Don't do that, come here! If it's handwritten, I'd rather tell you! Not as a favor to you by any means, but as a way of protecting the image of the Hot Class, because even though it's only temporary, you're still the head of the Hot Class, and if you hang out with the Cold Class bastards, it'll make the Hot Class look bad...!”

But Sinclaire just blinks wide-eyed and shakes his head.

“Who are you?”

“What, you don't know me, you ignorant Sinclaire! I am Granola de Leviathan, the current Vice-Head of the Hot Class! The third son of House Leviathan, vice-head of the Academy's Hot Class, and future head of the student council! How can you not recognize me, a highly-accomplished nobleman, and a brilliant student, while remembering the name of that lowly commoner, Vikir or Vikir? If you're just pretending not to remember my name for fear of losing your position, I'd tell you to stop futilely resisting your coming fate!”

Then Sinclaire said hesitantly, with a look of great embarrassment on her face.

“I, I don't know...”

“....”

“I'm sorry, I'll try to remember in the future, Kurukuru-ssi.”

Then Granola looked shocked once again.

“...I can't believe it. How do you not know me?”

“Calm down, Granola. That girl is playing mind games on purpose.”

“That's right, how could she not recognize you. This is what lowly commoners are....”

Granola's shoulders look poisonously slumped as his companions chuckle.

◆

Meanwhile.

Out in the hallway, Vikir's group emerged near the main staircase.

“See ya then, bro.”

Sinclaire waves to Vikir, then heads for the library.

When it was just the four of them again, Tudor looked irritated.

“Ugh, Granola, that arrogant bastard. I'm going to kick your ass at midterms.”

“You're right. Too bad they don't have a cadet-by-cadet dueling course for the first-year exams.”

Sancho, who usually didn't join in the badmouthing of others, unusually agreed.

Just then, Pigi poked Vikir in the side.

“Vikir, what happened?”

“What.”

“Sinclaire.”

“What.”

“Sinclaire.”

“I mean, what.”

Vikir's questioning look brought question marks to the heads of Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi, who were watching.

“You two were up to something?”

“Either that, or she's not interested in anyone else's business, so why would she be so hard on you.”

“Exactly. I could see the honey dripping from the way she looked at you earlier.”

But when his friends raised their suspicions, Vikir was adamant.

“There is no such thing.”

His friends looked a little sour.

When Vikir denied the rumors of a romantic relationship or a relationship, the topic turned again to the story of the Night Hound.

It's a hot topic that's been swirling around the Imperial Capital these days, and my friends seem to be just as interested.

“The Night Hound is really scary, though.”

“If he's a Graduator, he could easily join the Knights Order, so why is he a villain?”

“There's got to be a story, or he's just a real exhaust homicidal maniac.”

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi chat for a while.

Just then, Tudor tapped Vikir on the arm and said playfully.

“Hey, Vikir, aren't you the Night Hound?”

“....”

Vikir merely wiggles his eyebrows.

“Why would you think that?”

Tudor laughed at Vikir's serious question and said without thinking.

“Well, you were the only one who fell backwards on the way back to the dorm, so you're the only one without an alibi.”

“....”

“Well. I mean, I did say that we all went back to our rooms and fell asleep when the guards asked for a statement... but weren't you actually in the laundry room at the time, washing your pants? Hahaha-”

“....”

“Huh? Meh, I'm sorry. I was just kidding, I didn't think you needed to be so embarrassed... I didn't realize you still cared about that, sorry.”

Tudor laughed and then apologized for wanting to get sick.

Vikir smiled back.

Only then did Tudor laugh again.

“Oh, come on, man, why are you so red, you're scaring me! You're even scarier because you're so expressionless!”

“Tudor. You were bad. I'm sure the memory of that still scars Vikir.”

“Right.”

Sancho and Pigi reprimanded Tudor as well, and Tudor bowed his head to Vikir and apologized.

It is difficult for a man who is the eldest son of the high-ranking Donquixote family to be this flawless.

Vikir laughed dryly, remembering the fairness, justice, and childlike innocence of Tudor before his regression.

But he had to make sure he had an excuse.

“I'm not the Night Hound, he's a Graduator-level monster, and I'm an inferior who can barely pass for an Expert.”

“No, don't be ridiculous, I'm just kidding....”

Sancho and Tudor nodded in agreement.

“That's right. There's no way Vikir would be such a vicious villain.”

“That's right, Vikir, let's improve our skills and take down such a villain ourselves!”

Finally, Vikir nodded in agreement.

“...Yes. Villains like the Night Hound will be punished one day.”

It was a bone to pick with himself.

Just then.

“Euhum-Euhum!”

As soon as Vikir finished speaking, a loud coughing sound was heard from the stairs just above.

...?

Everyone looked up in surprise.

There was a familiar face staring back at them.

Student Council President of Colosseo Academy, head of the newspaper club, Ryukeion, and a member of the Faithful Quovadis.

It was Dolores.

Chapter 178

Midterm Random Defense (2)

◆

The triplets of the Baskervilles, who appeared out of nowhere, spoke to Vikir in a very stern manner.

“Hey, commoner. Hurry up and follow us. It's a group test, so we need to get this together beforehand.”

Highbro jerked his chin at Vikir in an arrogant manner.

“....”

Vikir silently carried the triplets' baggage. He looked like a porter.

He was just about to follow Highbro.

“Wait, Vikir.”

Someone stood in his way. It was Tudor Donquixote.

He turned to Vikir and spoke in a low voice.

“I'm not trying to ignore you, I'm just so angry. Can you let me talk to them for a minute?”

“?”

Vikir stood there, unable to understand.

Taking that as permission, Tudor walks toward the Highbro, his eyes narrowing.

Then he spoke in a low voice that only he could hear.

“Who do you think you are to tell my friend what to do? Vikir is not one of your men.”

“Huh?”

“And you carry your own baggage. There is no distinction between nobles and commoners in the Academy.”

Underneath Tudor's calm voice, searing anger burned.

Highbro looks back at Tudor in disbelief.

Behind him, Middlebro and Lowbro glared at Tudor.

Then.

“That's right. Vikir is a friend of ours. If you want him as a subordinate, try us first.”

“That's right, that's right, who are you to treat Vikir like a servant!”

Sancho, a large man, came to stand beside Tudor.

And beside him was a stern-faced Pigi.

Shake, shake, shake......

Pigi's legs were trembling, but he hadn't taken a step backward.

(This was a 180-degree change from the time before Vikir's regression, when Pigi had been pinned down by Highbro and held at his feet.)

Tudor shrugged and stepped in front of Highbro.

“I don't know what you're up to, but don't try to force Vikir to pick a team. He's supposed to be in the same group as us.”

“...Are these assholes crazy. Who said anything about forcing anyone?”

Highbro put his hands on his hips in disbelief.

But, as was the case with the Baskerville hounds, Highbro could not hold out for long.

Sssssss...

Tudor froze in his tracks at the sharp killing intent emanating from Highbro.

Tudor is currently tied for first place in Class A of Cold Warriors, along with Bianca, the current Cold Warriors' overall head of the class.

However, Highbro, in Class B, is ranked third overall in the Cold Warriors, far from being inferior to Tudor or Bianca.

Behind him are the fourth-ranked Middlebro and fifth-ranked Lowbro.

On the other hand, we have the #1 Tudor, the #6 Sancho, and the unranked Pigi.

It was inevitable that they would be outmatched.

“...Would you like to play? Will you beat me again?”

“...You think you can beat me?”

Tudor Donquixote and Highbro Le Baskerville stood face to face, teeth bared.

Donquixote, the spearman, and Baskerville, the iron-blooded swordsman.

The spears of empire, and the iron blooded swordman were about to collide.

At that time. There were those who joined the side of Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi.

“Who are you to persecute our brother?”

“It's not a pretty sight to see you all huddled and snarling. What are men....”

Sinclaire and Bianca joined them, and Tudor's face brightened.

Sinclaire and Bianca are the leaders of the Hot and Cold Class, which means they add a tremendous amount of power.

Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro's faces hardened even more.

“Persecution. We're just....”

“Just....”

“Just....”

The triplets opened their mouths in anger, but were forced to shut them.

“Enough.”

Vikir stepped forward.

Vikir stood with his back to the Baskerville triplets.

“I'm not being forced to go. It's a real agreement, and we're in a group together.”

“...What? Really?”

“Yep. They said they needed my knowledge of monsters and wanted me to join them first. That was weeks ago.”

Not much to say then.

Tudor rubbed at the base of his nose in annoyance, then whispered in Vikir's ear.

“You're not really being bullied or anything, are you?”

“Nope. I'm fine.”

“Well, in that case, just let me know if you're having a hard time.”

“Thanks.”

Vikir nodded, and Tudor stepped away, looking unhappy.

Sinclaire twiddled his thumbs ruefully.

“Hyung, are you really in the same group as those guys?”

“Yeah.”

“Why? Are you close to them?”

“Kinda.”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire all shake their heads in unison at Vikir's answer.

As far as they knew, Vikir hadn't socialized with the Baskerville triplets since he'd started school.

So where did they get so close?

“...You don't look like you're very close, are you really being bullied?”

Tudor muttered under his breath as he watched Vikir's back as he carried the triplets' baggage like a porter.

He was worried that something bad might happen to the weaker Vikir.

◆

Tudor was right.

Vikir was not very friendly with the Baskerville triplets.

And the bullying was real.

...Albeit with the subject and object reversed.

A back alley deserted.

“Good luck.”

Vikir opened his mouth to speak, and three responses came out of it in quick succession.

“Yes!”

“Yes!”

“Yes!”

Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro answered in a rumbling voice as they stretched out on their stomachs in a fetal position with their heads on the floor.

Vikir was perched on Highbro's back.

“You.”

Vikir looked down at Highbro and opened his mouth.

Highbro, his head on the floor and dripping with sweat, flinched as if he had heard the Grim Reaper's call.

Aah!

His reddened face turned white with blood.

The beads of sweat that had been dribbling down his cheeks are back in his pores.

He didn't have to look to know that Vikir's gaze was fixed on him.

The back of his head felt chilled, as if the blade of an awl had touched it.

Vikir asked the question in a flat, emotionless voice.

“What hound bares his teeth without his master's permission?”

“......It has to be boiled.”

Highbro replied in a crawling voice.

What would happen if a hound ignored its master's wishes and bared its teeth at the prey?

The hunt is bound to fail in all likelihood.

For the hunter, a failed hunt doesn't just mean missing the prey.

The hunter can become the hunted at any moment. That's why hounds must always obey their master's commands. Unless they want to be hunted alongside their master.

Vikir stepped down from Highbro's throbbing back.

“Wake up.”

“Wake up!”

“Wake up!”

“Wake up!”

As the triplets scrambled to their feet, Vikir spoke from behind them.

“From now on, any fighting that is not authorized by me is forbidden. Not even the slightest bickering. For the rest of your lives.”

“Yes!”

“Yes!”

“Yes!”

The Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro answered in unison.

Their faces were bright despite their punishment, and that was because of the last words Vikir had spoken.

'For the rest of your lives.'

What does that mean?

'...Means you're going to take us for life!'

They had sworn an oath of loyalty to Vikir when they were in Baskerville, and now they were fully reborn as Vikir's Trident, not Baskerville's Trident.

It was Vikir who had recommended the triplets to Hugo and gotten them into the Academy in the first place.

No longer were they always on the run, wondering when they would be abandoned by the family.

A dog is a hundred times more courageous when they are sure of their master and have been promised that their master will not abandon them.

What's more, they had witnessed Vikir's fight with Madam Eight-Legs, so they had some idea of his true strength.

He has reached this level at just 18 years old, so what will it be when he get older?

The triplets were convinced.

That their master would one day swallow Baskerville whole.

And by extension, the entire world.

That's why they were so happy and willing to pledge their allegiance to him.

For as a dog is blessed to have a good master, so is a knight blessed to serve a great lord.

Meanwhile.

Vikir said to the triplets.

“I don't really like being noticed by people. I happened to get a little carried away, but I'm not in trouble anymore.”

The triplets nodded believingly.

“We'll take care of the midterms.”

“We'll carry it.”

“We'll carry.”

The triplets said they would do the rest as long as Vikir, the archer, made a good one-deal behind them.

All Vikir has to do is hide in the back and passively takes the last hit while the triplets run wild up front.

That way, he'll get a decent grade on the test and stay out of sight.

Highbro explained to Vikir the ins and outs of the entire test.

“When our group 69 takes the field, the virtual reality circle will be activated, which will turn the area around you into a dungeon and monsters will swarm around you. The poison they release is diluted, but it's real and dangerous if you allow too much of it into your body. But don't worry, my lord. We will guard you vigilantly.”

“You know your stuff. Have you practiced before?”

“I've done it a few times in the training grounds of the house when my lord was away. It's not a very difficult test, since all you have to do is last as long as possible until your HP goes from 100 to 0. However, since it's a group test... you have to pay some attention to the survival of your companions, in addition to earning your own kill and assist points.”

It's the hounds of Baskerville who are born to actually walk the line between life and death.

This kind of virtual reality game is just plain ridiculous.

“Physical damage doesn't take effect until you're down from 100 HP to 0 HP, and poison damage takes effect from the start, right?”

“Yes, and if there's a dangerous incident, the instructors will break the magic firewall and step directly into the arena to intervene.”

The monsters were also professor-created golems, so it was a safe test.

“Kills are good, assists are good, so run wild. Just make sure I don't move.”

The Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro smirked at Vikir's words.

They looked like three puppies who had just been told by their master that they could run free.

And then.

Beep.

A whistle sounded, calling out the group that would take the next test.

[First year group 69! The four members of first year group 69 will please come up to the arena now!]

The skill evaluation of first-year freshmen begins now.

Chapter 181

Midterm Random Defense (5)

◆

Student Council President Dolores.

She watches with delight as the juniors in her club set a new school record.

But as the minutes ticked by, Dolores' expression hardened.

“ ...Why aren't the exams over?”

She wasn't the only one with this reaction.

All the spectators, students, and even professors watching the test were stunned.

“Hey, this is weird.”

“They all have 0 HP, why isn't the test over?”

“They're freshmen, who put them on phase two!”

The phases take the form of crystals that emit a blue light as a means of transmitting magic power.

The people in charge of it stared at the instrument panel with sullen expressions.

“There seems to be an error, as there are still strong life reactions outside of the registered students in the examination hall!”

“What? What do you mean, there are only four kids on the field!”

The professors are dumbfounded.

The stadium originally had about four human lives left, which were converted into points by the HP suits.

Now that it's down to zero, there should be no more life responses on the field.

But sure enough, the dashboard indicated that there was one “life-filled being” left that could fight.

The professors scanned the arena through the magic wall, but there was no sign of life other than the students.

“Anyway, it looks like the magic for the life reaction check and the phase management magic collided, causing the error.”

“Oh no. Why would there be such an error? There are obviously only four first-year students in the arena... ah, that's not the point now, hurry up and stop the collision!”

“We're technically the Phase Magic Management Department... and the Life Reaction Check Magic Department is not under our jurisdiction....”

“What the hell is your jurisdiction! No way, it's faster to stop the golems than to write and solve a magic circle code, right?”

“That's because... from this year, the creation and movement of the golems is automated, so the magic circle code related to it is also linked to the magic stones, and in order to dismantle it, we need to dismantle the magic for life reaction checks and phase management magic first.”

“What, are you kidding me, I can't believe the magic circle code needed for the test was designed so poorly! So what then! Tell me how!”

“Ba, of course there is a way! The code for the magic wall blocking the stadium is separate, we just need to break it to let the students out.”

“Then unlock the magic wall!”

“But the magic wall isn't under our jurisdiction, and if we mess with it, it could complicate our liability later....”

“Jurisdiction” and “liability” are such magical words that they can cause even the most normal, common-sense person's brain to harden.

This is especially true in times of crisis.

Somehow, the smallest of problems were being compounded by the operations of the other side.

But there was still a way out.

We just need to unlock the invisible magic wall that surrounds the stadium and let the students out.

The professor in charge gave the order with an impatient look on his face.

“Then quickly dismantle the magic wall. Let the students inside come out.”

“That's also out of my jurisdiction, so I'll try to find a practitioner who has the key to the magic wall at ....”

The professors at the head of the department scramble.

Soon, a professor with a key to the magic wall appears.

He was Professor Banshee Morgue, a potential candidate for the next vice principal.

Professor Banshee was supervising an exam that was taking place in another training center, and hurriedly rushed over when he heard the news of a series of incidents that occurred in Tudor's group.

“The key to the magic wall? I have it, but....”

Professor Banshee pulled out the key with a puzzled look on her face, which contained the spell to dismantle the magic wall.

The key had a large letter A written on it.

“Dismantling the magic wall cannot be done with just one key. Key A is useless without Key B.”

The key had been split into two for security purposes.

At Professor Banshee's words, all the professors started looking for the B key.

And then another incident happened.

“Professor Sadi, the holder of the B-key, has left the workplace without permission!”

“What! What the hell is that asshole doing again! It's been days since she was disciplined for neglect of duty... where the hell has she been!?”

“Uh, she said she had to go to the restroom and we lost contact.”

“Damn, what a fucking jerk this woman is...!?”

While professors are wasting time like this.

1. Tudor Donquixote

HP: 0/100

2. Sancho Panza Barataria

HP: 0/100

3. Usher Poe Bianca

HP: 0/100

4. Pigi

HP: 0/100

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca were exhausted and fighting the ants.

“Damn, now our HP suits are broken!”

“We might as well take them off, these uncomfortable tights.”

“The physical damage I'm about to take is going to be a real shock, everyone, watch out!”

“What the hell, why can't I unlock the illusion dungeon, spawn golems, and dismantle the magic barrier!”

Their HP had already been reduced to zero long ago, so they had to fight the monsters with their own bodies.

The ants were still swarming in droves.

Due to the structure of the defense game, the monsters are unlimited.

What's more, Phase 2 was for second year students only, so there weren't just regular ants.

[Ohhhhhh!]

A gigantic ant rose up from the rubble.

It had a wide, hard head like a shield, with many spikes, and its body was many times larger than the other ants.

“ ...It's a soldier ant!”

Pigi exclaimed in horror.

There was no way they could be mixed in with the regular ants.

“Damn it! We have to stop them!”

“We'll try!”

Tudor and Sancho fought back with all their might, but their already depleted mana couldn't keep their auras pumping.

The soldier ants rushed forward, pushing the ground with their shield-like heads, and blew Tudor and Sancho away.

...Quack, quack, quack!

Tudor's spear and Sancho's axe are smashed and scattered.

And soon after, the soldier ants started poking their heads in.

Quack, quack, quack!

Feeling overwhelmed by so many shield soldiers, Sancho, Tudor, Pigi, and Bianca were crushed by the swarming ants.

“Crunch, crunch, crunch!”

“Crunch! They keep coming!”

“...God, I'm going to die!”

“Ugh, what are the professors doing!”

Everyone was letting out pained moans.

The situation was quite serious, but it had happened so quickly that the professors hadn't yet found a way to deal with it.

“Since it's come to this, we'll have to smash the magic stone!”

“Who's going to break it, this magic stone has at least 4 departments' responsibilities mixed up in it!”

“Everyone knows that the magic stone is an extremely rare and expensive ancient opal, right? Yes, some department head will take responsibility! Let's make that clear first!”

“Is this the golem creation department? Is this the bioreaction detection department? Is this the phase management department? Is this the magic wall maintenance department? Whose jurisdiction is this? Let's make it clear where responsibility lies first!”

Adults' situations are complicated.

“The Golem Department made a mistake in adding the Automation Magic Circle to the original Golem Creation Magic Circle, so let's destroy the Magic Stones and take responsibility!”

“Why our side? The Bioreaction Detection Department made the mistake in the first place, they should be the ones to destroy the magic stones!”

“What are you talking about! If we hadn't gone through the phase, none of this would have happened! Who's more at fault and who's less at fault!”

“Has Professor Sadi contacted you yet, what are you going to do about this magic wall!”

“Didn't everyone hear the rumors!? There is a rumor that among the first year freshmen, there is a member of the royal family who came in hiding their identity! If this incident becomes known to the imperial family, we'll all be dead!”

While the children are dying, the adults do nothing but think about their own safety and gain.

Dolores, worried about her juniors, was disillusioned by the professors' behavior.

'Guys, hang in there... just a little longer!'

Dolores raised the sword herself.

Boom!

She grabbed the sword from the waistband of the professor next to her and ran towards the magic stone.

The professors shouted in horror.

“Student council president! What are you doing!”

“Are you crazy! Stop right now!”

“If you break it, you won't end up being expelled! Request compensation directly from Quovadis...... !”

But none of the threats or words could stop Dolores.

“Iyab!”

She swung her sword at the magic stone.

In this moment, the lives of her juniors were on the line.

It didn't matter that it was the Academy's Imperial Treasure No. 1, or that it was a national treasure of incalculable value, or even that she would be expelled for destroying it.

Driven solely by the need to save his juniors, Dolores plunged the sword in.

...No, she tried to stab it.

Puff-puff-puff!

If it weren't for the barrage of noise coming from beyond the magic wall, from within the arena.

“!?”

Dolores looked up in alarm.

The other professors, who had rushed to stop her, also looked at the stadium in surprise.

The magic wall that keeps outsiders in and insiders out is still intact.

However, there is one face within it that I hadn't seen before.

A man stands in front of an exhausted Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca, swatting at ants.

“...Stay away.”

It was Vikir.

Chapter 182

Midterm Random Defense (6)

◆

There was nothing Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca could do.

With all their health and mana gone, they're just 18-year-old kids.

The weight of the ant-shaped golems that were crushing them was too much for them to bear.

“Ugh. I can't believe I'm stuck here like this... and I haven't even become a hero yet....”

“I didn't think my end would be like this.”

“I'm going to be a hero. ....”

“Hey, Pigi! Why isn't this guy talking! Isn't he dead already!?”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca were paralyzed with despair.

They were just about to let go of their last hope.

...BAM!

With a loud booming sound, the pressure on their bodies disappeared.

As if the weight of the ants had been temporarily lifted, a rush of fresh air swept in, clearing away the suffocating poisonous fog.

“...?”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca gulped and looked up.

There was a black cloud of blood swirling around them.

“...Stay away.”

A familiar figure stood behind them, Vikir.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca could only stare in disbelief.

“Vi, Vikir! How did you get here....”

Tudor, who still had some energy left, stammered, but Vikir didn't say much.

Just.

“It's okay now.”

With those words, he raised his bow.

At the same time.

POP!

A black aura rose from Vikir's bow.

An arrow flew out with a red trajectory.

Quack, quack, quack!

It smashed the head of the giant army ant that was charging in front of him with a single blow.

...!?

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca's jaws dropped.

◆

A few minutes ago.

Vikir stuck to the magic wall that surrounded the arena and looked inside.

He saw a small ball of fur in the corner of the arena.

A cub. It was hiding among the rubble of the collapse, whimpering.

It was too small and insignificant for anyone to notice, but it was clearly being detected by the Life Response of the Magic Stone.

'When I took the test, the life response wasn't detected... Was that because it was overly starved?'

During Vikir's test, the starving cub had ingested a lot of poison all at once, and had even shed skin in the process.

It must have gotten quite a bit of life force into it, and had been caught in the magic stone's life detection magic net.

Vikir covered his face with his hands.

In the end, it was the greed of the little bastard to eat more poison that caused this.

And so it ate and ate and ate, until suddenly it realized that its master, Vikir, was gone, and it hid in a corner of the magic wall and wept like that.

In the distance, he sees the professors scrambling.

“No, well, who's going to be in charge!”

“Let's divide up the jurisdiction first, then!”

“Alright, let's dismantle the magic wall first! Can't we get a hold of Professor Sadi yet?”

“These people! Didn't you hear that there's an imperial family among the first years! What a disgrace!”

Dolores even stamped her foot and glared at the magic stone in the distance.

If this continues, I'm really going to have an accident.

Vikir stroked his chin.

'If the magic wall is dismantled and a full search begins, they'll find the cub. It can't be allowed to happen.'

This is why spider education must be straightforward.

Vikir headed for the edge of the stadium, out of sight of the crowd, thinking that he would have to give the cub a good scolding later.

Tsutsutsutsuts...

Vikir wore a picaresque mask on his face.

Black steam billowed out of it, and Vikir's body shrank.

Vikir looks up into the puddle of water on the floor and sees a black puppy, wrapped in a black cloak, pacing around.

Hodadak.

Turned into a dog, Vikir scooped up his clothes and ran, heading northwest of the Magic Wall.

Before regression, Vikir had stayed at the Academy as a bodyguard and messenger to assist Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro, and through that experience, he had some knowledge of this magic wall.

'There is a gap in the lower northwest corner of the magic wall.'

I've been to Baskerville a lot.

The triplets, Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro, were also the type of people who held a lot of personal grudges here and there for fear of being recognized as Baskerville.

As a result, they were often attacked when they were at the academy, even when they were taking tests in the arena.

At the time, an assassin had dug a tunnel to the bottom of the magic wall and slipped through a threadlike gap in the lower northwest corner, targeting the Highbro, Mibro, and Lowbro.

Later, the professors inspecting the magic wall were speechless as to how they had found this gap, which required digging about seven meters underground.

Whatever. Vikir had turned into a dog and was digging a tunnel into the lower part of the magic wall.

As he dug, he saw a small crack at the end of the wall. It was as he remembered.

Vikir squeezed through and was able to enter the magic wall with ease.

'The dog's small size is an advantage.'

Once through the magic wall, the rest was easy.

Vikir removed his mask and returned to his human form.

Woodduck.

A scream echoes through his body as he grows larger in the narrow cave.

But Vikir's body, strengthened by the protection of the River Styx and his immense mana, pushes through the dirt to gain space.

Vikir who quickly got dressed, pushed off the ground with his legs and came out onto the ground, breaking the stone floor of the stadium.

“....”

As he poked his head out of the ground, his vision was bathed in green. It was the paralyzing poison from the ant golem.

'With a fog this thick, it's hard to see in from the outside.'

Vikir was glad he couldn't see much beyond the magic wall.

If he couldn't see out from here, he probably couldn't see in from there either.

'Okay, then....'

The first thing Vikir did in the green, poisonous haze that surrounded him was to catch the hatchling.

But he didn't have to go looking for it.

[...!]

When the cub spotted Vikir, it ran to him and clung to the back of his hand.

Boo-boo-boo- swish-

Vikir couldn't help but furrow his brow as he asked where it had been.

“Look at this asshole's ass. Shameless little bastard.”

Retrieving the cub, Vikir took a step forward, knowing that he would have to give it a solid education later.

For now, the immediate need was to rescue Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca.

Vikir realized that the dense poisonous fog made it difficult to see from the outside.

He immediately fed an arrow to his bow.

It was only a supply bow and arrows, but with Ballak's archery skills and Vikir's mana, it would be a siege weapon.

Puff-puff-puff!

Vikir's rapid-fire arrows began to swat away the ants.

Whether they're worker ants or soldier ants, Vikir's arrows crush them in an instant.

After a few strokes, the path opened up and Vikir could see Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca in the depths ahead.

“...V, Vikir?”

Tudor's face is blank, like he's seen a ghost.

So did Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca.

Vikir didn't say anything, just walked to the front of his friends.

'You all look so weak.'

I want to tell them to get out through the tunnel, but they're too exhausted to move.

Pigi, in particular, has been poisoned with paralyzing poison and can barely lift a finger.

In the meantime, the giant ants began to surround Vikir.

<Killer Ant (Worker Ant)

Danger Rating: C

Size: 1 meter

Found in: Large colonies

-Name 'worker ant'

The most common form of the killer ant species.

They are the foremost burrowers and perform a variety of duties, including scout, assault, and nursery.

Armed with a hard and durable exoskeleton and powerful pincer jaws, they are known to dig deep burrows that extend from the human realm to Hell.

<Killer Ants (Soldier Ants)

Danger Rating : B+.

Size: 5 meters

Found in: Large Colonies – Filthy Spawning Grounds

-Also known as the 'soldier ant'

It was found that some individuals of this species have mutated, resulting in a massive body size and a more sturdy exoskeleton.

They are the ultimate manifestation of killer ant colony evolution and are not found in normal anthills, but in very large anthills or colonies of killer ants that have been left unattended for too long.

Countless worker ants clink their jaws, which are like large garden shears.

In between, there are soldier ants that can take on up to a thousand worker ants.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca shouted at Vikir's back in the face of this army of ants.

“Vikir, it's reckless! You're not going to win!”

“ ... Thanks for coming with us, but we're screwed.”

“For God's sake, run, Vikir!”

“You idiot, you'll get yourself killed!”

Everyone's attitude is one of despair and near hopelessness.

But Vikir didn't move from his spot.

Kirik.

He merely pulled away from the protest.

And then.

“...Uh!?”

Everyone's eyes began to turn in astonishment.

Chapter 187

Aftermath (4)

◆

With a midterm attack on the line, Vikir goes for a part-time job interview.

When Sinclaire hears about Vikir's financial situation, she immediately takes him to the boss's office.

Vikir silently thought to himself.

'It's not time to use Cindywendy's money yet. It's best not to make any contacts until 'the moment' comes.

Cindywendy's vast funds would be used later. At a very important moment.

Any contact with her must never be revealed until then, so it's better to refrain from such petty monetary transactions.

The best way for the agents to be discovered was to follow the money trail.

“..., A bourgeois family, I'll leave it as a hidden card for them.”

Vikir muttered a little to himself.

Then Sinclaire, who was walking slightly in front of him, turned her head with a puzzled expression.

“Brother, what did you just say?”

“Umm. Nothing.”

“ ... Did I hear you wrong?”

Sinclaire shook his head, then turned back to the topic at hand.

“This cafe is the best thing ever. The pay is a little low, but it's inside the academy, so there's no gossip and the work is easy, and the boss lets me make whatever I want to eat if I have extra ingredients. It's close to the dorms and the lecture hall, and there aren't too many people at night, so I can study privately, although I can't sleep, and the uniforms are pretty.”

Sinclaire quickly explained to Vikir the advantages of working at the cafe.

She added in passing at the end.

“ ... I want you to work with my hyung. I think it would be fun.”

But.

Contrary to Sinclaire's expectations, the cafe owner was firm.

“No way. We only hire girls.”

Mr. Pringles, the owner of 'Languid Noon, Moustache', was a middle-aged gentleman with a bushy mustache.

He had his own firm philosophy and beliefs about running a cafe, and one of them was that he only hired women for part-time jobs.

He believed that only a woman's meticulous and delicate hands could make the best coffee.

Faced with a gender barrier, Vikir was inevitably rejected.

But Sinclaire is a brave girl who doesn't let walls stop her.

She would break them down. With a weapon stronger than walls.

“But boss, what does my hyung look like?”

Sinclaire approached the back of Vikir, who was sitting on a chair, and stretched out her hands and almost hugged Vikir.

Sinclaire's hands pulled Vikir's bangs up.

Oof.

The bangs fell back, revealing Vikir's bare face.

“...Hoh. Now that's a different story.”

Mr. Pringles stroked his mustache once slowly with his hand.

Then, his mouth opened.

“Minimum wage, three months' probation. During the probationary period, I'll pay you seventy percent of your salary. If that sounds good to you.”

Sinclaire then turned to Vikir and grinned broadly.

“Hyung, that's a pretty generous offer! This cafe usually doesn't hire men at all....”

“I don't.”

But Vikir shook his head.

A minimum wage job and an apprenticeship, which would leave him with no time to go slay demons.

Vikir hadn't intended to work here in the first place.

He was just curious about how much kids get paid these days.

'If I want to pay for school, I'll have to find a job that will pay well in a short period of time.'

Vikir was reminded that it's hard to make money with a regular job.

'What kind of job should I do? Monster hunting would be the best, right?'

Once the midterm season is completely over and the holidays are here, I'll go hunting for monsters in the nearby area.

Of course, Vikir knew exactly what dungeons were hidden near the Imperial Capital and what monsters lurked there, so making money shouldn't be too difficult.

But Sinclaire, unaware of Vikir's thoughts, could only shake his head.

Then.

“Hmmm!”

Mr. Pringles coughed, for some reason.

He stroked his mustache with a hand gesture that was a little faster than before.

“So, how about no probationary period, just minimum wage?”

“?”

Mr. Pringles suddenly changed his tone.

Both Vikir and Sinclaire shook their heads.

“No.”

Vikir shook his head again, more firmly, and Mr. Pringles' fingertips twitched once in his mustache.

“Well, then, without a probationary period. I'll add 500 gold to your minimum wage, how about that?”

“No.”

“Ugh! Then add 1,000 gold to your hourly wage!”

“No.”

“Yuck! Then I'll pay you 1.5 times your hourly rate, just for that!”

“I won't.”

“Ouch! Then double! Double your hourly rate! Work for me!”

“No.”

Vikir frowned as he watched Mr. Pringles twitch his mustache.

At this point, it was Sinclaire who was flustered.

She stopped Mr. Pringles with an awkward smile.

“Oh, Mr. Pringles. You must be disappointed. You're going to have a lot of female customers with my brother, aren't you?”

“Huh? Is that so? Oh, well, I guess that's true. I hadn't thought of that.”

“What? Otherwise, why would you hire my hyung at double the hourly wage....?”

“Well, our cafe has a nice uniform.”

“Yeah, right, except we only have girls' uniforms.”

“Exactly.”

“...?”

Whatever.

Vikir decided not to take the cafe job.

Leaving the boss's office, Sinclaire lamented.

“All the good jobs around here are for women. Cafes, theaters, and bookstores are great places to work.”

“Why don't you try cross-dressing? It might not be so bad after all.”

Bianca, next to her, said with a rare look of seriousness on her face.

But Vikir shook her head silently.

“It's okay. I already have a part-time job in mind.”

“Eh? Where?”

Sinclaire opened his rabbit eyes.

There was no way he could say “demon hunting” right then, so Vikir just shut up.

Then.

Dolores, who had been waiting with her parfait, suddenly stood up from the table.

“Whoa, whoa, whoa, the 'copycat' again!”

She was trembling, clutching in her hand the newspaper that the mailman's owl had tossed through the cafe window just moments before.

[BREAKING] The Night Hound... a vicious act that knows no bounds!? / Views: 3,869

-The worst villain of all time, the Night Hound, has bared his fangs once again.

Last night, a group of students from the Varangian Academy, who were on a school trip to the Yellow Sea, were attacked by a Night Hound, causing great damage...

There were 00 minor injuries and 00 serious injuries... Among them was the head of the Varangian's academy, ...

Meanwhile, the Night Hound was not targeting the Varangian students in the first place, but had an ulterior motive, but the encounter was a result of the bravery of the Varangian students who spotted a suspicious person and came forward first...

Meanwhile, no fingerprints were detected on the only piece of evidence left at the scene, a “broken vodka bottle”...

?(Cold Class 1st year): Wow;;; The Varangian kids must have been victimized...

??(Hot Class 2nd year):??For so long, I felt like I was a stranger because I was in the academy... but it doesn't feel like a stranger that someone my age got attacked;;

??? (Hot Class 1nd year): I can't sleep at night because I'm scared these days....

??(Hot Class 1nd year): Really that criminal should be arrested sooner rather than later.

??(Hot Class 2nd year): Wow, I'm so excited for the Night Hound... He's a villain, but he's cool.

???(Cold Class 1st year): This is crazy;;;

???(Cold Class 1st year): Isn't he a psychopath???

???(Hot Class 3rd year): This guy needs to be checked out.

??? (Cold Class 1st year): But there are a lot of Night Hound fans in the academy;;;

??? (Hot Class 2nd year): Etta, they're just writing nonsense saying they're anonymous;;; I'm afraid I'll go blind ??

??(Hot Class 3rd year): I'm a Night Hounds fan, I support you! Bring a wake up call to this rotten society!

???(Hot Class 2nd year): Imperial Guard members are here!!!!!

.

.

Dolores looked at the newspaper, angry.

“This is not the work of the Night Hound, someone is copying him, a real villain!”

She jumped out of her seat and walked over to Vikir, Sinclaire, and Bianca.

“I'm sorry, girls, but I have an emergency and I have to go. We'll talk about the attack test a little later.”

“Yes, Ms. Chairman.”

Sinclaire and Bianca nodded obediently.

Vikir, meanwhile, was a little impressed by Dolores' glare.

'Did you realize it was a copycat? Excellent.'

Vikir read the newspaper article Dolores had left behind.

Apparently there was a madman on the rampage out there.

'No, not one, but two?'

Two copycats. One has been less active lately, the other is still on the rampage.

I was already avoiding eye contact, but now I was getting even more attention.

This had obvious advantages and disadvantages.

The pros are that Vikir's alibi is now stronger, the investigation is in disarray, and, hopefully, Vikir's crimes can be blamed on a copycat.

But there was one major drawback that all of these advantages didn't cover.

'It's that my vigilance is heightened when I'm acting as the Night Hound.'

This could disrupt assassinations.

The more vigilant a society's leaders are, the more guards there will be.

“....”

Vikir made a silent resolution to himself.

To eliminate the copycats, the fake Night Hounds, if possible.

'Once I do well in the attack test tomorrow, I will go straight to catch the copycat.'

I have to get a job, I have to study, I have to take exams, I have to go on assassinations, I have to catch and kill copycats....

Vikir's academic life is indeed busy.

Chapter 189

Attack Land (2)

◆

“....”

A drop of cold sweat trickles down Dolores' cheek.

However, her gaze is filled with laughter.

“Hohoho what do you see?”

Ms. Sadi. She turned to Dolores.

A black military cap, a long purple ponytail, hair spiked like horns in places, skin as pale as a corpse.

Underneath her black studded uniform, she wore a loose belt, and in the middle of it hung a rolled-up whip.

The heel of the black kill heel she was wearing was a whopping 31cm long, and the tip was sharp like an awl.

There were terrible scars burning like flames on the tips of her ten fingers, where her fingerprints should have been, and there was a rumor that she had been drinking vodka and chewed on her own fingers, thinking they were snacks, while she was drunk.

“....”

Dolores broke out in a cold sweat and met Professor Sadi's gaze.

Normally, she would have immediately turned a blind eye to that scary woman's gaze, but... having grown up through the Dantalian battle, Dolores was not about to shy away from a look of protest at the injury to her favorite junior.

“What, look at her?”

Professor Sadi drew the whip at her waist.

She turned and paced toward Dolores, who glared at her.

“What kind of a bitch with no blood on her bald head gives a grown woman a glare like that and thinks she's the student council president?”

“....”

“Hohohoho-honey, even your Abby Humbert can't open his eyes at me like that~”

The cold sweat that was drenching Dolores' body became even more intense as Ms Sadi slowly gave off momentum.

Dolores had fought Dantalian before, but Professor Sadi's aura exuded an entirely different kind of fear.

A woman who exuded an almost 'demonic' danger.

Then.

“Your disdain for the students is in moderation. Professor Sadi.”

A voice interrupted Professor Sadi.

Banshee Morgue, who stood in Dolores' way.

Dolores sank back in her seat, feeling the pressure on her body dissipate as Professor Banshee's back blocked her view.

Meanwhile, Professor Banshee turned to Sadi and warned her in a low voice.

“What kind of attitude is this in the middle of a sacred midterm? Not only did you overtest a student in your charge, but you crossed the line into verbal abuse and assault... Do you really want to get yourself fired?”

“Tsk-”

Professor Sadi interrupted, spitting phlegm at Professor Banshee's feet.

“What ...?”

Professor Banshee's brow furrowed at Sadi's rudeness.

But Professor Sadi was unfazed and pulled something out of her waistband.

It was a large glass bottle, half full of vodka.

Clink.

Professor Sadi showed his sharp teeth and bit down on the long, narrow mouth of the glass bottle, breaking it.

Wahzak- Wahzak-

She chewed the shards of glass in her mouth like candy, then slurped them down her throat, along with the vodka.

Professor Banshee's mouth was half open in disbelief.

“Is that alcohol? No, I mean, how can you have that kind of attitude on this exam with your students' lives on the line....”

“This isn't alcohol, asshole~”

“I can smell the alcohol all the way from here?”

“It's 76 degrees, it's not alcohol, it's water.”

“This crazy person....”

Professor Sadi's head snapped up as Banshee showed signs of rambling.

Then she spoke sarcastically for all to hear.

“The world has changed for the better, that an old man from House Morgue, who used to manage a Morgue, can be offended by a daughter of the Marquis de Sade.”

But Professor Banshee is a man of great family pride.

“Phew! That was hundreds of years ago. I'm the Marquis of Morgue now. Also, the Marquis de Sade has long since fallen, and your status is no more than a semi-baron.”

“Ah, it's a boring world, to hell with it.”

Professor Sadi flicked her ears and turned her head away as if she didn't want to deal with him.

Professor Banshee gave her a stern look.

“How far do you think the principal's favor will go? If you continue to treat students badly in the next exam, I will definitely discipline you with the authority of the next vice principal.”

“Ne-ne-”

Professor Sadi still didn't pretend to hear, but she didn't laugh or make sarcastic remarks anymore, not that she could completely ignore what Professor Banshee was spewing out to save her life.

Professor Banshee gritted his teeth and turned away.

He knew full well why they kept her on the faculty, even though it cost them lives every year.

Honorific. The opinion in aristocratic circles that the dignity of a nobleman, no matter how fallen, their dignity should not be overly damaged.

'...No. There are a few more factors.'

An unrivaled sense of combat. And a genius for criminal psychology.

She possesses enough combat power to be able to take on a company of the Imperial Army on her own, and shows an uncanny ability to predict, track, and apprehend the psychology of all types of criminals.

“A madman can understand a madman.”

Professor Banshee shook his head.

Professor Sadi is clearly a rare genius in terms of ability and talent, but her short temper makes her difficult to work with.

She had just brutalized Sancho Barataria, a promising young man who seemed to have a lot of potential.

Luckily, Sancho is a strong soul and hasn't suffered too much trauma yet.

How many up-and-coming elites have been traumatized by Professor Sadi only to find themselves peeing themselves at the mere sound of her laughter?

They often took a leave of absence from school or dropped out of school, and even if they managed to graduate, they were often so weak-hearted that they could not fight at all no matter where they went.

Considering this, Professor Banshee felt like thanking Sancho for being such a strong soul.

Dolores, next to him, was also looking at Sancho with pity.

The professor in charge was extremely unlucky. After all, 'that' Sadi.

But the nightmare was just beginning.

“Hohoho, come on up next. I'll be gentle from now on.”

Professor Sadi continued to call the students in her charge into the arena.

Jjaag- jjag!

Her avatar, Mudgolem, slapped the thorny whip in her hand against the floor a few times.

Then the next student stepped onto the field.

Puck! Puck!

The result was what everyone expected.

The student was unable to land a single effective hit on the mud golem, and was retired as his entire body was mangled by the whip.

0 effective hits, 4 effective dodges, 0 effective defenses, 0 critical hits.

Sancho's next student was left in tears, with a miserable score of just four points.

And the one after him, and the one after that, and the one after that.

None of them managed to land a single successful attack on the golem, which mimicked Professor Sadi's every move, only dodging the whip baptism.

Furthermore, Professor Sadi's whip, writhing and flying like a viper, was nearly impossible to defend against once it began to strike.

Four points. Three points. Eight. Six. Five. 7 points. 4 points....

The parade of disastrous scores continues.

It was a moment of reassessment that Sancho's score of 17 points was outrageous.

Meanwhile. The professors watching were grinding their teeth.

“Sadi, that stupid bitch is destroying the entire grade point average!”

“I'm sick to my stomach to see this kind of discriminatory test every year!”

“Why on earth does the principal favor that bitch every time!”

“As a last act of respect for the fallen Marquis de Sade.”

“Damn it. How unreasonable and absurd. I thought this was not the way the ranks and classes were supposed to be divided...”

“I can't help but think that the students in that class were unlucky.”

“Maybe we should give the sexually victimized kids extra credit for their work or attitude later on to make up for it.”

“Well, it's a good thing the assistant principal's faction has her, because she'll bring down the principal's approval ratings.”

In the midst of all of their complicated thoughts, Prof. Sadi chuckles, sending the students into a desperate state.

“Hohoho – it's fun to make the dogs sweat and train them. Well, not as much as making them bloody.”

The good news among the misfortunes was that Professor Banshee's threats were effective and Professor Sadi did not end up killing the student.

Still, the idea of treating students like dogs and whipping them with a whip was offensive to many.

This wasn't a teacher educating a pupil, it was just the stronger beating the weaker.

After giving the student she had just beaten a total of four points and retiring them, Sadi called for the next dog to be trained.

And then.

“Ho-o? You seem to be the only one with any sense, so you'll be worth training.”

Professor Sadi's eyes lingered on a student standing at the bottom of the arena.

A man with an expressionless face and a cold aura surrounding him at all times.

“....”

Vikir was standing there.

Chapter 194

Attack Land (7)

◆

'Blinded by anger, where are you looking?'

Professor Sadi's eyes widened to tears as she read the shape of Vikir's lips.

At the same time.

...Puck!

The vision in her left eye went black.

“Kaaaahhhh!”

Prof. Sadi's horrifying scream echoed throughout the training grounds.

The entire left side of her face is on fire!

But the golem's face is intact. Not a single arrow mark.

“...? ...? ...? ...?”

Professor Sadi reaches out and touches the left side of her face.

She can feel it.

Hot liquid running down her face, and a thick, hard arrowhead lodged where her eyeball should have been.

An arrow, deeply embedded in Professor Sadi's left eyeball.

The crowd is shocked and speechless.

“What, what? What happened all of a sudden?”

“I thought the wind was changing direction, but suddenly an arrow came flying at her!”

“Isn't that Vikir's arrow from earlier in the match?”

“Aww, that's ridiculous. Why is it flying now?”

“It was blown to a strange place by the wind at the beginning of the match, and now that the wind has changed, it's back!”

“Oh my God, is that even possible?”

“How can she be so unlucky...”

There was an unprecedented loss of life that no one could have predicted.

The professors were also stunned by this horrific and outrageous event.

“No, I've seen a lot of students get hurt, but I've never seen a professor get hurt.”

“And it's that Professor Sadi. Hehe, really...... Is it okay to call this retribution?”

“Uh-huh. A colleague is injured. What nonsense! No matter what, that's not true!”

“So, should I discipline that student, Vikir?”

“Why would you say that? He didn't do it on purpose, it was just a natural disaster.”

Earlier in the match, Vikir had made a number of misfires, and one of his arrows had soared high in the wind, only to spin around and fall.

In other words, it was just a coincidence.

Moreover, Professor Sadi was so focused on the golem mimicking her movements that she didn't notice the arrow falling toward her body.

Her vision had been so narrowed by her anger and obsession that she could only focus on what was in front of her.

-Ting!

By that time, the scoreboard appeared with a beeping sound signaling the end of the test.

, Class B-256, Cold Warrior Division>

-Effective hit: 2 (1 point each)

-Effective dodges: 28 times (1 point each)

-Effective parries: 0 (1 point each)

-Critical hits: 1 (10 points each)

=Total points: 40

Two points for two effective hits and 28 points for 28 effective dodges.

This was the result of Vikir's constant running away from the whip.

Finally, the attack on Professor Sadi's main body counted as one critical hit and was worth 10 points.

In a way, it was a critical hit since the golem was in a state where it was unable to fight.

It was a bit tricky to count it as a point since it was a human casualty, but that's what the magic system had decided.

Everyone was puzzled, as in the long history of the Colosseo Academy, a professor had never been injured in the middle of a test before.

Anyway.

And so Vikir's total score was 40 points. A new record for the grade.

This was despite the fact that the professor in charge was Sadi.

The professors looked at the timely scoreboard and chattered amongst themselves in disbelief.

“Hehe... was so focused on harassing the student in front of her, she didn't realize the danger she was in.”

“She's just unlucky, who would think an arrow would come flying at her?”

“A terrible tragedy of overtesting. Too bad the wind changed direction just then.”

“She brought it on herself. She brought it on herself.”

“But how am I supposed to grade that student, Vikir?”

“Give her what? The magic system says it's 40 points.”

“But if that were the case, wouldn't there be some students who deliberately target the professor?”

“That makes sense. How could they jump that long distance to harm you? What happened today was just an accident of bad luck.”

“This has never happened before, so I'm not sure what to do.”

The professors are also divided.

Some say it was an accident and Vikir's critical hit should count as a valid point.

Others say it was an accident, but that Vikir's critical hit should be excluded.

But either way, the consensus is that it was an accident.

Meanwhile.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca were reacting furiously.

“What the hell happened?”

“That means Vikir won!”

“Is there any winning or losing in this game, it's just a time limit?”

“Who cares, it's just Professor Sadi who ended up looking bad!”

At the reaction of the juniors, even the nice Dolores breathes a sigh of relief.

It was unfortunate that Professor Sadi had an arrow in her eye, but somehow it didn't seem excessive.

After all, she'd almost deliberately blinded Pigi's left eye, and she'd scarred so many talented students over the years, it was a small price to pay.

Then.

“Enough! All exams stop here!”

Professor Banshee's gruff shout echoed throughout the stadium.

He stepped onto the pitch himself, accompanied by the professors who specialized in Heal Magic.

“Vikir, the exam is over. You may now return downstairs.”

Vikir didn't say anything in response, just bowed his head.

Under Professor Banshee's direction, all of the tests that had been taking place on the vast training grounds came to a halt.

Soon, white-coated medics began to rush over in response to Professor Banshee's call.

The medics were only in the area where the students were taking their exams, so it took them a while to get to the area where the professors were staying.

Professor Banshee then walked over to the cowering Sadi and said.

“Professor Sadi. Get yourself some medical treatment. And I hope you will refrain from any further arrogant behavior after this incident...?”

But.

Professor Sadi didn't even bother to listen to Professor Banshee.

“Hoho... hohohoho-”

Sadi suddenly began to laugh.

She laughs in spite of the blood dripping from the fingers wrapped around her face.

Then. Professor Sadi pulls her hand away from her face.

“...Hmm.”

Professor Banshee frowned.

The sight of the arrow still lodged in her eye, the mangled flesh around it, and the gushing blood was too much to bear.

“Professor Sadi. Hurry up and get treatment... heog!?”

For a moment, Professor Banshee's face was colored with horror.

So did the students, professors, and spectators who were watching.

“Whoa, whoa, whoa-what is that doing?”

“Eek! She's crazy!”

“Oh my god... what am I looking at?”

All similar reactions.

And so it goes.

Pop!

Professor Sadi had just pulled the arrow out of her left eyeball with all the force she could muster.

A straight arrow shaft and a sharp tip at the end.

The eyeball that had just been removed from its socket.

Everyone is overwhelmed by Sadi's madness as she rips out her own eye.

And then.

Tsk-tsk.

Professor Sadi's mouth drops open, shocking everyone even more.

Then, sharp teeth begin to chew on the eyeball pierced by the arrowhead.

Crunch-clunk-clunk-clack-clunk-

Professor Sadi. Before anyone could stop her, she took the arrow into her mouth and began chewing on her own left eyeball.

The sound of the eyeball popping and chewing in her mouth was loud and eerie enough to be heard by all the spectators.

After swallowing her left eyeball whole, Sadi laughed hysterically.

“It's from my grandfather, If I throw it away, it will be wasted.”

Her maniacal smile sent the medical team scurrying back, unable to get any closer.

Even Professor Banshee, the Great Banshee, was at a loss for words, his mouth half open.

Sadi glared at the medics.

“I don't need your help.”

As she spoke, she rolled her one remaining eyeball.

There was a sideways glance at Vikir, who was just walking down the field.

Vikir doesn't seem to be paying any attention to this side of the arena, as if he hadn't been there since the last time.

His gaze has already left this place and is headed somewhere else entirely. It's as if everything that's happened so far hasn't mattered at all.

Professor Sadi's face turned red.

“Hohohoho- it's fun. This is so fun. That guy... You said you were in class B Cold devision, right?”

Professor Sadi turned her head to look at Professor Banshee.

“If you're going to feed me for this, feed me. Discipline.”

“....”

“Instead. The day my discipline is lifted, I'm going to take over Cold Warrior's class right away.”

There was an unusual heat in Professor Sadi's voice, as if he were possessed by something, and it struck fear into the hearts of every professor and student in the Cold Warrior Class.

And toward such a crowd.

Frown-

Sadi's eyeballs are sticking out and she just frowns at the empty cavity.

“I just winked at you, didn't you notice?”

She was indeed an unknown woman.

◆

The long midterms are over.

Defense, Attack, and a written test.

Everyone was surprised when the overall results of these tests, which were worth 50%, 40%, and 10% each, were announced.

1st place. Vikir

2nd place. Sinclaire

3rd place. Tudor Donquixote

4th place. Highbro Le Baskerville

5th place. Granola de Leviathan

6th place. Usher Pou Bianca

7th place. Middlebro Le Baskerville

8th place. Sancho Barataria

9th place. Lowbro Le Baskerville

.

.

199th. Pigi

.

.

On the attack test, students who had lost a lot of points after meeting with Professor Sadi recovered their scores.

This was due to a mysterious addition of extra points to their written scores.

Although it was a small part of the score, it was a game-changer, and students who had been unfairly penalized by Sadi were able to make up for it.

...But.

Of all the students who took the test with Sadi, there was one who did not receive any extra point.

It was Vikir.

The only perfect score.

There was no room for extra point for Vikir, who came up with research results so shocking that they turned the academic world upside down in his free research report on the written exam.

He performed well above average on the defense test and scored enough points against Professor Sadi to win the attack test.

And as a result of his outstanding achievements, such as resolving an accident caused by a magic stone error, hard-carrying the defense test by himself, and delivering a fatal blow to Professor Sadi, Vikir was ranked top of the class this year.

...Of course, this was not the outcome Vikir wanted.

In the first place, Vikir tried to get good grades only on written exams. Because he didn't want to attract attention.

However, there were a lot of variables, such as Madame's cub accident in the defense test and Professor Sadi almost blinding Pigi in the attack test.

Vikir used this as an opportunity to reflect on his lack of thoroughness.

But the students, who had no way of knowing that Vikir was thinking about it, simply crowded around him and chattered.

“Vikir, I really saw you again this time.”

“I honestly thought you were only good at study, but your physical skills were no joke.”

“Hey, buddy, would you like to have a date with the kids from Themiscyra Women's College? I think it would be very reassuring if you came out as a member.”

“Well, mana for mana, senses for senses, and monster strategy knowledge. A man who has everything.”

“A good head makes for a good body, and a good body makes for a good head, but you're good at both, so you'll be good at everything!”

“Hey, don't you think you're being too blatantly flattering? You're not really friends with Vikir! Go back to your seat!”

“But you, you don't belong here either!”

“I'm sitting next to Vikir.”

“I'm sorry, but I'm not selling, even for a laugh.”

“Hey, Vikir. Are you interested in studying? Do you want to join our study group? We only have kids from good families or who are good at studying~”

“Drink this. You were so cool yesterday~”

“Hey. Who are you having lunch with today? If you don't have anyone to eat with, why don't you eat with me?”

“All the professors are talking about you. When I went to the faculty office, they were all looking at your papers and admiring them.”

“Vi, Vikir, the seniors from the noble faction are looking for you!”

“Awesome! I saw this morning that the noble seniors are looking for you too!”

Vikir could only frown slightly at the many voices around him.

Then.

“Hey. What are you looking at, you want to get your ass kicked?”

A gruff-looking schoolboy pushes his way through the crowd.

Highbro Le Baskerville. He snarled, baring his teeth.

“I'm the head of the Cold B class, so don't you dare come crawling up to me and flatter some commoner like this. I'll kill you.”

Although Highbro was an outspoken bully, there were few students who could protest in front of the 4th-ranked overall student.

The cowed students scurried back to their seats.

Highbro turned to Vikir and gave him a thumbs-up, unnoticed.

'All taken care of.'

'...Well done.'

The words spoke for themselves.

Highbro took Vikir's praise and returned to his seat, smirking secretly.

The Mid and Low Brothers are quick to criticize Highbro.

“You're cheating, brother!”

“Keep the praise for yourself!”

“If you're unjust, you'll have to watch your master's back. Like me, always.”

The Baskerville triplets are now a loyal trio, waiting for Vikir's orders.

But there were some beings who would not be deterred.

“Vikir, how are you feeling?”

Tudor, Sancho, Bianca, Pigi, and Sinclaire.

Tudor laughed, clapping Vikir on the shoulder as he entered the classroom.

“You bastard, if you had that kind of power, you should've come clean and reported it to me first, you got me worried for nothing!”

Fortunately, his friends' attitudes didn't change much upon seeing Vikir's power.

Though Tudor and Sinclaire were a little disappointed.

“By the way, Vikir, I didn't talk to you back in the room because I was in a hurry. I want to show you something!”

Pigi stepped forward and held something out to Vikir.

It was an article from yesterday's paper.

[Breaking News] A major accident during a defense test! A first-year student of the Cold Class take care of it!? / Views: 50,899

The -1st year mid-term defense exam is a traditional exam that everyone goes through once in a while... But a recent accident occurred in this exam... This major accident was caused by safety insensitivity... At that time, the professors' responsibility was getting worse and worse... A male student came out of nowhere and saved everyone... Meanwhile, the main cause of the commotion was Professor S who left the duty station with a magic wall key without permission... Finally, we attach a video of the 1st year hero Vikir-kun breaking through the poisonous fog to the surface...

?(Cold Class 1st year): Wow;;; Look at him tearing through the poisonous fog;;; awesome...powerful...乃乃乃

???(Hot Class 2nd year): Is this the guy...that...why...you know...that....my husband?

???(Hot Class 1st year): Was his name Vikir? It was a pretty common name anyway?

??(Hot Class 4th year): Wow, but it's a legend that you went through the poison fog for your friends?

???(Hot Class 2nd year): I heard that there's already a fight between the 2nd year noble and 2nd year great house in the academy to recruit him.

???(Cold Class 2nd year): Don't you think that's just inside the academy? Guilds and families outside the academy are also lining up to take him as soon as he graduates.

???(Cold Class 3rd year): He's only a freshman?

???(Hot Class 3rd year): The prominence that has already been revealed is no longer a freshman class haha. That's something even a graduating class can't do like that~

.

.

Pigi's newspaper plays a video shot on the mana screen.

The video of Vikir tearing through the poisonous fog that filled the magic wall and shooting arrows was getting tons of views.

'When was the last time I shot something like this ...?'

Vikir ran a hand over his forehead.

After the midterm exams ended yesterday, I had to take some time off to go on an assassination mission, so I'm extremely tired.

Now that it was in the newspaper, it was only going to get worse for a while.

Then.

“Why are you all gathered in front of the first grade classroom, do you want to be disciplined?”

A stern voice comes from the front door of the classroom, down the hallway.

Professor Banshee was chasing away a group of students.

They were probably upperclassmen, second and third years.

Noble and Great House.

A group of children of noble families and a group of children of great families.

Along with the Student Council, these groups are the three major powers of Colosseo Academy.

While not recognized as an official group like the Student Council, they somehow wield more power over the entire student population than any other group of students, whether from the central noble families or the powerful houses.

They've come this far to embrace the rising dark horse, Vikir.

Of course, as powerful as they may be, none of them are confident enough to face the icy gaze of the students and Professor Banshee Morgue, so they disappeared in a hurry.

“....”

Professor Banshee.

The first thing he did upon entering was find Vikir sitting by the window.

Vikir, who had dozed off a bit, was woken up by Professor Banshee's cold voice, like a splash of cold water.

“Vikir-kun.”

“Yes.”

“Have you been closing your eyes again and thinking about what kind of magic trick you're going to discover today and surprise the academia with?”

“No. I dozed off.”

“ ...That's honest. One demerit point.”

Professor Banshee still hated Vikir.

He emphasized that class started immediately after the class bell rang and emphasized the justification for demerit points, saying that Vikir was dozing off during class time.

“Ugh, Professor Banshee, here we go again.”

“It seems like you're always giving demerits to Vikir.”

“Oh no, Vikir, you've racked up so many demerits that you're going to have to do community service again!”

“But this time, aren't we not going to do community service because of the festival?”

“Yeah, but it's festival season soon, and it would be unfair to do community service when everyone else is partying.”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, Sinclaire, and others each had their own words to say.

“....”

Of course, Vikir wasn't listening to Professor Banshee's point at all.

His mind was already racing with the details of the letter he'd received from Cindywendy last night.

'...Information has arrived about the next ten corpse.'

The boring assassination was over.

Now it was time for another blood and guts battle.

Vikir closed his eyes again, silently letting Professor Banshee's nagging voice drift out of his ear.

The Night Hound was on the hunt for his next prey.

Chapter 195

Preparing for the Festival (1)

◆

With all the midterms over, it's time for a little break at Colosseo Academy.

Following the principle that 'when you study, you should study hard and when you play, you should play hard,' Colosseo Academy holds a big festival every year to comfort the tired minds and bodies of students after midterm exams.

As the festival season approaches, professors tend to give students less class time and more breaks.

The idea is to get students thinking about and discussing things to do during the festival.

Of course.

“Shortened classes? Sounds ridiculous.”

Some, like Professor Banshee Morgue, were just plain mean.

He is known for his strict and sensitive personality, but he becomes especially more nervous during the festival season.

“Cutting classes short to prepare for the festival? That's not what a professor should do. Students pay a lot of money to attend classes, and cutting them short is a violation of their rights. I don't understand how a professor can cancel a class for the sake of the students. It's just a selfish desire to make things easier for the professor....”

Professor Banshee muttered in annoyance as he looked out the window at the banners and wreaths, the makeshift stage and tents, the sound equipment and fireworks display.

“In that case, today is an extended class. It will be at least an hour longer than the normal lecture time, so everyone take note.”

Professor Banshee's stern announcement is met with silence.

Tudor in the front grumbled under his breath.

'Damn it, I'm on the festival planning committee! I'm supposed to be out of class half an hour early....'

'Ha, is this really possible? According to the seniors, Professor Banshee does this every festival period.'

'Obviously, you've never had any fun in your life, so you can't empathize with the students.'

'Yeah, I guess all I did in school was study.'

Bianca, who was in the same boat, was frustrated and for once agreed with Tudor.

Then.

“Hey. What are you talking about?”

Professor Banshee's ghostly hearing picked up Tudor and Bianca's small talk.

“I guess being a member of the festival planning committee is worth the tuition, and, what, who's never hung out at a festival?”

“....”

As Tudor and Bianca remained speechless, Professor Banshee snorted lightly.

“Don't get all excited about the festivities. This is the time of year when we have the most accidents.”

With that, Professor Banshee deducted one point each from Tudor and Bianca's attitude scores.

Next. Professor Banshee is about to go back to class.

Professor Banshee was about to resume teaching when he heard loud music outside the window.

Bbangbangbangbang ???<

A military band from the Imperial Army was tuning their instruments in preparation for a performance.

Elsewhere, an invited dance troupe is putting together a choreography before taking to the makeshift stage.

And the excited chatter of students arriving for class and preparing for the festivities was creating a din of noise.

Despite the curtains on the windows, the soundproofing enchantments, and even the use of a separate silence spell, Professor Banshee groaned softly at the noise of the festival outside.

“This is why I hate festivals, ....”

◆

In the end, even Professor Banshee had no choice but to end the class a little early.

The students' attention span wasn't what it used to be.

“Well, if you're going to sit through class like this, just go out and play. It's better that way.”

As Professor Banshee grumbled, gathered her materials, and left the room, the children's eyes lit up.

Professor Banshee's class happened to be a joint integration class for all the classes in the Cold and Hot, so all the students were seated.

It was the perfect time to discuss what to do for the festival.

The members of the festival committee stepped forward.

Tudor from Cold Class and Granola from Hot Class were the ones who would lead the festival.

“Okay, friends, let's decide on a concept for the festival!”

The concept of the festival means what kind of monetization system will be set up at the festival.

In short, the idea is to create a simple facility that can be used for business, such as a bar, game room, or restaurant, and students can earn money by serving, cooking, or playing games there.

Traditional bars, haunted houses, and hunting clubs were generally popular profit models.

“But, no matter which one you choose, there is one 'law of the land' that must be followed!”

Tudor said, and all the students nodded in agreement.

At the Academy's festivities, there was one unwritten rule for all grades.

It was “TS”.

Trans-Sexual, which usually refers to the transformation of a man into a woman or a woman into a man.

At Colosseo Academy, it was fashionable for all the boys to dress as girls and all the girls to dress as boys during the festivities.

Sinclaire, always cheerful, claps her hands and laughs.

“Wow-that sounds like fun. Can we test it out before the festival?”

“Sure.”

Granola nodded, immediately agreeing with Sinclaire.

By now, the students in charge of the props were carrying out the disguises they'd been working on.

Sinclaire placed a mustache on her nose and chuckled.

“Look, Bianca, I look like the boss at our part-time job, don't I?”

“Yep. Did you rip off Mr. Pringles' mustache for this?”

Bianca giggles in a hip chin, thick eyebrows, disguised in a long Regent wig, and wearing a clumsily inflated inflatable muscle suit.

Sinclaire laughs awkwardly at the extent of Bianca's disguise.

“Ugh, you're disguise is so tight. Are you really going to do that for the festival?”

“Are you crazy? Of course I'm going to make myself look androgynous and sexy.”

“Great. Come with me.”

“Really? Oh, wait. We have to cross-dress men, too?”

Bianca's expression quickly turned sinister.

She walks over to Tudor, who is picking out his disguise.

“Hey, I'm familiar with your disguises, so I'll help you out!”

Soon, Bianca is using makeup and disguises to dress up the boys, including Tudor.

Tudor's hair was made long with golden partial wigs.

But it didn't look quite right on his handsome face, with its deep lines.

“Ugh, he doesn't look good as a cross-dresser because he has dark lines.”

Bianca shook her head and looked away.

“Hahahaha-”

And next to her, Sancho Barataria was laughing, arms crossed.

“She's crossed the... line by taking it too far.”

“Hahaha! I've never cross-dressed before, but I don't feel bad.”

“Really? I'm surprised. I thought you were more of a manly man and didn't like cross-dressing.”

“Nonsense! Cross-dressing is the most manly thing you can do, because women can't do it, and that's why the warriors of the North often have the world's greatest cross-dressing contest!”

Well, technically, yes.

Since women can't cross-dress, only men can, and consequently cross-dressing is a manly act.

Sancho nodded, looking in the mirror at his long hair and whitened face.

“With makeup, I look just like my sister, so blood doesn't lie after all!”

There was a slight murmur around him.

Unexpectedly, Pigi's eyes sparkled with admiration.

“Wah Sancho's sister must be very beautiful. I like strong women.”

“Really? Would you like to go on a blind date with her later? I'm afraid her taste is for shorter, fluffier, and cuter types.”

“Really, do you think someone like me would dare to meet Sancho's sister?”

“Hahaha- if you like her, you can keep seeing her, otherwise you can't!”

This was indeed a blind date set up like a warrior of the north.

But the women's interests had already shifted away from them.

No, their interests had been unified. They had already been.

“...'He'?”

“Where is he?”

“Where did he go?”

“Where is he!”

“Find him!”

“Hurry up!”

“Find him right away and... find him!”

Schoolgirls with all sorts of cosmetics in their hands, wigs of all kinds, various dresses, skirts, stockings, rings, necklaces, other trinkets, chokers, garter belts, and other accessories were looking for someone.

It was a frenzy that would have overwhelmed a search party of Imperial Army commandos.

'No. 1 most beautiful man in the Academy.'

'No. 1 Coolest Man in the Academy.'

'No. 1 sexiest man in the Academy.'

'No. 1 cutest man in the Academy.'

'No. 1 in the Academy's most wanted man to pet.'

'No. 1 in the Academy as the man you'd most like to put your arm around.'

'No. 1 in the Academy as the man you would most like to bite.'

'No. 1 in the Academy as the man you'd most like to cuddle and sleep with.

'No. 1 in the Academy for most cross-dressing.'

The man who topped every poll of the Academy's female students (and some male students who swooped in to vote).

The winner of all sorts of unofficial honors.

Some of the makeup artists, hair designers, and fashion people who've had their eyes on that beauty for a while now can't contain their lust and artistic spirits and are already searching for 'the one'.

And soon.

“....”

The predators' eyes caught sight of their prey, snoozing in the corner of the window.

Vikir.

This man always has an expressionless face.

◆

Normally, it's fairly rare for Vikir to be sleepy.

But lately, his grueling schedule of frequent meetings with scholars, award ceremonies, midterms, and even a few assassinations thrown in for good measure has been enough to make even the mighty Vikir doze off.

Is that why?

The sight of Vikir dozing off, his face usually hidden by bangs or glasses, lit up the eyes of many of his female classmates.

“I found him! There he is!”

“Wow! He's beautiful!”

“I'm so excited!”

“I've been practicing my makeup skills for this day!”

“I even brought my specially ordered dress!”

“I made a wig out of my own hair that I've been growing for ten years! I'm a former hair model in the Imperial Capital!”

“Ma'am, why didn't the rare underwear set I ordered four weeks ago come? Even if it's just the ones I was wearing in a hurry...!”

An army of schoolgirls swarmed around Vikir to dress her up.

And it wasn't just the first years, there were also a lot of second and third years, and even a few fourth years who were graduating.

They have casually infiltrated the first-year classroom during a break in class, and they are indeed showing off their first-year traditions.

“Move over, kid, what does a first year know about makeup!”

“Oh my God, look at you, do you even know what competition underwear is, and have you ever competed?”

“You made a wig out of that wild hair? Put it away! A wig made out of my hair is much better, I'm the Rapunzel of the continent!”

“Give me that, kid, I'll do the nose shading a thousand times better than you!”

“I'll do the cheeks, I have 5.6 trillion color cosmetics alone.”

“Hey, maybe you should do the eyeliner?”

“If we're going to do this, let's just divide the face into zones and do makeup by zone!”

“Hehe! I'll choose the color of Vikir's lower lip, no one else!”

“ ..., The lower lip? Why is my brother here in the first place...?”

Rows and rows of nameless makeup products. All sorts of whimsy. All sorts of dresses, skirts, uniforms, etc. And a whole lot of accessories, including garter belts, chokers, and other items that cater to a few special tastes.

The fascination of countless girls (and a few boys) was soon directed at Vikir.

And then.

“...Huck!?”

Vikir snapped out of his slumber and gasped at the sight of so many palms covering his vision.

A collective insanity that would surprise even the uninhabited in an age of destruction.

Suddenly, Vikir jerked upright, remembering the nightmare of his arrest on the verge of execution.

Hudadak-

As Vikir scurried away, the girls followed suit.

“We have to make him cross-dress!”

“It is the law of our academy!”

“Let's have a festival!”

With that, the girls followed the fleeing Vikir out into the hallway and around a corner.

But.

Somehow, Vikir was nowhere to be found.

The girls looked around, dumbfounded, like a dog looking up at the roof while chasing chickens.

But.

Hack, hack, hack.

From the corner of the locker room, a black puppy nonchalantly crossed the hallway.

◆

Vikir is currently wearing a picaresque mask.

Transformed into a black dog, Vikir made his way out of the main building, past the legs of the girls who were scrambling to find him.

'...No matter how tired I was, to those little guys.'

He dozes off, then jerks back when he sees the girls' palms, which would have made his comrades-in-arms from the Age of Destruction laugh out loud had they known about it.

'I'm sorry, my friends, I guess I've been a little too withdrawn lately.'

Living with young children while studying for the midterm exams, I couldn't afford to have a good night out.

The day is coming to an end, but there is still a long way to go.

Baskerville, Hugo, Traitors to Mankind, The Ten Commandments, The Demon World....

The path of Sura where one must move forward by killing and killing again. Vengeful ghost.

Vikir gritted his teeth, once again familiarizing himself with the heavy meanings of the words 'age of destruction' and 'returner'.

Chug-chug-chug-chug.

The tiny black puppy turned to face the Academy's outer walls.

In preparation for times like this, there are clothes hidden outside the walls in advance. Just pick a suitable hole, go out, and get your clothes back from there.

Vikir has been wandering around the Forbidden Zone (and racking up quite a few demerit points for it), but he's found a spot he's been eyeing.

People rarely come to this remote part of the wall.

Vikir had built an open hole here, just big enough for his tiny body to fit through when he was a dog.

'When I exit through this hole, I immediately put on my stash of clothes and enter the city, and....'

The information from Cindywendy floated around in my head.

The Demon Triangle, the only area of the Imperial City that her informants have been unable to reach, the only place where they've disappeared.

It was right near the orphanage where Dantalian was hiding.

'The Royal Cemetery.'

A cemetery where the heroes who defended the Empire rest.

According to Cindywendy's information, many informants had recently gone missing while investigating there.

Vikir recalled a newspaper article he had read relatively recently.

[Extra] The Night Hound, the Worst Villain of All, How Evil Is He? / Views: 89,269

-The Night Hound has caused another major accident.

After destroying the Central Clock Tower at around 1am, the Night Hound ravaged the Royal Cemetery at around 4am.

The Royal Cemetery is a sanctuary where the brave and fierce heroes of the previous era who unified the empire rest, so the fact that they attacked this place was a heinous act that was tantamount to a declaration of war against the entire empire, and indeed the entire human race...... Meanwhile, the number of remains damaged or lost due to this terrorist attack is enormous, and the exact damage has not yet been calculated......

It was an article about copycats imitating the Night Hound.

'...Maybe the copycat isn't really trying to copy me.'

Vikir had said that the world was just calling him a copycat for the sake of it, but what his true purpose was was still unknown, even to Cindywendy.

And now, Vikir speculated, almost with certainty, that the Mimic had something to do with one of the Ten Commandments.

It was a hound's instinctive sense of smell.

'Alright, then, let's get right down to business, shall we?'

Vikir licked his dry nose once, lustily, then trotted off to the opening in the bushes.

Dodo-dodo.

But.

Vikir didn't quite make it through the opening.

Bung-bung-bung-

'...?'

The quickly moving legs are just fluttering in the air.

Because someone had wrapped their arms around his back and waist and was lifting him up.

“Whoa Choco, we see each other again?”

A familiar voice rang in his ears.

It was the student council president, Dolores L. Quovadis, holding Vikir's back with a wide smile on her face.

She was dressed for the festival, wearing a fancy tuxedo and a black mustache.

'...?'

Vikir's mouth was half open in disbelief.

Why on earth is she here?

He was caught off guard because he had checked the area several times and found it deserted.

Vikir's questions were answered by Dolores.

“You're wandering around, too? There are a lot of stray cats and dogs around here. Maybe there's an open hole somewhere.”

“....”

“That's why I often feed them here, because I don't want to disturb them near the dorms.”

Dolores is indeed a good person. It's amazing that she's doing a service project that doesn't earn her any community service points, in a place where no one recognizes her.

Especially out here in the middle of nowhere, as far away from residential areas as possible, in case some people don't like stray dogs and cats.

Dolores laughed bitterly.

“There's been an unusually high number of abandoned puppies and cats in the dorms lately, especially in the first few months after freshmen move in. Some kids get into fights with their roommates or just get tired of their pets.”

“....”

“I love pets, but there are times when I wish there was a law banning pets in Academy dorms, so I'm going to push for it before my term as student council president ends.”

“....”

“But I'm also facing a lot of opposition from people who want to keep their pets. Some kids think I'm a pet hater, which isn't true....”

She stroked Vikir's head with a loving touch.

“By the way, were you abandoned by your master, or do you have your own butler?”

“.....”

“It seems like you've been traveling alone for a while now, would you like to come with your sister?”

Dolores seemed to be under some absurd illusion.

Perhaps she had mistaken Vikir for a poor stray dog that had been abandoned by its owner....

'...Hmm, come to think of it, you're not exactly wrong.'

Vikir suddenly realized that his situation wasn't so different from what Dolores thought.

It's a bitter pill to swallow. An abandoned hound, accused of every sneaky, dirty thing.

How was that any different from being a stray dog who trusted his master, only to be betrayed and abandoned.

Even worse, Vikir had been executed, so it was worse, not better.

'Even though I killed Seth, or rather Andromalius, the mastermind behind it..., that doesn't remove the Baskervilles and Hugo from the list of targets for revenge.'

Blood is blood. Nothing can replace it.

Well, whatever.

Dolores set Vikir aside for a moment, pausing to pick up the dog and cat poop and trash.

'...You sure do keep yourself busy.'

Vikir scurried away as Dolores wiped the sweat from her brow.

I don't like being touched by people, and more than anything......

“Ouch, Choco, come to think of it, you should be neutered!”

It was Dolores's not-so-veiled malice.

Hodadak-.

A black puppy running away.

It was a wind-like movement, and Dolores couldn't help but lose sight of Vikir.

Would she know?

Realizing that he's just about to turn the Night Hound into a eunuch.

“......Hey, it's gone. You don't give much attention to your side. You're so shy.”

However, Dolores, who is not aware of this fact, only makes a sad expression as she watches the black figure disappear quickly towards the edge of the bush.

Chapter 196

The Corpse Queen (1)

◆

The Night Hound continues to blend silently into the night.

Vikir glides from building to building.

But unlike before, Vikir's movements are many times more agile.

Although he became stronger through training, it was more due to the entity attached to the wrist of his left hand.

[Pow!]

A spider web spewed from his left wrist.

The creature shoots the webs onto the walls or railings of the building in front of him as he flings himself into the air.

Vikir then swings forward like a pendulum, attaching another web to the building in front of him, and so on.

The Baby Madam pulled out an enormous amount of spider silk from within its small body, and it seemed that the moment a very small amount of concentrated spider silk extract was ejected out of the mouth, it hardened upon contact with the atmosphere.

'If this little guy can spin so many webs, I wonder what Madam Eight-Legs was like?'

Vikir recalled the last time he had fought Madam Eight-Legs.

Madam Eight-Legs had consumed an enormous amount of webs during her raid on Ballak's village, so she hadn't really been able to pull out much in her fight with Vikir.

If Madam Eight-Legs had been able to spin as many webs as she wanted, Vikir probably wouldn't have survived that day with his limbs intact.

“You're more useful than I thought.”

[Hack-hack-hack-]

Vikir patted the head of the cub that was spitting out webs from its mouth.

It's a good thing, because the travel time has been dramatically shortened thanks to it.

Tap, tap, tap!

Running along the outer wall of the building, Vikir soon landed on top of a half-destroyed clock tower.

The city's landmark clock tower was half-collapsed after a massive impact.

However, because the tower originally had a long history and was built with great care from the foundation, it escaped complete destruction.

Vikir remembered a newspaper article he had read not long ago.

[Exclusive] Night Hound Strikes Again!

-At around 1 AM yesterday morning, the Hound of the Night struck again.

This time, it was the Central Clock Tower, a landmark of the Imperial City.

A copycat, a strange man imitating the Night Hound.

Vikir stared at the massive clock tower, destroyed by an unknown and mysterious entity.

The scars on the walls were too long and free-form to be sword marks.

'It looks like the marks of a whip. Destroying the city's landmarks makes me wonder if... is a person dissatisfied with society?'

Destroying the central clock tower, with its long history, would have done nothing for the city.

It's just a clock tower, a symbol of order and peace that everyone in the city sees several times a day.

Nevertheless, there was likely some symbolic meaning behind the attempt to destroy it.

For example, it could be a protest against the social system, an attempt to overthrow the order, or something like that.

'...Well, that's none of my business.'

But that wasn't the point right now.

Finding and killing the copycat was more urgent to Vikir than the identity of the copycat.

“Let's see.”

From the roof of the tower that had been destroyed by the copycat, there was a panoramic view of the city.

The lights are slowly dying down.

The city is dark and deserted as it prepares for a slow, steady sleep.

And the Night Hound, who only opens his eyes when everyone else has closed theirs.

'...That's where Cindywendy pointed out as suspicious.'

Vikir lifted his head and looked to the north of the city.

It was the area where Vikir had gone on a volunteer not long ago.

It was the site of the Indulgentia family's orphanage, now in ruins.

'It's definitely a ruin and there's nothing left...... Why are informants disappearing over there?'

Vikir lifted his mask slightly and sniffed the air.

“....”

I can smell it. An odor.

It was extremely faint, but it was unmistakably the scent of a demon.

The fact that the area had already been cleared of assassins meant that something was still there.

'But it's strangely faint. Why?'

It was much fainter than the usual demonic odor, and hardly noticeable.

Vikir instructed the cub to stretch the thread and then jumped off the clock tower.

The web ended just before he touched the ground, and the recoil caused him to bounce, flip, and land on the ground.

Vikir ran through the city, darting from alleyway to alleyway in the darkness.

He ran and climbed from roof to roof, ledge to ledge, wall to wall, higher to lower, and lower still.

Vikir eventually reached the ruins of the Indulgentia Orphanage.

It was only a hundred meters or so away, with the Royal Cemetery on the other side.

Moving from the outskirts of the ruins to the center, Vikir sensed something was wrong.

'The smell is getting fainter, then stronger.'

The demonic stench had been diluted by something.

A strange aura, as if human blood were mixed with half and half demonic blood.

'Is it possible for a demon to smell like this?'

Even Vikir, a veteran demon hunter, had never smelled it before.

Meanwhile.

The ruins of Indulgentia Orphanage were completely deserted.

The Quovadis had finished their investigation, and no one would set foot here.

Normally, there would be guards on duty, but with the recent wave of copycats, they've been short-handed.

There's a sign that says it's off-limits to the public, but no one seems to be stopping Vikir, so he keeps going.

Soon enough, Vikir was in the area where one after another of Cindywendy's informants had gone missing.

And then.

“...!”

In one fell swoop, Vikir realized why her informants had disappeared, what made them disappear, and what happened to them and where they went.

[...]

The missing lower jaw, the tongue down to the collarbone, had turned purple.

His body was gassy and bloated, and the flesh that had been shed had congealed into a greasy mess.

A few of the undead wandered through the ruins, their bodies emitting a foul odor.

Danger Rating: C

Size: 1.7 meters

Found in: All continents

-Nicknamed 'the lesser rotten'.

A common sight in graveyards, battlefields, abandoned houses, and sewers.

In rural areas and run-down cities, they are almost as common as rats.

The dead are walking around, moaning unpleasantly.

It was unknown what they had done in life to be walking around here now, but it was clear that at least some of them were informants for Cindywendy.

“Go to a good place.”

Not that there really was a good place.

Vikir drew his bow from his back.

Anubis, the bow of the Ballak, a powerful black bow that clung to Vikir's hand like a second skin.

“I've been letting this one rest too long.”

His hands felt like they were going to rot after handling nothing but entry-level bows during the Academy's midterms.

It is a lie to say that masters do not care about their equipment.

If only I could get this black bow Anubis out of there, I could smash golems and Professor Sadi and everyone else.

'But then I'd be in trouble.'

Anubis wouldn't have finished her off with a single eyeball, unlike a supply bow.

Vikir squeezed Anubis deeply, thinking to himself.

[Chuckles...]

Madame cub, who had been clinging to Vikir's left hand, moved back to his shoulder, apparently unhappy with Anubis.

The Black Bow Anubis was made from the remains of Madam Eight-Legs.

The Baby Madam seemed to hate traces of its mother because of the memory of being almost eaten by its mother when it was still an egg.

It suddenly occurred to me that for spiders, the parent-child relationship may not always be so strong.

'Like the dogs in Baskerville.'

And so it goes.

Klik-

Vikir pulled on Anubis.

Poof! Pow!

One by one, the heads of zombies in the distance exploded.

The zombies shattered before they could react, and Vikir continued to follow the faint stench.

Just then.

“...!”

Reaching the center of the ruins, Vikir saw a stunning sight.

Quilt, the patriarch of House Indulgentia. And Dantalian, the ninth of the ten.

He was dead, but one of his undead minions was still alive and well.

Geronto.

A lich with reddish-black hair and a black cloak.

But Vikir was not surprised that Geronto had risen.

The one who brought Geronto back to life.

Standing in the midst of the ruins, It caught Vikir's attention at once.

A person who exudes overwhelming demonic energy, the source of the demonic scent that led Vikir to this place.

A being wearing a helm and armor made of bone, with long hair flaming like red flames and a black cloak fluttering around.

The Eighth Corpse was there.

Chapter 198

The Corpse Queen (3)

◆

Night Hound in black robes and a plague doctor's mask.

The Corpse Queen, her skeletal armor and helmet hiding her true identity.

In the center of the battlefield, where everything had fallen apart, a man and a woman stood tall.

“Dogs live on bones.”

[Dogs that don't know the meaning of the word and show their teeth should be boiled].

Vikir drew on his mana.

At the same time, the hatchling on his left wrist spewed out a web toward the front.

Zap-!

The white mucus, scattered like a sticky mist, spread out in a web, blocking the opponent's vision.

The Corpse Queen, who had been hit in the face by the web, wiped it away with the hem of her cloak.

[...What a dirty trick].

Her reaction made one thing clear to Vikir.

'The current Corpse Queen is weaker than the Corpse King before he was turned.'

The 'King of Corpses', who dominated the Age of Destruction, was the owner of the Nine Heaven's Tomb and a fearsome demon who ruled the Sisan Blood Sea.

How many mortals have despaired in the face of his terrifying black magic as he raised countless dead soldiers and retrieved the corpses of the dead.

If Snake Morgue had become King of Corpses as I remembered before my regression, he would not have batted an eye at such an attack.

However, the current Corpse Queen was too inexperienced in battle to react to such a mild attack.

'You've only been under contract for a short time, so you still have the memories of your human past. When you were still a novice black mage....'

That had been the case with Seth Le Baskerville, who had also been contracted by Andromalius.

The fear of Hugo that lingered in his bones even after his death, a fear that Seth's body remembered, had caused Andromalius to fail at a crucial moment.

And it seemed to be a similar case with the contractor from Seere in front of him now.

'Perhaps it's even weaker than Andromalius the 10th or Dantalian the 9th.

Even though he couldn't let his guard down with a demon of the demon king class in front of him, he still felt slightly more hopeful.

Flicker.

Vikir took a step back after the corpse queen's web blocked his view of her.

'Intercept with bow as far as possible, then sword if distance closes.'

The Corpse Queen does not know the Night Hound.

It had the far greater advantage of not knowing whether his primary weapon was a bow or a sword, while he knew her primary weapon was black magic.

Vikir stepped back as the Madame cub drew back the cobwebs, and then quickly drew his Anubis.

Black Bow Anubis. A legendary bow with five quivers.

Vikir drew five arrows and fed them to the shafts, then nocked them.

Then.

[...!]

The sight of Vikir's bow stance froze the Corpse Queen in place for a moment.

The eyes within the skeleton's orbit wavered.

A slight agitation. It subsided in an instant, and what took its place was....

[You! You barbarian! I'll kill you! I'll kill you...!]

It was a rage so fierce that it could have burned the whole world to the ground.

It heated up so much that black flames flared up around it, turning it into a sea of fire.

Even Vikir was stunned by its terrifying power.

“What is it? Why is it burning?”

I don't know what made her so angry.

However, the corpse queen, who had been calm until just now, suddenly changed her demeanor and began to close the distance between them, before spewing out an infernal rage.

[You filthy barbarian, why don't you try blocking me with that little bow of yours!]

At the same time, the flames began to take the shape of an extremely long spear.

Quack, quack, quack!

As if he was facing a berserker, Vikir rolled on the ground to avoid the spear.

Clang! Clang! Clang, clang, clang!

There wasn't just one spear of fire.

Dozens of black spears flew across the ground.

The soil and stones in their path are melted away by the infernal fire and scattered.

The wasteland is turning into a lava field.

...Pot!

Vikir rolls on the ground, dodging a spear of fire.

Crunch!

The ground caved in, and then spikes of steel began to rise from the bottom of the pit.

[Dead Pool!]

The rebar with its sharpened tips snaked out of the death pit created by the Corpse Queen, aimed at Vikir like a snake.

Pooh-pooh-pooh!

The steel snakes burrowed into his body.

In an instant, Vikir was pierced by countless bars.

[You lowly barbarian, you shout and you look bad].

The Corpse Queen slowed her pace, as if sensing that the battle was over.

But.

“ ...I know. I know it's only half the battle, but it's still a battle.”

Vikir pulled the rebar out of his body with too much ease.

Thud, thud, thud!

The iron spikes fall to the ground.

The bog salamander's wraith, trapped within the magic sword Beelzebub, regenerated the wound in an instant.

Tsutsutsutsuts...

By the time Vikir climbed out of the pit of death, all of his wounds had healed.

Only the cloak that covered him was slightly tattered.

[...What? How?]

The Corpse Queen tilted her head in disbelief.

But the Night Hound did not answer the demon's question.

Vikir closed the distance again and fired another arrow.

Puff-puff-puff!

Five arrows flew in near succession.

Vikir had unleashed the skill of all the Ballak warriors, especially Aiyen, who was the best bowman of them all.

Each arrow curved in a different direction, but all were aimed at the same bullseye.

[...This must be the archery of those hideous 'Ballak'; I tried to be moderate, but no, I won't kill you nicely].

The corpse queen's neck was covered in blood.

Gurgle!

Next, the four elements tainted by the dark mana simultaneously formed a whirlwind.

Black ice, black fire, black earth, black wind, and black skewers flew toward Vikir.

This much multicasting would be unthinkable for most mages.

But Vikir was used to this sort of thing.

He had seen too many outrageous things in his past life.

Charalak-

Vikir flicked his left hand.

The wire from his sleeve caught on the steel frame of the half-destroyed building.

[Pow!]

Madame cub. The thread from the creature's mouth sent Vikir flying through the air, and he was soon out of the magical storm.

At the same time.

Puff-puff-puff!

Another bolt of arrows flew, aimed at the Corpse Queen.

Thud!

The skeletons, zombies, and ghouls that rose from the ground gathered together to block the arrows.

However.

...BANG!

The wall of bone and flesh shattered far too easily.

Chiiiit!

The arrows melted everything they touched.

The powerful poisonous aura that Anubis possessed was enough to make even the Corpse Queen retreat.

The Corpse Queen took Geronto's hand, which she had revived earlier, and stepped back.

[What a disgusting poison, these barbarians know how to take and ruin the precious things of others].

“...Do you hate the natives of the Black Mountain?”

[Hate them? Hahaha-]

The Corpse Queen laughed once in disbelief.

Then, she pursed her lips, which were barely visible beneath her bony mask, and asked.

[I know the archery you use, what is your relationship with the 'Night Fox' and her child?]

Vikir answered the question as if he knew something.

“I am the hunting party of Ballak.”

And with that, the corpse queen's fury was unleashed.

[Then you must have been 'there' on 'that night' as well, and I cannot forgive you for that!]

With that, the Corpse Queen drew something from within her cloak.

It was a black bag, ominously black and dripping with mana.

Flutter.

The Corpse Queen snatched the black bag and tossed it to the ground.

Immediately, the contents of the bag rushed out.

Dalgraak- Dalgraak- Tektegurrrr...

It was bones.

Bones covered in ash and the teeth marks of wild beasts, as if they had been burned and then eaten.

What's more, almost all of them were broken and cracked, as if they hadn't died a good death in the first place.

The Corpse Queen threw them to the ground and imbued them with dark mana.

Tsutsutsutsutsuts...

Soon, the bones began to rattle and move.

A shroud of darkness settled over them like a veil, allowing them to lead their miserable lives once more.

Vikir stared at the new undead that had taken on another life before his eyes.

It was a skeleton, a living corpse, covered only in dried flesh.

A high ranking dead man, wrapped in dark mana like a shroud.

<Lich

Danger rating: A+.

Size: 3 meters

Found in: Abyssal Edge

-Named the Exalted Dead.

Some mages have transcended the bounds of time and created a whole new kind of bondage.

A giant, mysterious hand lurks at the bottom of the Abyss of Witchcraft, and by binding their souls to the dark chains of its grasp, they have become immortal.

...But they didn't know it.

If a person dies at my age and then gains immortality, will his age still be my age? Or would he age even after achieving immortality?

Mages who became lichs because they were blinded by the desire for immediate achievement were separated from the world and sank deep into the abyss without even going through proper funeral procedures. After a long time, even their bodies were no longer left, and they crumbled to dust.

But even then, only the souls trapped at the bottom of the abyss remain, still thinking of themselves as mages.

Forever.

Lich. An extremely dangerous demon.

An entity far more powerful and terrifying than even the Gerontos he had faced before.

[Grrrr...]

The new Lich slammed into the ground with a snap of its jaws and landed in front of the Corpse Queen.

And then.

“...?”

For some reason, Vikir thought, the lich's face looked quite familiar.

[Yes. A barbarian of Ballak is a barbarian of Ballak].

The corpse queen laughed in a voice that sounded like she had cried so hard she was hoarse.

Purr!

The Lich draws dark mana at the Queen's command.

Vikir recognized the face of this revived Lich as a high-ranking undead.

“...!”

Brown skin, hair a mixture of black and silver.

Beneath the mask, Vikir's eyes widened to piercing slits.

Vikir knew what that man looked like in real life.

No, he didn't just know it, he knew it very well.

...How could he forget?

That it was the same face he'd spent the last two years with in Ballak's tribe.